Chapter 406: Feng Jiu Ge

Nine days later.

Atop of a lush green mountain valley, a small waterfall flowed downwards like a strip of silvery silk.

The waterfall's stream flowed into an ancient lake. The ancient lake was deep and dark jade in color, with ripples on the surface of the water.

In the pond, all kinds of carp were swimming about.

On the top of a white rock beside the water, Feng Jin Huang sat with her eyes closed.

Her face, bright and beautiful, was reflected in the water, causing this ancient lake to gain a brilliant elegance. The colorful carps in the water, the clear pool water, the silvery waterfall, and the green valley all complimented each other.

However, Feng Jin Huang's pretty brows were deeply scrunched.

Although she has tried her best to calm down, every time she closed her eyes for more than thirty breaths, an image flashed in her mind from the depths of her heart.

On an illustrious pink crystal mountain peak, a naked man looked down at her with his black eerie pupils.

She was sprawling on the edge of the cliff, and when she looked up, she saw everything on the man's body.

His bleeding left arm with a bloody hole, his strong muscles, his broad chest, and the massive thing between his legs... the image was engraved into her heart.

The memory was so vivid that the events of that day could never be forgotten by this proud woman.

Especially since afterwards, the man stretched out his right foot and stepped on her face!

Feng Jin Huang wanted to forget the feeling of being trampled on her face, yet the feeling was so vivid that she could clearly recall it even now.

"Forget it, Forget him! Keep a peace of mind, peace, peace of mind, calm down..." Feng Jin Huang breathed more and more rapidly.

Her breathing became heavier, and her chest moved rapidly as a result, and was becoming faster.

In her heart, shame, humiliation, and hatred mixed together, turning into a volcano.

"How dare he? He dared to do that to me! Ahhh!" Feng Jin Huang could not bear it anymore, and suddenly opened her phoenix eyes and stood up abruptly, raising her head and screaming.

Boom!

The volcano in her heart erupted, filling her chest with anger, almost melting her entire body!

"You are a despicable and shameless man, you dared to step on my face. I want to tear you to pieces!" Feng Jin Huang roared, her eyes glowing with fire as she punched randomly.

Bam Bam Bam Bam...

The loud smashing sound, like the sound of thunder, erupted continuously.

Feng Jin Huang's eyes exuded fire, the beautiful flames evaporated the ancient lake and burnt the green hills around her. She punched without a target, as her frenzied barrage sent the surrounding mountain rocks flying, as the ground cracked!

After almost a few short breaths, Feng Jin Huang completely decimated the valley. Such terrifying battle strength, even if ten Fang Yuan attacked together, he could not reach such a power level.

"Ahhhhhhh!"

"This scoundrel!!!"

"I want rend your flesh, limb by limb! I want to step on your bones and crush them into pieces! I'll make you suffer for seven days and seven nights!"

"I swear, I'll make you to suffer endless pain, I want you to die and regret everything you have done to me. Then, I'll turn you into ashes and scatter you into the wind!"

Feng Jin Huang bellowed without stopping, the anger in her chest making her lose all rationality.

...

A few hundred miles away, there were grass cottages built on a mountain peak.

Through the window of the cottage, a pair of beautiful eyes stared at Feng Jin Huang, looking worried.

"Oh, my little Feng Er..." Inside the cottage, a beauty was dressed in white silk adorned with a green belt. She was dignified and elegant, bearing a resemblance to Feng Jin Huang.

She was the biological mother of Feng Jin Huang, Fairy Bai Qing, a rank six Gu Immortal!

"Stop looking. You have already watched her for seven or eight times the during the last ten minutes. The jade sea tide tea that I carefully brewed for you is getting cold by now, go sit down and drink it." Feng Jiu Ge sat by her side, helplessly saying.

"Drink, drink, drink, all you care about is drinking tea. Is Feng Jin Huang even your daughter? As her father, aren't you worried at all?" Bai Qing turned around, her brows were wrinkled and her tone was resentful.

"Sigh! Our daughter, Feng Er, had always been competitive since she was a child. Her talent was excellent, and no one was her match in her sect, but suddenly she stumbled and lost. Hu Immortal Inheritance was the first failure of her life, but it is also the most important. You are her father, but you're actually still in the mood to drink tea here?"

"Nevermind the failure, what's more important is, Feng-Er suffered such a huge loss! She actually got trampled by someone! Think about it, Feng Er is proud and had never paid attention to any man her age. Yet she was beaten in such a way, with someone's foot on her face, and for the first time, saw a similar aged man's body. This, this..."

The more Fairy Bai Qing talked, the more anxious she grew, and her eyes slowly turned red.

Feng Jiu Ge looked at her and immediately got up, getting to her side, holding her in his arms. He frantically comforted her: "Don't cry, don't cry my Qing Er. Isn't your husband still here? In fact, in my opinion, this event was not without benefits."

"Oh? What good is there?" Bai Qing casted a doubtful gaze at him.

"Sigh, Feng Er is our pride and joy, I'm proud of her yet also worried. She's too competitive and always wants to get first place. Yes, her talent is higher than mine, and she also has great comprehension abilities, but so what if her talent is higher, is it higher than all the heroes in the world? No matter how good her talent is, can it compare to Desolate Ancient Moon?" Feng Jiu explained in earnest.

"The great Desolate Ancient Moon, daughter of Ren Zu, failed countless times. Feng Er had always experienced success and victory but had never understood the taste of failure. This is one of her defects, and also her weakness."

"Qing Er, you are a rank six Gu Immortal, and I am a rank seven Gu Immortal, but even if it was a rank nine Immortal Venerable or Demon Venerable, they can only live long, but not forever. We are able to protect Feng Er now, but one day we will leave her. By that time, she will only be able to rely on herself. Experiencing this failure will help her mature."

"Birds leave the nest and fly alone. After they withstand setbacks, they can train their wings and fight in the sky. In the future, when Feng Er leaves us, we can be relieved."

"Feng Er is my baby, I would love nothing more than to protect her inside the blessed land forever..." Fairy Bai Qing leaned on Feng Jiu Ge's chest as she wiped her tears.

She sighed and said: "Sigh, you are right, Feng Er will leave us one day, we should let her train more. But this is too much, she had lost too much this time. Hu Immortal Inheritance was lost, she was even bullied by that Immortal Crane Sect lad, are you as her father not going to do anything about it?"

"Hmph." Feng Jiu snorted, squinting as his eyes shone with a cold light: "Immortal Crane Sect went too far indeed, even though they had promised to compensate us and the other eight major sects. But Feng Er is my daughter, how she can experience such bullying? I have already written a letter and it has been sent to them. If this He Feng Yang does not know what's good for him, I will go to their sect to find him and settle the score!"

Fairy Bai Qing's heart eased, it turns out that her husband had already acted. But immediately, Bai Qing was nervous and looked at her husband: "Husband, don't be rash, don't make a huge commotion. Back when you attacked the top ten sects, Immortal Crane Sect was also one of the victims. They know that you're the strongest, but don't do this kind of thing again."

"I know, I know. Haha, you can be at ease." Feng Jiu Ge calmed his wife lying in his arms, his eyes subconsciously squinting as he snorted in his heart: "Out of the top ten sects in central continent now, none are worthy of facing off against me."

...

South of the Central Continent, thirty thousand feet above the mountains.

In the sky, Fei He mountain was floating among a sea of clouds, looking magnificent and grand.

Trees were swaying on the mountain as ten thousand cranes flew by, giving off a living atmosphere of an Immortal's residence.

Currently, in Shang Qing pavilion at the top of the mountain, it was a heavy and grim atmosphere.

"Feng Jiu Ge has gone too far!" The supreme first elder was staring furiously, his hands clutching a thin letter as he trembled with anger.

With a bang, he slammed the letter on the white jade stone table.

In the letter, Feng Jie Ge listed several overbearing demands. But despite so, supreme first elder did not dare to destroy or burn this letter.

This letter was shining with an azure green color, it was the transformation of the rank five letter sending green bird Gu. Once destroyed, Feng Jiu Ge would sense it, if he became furious, the situation would become troublesome.

This guy, Feng Jiu Ge, was born into the demonic path. In the past, he obtained a rare opportunity and cultivated painstakingly, soundlessly reaching rank six Gu Immortal realm. Once he came out, he amazed the world as he challenged all the heroes in the world, and no one could stop him. The ten sects sent people to challenge him, but they all lost terribly, forced to join forces to resist him.

Feng Jiu Ge, was not afraid, fighting as he travelled for over ten million miles, suddenly changing his tactic and going for the yellow dragon, causing the ten sects to lose miserably. The scene was total chaos and there was nothing anyone could do.

Fortunately, Fairy Bai Qing from Spirit Affinity House moved him with true love, finally reforming this demonic head.

"Back in the day, Feng Jiu Ge used his rank six cultivation and caused a commotion among the ten sects, it was unimaginable. Now, he has rank seven cultivation and has Spirit Affinity House, one of the ten sects backing him. This person has the demeanour of a heavenly immortal, although his requests are slightly overbearing, we can agree to it." Supreme second elder took out the letter, reading it and said with a calm tone.

"He Feng Yang, how can there be such a huge mistake in this matter you were in charge of? That Fang Yuan is not our disciple at all, what motives do you have, defending him like this?" A thunderous voice echoed in Shang Qing pavilion, causing the windows to vibrate.

The person speaking was Lei Tan, rank six Gu Immortal, and was at loggerheads with He Feng Yang.

Places with people have conflict, Immortal Crane Sect also has their conflicts and competition among factions.

At once, all the gazes fell on He Feng Yang.

He Feng Yang was like a young man, gentle like jade. A pair of jade colored brows extended to his waist.

His expression was calm, looking around slowly, then laughed and said: "This Fang Yuan is indeed not our disciple, but his brother Fang Zheng is one of us, the leader of the elite disciples of this generation."

Lei Tan snickered: "A tiny elite disciple's relative, he is worth our backing, the entire Immortal Crane Sect?! He Feng Yang, do you know how much compensation we will have to give to the nine sects for this Fang Yuan?"

"Of course I know." He Feng Yang glanced at Lei Tan, laughing in disdain: "But these things, even if you multiply it by three, can't compare to a Hu Immortal blessed land. Not to mention a fixed immortal travel Gu?"

At once, many of the supreme elders understood.

"He Feng Yang! What are you trying to say?" Lei Tan frowned, asking impatiently.

Chapter 407: Immortal Crane Sect’s objective

He Feng Yang only smiled without replying Lei Tan's question.

It was supreme third elder who laughed and replied: "I understand Elder Feng Yang's intention. If we didn't choose to shield this Fang Yuan, Hu Immortal blessed land would still be up for grabs for the ten sects. However, by admitting that Fang Yuan is a member of our Immortal Crane Sect, we have eliminated the other nine opponents, letting only our Immortal Crane Sect seize control of this blessed land."

Lei Tan's gaze flickered and his expression slightly changed, but he no longer asked any questions.

At this moment, He Feng Yang stood up from his seat.

He first cupped his fists towards supreme third elder who explaining the reason: "Third elder is wise! Things happened too suddenly, who could have thought a mortal would use the Immortal Gu fixed immortal travel to appear the peak of Dang Hun mountain and inherit Hu Immortal blessed land in front of everyone."

"This Hu Immortal inheritance is at Tian Ti mountain. Everyone might know Tian Ti mountain is the stairs that connects to the heavenly court. Even though it was destroyed and had been abandoned for many years, it still represents the might of the heavenly court. In a way, attacking Hu Immortal blessed land is attacking Tian Ti mountain; and attacking Tian Ti mountain is attacking the heavenly court."

"Thus, although there are many blessed lands on Tian Ti mountain, there has never been anyone who had the courage to attack it. Even this time, we waited for Hu Immortal blessed land to open before we ten Gu Immortals joined forces to enlarge the passage, with no intention of attacking."

"Even if we really attacked Hu Immortal blessed land, the blessed land has a land spirit which would require at least three rank six Gu Immortals to join hands and even then they might not succeed. Moreover, the control area of the blessed land is being protected by Dang Hun mountain. Without five or six Gu Immortals cooperating earnestly, who would dare to say they can climb to the peak? Lei Tan, can you?"

Lei Tan snorted, he wanted to retort but kept quiet in the end.

In blessed lands, the land spirit could freely mobilize all the resources and their battle prowess could be compared to a Gu Immortal. The most important thing was that the land spirit could suppress rank one to rank five Gu worms.

If a Gu Immortal wanted to attack the blessed land, their most powerful weapon would be Immortal Gu because land spirits could not restrict Immortal Gu.

However, Immortal Gu were hard to find and many Gu Immortals did not even have one Immortal Gu. Even if they had, it might not necessarily be suited to attack.

This was the classic situation of low offense but high defense.

If they were set on attacking the blessed land, it would often require the cooperation of several Gu Immortals to create a numerical advantage, and then competing through the expenditure of immortal essence. Once the blessed land's immortal essence was exhausted, they could start their attack.

However in truth, unless it was some special situation, Gu Immortals rarely attacked blessed lands.

Because it was really not worth it.

Not only was immortal essence precious and hard to accumulate, there was also the danger of the blessed land self-destructing.

In the case where the land spirit could not defend and chose to destroy the blessed land, the winds of assimilation would blow over and destroy everything, causing the attackers to have no gains.

When Gu Immortals attacked blessed lands, they would often gain nothing and instead suffer heavy losses. Unless it was a matter of deep hatred, nobody would agree to do such a transaction that only created loss.

Seeing that Lei Tan was keeping quiet, He Feng Yang continued: "That Fang Yuan ascended to the peak and got the inheritance, immediately commanding the land spirit to close the blessed land. Fang Yuan and Fang Zheng looks almost the same, the Gu Immortals of the other nine sects realized this and subconsciously thought this was our Immortal Crane Sect's hidden move and questioned me one after another. At that time, I thought that if I were to say the truth, the Hu Immortal Inheritance's belonging would be undecided once again as the ten sects would still compete and fight over it. Thus, I acknowledged it, and even if we had to pay such a price for it, we have eliminated the other nine great sects from the competition. Like this, we can secretly strategize about Hu Immortal blessed land without worrying about other forces."

He Feng Yang explained the whole story, Lei Tan snorted and asked: "There is a big problem in this plan! Hu Immortal blessed land is on Tian Ti mountain and is also closed now, without attacking and creating a loophole, how can we enter?"

He Feng Yang laughed, it seems he already predicted this: "How could I not have any plans? Blessed lands face calamities and tribulations; Hu Immortal died during the fifth earthly calamity. I have already calculated the time, Hu Immortal blessed land will face the sixth earthly calamity in a year and three months' time. Fang Yuan is only a mortal, how could he know how to resist the earthly calamity? Even with the help of the land spirit, without a sect's support, the blessed land will suffer heavy damage at that time and a loophole will appear."

Lei Tan scoffed: "Even if there is a loophole, do you dare to attack? Didn't you say just before that Hu Immortal inheritance is on Tian Ti mountain!"

He Feng Yang instantly replied: "Forcefully attacking is a terrible move and we will only use it if all else fails. That Fang Yuan is only a mortal, as long as a loophole appears and we use some plans and schemes, is there a worry of failing to capture him? Hehe, once the earth calamity passes, he will definitely start worrying and thirst for external help. I have already planned it, first we use Fang Zheng and use the kinship to move and persuade him into cooperating for some transactions. As we make more transactions, his guard against us will naturally loosen, and using logic to persuade him, we might just convince him to join Immortal Crane Sect!"

"If he keeps on being stubborn, we can use some secret methods. Slavery Gu is one good method. There aren't many ways to deal with the land spirit, but there are plenty of ways to deal with a mortal like him. If we can obtain fixed immortal travel Gu like this, then it is no doubt the perfect outcome."

The elders present felt a rush of excitement at the mention of fixed immortal travel Gu. Many began to whisper and discuss with each other; the outcome He Feng Yang portrayed was truly beautiful. Most importantly, his plan had a chance of success.

Lei Tan could feel the change in the atmosphere as he sat down in anger: "You speak nice words, let's hope it goes our way."

Supreme third elder mumbled: "Besides special Gu like dream wings Gu that needs to be activated using the soul, most of the other Immortal Gu need immortal essence to activate, and this fixed immortal travel Gu is not an exception. This Fang Yuan has fixed immortal travel Gu and with the help of land spirit to use the blessed land's immortal essence, he can escape any time he wishes. We need to be very careful to deal with him. Furthermore, there is one point to note, he is but a mortal yet he possesses an Immortal Gu, he should have a rather deep background."

He Feng Yang nodded: "Junior has already thought of this point. Back then, when I claimed Fang Yuan was our sect's disciple, I checked the reactions of the other nine sects. It seems that not one of the Central Continent's nine sects are behind him. I am guessing, since Fang Yuan came from Southern Border, he is very likely to have a super clan of Southern Border behind him. But be it Wu clan, Shang clan, Tie clan, Yi clan or other super clans, they are all situated far at Southern Border and cannot help him here. If they were to enter Central Continent, their battle strength would be suppressed. Our Immortal Crane Sect is one of the ten great sects of Central Continent, we have a huge chance of winning against them."

All the elders nodded at these words and started another round of soft discussions.

"Indeed, a mighty dragon cannot suppress the local snake."

"Central continent is our Immortal Crane Sect's territory!"

"If they were to make a move, hmph."

"Even if their battle prowess was not suppressed, our Immortal Crane Sect is still stronger than any super groups of the four other regions by a mile."

Third elder's furrowed brows relaxed: "There is one doubt remaining. To use fixed immortal travel Gu, the user needs to have a vivid memory and clear understanding of the terrain he teleports to. Fang Yuan is only a mortal from the far away Southern Border, how could he know the scenery in Hu Immortal blessed land? And how could his timing be so precise? Could it be, Hu Immortal had once set an inheritance in Southern Border? Or it could be one of the tricks of Tian Ti mountain's demonic path Gu Immortals?"

He Feng Yang bowed: "Junior is also not clear about this. This matter is strange, originally, there was only a clue about the blood sea inheritance. At that time, one of our sect disciples defected and fled to Southern Border. A few years ago, I sent Lord Sky Crane to Southern Border to clean up and trash and bring back the inheritance. But Lord Sky Crane failed and instead it was Fang Yuan who obtained the inheritance, gaining blood skull Gu. This kid is very ruthless and sinister, unexpectedly killing all his clansmen on the spot and used blood skull Gu to raise his aptitude. Lord Sky Crane was unresigned and brought back Fang Zheng for future plans to retrieve the Gu.

He Feng Yang naturally had never have expected a nobody to so outrageously disrupt his plan back then, causing such a huge problem for him.

This was a weird feeling.

It was as if person was walking on the road, when suddenly a small ant jumped on their nose and started scratching it.

Where did this ant come from? Such guts!

The person could just crush it with their finger but because of the peculiar situation, they were not able to catch the ant and could only let this ant feel triumphant for the time being.

"Not this blood sea inheritance again..." Hearing He Feng Yang narrate the whole story, the elders present frowned, their heart turned irritated.

Blood Sea inheritance came from a big shot of the demonic path, Blood Sea Ancestor.

He killed people like cutting grass and his infamy had gone down in history. With the might of a rank seven Gu Immortal, he had unexpectedly set up hundreds of thousands of inheritance sites that spread over Central Continent, Southern Border, Northern Plains, Western Desert and Eastern Sea.

Before his death, he had laughed and proclaimed: "Blood path is not lonely, my mark will remain for all eternity!

Now, just like he proclaimed, countless mortals had benefitted. Blood sea inheritance was already proclaimed as the most popular inheritance with the greatest number in the world. There was no competition! Countless righteous path figures were getting headaches because of it.

"Didn't that Xue Tu who was only a butcher, become a famous demonic cultivator after obtaining blood sea inheritance?"

"Years ago, Myriad Dragon Dock's Song Zi Xing obtained one of the true blood sea inheritances and defected his sect, causing great humiliation to our ten great sects. Now, he is already a rank seven Gu Immortal with the title 'Blood Dragon'. To kill this defector and wipe away their humiliation, Myriad Dragon Dock dispatched eight Gu Immortals - five rank six and three rank seven. The result was he killed four of them, crippled three of them and beat one into retreating!"

"It is said that Blood Sea has nine true inheritances. They are: blood skull Gu, blood handprint Gu, blood qi Gu, blood sweat Gu, menses blood Gu, blood shadow Gu, blood battle Gu, as well as the ancient desolate beast violent blood dragon bat and finally, the rank six Immortal Gu blood deity. He was truly someone who achieved great success in blood path..."

"Speaking of which, four true inheritances of the Blood Sea Ancestor had already shown up. One is blood skull Gu which is with Fang Yuan. Another is blood handprint Gu which is with Southern Border's current Shang clan leader. Violent blood dragon bat is with Song Zi Xing."

"It is said that Shang clan leader has already obtained the second blood sea inheritance..."

"That is only an unconfirmed rumor, there is no evidence to conclude it."

The elders whispered to one another.

"Alright, there is no need to talk about blood sea true inheritance. It is like searching for a needle in a haystack, all kinds of rumors are increasing day by day. My ears are already getting callus from hearing them." Supreme Grand Elder waved his hand and immediately put a stop to the discussion.

He turned his gaze towards He Feng Yang: "Elder He Feng Yang, since you brought up this method, then you shall be in charge of it. If you are able to seize the blessed land and establish your merit, the sect will not be stingy in rewarding you."

"Junior understands!" He Feng Yang accepted the order with a smile.

Seeing He Feng Yang gain such a lucrative task, Lei Tan felt stifled, but since it was Supreme Grand Elder who said so, he could only hide his hatred inside.

However, Supreme Grand Elder added: "Since you are in charge of it, then Elder Feng Yang, you should hand over your one's own way Gu, right? In Feng Jiu Ge's demand, he had asked for an Immortal Gu. You are the person in charge of this matter, so you should be the one to settle this."

Lei Tan was immediately joyous.

He Feng Yang could only accept the order with a bitter smile.

Chapter 408: Fang Yuan regains consciousness

Fang Yuan slowly opened his eyes.

All he saw before him was a blur pink color, as his vision gradually returned, he saw a thin silk curtain.

A light wind blew, the chimes rang, the light pink curtain slowly swayed, making it feel like a dream or illusion.

Fang Yuan slowly got up from his bed.

This round bed was extremely large, forty to fifty people could fit on it.

A silk blanket that was red on the bottom with golden rims was covering his body.

Fang Yuan looked around and found himself in a large bedroom.

There was a stove beside the bed, burning some incense. There was a fragrance that arouses people's feelings in the air.

This room was made with golden brick walls, silver bricks were used on the ground. Beside the bed, the corners of the room, tables and chairs, dressing table, all of them had large amounts of pearls, agate, diamonds and all sorts of precious gems.

The room was grand and elegant, luxurious and glorious, the affluence of the previous owner was emanating in the room.

This was Hu Immortal's Dang Hun Palace.

"It is a gentle home." Fang Yuan commented lightly, getting down from his bed.

His body shook uncontrollably, as his brain was still dizzy.

Fang Yuan did not find it strange, instead he understood clearly — this was because he had forced himself too much back on San Cha mountain.

Bai Ning Bing's betrayal, the pressure from the two factions, and he even had to scheme against the land spirit. First refining second aperture, then refine the fixed immortal travel Gu in the torrential light stream. The entire process was accompanied by the mental pressure of taking a risky gamble. To Fang Yuan, be it his body or mind, they had reached their limits.

When he used the fixed immortal travel Gu to arrive at Dang Hun Mountain, Feng Jin Huang and Fang Zheng were at their limits, but so was he.

Compared to them, Fang Yuan's mental pressure was greater. Spring Autumn Cicada could no longer be used, and he had snatched the Hu Immortal Inheritance right in front of the ten sects' Gu Immortals, he was trying to pull the teeth out of a tiger, like playing with fire, it was an extremely dangerous move!

Fang Yuan was the first to ascend the mountain, and the land spirit chased the other competitors away. After Fang Yuan officially became the blessed land's owner, he ordered the land spirit to close the entire blessed land.

After instructing the land spirit with a few key points, Fang Yuan relaxed at a safe area, falling asleep instantly.

"Just how long did I sleep..." Fang Yuan shook his head, he still felt extremely tired, there was a sense of weakness coming from his soul.

At the same time, his ears were buzzing, as his brain could not think as quickly as normal. It was difficult to process questions in his head.

"Oh no, I injured my soul." Fang Yuan's heart sank, sensing his condition was not looking good.

The main reason was became of the Immortal Gu refinement.

Were Immortal Gu so easily to refine? Many Gu Immortals would suffer a backlash when making a mistake while attempting to do so, injured at best, death at worst.

Fang Yuan used a mortal's body to refine an Immortal Gu. The main reason was because the recipe was good, originating from Ren Zu's tales. Secondly, the materials used were appropriate, focused on the divine travel Gu, looking from another angle, it was simply converting divine travel Gu into fixed immortal travel Gu.

It was not like in Fang Yuan's previous life, where he used a large number of mortal Gu to refine the Immortal Gu Spring Autumn Cicada. Turning from mortal to immortal, the difficulty was a hundred fold.

"Even so, the foundation of my soul was too weak and got injured. But thankfully, this is Dang Hun mountain..." Thinking so, Fang Yuan's expression turned solemn, as he said lightly: "Where is the land spirit?"

Swoosh, Hu Immortal land spirit appeared before him.

"Master, you are finally awake." Hu Immortal lowered her head, her face was red as she looked at her feet, speaking in a meek tone.

She had the appearance of a five to six year old girl, she was cute and young. With a colorful dress, and a snow-white fox tail behind her, swaying to express her unease.

"Master, when you were sleeping, I acted on my own accord and healed the injury on your left arm. I wanted to bring you clothes but what we have here are not your size." Hu Immortal land spirit reported.

The clothes she mentioned was Hu Immortal's clothing, they were women's clothing, of course Fang Yuan could not fit in them.

Fang Yuan frowned: "Clothing is not important, how long have I slept? During this period, did any strong enemies attack the blessed land?"

Hu Immortal's eyes were large and shining, blinking: "Master, during the seven days you were asleep, nobody attacked."

"Oh?" Fang Yuan's eyes shone.

He did not know that Immortal Crane Sect's He Feng Yang defended him, blocking the assault of the other nine sects.

But he understood somewhat why no Gu Immortals attacked the blessed land.

Hu Immortal blessed land was not like the three kings blessed land on San Cha mountain.

This blessed land was still very young, it had a land spirit and ample immortal essence storage, and even Dang Hun mountain as the core protection of the blessed land.

These three elements made Hu Immortal blessed land as secure as a fortress, most Gu Immortals had no way to force their way in.

How hard was it to attack this blessed land, Fang Yuan knew most clearly!

Five hundred years into his past life, he allied with almost ten demonic Gu Immortals, invading this place. Eventually, he had a narrow victory, only he and Song Zhong were left.

Song Zhong was the son of Song Zi Xing, a rising star of the demonic path, he has not been born yet.

"Back then, I was already a senior of the demonic path. Song Zhong inherited his father's inheritance, gaining great strength and was able to fight with me for tens of rounds without a winner emerging, causing him to rise to fame from that battle."

Thinking of his past life, being used as a stepping stone for this junior Song Zhong, Fang Yuan snickered continuously.

"Everything's changed now. I'll find a chance to kill Song Zi Xing, hehe, let's see how you'll come into this world."

Song Zi Xing had one part of the blood sea inheritance, it was the ancient desolate beast violent blood dragon bat. This dragon bat is not a Gu worm, it can be captured and taken away.

"With the violent blood dragon bat, I will gain an endless number of blood bats. Manipulating blood bats was one of my greatest skill in my previous life. Of course, that is a plan for the future. Now, I have to rely on this blessed land to cultivate quickly, getting back to my Gu Immortal stage!"

Thinking so, Fang Yuan thought of an important question: "Land spirit, how long more till the next earthly calamity?"

"Master, I was about to inform you if you did not ask me. Right now, the blessed land has already endured five earthly calamities, the sixth is a year and three months away." Hu Immortal's voice was filled with anxiety and worry.

"What? A year and three months!" Fang Yuan jumped up from his bed, unable to sit any longer, his face turning grim.

Everything exists in balance, heaven is impartial. Strength comes with weakness, blessing comes with calamities. Blessed lands have calamities and tribulations, an earthly calamity every ten years, and a heavenly tribulation every hundred years.

Not mentioning the heavenly tribulation but just the earthly calamity; once it occurs, the might is overwhelming, often causing great disasters, if the blessed land cannot endure it, they will face destruction.

Fang Yuan had a blessed land in his previous life, he was extremely clear of the danger of his current situation!

To a blessed land, every earthly calamity is a strict test. Earthly calamities get stronger than the one before, Hu Immortal died in the fifth, and Fang Yuan was about to face the even stronger sixth calamity.

"There are only a year and three months left to the earthly calamity. Why was it not mentioned in Feng Jin Huang's biography? That's right, she is a disciple of Spirit Affinity House, her parents are both Gu Immortals, with their help, it is not hard to block the earthly calamity. But to me, this is a grave situation!"

The sixth calamity is coming too quickly, even with Fang Yuan's experience, he would not have time to make ample preparations.

Other than that, he still had to guard against external enemies.

"Under everyone's watchful eye, I snatched Hu Immortal blessed land, although the tens sects have not made a move, they are surely waiting to pounce on me. I understand now, the ten sects are waiting for the earthly calamity, and want to make use of it?"

Once the earthly calamity descends, the land spirit will have to face it with everything she had, she would not have time to take care of this master. Fang Yuan was still rank four upper stage, he was easy to target. Once he dies, the blessed land would be ownerless, and the land spirit will have to find a new master.

If the earthly calamity causes a huge loophole, Gu Masters outside would be able to enter at will. If the ten sects find trouble then, it would add on to his problems, and the situation would certainly turn deadly.

Fang Yuan's gaze shone, because his soul was injured, it caused his head to hurt.

He rearranged his scattered thoughts, and breathed out deeply, deciding: "I'll take a look at the situation, make the best preparations for this earthly calamity. If I fail, I will give up the blessed land and order it to self-destruct, not giving the righteous path any resources for free, then escape using fixed immortal travel Gu."

Although the blessed land was good, how could it compare to his safety?

With such a thought, Fang Yuan called the land spirit to bring him outside, he needed to know more about the blessed land now.

"Yes." Land spirit nodded obediently, but hesitantly added: "Master, you do not like clothes? Actually, wearing nice clothing would make one feel more energised, and you will feel happier too."

Fang Yuan: "..."

The dresses in Dang Hun palace was not for Fang Yuan to wear. But he had stored some spare clothing inside the tusita flower.

After changing into a black robe, Fang Yuan followed the land spirit, going up on the stairs and reaching the mountain peak.

Dang Hun montain's winds were very strong.

But land spirit waved her hand, and it turned into a soothing breeze.

"Master, this blessed land has 4000km2 of land. The flow of time is five times. The 4000km2 of land is mostly grassland, the grass is made up of blue degree grass, water chestnut grass, and six divine grass primarily, there are also seven treasure flowers and milk tea flowers etc."

The land spirit introduced as she drew a virtual image, floating in the air for Fang Yuan to see.

In the image, there was a classic grassland, with all sorts of colors, like a grass carpet right before him.

The blue and poisonous blue degree grass, the chestnut shaped water chestnut grass, six divine grass which looked like six thin leaves with the feeling of jade. And also the seven colored seven treasure flower, the cup shaped milk tea flower filled with nectar that were like milk tea.

With these seven as the main, there were also a lot of weed and wild flowers.

Fang Yuan looked as he nodded.

Do not look down on these grass and flowers, they are cultivation resources.

These seven types of grass and flowers were Gu refinement ingredients. Some of the flowers and grass even has wild Gu worms. With 4000km2 worth of land, compared to Earth, that was one and a half Hong Kong added together. How many Gu would there be in total?

These wild Gu worms were extremely easy to catch. With just a command from Fang Yuan, the land spirit would be able to capture them intact and hand it over to Fang Yuan.

Chapter 409: Managing the Blessed Land

Fang Yuan asked: "Then how many Gu are there in the blessed land now?"

The Hu Immortal land spirit raised her head by a bit: "At present, there are over eight hundred and sixty thousand rank one Gu, with about fifty-two types of them. Over a hundred and thirty thousand rank two Gu, with forty-eight types. Five thousand rank three Gu, with twelve types. Only over sixty rank four Gu, with eight types. And only one rank five Gu - fox skin Gu."

After Hu Immortal died, her obsession did not disappear and combined with this land's heavenly power to form into an unusual existence known as the land spirit. In some way, it could be said to be a continuation of her life.

Thus, the land spirit was the representative of this blessed land and was clear about everything in the blessed land.

As Fang Yuan had become the master of the blessed land now, everything in the blessed land was his.

Over eight hundred and sixty thousand rank one Gu, hundred and thirty thousand rank two Gu; these two combined meant nearly a million Gu worms!

Fang Yuan recalled the time in Qing Mao mountain, those days where he had to scheme and fight for two to three rank one and rank two Gu.

A blessed land could only be created by a Gu Immortal, it was the foundation of their wealth, a heavenly estate. Just this Hu Immortal Blessed Land alone could supply for a super clan. There would not be any problem to put five or six small-mid sized clans like Gu Yue clan here!

As for the Gu worms in the blessed land, their quantity sharply decreased at rank three. Rank four Gu worms did not reach hundred and there was only one rank five Gu.

This situation was also natural.

It was the same with Gu Masters.

Rank one and rank two Gu Masters were extremely common, rank three were already rare, rank four were even fewer, and only one or two rank five Gu Masters might appear among a million people.

This was a pyramid distribution; the quantity reduces the higher you go, and the ones who occupied the top were extremely few in numbers.

"This blessed land is still young and with appropriate managing, the quantity of the Gu worms will still increase. Reaching ten million rank one and two Gu will not be difficult. But whether I can raise them properly or not, it depends on the types and quantity of the rank four and rank five Gu." Fang Yuan calculated.

Mortal Gu Masters would usually only raise five or six Gu, while Gu Immortals could raise a million or even ten million Gu worms. The difference between the two is as far as the clouds were from the mud.

These Gu being raised in Hu Immortal blessed land could only be considered passable.

On the one hand, the numbers were little, being only about a million. On the other hand, the Gu were not elites. From the introduction Fang Yuan got, they were all ordinary Gu. If they were changed to Gu like liquor worm or breath concealment Gu, their value would be much higher.

Even the rank five fox skin Gu was an extremely common defensive Gu; it was effective against wind and water path Gu worms, but was difficult to use in complex battlefield. Fang Yuan did not even take a look at it.

The thing that really moved him was the time in the blessed land.

Time flowed five times faster in Hu Immortal blessed land. That is to say, one day in the outside world would mean five days here.

This meant Fang Yuan's cultivation speed would be five times faster in the blessed land! He could cultivate for a year and three months here when only three months would have passed in the outside world.

With this, Fang Yuan's cultivation speed would surpass most Gu Masters and he would have greater initiative for his future plans.

Naturally, there was a huge disadvantage to this. Fang Yuan's lifespan was only about a hundred years, thus with this, he would age five times faster as well.

The land spirit continued with the introduction: "At present, there are about a thousand groups of fox living here; red fox, golden fox, cloud fox, wind fox, autumn fox, flowing light fox, and so on. The three largest groups of foxes each has about eight hundred thousand foxes. Altogether, there are about four million and seven hundred thousand foxes."

Fang Yuan quietly listened to it and nodded his head.

Three groups of myriad foxes meant three myriad beast kings. The development of the beasts in the blessed land had still not reached a level of creating a beast emperor.

The classification of beasts was simple. From low to high, they were hundred beast king, thousand beast king, myriad beast king and beast emperor.

For example, Ba Huang and Ying Ming of three kings inheritance were two beast emperors with battle strength that could match rank five Gu Masters; they were able to temporarily obstruct Mo Wu Tian and Xiao Mang's advance.

"There are a lot of fox groups, but unfortunately they are all common foxes and not mutated beasts." Fang Yuan inwardly evaluated.

Ordinary beast's worth naturally could not compare with mutated beasts. Examples would be comparing boar and thunder boar; green bull and kunlun bull; wild dog and lion mastiff.

Above the mutated beasts were desolate beasts; above desolate beasts were ancient desolate beasts and immemorial desolate beasts.

Song Zi Xing's violent blood dragon bat was an ancient desolate beast, one of the nine true inheritances of Ancestor Blood Sea. Immemorial desolate beasts were recorded in <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>, an example would be the nine-tailed fox.

"Raising a nine-tailed fox in Hu Immortal blessed land is but a dream. Even raising an ancient desolate beast is impossible. If it is ordinary desolate beasts like hurricane fox or phoenix wings fox, raising one or two of them could be feasible but it would greatly depend on luck." Fang Yuan continued to consider.

Since he had obtained Hu Immortal blessed land, his plans after rebirth had reached a whole new level, thus he had to revise and modify them.

At this time, Jia clan's internal strife should have already stirred like a wildfire and he would not be able to participate in it. He also could not participate in the great battle of Yi Tian mountain. Fang Yuan intended to make full use of this Hu Immortal blessed land and cultivate to the realm of Gu Immortal. This meant that he not only had to resist the continuous earthly calamities but also had to manage the blessed land.

Currently, the Gu worms were barely passable and the foxes might be ordinary but they had the potential to grow.

"Actually, there were a lot more fox groups in the blessed land. At least, three times more than the present. But the second earthly calamity caused a meteor fire rain that smashed the blessed land's east area into ruins, burning hundreds of thousands of foxes to death; the dark flames of that time have not been extinguished even now. The fourth earthly calamity was a huge flood that submerged most of the grassland of the blessed land's northern area, killing many more foxes. Thus, there are only this many remaining at present." The land spirit pursed her pink lips, her eyes revealing fear and panic as she talked about the earth calamity.

At the same time, she waved her small hand and smoke flew into the air, showing the scenes of the eastern and northern parts of the blessed land.

Fang Yuan could see: The eastern part was a scene of ruin with dust and smoke pervading the whole place. There were meteoric craters all over the place, and black flames were burning around the craters. The flames burned without emitting the least bit of sound, but this manifested an even more terrifying aura.

And the northern part was a scene of vast clear water. Dark clouds rumbled in the air and rain fell endlessly. The surging water emitted bleak and gloomy sound. There were bits of grass and destroyed flowers, along with fox corpses floating on the water.

"These are the dark flame meteor and clouded white sea calamities." Seeing such a bleak scene, Fang Yuan could not help feeling gloomy.

The might of an earthly calamity was extremely strong; moreover, there were countless types of calamity, and were simply impossible to plan against.

Every ten years, the earthly calamity would pose a destructive threat towards the blessed land. Hu Immortal defended five times before losing her life. And the devastation the previous earthly calamities left were still there and had not been cured.

This was a really bad news to Fang Yuan.

Hu Immortal Blessed Land has an area of 4000km2, but northern and eastern areas were gone, causing the loss of over 1300km2 of area. Such loss was truly disastrous.

"I must settle these two problems. Apart from anything else, a lot of Immortal Essence will be used in order to suppress the burning black flames and the spreading flood." Fang Yuan mumbled in a soft voice.

However, following immediately, Hu Immortal land spirit mentioned an even worse news.

"Master, the biggest trouble is here. Look, this is what was left from the fifth earthly calamity." She waved her hand and the image changed to show a different scene.

Fang Yuan saw a scene of scorched black prairie, and a human figure formed from blue lightning was sitting cross-legged on the ground.

It's physique was not big and looked quite alluring, however it was formed purely from lightning. The glorious blue light let out an extremely terrifying might!

"Human shaped lightning, this is the earth calamity — blue charm lightning shadow!" Fang Yuan drew in a cold breath.

This human shaped lightning was one of the earth calamities; it was extremely strong and could match a rank six Gu Immortal!

Fang Yuan looked at this scene and immediately realized the killer that killed Hu Immortal was probably this blue charm lightning shadow!

Hu Immortal was an enslavement path Gu Master who controlled fox groups. Enslavement path was strong but also weak, and could very easily be subdued by beheading the leader tactics. Although there were many fox groups, they could not obstruct blue charm lightning shadow. In the end, Hu Immortal had to fight the lightning figure in close combat and lost her life.

"Damn it, how could there be this lightning shadow in this blessed land?" Fang Yuan's expression turned extremely unsightly.

He had ways to slowly settle the previous two problems. However, this human shaped lightning was already beyond his current ability.

"Master, you need to be careful when you roam around later, this human shaped lightning strolls randomly around the blessed land. Only Dang Hun Mountain, it dares not approach." The land spirit's pink and delicate face was bathed in the image of the blue lightning, her voice slightly shaky.

"This lightning is an earth calamity but is also a type of living thing. Since it is a living thing, it has a soul and thus if it approaches Dang Hun Mountain, its soul will receive shockwaves until it turns to ashes." Fang Yuan had already settled his mind now.

"Maybe I can use Dang Hun Mountain to settle this lightning shadow? But how can I lure it?" Fang Yuan's thoughts took a turn, however the next instant the buzzing noise echoed in his ears again.

He shook his head and did not continue thinking.

"Are there any other bad news, tell them all at once." He gave a wry smile and asked the land spirit.

The situation was much worse than what he imagined. Hu Immortal blessed land was in imminent crisis; whether it was the internal worries or external aggression, they were both very grave.

As for Feng Jin Huang - with Gu Immortal parents and also the help of Spirit Affinity House - she naturally did not need to worry about these things.

But Fang Yuan was just a lone force.

Naturally, there were benefits that only a lone force could have. In the biography of Feng Jin Huang, it was recorded Feng Jin Huang had to offer a large amount of resources to her sect after obtaining the blessed land.

The land spirit shook her small head. She had already reported the worst situations, remaining were all good news.

First of all, in the southern area of the blessed land lived a tribe of rockmen.

Rockman was a type of variant humans who lived underground and ate ore as food.

This news was an unexpected surprise to Fang Yuan.

Secondly, there was abundant immortal essence in Hu Immortal blessed land.

The land spirit brought Fang Yuan to the palace in Dang Hun Mountain. In the deepest parts of the palace was an enormous golden bowl which was filled with green immortal essence.

Besides the green liquid in the bowl, most of the Immortal Essence had automatically congealed into a ball. At first glance, it looked like a grape.

This was something only rank six Gu Immortals had — green grape immortal essence!

Each green grape immortal essence pearl contained immortal essence that was much more than the immortal essence in the three kings blessed land.

"With this immortal essence, there is still quite a bit of hope!" Fang Yuan finally breathed in relief.

Chapter 410: Dang Hun Mountain’s Gutstone

Fang Yuan counted, the golden bowl had seventy-eight pieces of green grape immortal essence. Adding in the layer of blue-green immortal liquid essence at the bottom of the bowl, it amounted to seventy-eight pieces and a half.

There was ample immortal essence, a hundred times that of the three kings blessed land.

Fang Yuan took out one bead of green grape immortal essence, holding it in his hand, willing and summoning fixed immortal travel Gu.

Fixed immortal travel Gu was like jade, a meticulously crafted butterfly, it was brilliant and elegant, flying over smoothly.

Fang Yuan's face paled as his body shook, cold sweat emerging on his body as his vision turned dark. If he was not holding onto the golden railing at the side, he would have fallen.

"Master, be careful. Your soul injury was severe, do not summon an Immortal Gu so carelessly, otherwise you would fall into another coma." Little Hu Immortal shouted, her tone anxious and her expression concerned.

"No worry, I know." Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, waving his hand as he spread his palm for fixed immortal travel Gu to land.

Fixed immortal travel Gu sensed the green grape immortal essence's aura and fluttered its wings, gliding in the air and landing in Fang Yuan's palm.

Next, it laid down on the green grape immortal essence and slowly consumed it.

Fixed immortal travel's name contained an "immortal" word, that was not for show. Its food was immortal essence.

A moment later, one green grape immortal essence was expended.

Gu Masters refine Gu, use Gu, and nurture Gu. After Fang Yuan succeeded in its refinement, he had not fed the fixed immortal travel Gu yet.

He slept for seven days and seven nights, the fixed immortal travel Gu was starving and its lustrous wings had dimmed.

This was Fang Yuan's first feeding session for it.

After fixed immortal travel Gu had its fill, it spread its wings and flew in the air. The bright green light appeared again, like dust particles in the air, every time it flapped its wings, it would be a beautiful light show. The unique aura of an Immortal Gu continued to radiate.

"Immortal Gu are expensive to feed, fixed immortal travel Gu consumes an entire piece of immortal essence every time! But after this, I would not need to feed it for six years."

The higher the rank of the Gu worm, the heavier the cost to feed it, but the interval between each feeding session would increase greatly as well.

Rank one and two Gu worms needed to be fed every few days. Rank four were fed one a few months. Rank five were fed every one or two years, and each time they ate, it would be extremely expensive.

After feeding fixed immortal travel Gu, Fang Yuan left it alone to roam Dang Hun palace, as long as it did not leave Dang Hun mountain and get killed by that lightning shadow.

At this moment, Fang Yuan's aperture was still rank four upper stage, it could not contain a perfectly healthy Immortal Gu.

The reason he could keep Spring Autumn Cicada was because it was too weak. Other than that, it was also his vital Gu.

Problems are classified into important and trivial, after understanding his situation, Fang Yuan confirmed that he was safe for the time being. After settling fixed immortal travel Gu's matter, he had to fix his soul's injury next.

"Let's go, little Hu Immortal, go find the gutstones with me."

"Yes!" Land spirit answered quickly: "Master, you should've done this long ago, come with me."

Little Hu Immortal brought Fang Yuan to Dang Hun mountain.

The two moved on the uneven mountain rocks, Fang Yuan's body was swaying, causing the land spirit to feel worried: "Master, shall I teleport you over?"

"Teleport for what? We have to save immortal essence!" Fang Yuan stared with wide eyes.

Little Hu Immortal stuck out her tongue, frightened by Fang Yuan's words, thinking: This master is so domineering, even if he is injured, he is still so scary.

"Master, there is a gutstone here." After walking for a while, land spirit stopped and pointed at a rock below her feet, shouting.

This stone was like a person's gallstone, it grew on the mountain rocks, having mixed colors. If one did not look properly, they would think it was an ordinary stone.

Fang Yuan quickly walked over, squatting down and smashing this gutstone with his hand.

Once the stone shattered, a Gu flew out and turned into a grey eerie light, entering Fang Yuan's body.

Fang Yuan felt his brain turning clear, a new type of strength had entered his soul, and the buzzing in his ears had lessened.

Dang Hun mountain could shake souls, it was the death grounds of all living beings. It was only because of the land spirit's suppression that Fang Yuan could move around with ease.

But Dang Hun mountain was not a simple death ground.

The souls of living beings break into pieces on the mountain, scattering and fusing with the mountain. As time passes, gutstones are formed.

And in some gutstones, guts Gu are found, it could strengthen a person's soul.

This is like how the resting place of a poisonous snake has the herbs to create an antidote. All living beings compete, and the world is fair; where there is life, there is death.

Dang Hun mountain might look like an absolute death ground, but a chance of survival was hidden in it.

But this guts Gu can only exist for an instant, after that, it would either disperse or be broken down by Dang Hun mountain again. Although the land spirit can suppress the mountain, the gutstones cannot be moved, they can only be used on the spot. Thus, Fang Yuan had to go there himself and walk around Dang Hun mountain.

After being rejuvenated by this guts Gu, Fang Yuan was like a thirsty traveller in the desert getting a mouthful of fresh water.

He continued on his way, and with this land spirit acting as a dutiful guide, they found another dozen gutstones, smashing them open one by one.

Thus, Fang Yuan gained another eight guts Gu to replenish his soul. Not only did his injuries heal completely, it even improved compared to before.

"Hahaha, with this Dang Hun mountain, I have a mountain of gutstones. As long as I continue to consume guts Gu, one day, the foundation of my soul will reach a stage where no one has ever gotten to!"

Standing at the mountain waist, Fang Yuan became spirited as he laughed loudly.

Hu Immortal was a lucky person, because of an opportunity, she managed to obtain Dang Hun mountain, like she won lottery, and moved it into her blessed land.

But she was an extremely unlucky person, dying during the fifth earthly calamity.

"If it was not for the blue charm lightning shadow, she would eventually become the strongest enslavement path expert! Unfortunately, Hu Immortal only had Dang Hun mountain, but did not manage to use it for herself. But fortunately, this Dang Hun mountain is mine now!"

The most valuable part of Hu Immortal blessed land was this Dang Hun mountain!

Of course, the soul could not be strengthened endlessly with guts Gu. Once the soul was not concentrated enough, using large numbers of guts Gu would cause it to over-inflate and trigger a certain-death disaster.

But Fang Yuan had his five hundred years of experience, all his ups and downs after rebirth, constantly struggling at death's door, his soul was already tempered like steel!

Keeping calm at the face of death, a heart of ice at impending doom.

To Fang Yuan, a few hundred guts Gu was no problem at all.

There were a lot of benefits and implications in having a strong soul foundation. Be it refining Gu or enslaving beasts, it would make it much easier. Other than these, once the soul becomes stronger, Fang Yuan would not have to worry about killer moves like Mo Wu Tian's purple eyes.

Dang Hun mountain is a forbidden ground, first appearing in \<\<Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

Legend says that Verdant Great Sun flew towards the sky, and ended plunging to his death.

Ren Zu, as his father, was extremely upset after receiving the news, finding wisdom Gu for an explanation.

It was wisdom Gu who taught Verdant Great Sun to drink, causing the series of events thereafter.

Wisdom Gu quickly said: "Ren Zu, oh Ren Zu, don't find trouble with me. Although your son died, it is not impossible to revive him. As long as you enter the door of life and death, and lead him towards the road of life, walking under the sunlight, he would be revived.

Ren Zu was shocked, before becoming overjoyed, and then extremely furious.

He grabbed wisdom Gu and questioned: "Wisdom Gu, oh wisdom Gu, do you still think I am that ignorant boy from before? The door of life and death is a dangerous place, once I enter I will never be able to leave. After harming my son, you want to kill me too?"

Wisdom Gu quickly said: "Other living beings do not know the secret of the door of life and death, thus they cannot leave. But I can teach you all of these secrets."

"You are a living person, to enter the door of life and death, you have to enter from the road of death. This road is extraordinary, it was the road left behind by fate Gu when it left fairness Gu. The road left behind was called path of destiny. There are many suffering Gu inside the path of life, you have to enter from the road of death, and you need to own courage Gu. That way, you will not fear the torture of suffering."

"When you enter the door of life and death, and see fairness Gu, you are already dead. But at the same time, you will see your eldest son, Verdant Great Sun's soul. You will bring him away, and go out from another road, the road of life. Road of life was the path treaded on by fate Gu when it visited fairness Gu, it is also called the path of destiny."

"But during this path, you will meet three obstacles. One is Dang Hun mountain, another is called Luo Po valley, and lastly the reverse flow river. To climb past Dang Hun mountain, you have to smash the gutstones on it, and obtain guts Gu's help. To get past Luo Po valley, you need to find faith Gu to help. To get through the reverse flow river, you have to move forward continuously, not stopping for even a second during the process."

Ren Zu heard wisdom Gu's words and let it go.

He quickly found faith Gu.

Ever since he became blind, faith Gu's light was the only light he could see.

"Oh Ren Zu, I can feel your determination in getting back your eldest son. I am willing to help you, but I urge you not to give up on this goal. Because when you give up, I will leave you for good." Faith Gu said with concern.

Ren Zu found courage Gu next.

Courage Gu and hope Gu were good companions.

Ren Zu had hope Gu, and thus saw courage Gu occasionally, he had a decent relationship with it.

After getting courage Gu's help, Ren Zu came to the door of life and death, entering the road of death.

The road of death was pure darkness, the large number of suffering Gu were like yellow fireflies, swarming towards Ren Zu. At this time, courage Gu shone brightly, chasing away the suffering Gu for Ren Zu.

Courage was needed to face death.

Ren Zu succeeded in going down, his body turned whiter as it turned hollow, gradually turning into a ghost.

He could "see" again.

When he got to the end of the road, amidst the calm darkness, he saw fairness Gu.

He was extremely shocked by fairness Gu's huge body, exclaiming: "You are fairness Gu? Why is your body so huge? A mountain is a speck of dust compared to you. The sea is like a droplet compared to you."

Fairness Gu's voice was grand: "Life and death are the greatest fairness in this world, when I am inside the door of life and death, my body will become enormous. Oh Ren Zu, you are here for your son right. Feel free to go, he is right there."

Chapter 411: Great Future Plans

Ren Zu was overjoyed upon seeing his son and ran towards him.

Verdant Great Sun had turned into a white ghost and was lying beside a lake, scooping out the water with a bowl and drinking it.

The water was like wine with its fragrance pervading the area.

Verdant Great Sun drank it with utmost satisfaction.

"My son, don't drink anymore. Come, let's go back." Ren Zu walked towards Verdant Great Sun and shouted.

"Esteemed father, how did you come here? This is great, let's drink together." Verdant Great Sun opened his hazy eyes and looked at Ren Zu.

Ren Zu seized the wine bowl from him and said with exasperation: "Don't drink anymore, you only know how to drink wine! Everyone knows there is a bewitching lake in the land of the dead, and its water is the bewitching soup. When ghosts drink it, they become muddle-headed and lose the desire to leave."

Verdant Great Sun, however, refuted: "Father, you are wrong. This is not the bewitching soup, it is the soul calming wine. It can calm down your soul and remove all the impurities; your soul will no longer be restless and you will experience utmost tranquility in your heart. This is one of the best quality wines in this world."

"I don't care what wine it is, you have to follow me back." Ren Zu pulled Verdant Great Sun's hand, but found Verdant Great Sun was as heavy as a mountain and could not be budged.

Verdant Great Sun shook his head: "Some people, upon death, will be as heavy as a mountain. Some people, upon death, will be light as a feather. Father, I had reputation Gu in my life and died after bathing in the light of glory. When I arrived here, my body had become heavier than a mountain, I cannot even walk a single step and can only lie down here."

"What!" Ren Zu immediately felt gloomy and anxiously shouted, "I told you before, a tall tree attracts the wind, reputation is not always a good thing. Throw away the reputation Gu."

Verdant Great Sun shook his head and sighed: "We were not born with fame and fortune, we also cannot take them with us after death. After I died, reputation Gu left me. It is fixed immortal travel Gu that has accompanied me."

Fixed immortal travel Gu could bring Verdant Great Sun's soul out of the door of life and death or even bring him to any place in the outside world.

However, Verdant Great Sun could only truly resurrect after walking through the path of life.

"What do we do now..." Ren Zu realized he had been played by wisdom Gu. Although he had arrived at the deepest part of the door of life and death — a death domain that had endless darkness, and has also found Verdant Great Sun, he discovered he could not bring back his son.

At this moment, fairness Gu spoke: "Oh Ren Zu, do you still not understand? There are only two paths in door of life and death, both appeared because of fate Gu. Life and death are determined by fate! All living beings live and thus die, this is the cycle that allows the universe to continue existing. Your eldest son Verdant Great Sun died, this is fate and you should accept it. Moreover, he is living a good life here, obsession death domain is the world's most tranquil place. He is drinking the world's supreme quality wine and is free from all the worries of the outside world, do you know how blissful this is?"

Ren Zu stood there and looked at his flesh and blood for a while before heaving a deep sigh.

He knew he could not bring back his son's soul, at least it was like that for now.

He bid farewell to the fairness Gu and also his son, and left the obsession death domain.

He stepped on another path this time; it was the path of life which went from darkness to light.

However, Ren Zu soon realized walking this path was countless times more difficult than when he walked in through the path of death.

There were many more suffering Gu on path of life than path of death. When Ren Zu had walked through the path of death, his journey became smoother along the way and the suffering Gu lesser the further he walked. But as he walked through the path of life, there was not only more suffering Gu, but every step he took would cause much more suffering Gu to fly over and obstruct him.

Courage Gu could not resist them any longer: "Ren Zu, there are too many suffering Gu and they will continue to increase. There is peace in death, but life has endless suffering. Go to Dang Hun mountain quickly and break some gutstones. If you want to survive, just relying on courage won't be enough, you need guts too."

Ren Zu hurried forward to Dang Hun mountain and picked the guts Gu while enduring the tremors in his soul.

With guts Gu's help, his soul strengthened grealy, and although he still suffered the tremors, it was not of much worry.

He passed through Dang Hun mountain and arrived at Luo Po valley.

Luo Po valley was a maze with winding and twisted paths. Occasionally, there were a large area of bewilderment fog which could cause the soul to loosen; and occasionally, Luo Po wind would blow through and cut apart the soul.

Ren Zu had fallen into the lowest part of my life and could not distinguish the directions. Because his soul was strengthened by guts Gu, it was loosening in the bewilderment fog at a slower speed. The loosened soul was cut apart by the Luo Po wind.

Ren Zu almost completely lost his way, but fortunately at this time, faith Gu flew out and shone upon his path.

Ren Zu was able to walk out of the Luo Po valley with only the essence of his soul remaining.

He let out a huge breath of relief and could feel he was close to success.

He walked to the reverse flowing river, this was the final barrier in the path of life.

It was extremely difficult to move against the stream.

Endless suffering pushed upon him, causing him to make very slow progress.

However, he forcibly persevered and walked towards the light.

"Almost there." He looked at the success that was just ahead of him, only one final step remained.

He let out a breath of turbid air and relaxed; forgetting the warning of the wisdom Gu, he stopped.

This brief pause caused Ren Zu to be washed away by the river.

Life was not easy, it was like a boat moving against the flow of the river, if you do not continue moving forward, you will be pushed back.

Ren Zu was washed away by the river into the depths of Luo Po valley, he was so tired he could not budge a bit and was trapped in the Luo Po valley.

　　...

Fang Yuan broke the final guts stone and groaned in satisfaction.

Right now, he felt very comfortable. The heavy injuries in his soul were already completely recovered and moreover, his soul had even strengthened by five times!

A feeling of power burst out from the depths of his heart.

This feeling did not come from the strengthening of his physical body but from the vigor of his spirits. Fang Yuan had a feeling he could do anything easily, whether it was analyzing problems or doing multiple tasks.

"Unfortunately, there are only over a hundred gutstones on Dang Hun mountain and not all of them contained guts Gu." Fang Yuan felt some regret.

When Hu Immortal obtained Dang Hun mountain, it had already changed hands several times and was completed looted.

Hu Immortal moved it to the blessed land and managed it for decades. Almost every year, she would send large amounts of foxes to their deaths at Dang Hun mountain. Using their soul to irrigate the mountain and create gutstones.

However, these gutstones were almost all used by the Hu Immortal. After she died, these over hundred gutstones had slowly grown over close to eight years and now were completely used by Fang Yuan.

According to the Hu Immortal land spirit's description, close to ten thousand foxes needed to be sacrificed to grow a guts stone. The stronger the beast kings that died, the more gutstones would be produced.

Fang Yuan could not adopt this method.

When the blessed land was at its prime, it was inevitable and alright for Hu Immortal to do so. However, the blessed land was very weak now and the fox groups had decreased by a large amount. Killing these fox groups was not sensible for long term prospects.

With his soul injuries recovered, Fang Yuan started quietly thinking his future plans without relaxing the slightest bit.

Obtaining the Hu Immortal blessed land was no doubt a huge help to his plans, but at the same time also greatly affected his plans.

"Now, with Dang Hun mountain in my possession, my soul's foundation can continue to strengthen. And from my previous life, I have experience and insight in controlling the blood bats, such enormous advantage should be used. Walking the enslavement path is an obvious choice now."

"However, there is also a disadvantage in enslavement path in that the enslavement path Gu Masters can be easily assaulted and beheaded. So I cannot relax in my strength path cultivation as well!"

With this, Fang Yuan was going to walk on both strength and enslavement paths, organizing and feeding two sets of Gu worms.

If it was before, it would be difficult for Fang Yuan to do this. But now, with Hu Immortal blessed land, it would be no problem.

"The perfect outcome is to refine second aperture Gu. With second aperture, I could divide the sets of enslavement and strength path into different apertures without disturbing each other. At the same time, there would be enough primeval essence to control the two sets of Gu worms."

At that time, with a wave of his hand, a huge army of beasts and insects would cover the sky and earth, creating a river of blood in a blink of an eye, creating destruction and mayhem.

If there was any foolish person who tried to use the tactic of beheading the leader, then Fang Yuan's strength path cultivation would make them realize how cruel reality was and why flowers were red[1]!

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan took out the second aperture Gu from his aperture.

This Gu was like a peanut shell, shining with golden light, the patterns on its surface were scarlet veins of blood. This was the embryo form of the second aperture Gu, formed from combining false Gu and lifespan Gu; it could survive for forty years.

"There are enough immortal essence to truly refine the second aperture Gu, two third watch Gu can also be easily obtained, but I still require divine travel Gu." Fang Yuan pondered.

Immortal Gu were unique, only one Immortal Gu of the same type could exist in the world. Divine travel Gu was already transformed into fixed immortal travel Gu and no longer existed now. This allowed a new divine travel Gu to appear in the world.

Moreover, there was an extraordinary advantage of divine travel Gu - it could be easily obtained. It was not like the other Immortal Gu that were so hard to capture.

The legends of Ren Zu had written it clearly; as long as one drank the four top quality wines of the world, divine travel Gu could condense into being in their body.

Apart from the wine brewed by the wild beasts and those that were naturally formed, human's brewing techniques had flourished continually, and now the amount of top quality wines were much more than the ancient times.

Searching for the four top quality wines might be somewhat troublesome, but could be done by spending some time.

Fang Yuan had the blessed land and the assistance of the little Hu Immortal land spirit,

But the main problem did not lie here.

Because divine travel Gu could be easily obtained, others could also easily take advantage of it. In case, someone else obtained divine travel Gu, no matter how much top quality wines Fang Yuan drank, he would not obtain the divine travel Gu.

"Southern Border's Fei clan possess a top quality wine Zhuang Si Fei. Eastern Sea's rank seven Gu Immortal Zui Xian Weng has created a sea of wine, concealing countless wines, and holds a wine reception every year. Northern Plain's Imperial court has the long life wine. These great forces or maybe other Gu Immortals as well could be in possession of one or two top quality wine; their chances of obtaining divine travel Gu is much greater than mine."

With this calculation, Fang Yuan not only had to resist the earthly calamity and manage the blessed land, he also had to quickly gather the four top quality wine and refine second aperture Gu.

"However, these are not all, the crucial point lies in Spring Autumn Cicada. Time is flowing five times faster here, Spring Autumn Cicada's recovery speed will also become extremely quick. Being able to rebirth three times is already an extremely good luck, I cannot gamble on luck the fourth time. Before Spring Autumn Cicada recovers, I need to have success at first attempt Gu, immediate success Gu, smooth success Gu or any of the others."

Fang Yuan did not have enough strength before. Now, he had the blessed land and abundant resources, he could try to get these Gu already.

[1] Basically, injured until the chrysanthemum at their lower body bleeds, thus resembling a red flower. Back

Chapter 412: I like your fear

Hu Immortal blessed land, southern district.

"Yan Yong, Yan Yong, wake up quickly. Stop sleeping, you've slept for three years already!"

A voice woke Yan Yong up from his sleep.

A lump of grey stones with a mossy surface started to vibrate, as the tremors intensified, causing the dust to disperse. From the large oval stone, four limbs and a head appeared like the blossoming of a flower.

Next, a grey rockman stood up — Yan Yong woke up from his sleep.

"Grandpa?" Yan Yong opened his eyes, looking at the rockman who woke him up, it was his eight hundred year old grandpa, the leader of the Hui Shi tribe.

"Grandpa, why did you wake me up, I want to sleep for another two to three years." Yan Yong sighed, begrudging.

Rockmen loved to sleep. When they sleep, the curled into a ball, forming a large oval stone. Each sleeping session lasts seven to eight years.

"Stop sleeping, my grandson, you are already a hundred and eighty years old. Your father died earlier, and I cannot live much longer. In a few decades, you will be our Hui Shi tribe's new tribe leader."

Rockmen have a long lifespan, generally a thousand years to live. Ordinary humans could barely live for a hundred years, but Yan Yong was a hundred and eighty, and had just reached adulthood.

"Grandpa, I do not want to be tribe leader. After becoming leader, I will not have time to sleep casually anymore." Yan Yong pouted, but saw his grandpa staring angrily, and chose to shut up.

Hui Shi tribe leader chided: "Why haven't you grown up? You slept for so many years in vain. Quickly pack up, and clean the moss off you, pull off all the weed that had grown on you. Bring the offerings with you and go with grandpa to the ground, we have to meet the immortal, we cannot be disrespectful!"

"Ah? It is time to pay offerings to the immortal again? But I remember there is still a year left." Yan Yong said as he plucked the weed off him.

After sleeping for so many years, his armpits, his groin, and back all had lots of weed. Especially the black thread grass in his groin area, they were hard as steel and curly. Every time he plucked one, Yan Yong felt great pain.

"Sigh, there is a problem this time. The immortal changed, this immortal came not too long ago, he is calling for us." Old clan leader sighed and said with worry.

"New male immortal? I hope he is easier to speak to than that female immortal. Maybe we can discuss with him, after all, we have to contribute so much offerings every ten years, it is taxing."

"Mm, the other tribe leaders and I also have this thought."

　　...

On a large altar made of green rocks, Fang Yuan wore his black robe as his long black hair was let down, sitting at the main seat staring at the people below with his deep dark pupils.

There were tens of rockmen kneeling below, among them, eight were rockmen leaders, two grey rockmen, three granite rockmen, one iron rockman, one green rockman, and one white rockman.

At the same time, there were offerings.

Large amounts of ore containing gold, silver, bronze, iron, as well as other gems and jewels, Gu worms etc.

All sorts of metallic elements would grow on the rockmen's bodies as time passed. Fang Yuan looked at these offerings, understanding at once why Dang Hun palace was built so luxuriously.

If these were brought to Earth, they would be a huge asset, but here, their greatest use was to become Gu refinement materials.

Hu Immortal using these things as decoration was only her womanly love for beauty. If she could choose to exchange them for primeval stones, she would trade away all these gems and jewels without a second thought.

Among the offerings, the most valuable were Gu worms.

But these Gu were mostly rank one rock skin Gu, rank two monolith Gu. There was only one rank three Gu, stone aperture Gu.

Fang Yuan had once used this Gu, back then Spring Autumn Cicada's pressure on the aperture could not be relieved, thus when he was desperate, he used it.

The rockmen were skilled at digging, they lived deep underground. Their food was dirt, and sometimes when they dig underground, they would discover Gu worms.

"What did you say? You want to reduce the offerings?" Fang Yuan's eyes squinted as he stood up, slowly walking down the stairs, coming towards the rockmen leaders.

The rockmen were tall and huge, even when they kneeled on the ground, their shoulders were still higher than Fang Yuan's head.

"Esteemed lord immortal, our rockmen tribes have contributed so much offerings during these thirty years. During these years, the earth rumbled, the north area had floods, the east area had fires, life is difficult. These things that we managed to acquire are getting harder and harder to find. Immortal, please have mercy, and forgive our inability, reduce the offering amount by a bit." The oldest rockmen tribe leader begged.

"That's right, lord immortal, please reduce the offerings."

"These years, we have been decreasing in numbers."

"Immortal, please understand, we will never forget your kindness!"

The other rockmen leaders started saying.

"Reduce the offerings? Hehehe, of course you can! In fact, I can exempt you all from these offerings." Fang Yuan smiled kindly and warmly.

The rockmen's expression were joyous.

"But I have a condition." Next, Fang Yuan said: "I need you all to dig a river, from the north, transport the water towards the east, to stop the fire from spreading."

"What?!" Hearing this, the rockmen were shocked.

Quickly, they reacted, shouting loudly.

"Esteemed lord immortal, you cannot do this!"

"Digging a river from scratch, this is a huge project, we rockmen need sleep. Without sufficient sleep, we will die."

"And there is a great fire and huge amounts of water. You ask us to go dig a river, but isn't that asking us to go die?!"

At once, everyone flew into a rage. Many young rockmen were kneeling at one corner, but hearing this, they rushed over, staring at Fang Yuan vigilantly.

"Master." Hu Immortal land spirit beside Fang Yuan saw this and she felt slightly worried.

The rockmen had a stubborn nature, they had foolhardiness, emphasizing their pride and would not accede to demands. When they are rash, they would even attack Demon Venerables or Immortal Venerables, regardless of who the other party is.

Hu Immortal was only to contain these rockmen because at the start, she had spent a lot of effort and gave them a lot of benefits.

"Master, these rockmen do not reason with people, asking them to offer these things was already their limit..." Little Hu Immortal sent her thoughts to Fang Yuan secretly, reminding him.

"Limit?" Fang Yuan scoffed, his mouth opening as he showed his bright white teeth, laughing ruthlessly: "You rockmen are too insolent, you dare to bargain with me? Hmph! The place you are living at is mine. The dirt you eat is mine. The spirit spring beside your tribe is also mine. You live here, you are my slave! I want to dig a new river, that is not a request, and not a transaction, it is an order!"

The rockmen heard this and they all stood up, looking furious.

"Immortal, you don't know what's good for you, you dare to look down on us rockmen!"

"Back then when we relocated here, it was because of a female immortal. But the environment here is getting worse, who would want to stay here anymore?"

"You want us to dig a river, that is asking us to die. Do you think we rockmen are fools?"

"We rockmen are born from heaven and earth, we will not be your slaves. Let's go, relocate, I've had enough of this shitty place!"

The rockmen leaders shouted, falling out with Fang Yuan at once.

The followers they brought, the young rockmen all came forward, clenching their fists as they stared at Fang Yuan with a dangerous look.

"You want to leave? Hahaha." Fang Yuan threw his head back and laughed, like he had heard the funniest joke in the world. Next, he stopped laughing, looking at these rockmen coldly, his tone was chilly: "Where do you think this is? Come and go as you please? The old rules are no more, from today onwards, I am the greatest ruler, my words are heaven's will! You will abide by my rules, even if you don't want to!"

"Ahh!" Many young rockmen clenched their fists and howled.

"Immortal, you are trying to step over my tribe's baseline!"

"Immortal, you might be strong, but we are not afraid."

"We rockmen will never lower our heads to brute force, we are natural warriors, we fear no death!"

"Only love can make us dig out our hearts. Only warmth can make us lower our backs."

Roar!

Fang Yuan pushed with his hand and a golden dragon flew out.

The golden dragon roared, killing the rockman that was screaming the loudest.

"Ah, he killed the granite rockmen's old tribe leader!"

"Old tribe leader is dead, we have to get revenge!!"

"Even an immortal has to die under our tribe's fury!"

Granite old tribe leader's death was like the trigger, causing the rockmen's anger to erupt.

The rockmen attacked Fang Yuan in waves, every step made a dent in the ground, as they gave off an impressive aura. Dozens of rockmen attacked together, giving off the disposition of a grand army of ten thousand.

From their bodies, numerous lights shone. There were also Gu worms inhibiting these rockmen's bodies, they were activated through their will.

But a moment later, these lights vanished.

Little Hu Immortal struck, sealing all the Gu worms.

Fang Yuan snickered as he began his slaughter.

The rockmen were not afraid of death, but their strength was inferior to fang Yuan, they were all broken down into shards, dying a pathetic death.

But these rock fragments gathered like magnets, forming new rockmen.

"Kill!"

"Resist the tyranny, take revenge for father!!"

"We are born from heaven and earth, we die due to heaven and earth, thus we have no fear!"

Tiny rockmen charged over, and were all slaughtered by Fang Yuan.

But these rock fragments gathered into even smaller rockmen.

The number of these rockmen continued to shrink, but after they were formed, they charged towards Fang Yuan and shouted things like exacting revenge for their grandpa, father etc.

This was the way the rockmen reproduced. It was a male only race, after the old rockmen dies, the soul and rocks they split into will form new rockmen, and inherit a portion of the old rockmen's memories, or some important experiences. In some cases, old rockmen sleep too much and their soul foundation accumulates to a degree, they would split out a portion of their bodies to form new tiny rockmen.

After Fang Yuan killed the third wave of rockmen, the world was finally silent once more.

Only one rockman remained, lying on the ground, shivering.

"What is your name?" Fang Yuan slowly walked towards him.

"My... my name is Yan... Yan Yong." The young rockman stammered.

"Do you know why I left only you alive?" Fang Yuan stood on Yan Yong's head.

"No... I do not know..."

"Because you are terrified. Because I like your fear and horror towards me." Fang Yuan smiled warmly.

Chapter 413: A show

Three days later, a seriously injured Yan Yong returned to his tribe and woke up all the hibernating rockmen.

"A male immortal is here, he is a demon, he wanted to enslave all of us!"

"Not only this, he also wanted to take away the beautiful men of our rockmen tribe, to become his plaything."

"We rockmen are born of nature, free and unfettered, how could we bow our backs to such lecherous authority?"

"We resisted at the spot. The immortal was too strong, but we rockmen were not afraid of sacrificing and fought him without fearing death; finally, we injured him and beat him into retreat."

"The other tribesmen were all sacrificed and only I was able to return. I am dying but that immortal is still alive. Before he ran away, he said he will lead his fox army and annihilate all our rockmen tribes!"

Yan Yong weakly lamented, announcing a frightening information to his tribesmen.

The rockmen were shocked and afraid, grieving and also furious; some declared war, some wanted revenge, some mentioned migrating and some wanted to discuss.

They had lost their bearings without a leader; whether it was the inheritor or the old tribe leader, they had all died at Fang Yuan's hands. There were altogether eight tribes of rockmen and they had fallen into chaos now.

Some rockmen wanted to get the concrete details from Yan Yong, but Yan Yong's injuries were too severe, and after informing them of this grievous news, he lost consciousness.

While they were still in the midst of discussing, just like Yan Yong said, waves after waves of fox groups started attacking rockmen tribes.

The rockmen resisted with all their strength, but there were way too many fox groups; the situation was gradually turning grave, the eight tribes had no choice but to ally and retreat underground to defend themselves.

However, the fox groups did not let them go and repeatedly attacked the underground. The fox groups paid a disastrous price every time they attacked, but they still came endlessly.

The rockmen cursed Fang Yuan, their hatred towards him were like a inferno that could not be extinguished. The situation became worse day by day and despair spread in the hearts of the rockmen.

However, right at this time, Yan Yong woke up.

Rockmen could recuperate from their injuries through sleep; his injuries had healed for the most part. He immediately led the rockmen and made beautiful counterattacks.

"We rockmen are a courageous group with no fear of death!"

"Even the immortal cannot humiliate us!"

Yan Yong announced to everyone and raised their morale.

"Don't think the immortal is strong, he is only a paper tiger and can only send these fox groups to their death, he is already injured."

At the same time, he proclaimed the injuries of the immortal and gave hope to the rockmen.

The despairing rockmen tightly grabbed onto this hope like it was a straw that could save them as they were drowning.

Yan Yong changed the subject and talked about the old tribe leaders.

"He was injured by the combined efforts of the old tribe leaders, the sacrifice of the old tribe leaders is our greatest grief."

"Especially the old white rock tribe leader, his life ended as he was in my arms, before he died he entrusted the whole tribe to me. I looked as his soul dispersed, and felt ashamed, why wasn't it me who died, but him!" He beat his chest as he said this, appearing to be extremely sad.

Immediately, some rockmen persuaded: "Lord Yan Yong, don't grieve. It is already very amazing you were able to survive and bring us the warning, even leading us towards victory."

"That's right, we iron rockmen all admire you."

"Since the old tribe leader entrusted the tribe to you, then please lead us white rockmen."

What rockmen liked was to sleep soundly and were not too obsessed with authority. Especially, at this juncture of life and death where they were living in anxiety, the rockmen hoped for a strong and brave rockman to lead them.

Thereupon, Yan Yong first inherited his tribe's tribe leader position and then white rock tribe.

Over a month later, he got hold of the remaining tribes one after another, becoming the joint leader of the eight rockmen tribes.

Another half a month passed, he led the rockmen and drove out the fox groups, protecting his tribes.

"This is not enough. As long as the immortal doesn't die, we have no future. The fox groups will regroup and attack our home again."

"We can only attack, attack that immortal mountain and completely kill the immortal for a beautiful and peaceful life."

Yan Yong immediately mentioned attacking Dang Hun mountain.

Some rockmen, however, seemed to hesitate.

"We have just suffered such a bitter battle, we just want to sleep now."

"Our rockmen population has decreased greatly, we don't have the strength to attack that demonic stronghold."

"We have large numbers of offsprings born from this bitter battle, we need to raise them properly till they become adults."

Yan Yong could only shift the topic to the old white rock tribe leader.

"My tribesmen, will I bring you to your deaths?"

"Attacking the immortal mountain was not my idea. It was a secret the old white rock tribe leader told me before his death."

"He said this immortal mountain is the legendary Dang Hun mountain. Dang Hun mountain has gutstones, if our rockmen can obtain these gutstones, it can increase our strength and make our tribes stronger!"

The old white rock tribe leader was the oldest and the most experienced rockman. He was widely known by the rockmen as the sage.

With his 'last words' along with Yan Yong's clear might, the rockmen were agitated and formed an expedition to attack Dang Hun mountain.

Fang Yuan had intentionally arranged some fox groups around Dang Hun mountain, forming a weak defensive line.

Yan Yong continually boosted the rockmen's morale: "See, there is not much left of the demonic immortal's fox army. We are already close to victory."

The rockmen sang of victory and triumph along the way, charging toward Dang Hun mountain with uplifted morale.

At Dang Hun mountain, Fang Yuan appeared with a group of foxes and fought a 'great battle' with the rockmen.

Fang Yuan showed terrifying strength and killed many rockmen, causing all the rockmen to be terrified.

But at this moment, Yan Yong stood up and pointed to Fang Yuan's injuries and his paper tiger 'immortal essence', and fought a 'decisive battle' with him.

The fox groups were eliminated, as Fang Yuan was 'defeated', forced to escape from Yan Yong's assault.

"Wait till I come back after gathering immortal essence from the water and fire! That moment will be your end!" Before retreating, Fang Yuan shouted loudly with a malevolent expression.

Rockmen had rough physique and their movements were slow, and not being familiar with Dang Hun mountain's terrain, they could only let Fang Yuan 'escape'.

The rockmen worshipped Yan Yong for beating back the immortal and cheered victoriously.

"My tribesmen, now is not the time to cheer." Yan Yong stood up, "We can't stay on Dang Hun mountain for long, this is a demonic land. The old white rock tribe leader had told me, every year only during these few days, we rockmen can enter this place safely. We need to hurry and collect the gutstones here. Three days later, we need to leave this place!"

Their bodies were made of solid rock. There was a burden on their soul to hold up such a strong and firm body. If the rockmen moved too excessively, it could harm their soul.

Thus, rockmen would spend eighty percent of their whole life sleeping and nurturing their soul.

When the foundation of their soul was thick enough, it would leak out. This overflowing part of the soul would fall on a rock and form a new life. Rockmen tribes reproduce like this.

After the rockmen obtained the gutstones, the guts Gu could strengthen and expand their soul, causing the soul to overflow and form little rockmen.

Three days later, inside the mountain, in Dang Hun palace.

Yan Yong kneeled on the ground and reported with reverence and fear as he lowered his head and bowed: "Reporting to the immortal, with these three days of soul strengthening, our rockmen tribes have increased by six thousand little rockmen. Including us old tribesmen, the whole population has increased to three times the population before the battle!"

Fang Yuan was sitting grandly on the fluffy bed and looked down at Yan Yong.

"Good, with this, your rockmen have enough manpower to start the river construction. Next, you remember what to do, right? Or do you need me to tell you again?"

Yan Yong promptly replied: "Supreme immortal, I did not dare to forget your words and have engraved them in my mind."

"Good." Fang Yuan nodded indifferently, "I will give you three months of time to dig a great river that cuts across the eastern and northern areas."

"Ah, three months?" Yan Yong was stupefied, "Mighty immortal, us rockmen need sleep to nurture our souls. If we move excessively, we will tire ourselves to death. The great river is so long, and with only three months of time, we would have not be able to have any rest. If we work like this, our rockmen tribes will probably die out."

"Hehehe, you won't die completely. I have already calculated, there will be over two hundred rockmen remaining." Fang Yuan laughed.

Yan Yong felt a chill in his body. There were ten thousand rockmen now, but there would only be over two hundred after the project. How terrifying of a sacrifice was this?

"Three months later, I want to see a great river! If I don't see it, I will tell the truth to your tribesmen before I kill you. Now roll away." Fang Yuan's tone was cold and unfeeling.

Yan Yong's body trembled all over hearing this demonic threat.

He had a very deep fear towards Fang Yuan and did not dare to retort, his body curled up into a ball and surprising, he really rolled away.

"Master, we paid a huge price back then to bring in these rockmen." The little Hu Immortal land spirit tactfully persuaded, she could not endure seeing such a huge amount of rockmen dying like this.

"Don't worry, the rockmen has still a great use to me. And isn't it easy to increase their population?" Fang Yuan leaned on a chair with his eyes squinting as he took out a burial soul toad from his aperture.

Burial soul toad was a rank four Gu used to store things. It was one of the Gu worms left by the Hu Immortal.

It was palm sized big and was grey color. There were small warts all over its back and its large eyes flashed with weird and gloomy green light.

It could only store souls and its belly would inflate as it sucked in the souls.

Fang Yuan used this to collect the souls of the rockmen who died in the battle with the fox groups.

Now, this soul burial toad's belly was deflated. The souls that were inside it before were placed on Dang Hun mountain by Fang Yuan to breed new gutstones.

Fang Yuan used a part of the gutstones to make his soul six times stronger than that of a normal person.

And the remaining gutstones were given to the rockmen tribes.

The rockmen had no idea, the strengthening of their souls was all due to the death of their companions.

Chapter 414: Conscience of those in power

Yan Yong got out of Dang Hun palace, after getting through some twisted and dark tunnels, he arrived on Dang Hun mountain.

After seeing the crystal pink mountain, Yan Yong blew out a breath of turbid air, his fear and pressure had decreased greatly after leaving Fang Yuan.

After moving on the mountain for a while, he was finally discovered by his tribemates.

"Oh, our great and honorable leader, our hero, you are here!" Some rockmen cheered.

"Please let me kiss your foot, to express my adoration of you." A few rockmen kneeled on the ground.

"Big hero, big hero! Your courage is greater than heaven, your guts is thicker than the earth." Some tiny rockmen formed into groups and shouted loudly.

Yan Yong laughed, no one knew how bitter he felt.

The cheers he heard were extremely joyous, there were many tribesmen around him, gathering together, but he felt extremely lonely at this point.

He looked at these tribesmen, these smiling rockmen, they were all going to die three months later. Dying of exhaustion after digging the river. But what could he do?

From what the other rockmen saw, Dang Hun mountain's victory was glorious, it was worth celebrating. But only he knew, this was only a game manipulated in the dark by that immortal.

The cruel and chilling truth made him understand clearly that the sacrifice of those rockmen, and this difficult victory, it was so laughably pathetic, they were powerless.

He led his tribesmen and gained more victories, but at the same time his fear towards Fang Yuan grew.

"That immortal, he is a demon! His heart is harder and colder than us rockmen, his strength is greater than the weight of the mountains. I am so weak, what can I do? Resistance means death. I admit my cowardice, I am really afraid of dying. I have not slept enough, I am only a hundred and eighty years old."

The moment Yan Yong thought about Fang Yuan's appearance, his heart was filled with terror.

His lingering bit of conscience was torturing him.

He knew: he was about to send his tribesmen to death personally. He was being grilled by his conscience, every praise from his tribesmen was like a whip, causing his heart to be full of pain and scars.

"Our esteemed, beloved tribe leader, you are finally back! Everyone's waiting." The rockmen gave way to Yan Yong, as he walked unobstructed towards higher ground.

"My tribesmen, these three days, our tribe has grown by many times. Our conquest has gotten us glorious results. But such victory is insufficient. Are you all willing to continue following me, towards a brighter future?" Yan Yong looked down at his tribesmen and shouted loudly.

The rockmen used the loudest cheer they could muster to express their hundred and twenty percent support towards Yan Yong.

Yan Yong nodded, he had expected such an outcome.

Among the rockmen, there were no outliers or knowledgeable old rockmen. During the few intense battles, they had "gloriously" sacrificed themselves.

The remaining rockmen were all newborn, they had a simple mind. As for the remaining old rockmen, they were all hardcore supporters of Yan Yong, his loyal worshippers.

Yan Yong patiently waited for the cheers to stop before continuing: "These three days, I had been considering — how do we deal with the escaped immortal. Immortals have immortal essence, thus they are able to control the fox army, and have terrifying strength. He must have retreated to the lake at the north area, or hid in east area's fire pit. We cannot allow him to recover."

"Tribe leader is right!"

"Tribe leader is too smart, we cannot allow that evil immortal to recover his immortal essence."

"When that accursed demon recovers his strength, he will definitely find trouble with us rockmen!"

"But what do we do now? The lake and fire pit are both dangerous areas. Even us rockmen cannot last long there. And these two areas are so wide, who knows where the immortal escaped to."

Everyone was speaking as the scene turned noisy.

Yan Yong interrupted everyone's discussions, shouting: "That's why, I thought of the only solution. We will use soil to fill the fire pit and lake, that way, the immortal will be unable to recover his immortal essence!"

"Oh god, that is an insane idea!" At once, some rockmen shouted.

"My great tribe leader, the lake is so wide, it causes people to stare in amazement. The fire pit has a fatal temperature, how can we use soil to fill it? That is impossible." An old rockmen immediately argued.

Yan Yong stared at this old rockmen deeply, remembering him to heart.

This rockmen dared to question him, it showed that his idolization was not deep enough, thus he shall get the heaviest and toughest job later, working to death.

At this time, another old rockmen said: "We cannot do this forcefully, I have a solution. Maybe we can dig out a river and direct the lake water to the fire pit, using water to neutralize fire, that will be easier."

Yan Yong's killing intent rose even more.

This old rockmen was very intelligent, he was a bigger threat than the old rockmen who rebuked him.

He immediately decided in this heart, he was going to send this old rockmen to a defense mission. He shall be killed by the fox army, this threat has to be eliminated!

Yan Yong praised this old man plainly, shouting: "That is exactly my idea, we have to dig a river and direct the water over to end the fire. The immortal will have no place to recover immortal essence! Actually, white stone old tribe leader taught me before dying, he said that the water at the north and the fire at the east were all done by that evil male immortal. That is the source of his power, just like how we rockmen eat soil."

"So white stone old tribe leader predicted this."

"White stone old tribe leader, as expected of our philosopher."

"White stone old tribe leader was already nine hundred and ninety-eight years old, of course he knew a lot."

All the rockmen nodded, expressing their agreement with white stone old tribe leader, but also felt deep pity and anguish towards his death.

Rockmen sleep for a long time, they have little interaction with each other. This sense of distance and mystery caused the deceased white stone old tribe leader's knowledge to feel extremely profound.

Using a phrase from Earth, if white stone old tribe leader could hear this in the afterlife, he might jump out of his coffin in anger.

But unfortunately, he was completely killed by Fang Yuan, his soul was not spared, broken down on Dang Hun mountain by Fang Yuan. The essence landed on the mountain, forming a gutstone.

Whether this gustone was smashed by a rockmen, or Fang Yuan himself, that would be an eternal mystery.

After discussing, the rockmen agreed that Yan Yong should be the leader, overseeing the digging to connect the water and fire.

Fang Yuan hid in the background, looking at this scene secretly. After seeing the finalized plan, he ordered little Hu Immortal.

The land spirit released a trace of Dang Hun mountain's power, and the rockmen felt their soul tremble, they got very dizzy. Many young rockmen fainted on the spot.

"Oh no, let's hurry and get out. Dang Hun mountain is going to attack!" Yan Yong said, as he left his tribesmen away from Dang Hun mountain.

They did not return to their original home, but instead got to the north and east area in a grand fashion.

In Dang Hun mountain, Fang Yuan looked expressionlessly at these leaving rockmen using the smoke cloud.

"Master, have you heard of the story of the rockmen?" Little Hu Immortal's tail was swaying as she spoke meekly.

Fang Yuan laughed lightly: "You want to urge me to use soft tactics with the rockmen?"

"Master is so smart." Little Hu Immortal's large eyes were shining.

"Heh, it seems you are not too familiar with this. Often, the power of fear and hatred surpasses gratitude greatly.

Back then, when Fang Yuan found out that there was a group of rockmen, he was overjoyed.

The rockmen lived underground, they ate soil as food and were skilled at digging. A large ground of rockmen could even build and underground city deep in the ground.

Rockmen could excavate resources for the blessed land's owner, they were excellent slaves. Many Gu Immortals want to buy rockmen and move them into their own blessed land.

For Hu Immortal blessed land, because of Dang Hun mountain, and provided it had enough souls, just one rockman can use the gutstones to breed into a large clan.

Fang Yuan could use this to mass produce rockmen and engage in slave trade with other Gu Immortals.

Back then, Hu Immortal brought all these rockmen in with the same intentions.

It was true, rockmen only succumbed to soft tactics. Most of the rockmen were stubborn and tough, warrior not afraid to die. Thus, many Gu Immortals have to use kindness and benefits to slowly use these rockmen and maximise their worth.

Hu Immortal used such a method.

But Fang Yuan did not adopt this.

It was too gentle.

He wanted squeeze them dry, to gain the most benefits!

This world's competition is so cruel, not only did man compete with each other, they also had to deal with disasters and calamities, who knows how many heroes had fallen to floods.

So what if you are a Gu Immortal?

If you did not arm yourself and make use of every resource you had to strengthen yourself, Hu Immortal's demise would be the best example.

A demonic path member has to make the best of his time, considering even the small bit of benefit, taking whatever he can and make himself stronger!

"Anyone in power has to understand: Rules, laws, friendship and morals, these are all tools to squeeze out benefits. Leniency and conscience, cruelty and hatred, they are all the same." Fang Yuan laughed coldly in his heart.

After wasting so much time with the rockmen, there were only seven months left to the sixth calamity.

The lake at the north, fire pit at the east, they were all scars left by previous calamities, weak spots of the blessed land. When earthly calamities occur, they would be the weakest link.

A team is only as strong as its weakest player. The weight a chain can hold up depends on the most fragile section.

"So what if I am hated, detested, and scolded by countless people?"

"If this world was so simple such that hatred, loathe, and curses work, why would I still need strength?"

The most important thing was digging the river as soon as possible, to help the blessed land recover as much as it could, it did not matter how many rockmen died in the process. Since Dang Hun mountain was here, he just had to capture a few souls and there would be an uncountable number of rockmen produced!

Chapter 415: For tomorrow!

Rumble rumble...

Explosions went off one after another, as dust and smoke rose into the air.

This was the site of the river digging project.

The rockmen ate soil as food, many of the Gu worms on the rockmen's bodies can be used.

"Lord tribe leader, we cannot continue like this! Yesterday, three tribesmen died from exhaustion, they had a pitiful death, not even leaving behind a single offspring."

An elderly rockmen kneeled before Yan Yong as he cried.

Once a rockman dies of exhaustion, their soul will dissipate, they will die for real, there will not be any young rockmen formed from their remaining soul.

Yan Yong slammed his chest, howling: "Why would I not know? Why would I not know? Heroes have sacrificed for our tribe again! For the bright future of our tribe, for a beautiful tomorrow, they contributed their lives!"

"But precisely so, we cannot slow down. Since the start of the excavation, we have faced many attacks from the fox army. The size of the fox group is getting larger, evidently that accursed male immortal is regaining his immortal essence! We have to continue and work hard, digging the river so that he loses his source of power!"

Old rockman was stunned: "But tribe leader..."

"You are a good rockman, you think for our tribe, I understand that. These heroes will not die in vain. Look there, I have already made heroic gravestones for them. Their children and descendants will remember them, and feel gratitude for the sacrifices made." Yan Yong pointed at the gravestones erected, there was a large number of them.

The old rockman looked at the gravestones, sighing.

Once the death of the rockmen appeared, the new tribe leader Yan Yong immediately ordered people to build these gravestones.

The low morale was immediately raised, although everyday, countless rockmen die of exhaustion, they were still in high spirits.

"They are dead, what is the use of these gravestones?" The old rockman was one of the few left who understood the situation, he felt deeply worried.

"Oh leader." He bitterly urged: "Us rockmen have to reproduce as well. These rockmen who die of exhaustion will not even have their souls left, they cannot leave behind descendants."

Yan Yong's expression remained unchanged, not saying a word.

A young rockman beside him started grumbling: "You old man, are you afraid of dying!"

Old rockman immediately retorted: "Young man, how can you say that? Yes, I am old, but I am a rockman, how can a rockman be afraid of dying?"

"Since you are not afraid to die, why are you talking so much?"

"That's right. We are making contributions to the tribe!"

"What's the matter? We are making a small sacrifice for the bigger good."

Beside Yan Yong, a group of young rockmen started arguing.

"Old senior, if you feel tired, take a rest first. It is not a problem, my time is limited, I have to go to the other areas to inspect the progress." Yan Yong patted this old rockman's shoulder as he walked away, continuing on his inspection.

A group of young rockmen followed behind Yan Yong, talking among themselves, expressing their disdain for that old rockman.

Being despised by these juniors, the old rockman felt very depressed, smoke was coming out of his ears.

He wanted to rebuke them loudly, but he saw all the gravestones near the construction area, with all sorts of words carved on them.

"We have to do this at all cost!"

"As long as we are united, within three days, we will complete the river!"

"The bigger our courage, the more we can achieve."

"To build a beautiful future for our rockmen tribe!"

"Long live tribe leader Yan Yong!"

"For the bright future of the rockmen, we contribute our lives, we contribute our youth!"

The crazed atmosphere engulfed the rockmen's hearts. Even those rockmen who died from exhaustion showed a smile before they died.

Old rockman wanted to speak, but his mouth opened many times and did not manage to say a word.

He kneeled on the spot in a daze for a long while, until suddenly, he lifted his fist and slammed the ground heavily.

Bam, it was a heavy sound.

The old rockman stood up slowly, silently moving his aged body towards the construction ground.

Yan Yong rushed to the next site.

The river channel was already starting to form, large numbers of adult rockmen were digging in the channel. Beside them, the physically weaker young rockmen formed into patrolling groups. Some were inspecting the river digging, some were carving slogans, some were making heroic gravestones.

These young rockmen were called rock guards, formed by Yan Yong personally.

"Reporting to tribe leader!" Five to six young rockmen went to Yan Yong and reported the results of these few days of labor.

"Reporting to great leader, we have dug another 25km in this segment!"

"Reporting to great leader, we have unfortunately sacrificed a hundred and twenty tribesmen, they are all heroes of our tribe!"

"Reporting to great leader, we actually found three tribesmen sleeping on the job. This is a disgrace to our tribe, we have to criticize them!"

"Very good, very good, you have all done well! Remember, you have to erect gravestones for our deceased heroes. At the same time, tie up those disgraceful rockmen and criticize them up public, let them learn courage from humiliation." Yan Yong spoke caringly.

"Understood!"

"You are all the future of our tribe, seeing you all is like seeing the bright future of our tribe. You have to continue working hard." Yan Yong praised.

The young rockmen were extremely spurred on, their bodies were trembling.

"Everything for the rockmen tribe!"

"Our esteemed and beloved leader, you are our symbol of pride!"

"We unite by your side, walking towards a bright and meaningful future!!"

They growled one after another, showing a fanatic gaze.

But Yan Yong avoided eye contact with them, these young rockmen's enthusiasm made him fearful.

He looked at a faraway place.

There, all the different segments of the river were being excavated, Yan Yong could see many rockmen looking down at the yellow soil while lowering their thick backs.

The river channel was tens of meters wide, segment after segment, a long line showed up in his vision.

This was a majestic project!

Every time Yan Yong saw this sene, his heart palpitated — as long as they are united, the rockmen tribe's strength was overwhelming, it could change the world!

But when Yan Yong thought of Fang Yuan, that terrifying demon, his heart felt a strong chill that turned his enthusiasm into a frozen river.

Be it the fox groups outside, the slogans on the stone boards, or the rock guards he created, they were all a part of the demon's plot.

With so many methods, he forcefully reduced the rockmen tribe's resistance to the minimum.

Yan Yong was the one who created this scenario personally, seeing the formation of the river, his fear towards Fang Yuan became greater and greater.

That male immortal not only had terrifying strength, what truly caused despair was that scheming and devious mind of his, making him seem like an unpredictable abyss.

Yan Yong felt himself sinking into purgatory.

He was meek like an ant, while behind him, Fang Yuan giant figure was staring down at him.

He was like a corpse, a puppet, the strings that controlled him was in the hands of Fang Yuan.

Everyday, he saw his tribesmen die, his heart hurt like a dagger was stabbing it.

Seeing the enthusiasm of his tribesmen, dying to dig the river, he felt a pitiful grief.

"If possible, I would rather not know the truth. Maybe, continuing to live in this lie is true bliss?"

Yan Yong retracted his gaze, waving his hand and bringing the young rockmen towards the next river segment.

　　...

"This is the last estrus Gu, go."

Primeval essence had already been injected, as Fang Yuan flicked his finger and shot the green bean looking Gu into the air.

Estrus Gu exploded, turning into pink powder as it rained down on the fox group below.

The entire fox group breathed in this powder, and immediately stirred.

Very soon, numerous male foxes sprawled on the female foxes' backs, moving vigorously as they injected their life essence into the female fox's body.

The fox gestation varied. For example, golden fox took two months to give birth once. Every time, there were three to four foxes. As for desolate beasts like three-tail fox, even a hundred years was not enough to nurture their fetus.

Normally, the stronger the beast, the longer it takes for one gestation.

But right now in Hu Immortal blessed land, the fox groups were ordinary, they had a short gestation period.

Ever since the rockmen started digging the river until the process became smooth, Fang Yuan had been using estrus Gu everyday, creating new foxes and strengthening the fox army.

Hu Immortal did not have an Immortal Gu, during the fifth earthly calamity, she was killed by blue charm lightning shadow, thus her set of enslavement path Gu worms were not spared.

But within Dang Hun mountain, she left behind a number of Gu worms.

For example, assistance type Gu like burial soul toad, or expenditure type Gu like estrus Gu, as well as some spare Gu worms for the enslavement path, most were fox enslavement Gu.

To quickly increase his strength, Fang Yuan already used up most of these Gu worms.

The fox group had increased in numbers by several times after his hard work.

Although the foxes were omnivores, the blessed land could not sustain such a large number. In less than two years, a lot of foxes would be unable to find food and die of starvation.

But Fang Yuan could not care less, his whole mind was on enduring the sixth earthly calamity now.

A few months passed quickly.

A river connected the north and east.

The overflowing lake flowed along the river channel, moving quickly with ripples splashing.

Swish swish...

The great flood flowed into the fire pit, as the two forces clashed, river water evaporated and turned to steam, rising into the air.

After the river water calmed down, almost half the black flames were doused. Only three burning areas remained at the edges.

This way, fire and water wiped each other out, the north area's flood was alleviated, and the ground surfaced once more.

Large amounts of water flowed along the river and filled tens of pits, forming many lakes.

Even though the north area was still full of mud, and the east area was a burnt land without any living plants, the fusion of fire and water had created something like a scab on a bleeding wound.

As long as time passed, the east and north areas will eventually regain their vitality.

Under Fang Yuan's instructions, Yan Yong brought the injured and tired hundred or so rockmen back to their homes at the south area.

"Master, what do we do with these clouds?" Little Hu Immortal looked at the sky, the thick clouds made her feel helpless.

Even though it rained many times already, a lot of water vapor was still in the air, forming into clouds.

These clouds blocked the natural light, causing the east area to be shrouded in darkness, it made people feel irritated.

The blessed land did not have sunlight or wind. These clouds would heavily affect the lives of the east area's inhabitants.

"Ignore them." Fang Yuan looked at the sea of clouds and retracted his gaze.

The appearance of the clouds was expected, it was a minor detail. What is truly important, is the sixth earthly calamity!

If the blessed land survives this, he would slowly settle the issue about the clouds. If it fails to make it, then there is no point in thinking about it.

Chapter 416: Enduring the Earthly Calamity (1/2)

Several months later.

In Hu Immortal blessed land, the fox groups gathered into an army and surrounded Dang Hun mountain tightly.

Fang Yuan stood with his arms behind his back at the peak of the mountain and looked at the sky with a solemn expression.

Time passed mercilessly, today was the day of the sixth earthly calamity!

Even though Fang Yuan was a Gu Immortal in his previous life, he still felt uneasy facing an earthly calamity.

Every earthly calamity increases in intensity compared to the previous one, it was a cruel trial that decided the life and death of the Gu Immortals and their blessed land. Fang Yuan took over the blessed land when there was only a year and three months left.

This time was truly short, he could only prepare with his best efforts. Digging a river and alleviating the water and fire crisis was one, nurturing foxes and increasing their numbers was two. Holding onto fixed immortal travel Gu and being prepared to retreat was the third preparation.

As for the clouds in the sky, as well as the blue charm lightning shadow at the west area, he had no way of dealing with them.

The mild wind gradually stopped. High up in the sky, clouds were rumbling and a lump of light was forming..

"It's coming." Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk as he muttered.

In the cloud sea, the lump light burst out, forming a great white round door, facing the blessed land directly.

The light was glaring and dazzling, as a brown-yellow colored large monster descended from the light door like a large rock.

"Looking at this scene, is this the desolate beast calamity?!" Fang Yuan squinted and stared without blinking.

The giant rock continued to descend silently.

Fang Yuan could not help but lick his dry lips as his heart sank.

There were countless types of earthly calamities, among them were the desolate beast calamity.

In the blessed land, one or multiple desolate beasts will appear, charging towards the blessed land's central control area, wreaking havoc and causing destruction to the blessed land.

If they were not exterminated in time, even a large blessed land would be destroyed and reduced to ashes.

"Damn it, it is a desolate beast, I just hope there is no Immortal Gu on this desolate beast!" Fang Yuan cursed in his heart.

If desolate beasts had Immortal Gu on them, their battle strength would surpass Gu Immortals!

This mysterious desolate beast landed on the ground in a light manner contrary to its giant size.

Looking from afar, it looked like a slightly flat giant rock.

But Fang Yuan could tell from the images that this large rock was only a brown-yellow exoskeleton glowing with a golden lustre. There were thick layers of mud on the shell armor.

Just as Fang Yuan was guessing what sort of creature it was, a large pair of cheliped, like two bronze poles, stretched out from the shell.

Next, nine pairs of chelipeds stretched out from two sides, landing on the ground, raising the heavy body off the ground.

"Swamp crab!" Seeing this, Fang Yuan spoke immediately, recognising the true identity of this desolate beast.

This was a large crab, with a body that was the size of a mountain. When its body was lifted, the height could reach a quarter of Dang Hun mountain.

Its first pair of chelipeds was more fearsome than steel poles, a pair of pincers that could break mountain rocks or cut a flood dragon in half!

Its remaining eighteen chelipeds, although thinner than the first pair, they were still thicker than hundred year old trees.

There were large numbers of Gu worms on its body, most would be water and earth path Gu worms. Rarely, it could even contain an entire set of Gu worms.

"Thankfully, Hu Immortal blessed land has ample immortal essence!" Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, feeling glad in his heart.

Earlier when the swamp crab appeared, the land spirit already struck, using the heavenly power to restrict its Gu worms.

All rank one to five Gu worms could not display their abilities.

The most important point was, this desolate beast had no Immortal Gu. If it did, then the question would be what Immortal Gu that was.

Immortal Gu were unique, surpassing the laws of the mortal realm; blessed lands could not restrict them.

The existence of an Immortal Gu was the most important element in this battle!

The swamp crab fully stretched its limbs and started slowly moving towards Dang Hun mountain.

Fang Yuan willed and moved his troops quickly. Large numbers of foxes all over the mountain, rushed like the tides towards the desolate beast.

In moments, they encircled the swamp crab.

Their claws and teeth scratched the swamp crab's legs, and the physically tougher golden foxes directly crashed into it.

But the swamp crab was huge like a mountain and continued moving forward. The ordinary fox groups could not stop it, instead they were stomped into meat paste.

Fang Yuan's expression was cruel as he directed the foxes to continue giving up their lives.

He bred so many of them, they were meant to be used as disposable pieces. Damage accumulates; any amount of damage they could deal counted.

But the swamp crab gave off an unstoppable momentum as it advanced without halting a single step. Like a moving mountain, it did not care about the foxes below.

All sorts of attacks landed on the swamp crab's body, like a beautiful display of fireworks.

These were the attacks of the hundred, thousand and myriad beast kings of the foxes. They had all sorts of Gu worms.

Under the strength of all the Gu, the mud on swamp crab's body was all blown away.

This giant crab, for the first time, stopped its movement.

It opened its mouth and spewed out large amounts of mud. At the same time, from its stomach, yellow mud spewed out like a waterfall.

The mud landed on the grass and formed a swamp.

From the mud, weird looking crabs stood up. Some had large sizes, ferocious like a tiger. Some had sharp thin needle like pincers. Some had claw-like legs, having quick speed.

In the blink of an eye, a crab army that numbered to a million formed.

"It is the swamp crab indeed! It can breed at any time and place, creating numerous smaller crabs and forming an army." Fang Yuan's expression turned darker.

The fox groups were fighting against the crab army, engaging in fierce combat.

The number of foxes continued to decrease. The crab army's deaths were much greater than the fox group, but the desolate beast continued to give birth, and there was an endless number of crabs.

Fang Yuan quickly instructed the fox groups hiding outside the mountain to return.

"Thankfully, I expended my estrus Gu and bred a large number of foxes, otherwise, my total force would not be enough!"

In just this short period, Fang Yuan felt dizzy.

He directed an insanely large number of foxes, and even though his soul was six times as strong as a normal person, it could not take this pressure.

With the crab army paving the way, the swamp crab continued moving forward, regaining its former speed.

The legs on its body moved one after another, like fingers playing on a piano, with a rhythmic beauty.

But an intense battle was going on below it; blood flowed into river, corpses piled into a hill, and every piece of land was tainted with blood.

The swamp crab did not differentiate enemies from allies, every time its legs landed on the ground, there would be a fountain of blood squirting all over the place. When the crab raised its leg, there would be foxes' crushed bodies and broken crab carcasses in the deep pit on the ground.

This desolate beast's body was so large, and honestly speaking, it did not move quickly.

But because of this, it was able to create an immense mental pressure; seeing it moving unhindered, Fang Yuan felt that a grim reaper's scythe was hanging over his neck.

"Damn it!" Fang Yuan gritted his teeth.

This desolate beast before him was the King of the Swamp. Its body was covered in hard shell, it had lurked deep within the swamp for many years, even its eyes had vanished due to de-evolution, it had no weaknesses left.

Fang Yuan manipulated the fox groups to hold it back, but it was no use.

He could only watch helplessly as the swamp crab got closer!

"Can you teleport it away?" Fang Yuan turned his head, asking the little Hu Immortal land spirit.

Different Gu Immortals gave birth to different blessed lands, and the land spirit's abilities also varied. Some land spirits could teleport others, like Ba Gui from three kings blessed land, while some could not. Some land spirits could summon rain and wind, and some could manipulate the flow of time freely.

"Let me try." Little Hu Immortal breathed roughly as she felt an intense mental pressure. She activated the immortal essence, and used all her strength until her cute tiny face turned red.

"Ahhh ahhh!' She shouted in a childish way.

With a swoosh, the giant swamp crab vanished on the spot and was teleported about nine thousand steps away.

"We succeeded!" Little Hu Immortal's face was red as she gasped.

Fang Yuan relaxed slightly.

"Ma... master, I just expended one bead of green grape immortal essence." Little Hu Immortal reported painfully.

"No matter." Fang Yuan's expression was cold as he continued to order the foxes to attack the swamp crab.

After five minutes, the swamp crab got close again. Land spirit teleported it away once again.

And thus, another green grape immortal essence was expended.

Little Hu Immortal felt immense pity at this waste, and Fang Yuan's heart was bleeding.

In the entire Hu Immortal blessed land, there were only seventy-eight beads of green grape immortal essence. Fang Yuan used one to feed fixed immortal travel Gu. Now he used another two to teleport this swamp crab.

He still had to use the immortal essence to refine Gu and manage the entire blessed land in the future.

There were many areas in which immortal essence were needed, but because Hu Immortal died already, these green grape immortal essence could not be replenished, every single bead used was one less left for the future.

Some crabs got through unguarded areas and charged up the mountain.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly at this and ordered the land spirit to unleash the might of Dan Hun mountain.

At once, the area the crab army walked on became a death domain. Numerous crabs died, lying on the ground with their bodies intact. Their souls, however, were completely destroyed, creating a peculiar scene.

"Unfortunately, Dang Hun mountain's power is to continuously pressure the soul, but the desolate beast's soul is strong and can last for a while. I cannot let it reach Dang Hun mountain and destroy this precious forbidden ground."

Fang Yuan did not participate in battle.

Even if he used his strength path Gu worms, he would not be able to break its shell.

Most importantly, the swamp crab had not used an Immortal Gu yet, Fang Yuan was uncertain if it had one or not.

The unknown was the greatest threat, Fang Yuan did not dare to strike rashly.

Soon, the swamp crab came again. Just as it was teleported away for the third time, little Hu Immortal's expression changed.

Not waiting for Fang Yuan's reaction, she stretched her hand to grab his arm, and they both vanished on the spot.

The next moment, a fierce lightning bolt landed on the area they were standing.

Boom!

With a thunderous sound, mountain rocks shattered.

The lightning paused for a moment before shooting back up.

It turned into a human-shaped lightning and emitted a loud growl.

This was the blue charm lightning shadow!

Chapter 417: Enduring the Earth Calamity (2/2)

Blue charm lightning shadow held its head and screamed in pain. The blue lightning flashed around without any target and only settled down after a long while.

Clearly, the lightning figure had suffered injuries in its soul when it entered Dang Hun mountain.

Inside Dang Hun Palace, Fang Yuan's face became ashen as he looked at the scene in the smoke.

If it was not for the land spirit's prompt teleportation just before, he might have been dead already.

Little Hu Immortal patted her chest, her face pale and showing lingering fear.

When it rains, it pours. The blue charm lightning shadow joining the battle no doubt made things worse!

Blue charm lightning shadow flew into a rage after its sneak attack did not succeed and started to collide continuously into Dang Hun mountain.

Every time it collided with Dang Hun mountain, there would be tremors in Dang Hun Palace. Soil and stones flew from the impact and large scorched pits were created from the attacks on the mountain; Fang Yuan felt his heart bleed at this scene.

This was Dang Hun mountain!

In this entire world, there was only one of it!

Fortunately, blue charm lightning shadow stopped its attacks after dozens of collisions. Its soul had received considerable damage and the lightning around it was becoming very disorderly. It did not dare to attack again.

During this time, the land spirit had teleported the swamp crab another two times. In total, they had wasted five beads of green grape immortal essence on it!

And the originally endless fox army was already at the brink of extinction.

What made Little Hu Immortal even more discouraged was that this desolate beast only had small wounds and was still moving forward stably like before. It was like an indestructible bone!

Whether it was blue charm lightning shadow or swamp crab, they both had one target; destroying the central area, expending the immortal essence and killing the land spirit. Their final target was to destroy the whole blessed land.

They were on the same faction and did not have any conflicts, instead they cooperated.

While Fang Yuan and the land spirit were having a headache due to this swamp crab, the blue charm lightning shadow gave up on Dang Hun mountain and changed its target to the blessed land itself.

It did not dare to collide against Dang Hun mountain anymore, so it began attacking the sky and the earth of this blessed land.

It destroyed everything it saw and created craters everywhere. Sky crumbled and showed scars like that of a broken mirror.

Fang Yuan felt deep helplessness.

"Not good! Master, there is a hole in the blessed land!" Little Hu Immortal spoke hurriedly.

Blue charm lightning shadow's attacks shattered the world and created a hole.

"Cut away the surrounding area around the hole." Fang Yuan spoke indifferently, his tone cold as ice.

"What?" Little Hu Immortal opened her eyes wide and gave a cry of surprise.

If they cut off the area like this, they would not be able to restore it.

The holes in blessed lands could be repaired with immortal essence. If the holes were not patched in time and were allowed to enlarge, they would form a passage to the outside world.

Once there was a passage, those Gu Immortals outside the blessed land would absolutely charge in and make all kinds of schemes; at that time, the situation would be even more out of hand.

There were demonic path Gu Immortals on Tian Ti mountain.

Righteous path Gu Immortals did not dare to attack because they had a lot of businesses and assets. However, demonic path has no lack of demented people, they were lone forces and liked to take risks. In any case, Fang Yuan had done this a lot in his previous life.

Under Fang Yuan's order, Little Hu Immortal repeatedly cut off nearby half a square kilometer of the blessed land.

Blue charm lightning shadow continually destroyed the world and created holes, while the land spirit continually cut them off.

The swamp crab charged towards Dang Hun mountain again and again; the land spirit had no choice but to teleport it time after time, the amount of green grape primeval essence consumed already reached thirteen beads.

"Sob sob, the blessed land has become smaller and so much immortal essence has been lost...." Tears started falling out of Little Hu Immortal's eyes as she sobbed.

"Don't cry!" Fang Yuan coldly shouted, his expression ashen.

"There is no point in delaying. Our only hope is to kill these two calamities! But I don't have an attack type Immortal Gu, and it would be difficult to see any results from attacking the swamp crab with rank five Gu in a short time. My only option now is to gamble!" Fang Yuan gritted his teeth and revealed a crazed determination.

Desolate beasts were very strong, just by relying on their majestic physique and their fierce recovery ability, they could ignore most rank five Gu.

Especially this swamp crab; it had a strong defense and was upper-tier even among the desolate beasts. Fang Yuan had a lot of rank five Gu; turn gold Gu, soft bones Gu, pitch black Gu and so on, but using them against swamp crab would be like throwing pebbles in the lake; they could only create slight ripples. They needed to attack continuously for a slight bit of results.

However, Fang Yuan was unable to activate these Gu and participate in the offense.

If he left the mountain, he could meet with blue charm lightning shadow's attacks. He could give the Gu worms to the land spirit to use, but he did not dare to take the risk.

Land spirits could also die, and if it was destroyed by blue charm lightning shadow, then Fang Yuan would have no means to even activate fixed immortal travel Gu.

Only Immortal Gu could change the situation.

Fang Yuan might have two Immortal Gu, but both did not have offensive abilities.

"Don't teleport it anymore, let this damned swamp crab attack Dang Hun mountain!" Fang Yuan said resolutely and commanded the land spirit, "Release the whole might of Dang Hun mountain!"

Ringgggggggg!

Dang Hun mountain had been restricted by Little Hu Immortal the whole time, and right now, as it was finally let loose, dense fog started rising over the whole mountain. An enormous and formless soul shaking power burst out of the mountain, spreading as far as three thousand steps and eradicating everything in its surroundings.

Only Dang Hun Palace - under the land spirit's control - was intact.

The giant swamp crab soon got close to Dang Hun mountain.

Under the power of Dang Hun mountain, its sturdy shell was unable to provide any defensive support. Its soul received fierce attacks, causing its movements to slow down.

However, this made it go berserk and it increased its speed by another fold, charging towards Dang Hun mountain.

Bam!

The enormous pincers heavily smashed on Dang Hun mountain like steel clamps.

The sturdy boulders were as fragile as flour as they were smashed by the attack, holes forming from the impact.

The huge crater was at least 0.6 acres wide. Smoke and dust flew all around and the entire Dang Hun Palace also shook from the tremors.

The land spirit Little Hu Immortal's face paled from shock. Dang Hun Palace kept on shaking, dust started falling from the roof and there were fierce cracks on the walls and pillars.

Suddenly, Little Hu Immortal let out a tragic shout: "Not good! That blue charm lightning shadow has already moved towards the north and is openly destroying the sky and earth, creating many holes."

The image in front of Fang Yuan changed and showed the scene of blue charm lightning shadow attacking the world and creating holes.

The blessed land's eastern and northern parts had been corroded by the remnant force of the earth calamities, and were weaker than other areas. The blue charm lightning shadow saw these weak points and started attacking them.

"Fortunately, we had settled the water and fire, otherwise the result of blue charm lightning shadow's destruction would be ten times more severe! Master, what should we do?" Little Hu Immortal was feeling at a loss.

The situation had turned to an extremely terrible state.

The swamp crab was like a steel hammer directly pounding the heart and continuously depleting immortal essence while also wrecking Dang Hun mountain.

And blue charm lightning shadow was like an extremely sinister poison. It purposely searched for the weak points of the blessed land and stabbed at them. Every hole it created was like a fresh wound to the blessed land.

Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with an ominous glint.

The situation was turning more critical, but it instead aroused his fighting spirit!

"Land spirit, every time you teleport the swamp crab, send it away by three thousand steps!"

"Yes!"

With the distance shortened, the immortal essence expenditure was also comparatively less. And Dang Hun mountain's soul shaking power worked within three thousand steps, creating injuries to the swamp crab's soul.

"Land spirit, cut off the whole northern area!" Fang Yuan gave another command.

"What?!" Little Hu Immortal was stupefied and almost did not dare to believe her ears.

Hu Immortal blessed land's northern area was over 600km2, and Fang Yuan wanted to give up the whole region?

Once they cut off the area, Hu Immortal blessed land would lose this territory forever!

This was definitely a huge sacrifice by Fang Yuan! Hu Immortal blessed land had altogether 4000km2 of land and he was cutting off one-sixth of it!

"Master, this... this..." Little Hu Immortal hesitated.

"Do as I say!" Fang Yuan's gaze was fixed on the image in front of him as he shouted in a stern voice.

Little Hu Immortal's pink lips puckered and her eyes were filled with tears. The tears fell down and she started crying loudly.

Land spirits were the representatives of the blessed land; cutting off a part of the blessed land was the same as cutting their own flesh. And abandoning the whole northern area was like a person cutting off one of their legs.

"Master, don't, don't do it!" Little Hu Immortal cried loudly and begged.

However, Fang Yuan's expression was ruthless and did not make the slightest compromise.

Master's orders could not be violated, Little Hu Immortal could only endure the pain and cut off the whole northern area!

That blue charm lightning shadow was currently in the center of the northern area, destroying the world and creating holes. It suddenly felt something wrong and immediately moved, trying to charge out of the northern area.

However, because of 5km of distance, it could not escape and was trapped in the northern area.

It let out a mournful and sharp screech, its tone full of indignance. However, that bit of distance determined its fate, the blue charm lightning shadow could only follow the evaporation of the northern area and land in the outside world.

"Success!" Fang Yuan almost shouted in joy at this scene.

If it were normal times where the blue charm lightning shadow had no injuries in its soul, it could absolutely react in time. If not for its crazed attacks towards the world, expending its energy and causing its speed to fall, it could absolutely escape.

At the critical moment, Fang Yuan endured the pain and made a minor sacrifice to protect his bigger interests, finally settling this calamity!

As to what calamities it would create at the outside world, that was not part of Fang Yuan's consideration.

Bam Bam Bam...

The whole Dang Hun mountain was still shaking, the desolate beast swamp crab's soul was very strong and forcefully withstood the pressure, continuously attacking Dang Hun mountain.

The nearer it got to Dang Hun mountain, the stronger the soul shaking power became.

Little Hu Immortal teleported the swamp crab away time and again.

Right now, it was a battle of foundation between the two sides.

If the desolate beast's soul foundation was strong and it overthrew Dang Hun mountain, it would be Fang Yuan's defeat. Conversely, if Dang Hun mountain did not fall, it would be the earthly calamity's defeat.

Bam Bam...

Dang Hun palace's pillars crumbled and the beams of the roofs snapped. Dust and dirt flew everywhere, accompanied by Little Hu Immortal's whimpering cries.

Fang Yuan was silently standing with a cold expression.

"Strength, I need more strength!" He clenched his fists and let out an indignant scream in his mind.

Why was it that despite growing so much, he was still so weak when facing heaven and earth, when facing fate?

"Then continue to grow, continue to become stronger, stronger, and even stronger!"

As he screamed silently, the swamp crab's movements were gradually slowing down and eventually it collapsed at the waist of Dang Hun mountain... dead.

After an arduous process, the sixth earthly calamity was finally over.

Chapter 418: Losses and Gains

Fang Yuan walked out of Dang Hun palace.

The pink crystal mountain had holes everywhere, broken rocks were scattered on the ground showing a pitiful sight. Fresh red blood, yellow murky mud, fox and crab corpses mixed together.

The desolate beast swamp crab's humongous body was pressing on Dang Hun mountain's mountain waist. It was like a small mountain, extremely eye catching.

The mild wind blew on Fang Yuan's black hair, as his eerie black eyes stared at the battlefield.

The pungent smell of blood entered Fang Yuan's nostrils.

Closely behind him, little Hu Immortal land spirit's eyes were red, as there were tears on her face. She reported while sniffing.

"Master, we suffered immense losses. We lost about 666km2 of land, and we only have sixty-eight beads of the immortal essence left. Our fox army of four million and seven hundred thousand has fallen to three hundred and ten thousand. As for Gu worms, we lost around seven hundred thousand of them."

Hu Immortal managed her blessed land for so many years, after this calamity, the entire blessed land lost about forty years of development.

But Fang Yuan did not think so.

His expression was tired, but his gaze could not hide the happiness in his heart.

He survived this earthly calamity. It was an obstacle, now that he survived it, Fang Yuan had time to recuperate.

He had ample time to deal with the seventh earthly calamity.

"Stop crying, the blessed land is safe, that means our hope is safe too. Dang Hun mountain did not collapse, thus we have the resources to start over. Although we lost some land, in the short run, we cannot make use of that land anyway, it will not hinder our development."

Fang Yuan patted the land spirit's head, consoling: "Look, not long later, Dang Hun mountain will be full of gutstones, and we will control another group of rockmen. Most importantly, that blue charm lightning shadow was exiled, now, we can develop without any worries. Hu Immortal blessed land will definitely flourish again!"

This battle was intense and tragic, there were countless foxes and crabs who died near Dang Hun mountain. At the same time, swamp crab's soul was smashed into bits by the mountain's vibrations, absorbed into Dang Hun mountain.

In the near future, not too long away, large numbers of gutstones will appear on Dang Hun mountain unceasingly.

"Master's words... makes sense." Little Hu Immortal stopped crying and thought about it clearly, it seems he made sense.

The earthly calamity was like a trial, Hu Immortal blessed land got through it, there was not only great losses, but also great gains.

"What a pity, there were many Gu worms living in this swamp crab, but now Dang Hun mountain killed them all." Little Hu Immortal pouted, staring at this swamp crab's corpse angrily.

"Rejoice, this desolate beast did not have an Immortal Gu, otherwise, we might not be standing here." Fang Yuan sighed deeply.

This was the luckiest part of this ordeal.

One crucial Immortal Gu with overwhelming ability can easily overturn the entire situation.

Even if this swamp crab had an Immortal Gu, and was killed by Fang Yuan, how Fang Yuan would catch this Immortal Gu was also a huge problem.

Maybe this wild Immortal Gu might replace the blue charm lightning shadow and become the next great threat to Hu Immortal blessed land.

Fang Yuan was satisfied enough to have survived this earthly calamity.

After all, he was only a rank four upper stage mortal Gu Master, yet he managed to kill a desolate beast that was a problem even for Gu Immortals.

"Land spirit, clean up the battlefield. Preserve the corpse of the swamp crab well, I am going to rest." Fang Yuan looked around once more before relaxing, immediately feeling strong fatigue.

He commanded over a million foxes, his soul and mind was overused, he needed sleep immediately.

"Okay." Little Hu Immortal answered quickly as she looked at the swamp crab's shell with glowing eyes.

Every desolate beast was a moving treasure.

The blood, fur, bones, intestines in its body were great Gu refinement material.

"You accursed crab, I will tear you apart!" Little Hu Immortal raised her chin as her mouth opened, showing her small canine teeth, angrily walking towards the swamp crab while muttering to herself.

　　...

Fang Yuan had an extremely enjoyable sleep.

Three days later, he woke up, and laid on the bed, not wanting to move at all.

This time, he really relaxed his body and mind.

The sixth earthly calamity was over, Fang Yuan earned a lot of time for himself, he could finally catch a breath.

Ever since his rebirth, he had been plotting and resisting, especially on San Cha mountain, he overexerted himself thinking of the ways to get out of his predicament.

Now, he finally protected the blessed land. To Fang Yuan, this was a safe and stable place.

If Hu Immortal blessed land was destroyed, he would be in big trouble.

He exposed many things, let's take for example, the fixed immortal travel Gu.

Fang Yuan was not a Gu Immortal, he could not keep this Immortal Gu into his aperture, once its aura was leaked, Gu Immortals would easily sense it and come to snatch it from him.

Now, fixed immortal travel Gu was placed inside Hu Immortal blessed land, and because there was immortal essence, he could feed it without worry.

Other than that, there was also the refinement of second aperture Gu.

Without little Hu Immortal to control the immortal essence, Fang Yuan could not refine this Immortal Gu, he had to at least reach Gu Immortal realm first. By then, divine travel Gu might've been refined by another person already, it would be too late.

Having protecting Hu Immortal blessed land, it was a great help to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan lied down for a while before getting up to eat. After filling up his stomach, he went to sleep again.

This time, he slept for ten hours, he woke up slowly as he felt all the fatigue had been washed away. His mind was clear, his head was working well, and his condition was as good as it could be.

"Where is the land spirit?" He stomped his feet, calling.

Little Hu Immortal tore through space with a swoosh, appearing before him.

"Master, I have dismantled that crab, we can sell it for a good price!" Little Hu Immortal's face was red as she was extremely satisfied at breaking apart the culprit for the blessed land's predicament.

"Oh right, master, there are three letters here, they were sent in from the loophole on the day of the calamity." Little Hu Immortal said, taking out three Gu and handed them to Fang Yuan.

When loopholes enlarge enough to become tunnels, people could enter and exit. But before that, only Gu worms could enter through the small gaps.

These three Gu were all letter path Gu worms.

One had a paper crane appearance, it was the rank three lightning symbol paper crane Gu. One was a green bird, rank five and looking lifelike, it was the letter sending green bird Gu. One looked like a sword, it was the rank three flying sword letter Gu.

Fang Yuan's gaze shone as he took out the letter sending green bird Gu.

The green bird transformed into a letter, it was sent by the rank seven Gu Immortal Feng Jiu Ge!

Fang Yuan was not surprised, the moment he saw this green bird Gu, he had a feeling it was him.

Feng Jiu Ge's tone in his letter was calm, he first expressed his admiration and praise for Fang Yuan, before stating his intention — to arrange for a battle with between Fang Yuan and his daughter Feng Jin Huang!

It seems that after Feng Jin Huang returned to Spirit Affinity House, she had been gloomy, moody, and dispirited. During this period, she had been cultivating diligently, to reclaim her pride. The battle was initiated by her, she wants to have a fair and square fight with Fang Yuan, betting the glory of Spirit Affinity House and Immortal Crane Sect!

"Hmph, you want to battle, do I have to agree?" Fang Yuan scoffed in disdain.

His time was so tight, there was not enough time to cultivate, Fang Yuan would not waste his time and effort accepting Feng Jin Huang's challenge.

Feng Jin Huang was born in a great family, she had Gu Immortals as her parents, and a sect to support her. Even if she had a blessed land, and the calamity came, there would be a huge group of people fighting it for her.

But Fang Yuan was all alone, he had to rely on himself for everything. He had no mood to play around with this rich missy.

"What a stupid idea, she wants to reclaim her glory, so I must play along with her? Laughable!" Fang Yuan snorted. Different from others, he did not fear Feng Jiu Ge. That is because soon, Feng Jiu Ge would be called up by the heavenly court, and would successfully ascend, it will not be easy for him to come down and enter central continent again.

"But in this letter, it seems that this pair of father and daughter think that I am a disciple of Immortal Crane Sect, what is going on?" Fang Yuan's eyes shone with suspicion.

The other party was a Gu Immortal, they would naturally not make such a lowly mistake. That means, there were hidden complications.

Fang Yuan retrieved the flying sword letter Gu.

Opening it and taking a look, it was another challenge letter!

But in this letter, it was all swearing and scolding, almost all of Fang Yuan's ancestors were mentioned, even Immortal Crane Sect's honor was used to incite Fang Yuan to accept the battle. Finally, there was even a threat, if Fang Yuan did not agree, he would reveal the contents of this letter to the public, and let the world know that Fang Yuan was a coward!

Fang Yuan looked carefully, lightly smiling: "Oh, it is this rascal Jian Yi Sheng."

Jian Yi Sheng, a metal path Gu Master, his appearance and personality were very perverted. He was most skilled at sneak attacks, and hated suffering losses the most.

He was one of the demonic path Gu Immortals on Tian Ti mountain, he was truly a mean and devious coward.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, he got ambushed by him many times. He eventually made Fang Yuan angry enough to summon the blood sea, forcing this Jian Yi Sheng to hide in his blessed land, afraid to battle. He blocked him for twenty years, until Jian Yi Sheng realized that he had angered the wrong person. He could not take it, and eventually kneeled down before Fang Yuan to surrender, without a trace of a Gu Immortal's dignity.

As for why this person was challenging Fang Yuan, it was because he was extremely unlucky.

After Fang Yuan discarded a portion of the blessed land, and threw the blue charm lightning shadow towards Tian Ti mountain, Jian Yi Sheng coincidentally met with it.

At this time, although Jian Yi Sheng was a Gu Immortal, he had no Immortal Gu, and was thrashed by the blue charm lightning shadow. He escaped back to his blessed land pathetically, and finally managed to get free of the blue charm lightning shadow.

After he got home, he counted his losses, and was filled with rage, stomping his feet. After finding the culprit, he sent a flying sword letter Gu, challenging Fang Yuan.

"Hmph, he knows I am a mortal, but still challenged me as a Gu Immortal. He even wrote his letter so righteously, talking about fairness... this piece of shit is still as shameless as I remember. But, why did he think I am a member of Immortal Crane Sect?"

Fang Yuan opened the lightning symbol paper crane Gu with great suspicion.

He opened it slightly, and his pupils shrunk, showing a surprised expression: "What! Fang Zheng is alive?"

Reading on, his suspicions were cleared.

"So that's it, this He Feng Yang from Immortal Crane Sect is a smart person, using this method to eliminate his competitors."

"But he greatly underestimated me. Why would I join Immortal Crane Sect? But what the letter mentioned is exactly what I need now."

Thinking so, Fang Yuan made up his mind.

He called the land spirit: "Go, open the blessed land slightly, and let the Gu Master who resembles me in."

Chapter 419: Fang Zheng’s pain

Tian Ti mountain stood high above the clouds, reaching 3000km in total.

It was situated at the center of Central Continent, it was the land of inheritances, the mountain of saints. During ancient times, it was the ladder of immortals, able to ascend to the heavenly court.

Immortal Crane Sect's elite disciples were now standing at the foot of Tian Ti mountain, having waited for an hour already.

"How much longer do we need to wait?"

"This Fang Yuan is putting up too much airs right?"

"Ssh, quiet. He is the brother of Gu Yue Fang Zheng, the owner of Hu Immortal blessed land!"

"Speaking of that, this brother of Fang Zheng's is really amazing, he managed to defeat Feng Jin Huang, Xiao Qi Xing, Ying Sheng Ji and the others."

"So what? If I had a supreme elder supporting me in the dark, helping me to use fixed immortal travel Gu, I would be able to win the blessed land as well."

"Our clan's elders are truly smart. Using Fang Zheng to attract their attention, while the real trump card was Fang Yuan all along!"

　　...

In order to make this a reality, Immortal Crane Sect lied to all their disciples. Immortal Crane Sect' disciples now knew, that there was someone named Gu Yue Fang Yuan in their sect.

During these three months, he had become the hottest topic that everyone was discussing. He was mysterious and low-key, it made people curious. Shocking the world in one move, he obtained Hu Immortal blessed land for Immortal Crane Sect, and even allowed Immortal Crane Sect to stand out among the ten sects, it made the other disciples feel proud.

All their discussions entered Fang Zheng's ears.

Fang Zheng was stand at the front of these people, his gaze was dim as he looked at Tian Ti mountain.

These days, he had been a walking corpse, he did not know how he survived the last few days.

After Fang Zheng left QIng Mao mountain, he swore to exact revenge, to get justice for his deceased clansmen.

He carried a great hatred with him, the objective of revenge was sustaining and motivating him to cultivate. He was more hardworking than all the other disciples, he did not even slack for a second.

He had fantasized many times, the scene when he finds Fang Yuan — defeating him and making him kneel on the ground, repenting for all that he did on Qing Mao mountain. The clansmen in the afterlife would finally rest in peace after that.

Thus, on Dang Hun mountain, he did not give up despite numerous occasions of wanting to do so.

Every time he thought of Fang Yuan, there would be a strong driving force in his heart, supporting him to continue climbing.

He wanted to get Hu Immortal Inheritance, not only because he did not want to let his master down, or disappointing the clan's expectations, it was also because his chances of getting revenge would be much greater if he had the blessed land.

But, he did not expect, that life would come hitting him this hard and suddenly.

Gu Yue Fang Yuan, his blood related brother, the main character of his numerous nightmares, appeared on the mountain top! Under everyone's view, he obtained the inheritance, even Gu Immortals could do nothing to him!

Fang Zheng who failed returned to the sect.

Shock!

Pain!

Loss!

Fear!

He knew the clan's lies, he knew the truth, but precisely so, the shadow in his heart grew by many times.

This trauma had been nurturing in him since he was young.

Why is brother so smart? But I am so stupid!

Why was it that I cultivated so hard, yet I still lost to Fang Yuan?

Why did this happen in southern border, and also in central continent?!

"Is it true that I Gu Yue Fang Zheng, am destined to live in his shadow my entire life, never to surpass him?!" Every time Fang Zheng thought of this, there would be an indignant feeling in his heart, urging him to cultivate more.

But this time, it was different.

It was different.

Thinking of the mission the clan just passed to him, Fang Zheng's body shuddered.

The blessed land was in Fang Yuan's control, in order to obtain Hu Immortal blessed land, the sect was recruiting Fang Yuan. As long as he handed over the blessed land, he would be Immortal Crane Sect's elder.

Central continent sect members were classified from low to high as outer disciple, inner disciple, elite disciple, legacy disciple.

Above disciples, there were sect elder, often at rank four cultivation, controlling the many aspects of the sect. Above sect elder was sect leader, he had to be at least rank five middle stage, and was the key person in charge.

And above the clan leader, there were supreme elders.

These supreme elders were all Gu Immortals, they were rarely seen during normal times, secluded in cultivation. Only when the sect faces a life and death situation, or when something important happens, they would appear and let the world know the true power of Immortal Crane Sect, as one of the top ten sects!

"Since I joined Immortal Crane Sect, I had cultivated so diligently these years, from outer disciple, I became an inner disciple, and from inner disciple, I became an elite disciple. During the sect examination, I emerged as the top disciple of among the elite disciples. But now, Fang Yuan just has to say a word, and he would become a sect elder. Any disciple who sees him have to bow and pay respects!"

Fang Zheng felt a great pain in his heart every time he thought about this.

If Fang Yuan really became an elder, he would have to bow and pay respects to this enemy every time he saw him! Was there fun in such a life? Was there meaning in living?

"Master, has all the effort and hardwork I put in been in vain?" At this point, Fang Zheng was standing at Tian Ti mountain foot, waiting to meet Fang Yuan. He had unavoidably fallen into deep self-doubt.

Lord Sky Crane quickly consoled him: "Fang Zheng, you have to adjust your mindset. Immortal Crane Sect sacrificed a lot for Hu Immortal Inheritance, we even used an Immortal Gu! For the sect, we have to look at this from the big picture, and put down our personal grudges temporarily. Fang Zheng, you have to understand, it was Immortal Crane Sect who nurtured you, now that the sect needs you make some sacrifices, you cannot forget your roots!"

Although he said that, Lord Sky Crane was sighing in his heart.

He understood Fang Zheng's personality, thus his heart was even more worried.

All along, the notion of revenge was driving Fang Zheng forward like a pillar, it was also his obsession in this cultivation journey.

But now, the sect's orders were for Fang Zheng to let down this obsession, this was more fatal than any injury. Most likely, after suffering such an impact, Fang Zheng would no longer have any drive left, he would let himself dwell in self-pity.

"But what can we do? That is a blessed land, and it even contains a forbidden ground like Dang Hun mountain! The gustones on the mountain can be used by our disciples and make our entire sect's strength surge. Other than that, Fang Yuan has blood skull Gu and fixed immortal travel Gu on him! These things are way too valuable, they are so important, how can an elite disciple compare to them at all?"

Lord Sky Crane felt sad in his heart, but he still said to Fang Zheng: "My good disciple, you have to control your desire for revenge. A little impatience spoils great plans, treat this as a trial of your endurance! After seeing your brother, do not attack. Within the blessed land, you are not his match."

Saying so, Lord Sky Crane recalled what He Feng Yang instructed him —

"I know the enmity between Fang Yuan and Fang Zheng. If needed, we can sacrifice Fang Zheng, you can negotiate in place of Fang Zheng!"

He Feng Yang's pressure was great at the moment, all the supreme elders were looking at his actions.

"Master, you are telling me to treat this as a trial? I... I will try." Fang Zheng loosened his clenched fist, then clenched it again, he was struggling in his heart, he felt pain and anger.

If someone swore to get revenge, and cultivated to succession, only to find that his enemy had died. That is pain.

If someone swore to get revenge, and cultivated to succession, but found that he could not beat his enemy, and that his enemy was still living well. That is much greater pain.

If someone swore to get revenge, and cultivated to succession,but found out that not only was he unable to beat his enemy, he even had to use a fake friendly attitude to negotiate with him, hoping the enemy would become his superior. This was the greatest pain of all pain.

"Hehe, Fang Zheng, don't think much of it. Fang Yuan might not be having a good time, there is a calamity in the blessed land. You cannot imagine the might of a calamity. Even if your brother had an Immortal Gu, he is still a mortal. Soon, he will experience the terrifying powers of an earthly calamity. By then, the blessed land will be full of loopholes, and he would have suffered a huge loss. You have a high chance of succeeding in this trip." Lord Sky Crane consoled him again.

Fang Zheng heard this and his mood became slightly more relaxed.

"The earthly calamity is beginning." He Feng Yang muttered, he had been staying behind the scenes, firstly, it was to protect these elite disciples, secondly, it was to prevent the ill-intentions of other Gu Masters, and thirdly, if Fang Yuan could not block this earthly calamity, he would have to help out.

At this moment, he was starting at the spot where Hu Immortal blessed land was hiding in on Tian Ti mountain, sensing that there was an aura of destruction.

Soon, his lips curled into a smile as there was a peculiar sight on Tian Ti mountain.

Pieces after pieces of grassland appeared on Tian Ti mountain. They were like clouds or fog, illusory and not real.

How could there be a grassland on a mountain?

This was the loophole of the blessed land, and a large loophole at that, allowing outsiders to see the scene inside the blessed land.

Such a loophole could only fit Gu worms, there was still some way to go before Gu Masters can go in.

Lord Sky Crane at the other side had already called out: "The loophole appeared, send the lightning symbol paper crane Gu in."

Fang Zheng gritted his teeth, under everyone's supervision, he injected primeval essence and activated the Gu worm.

Lightning symbol paper crane Gu was fast as lightning, flying into the loophole.

But right after, the grassland image turned into a lump of primeval essence, as it dissipated in the air. Lightning symbol paper crane Gu flew for two rounds before flying back to Fang Zheng's hands.

"This Fang Yuan is giving up a portion of the blessed land, completely removing it! It seems he is worried that Gu Masters might entire when the loophole turns into a tunnel." He Feng Yang was slightly shocked, but sneered soon after: "Go ahead, let's see how much land you can discard. Every piece of land you abandon is akin to giving up your own flesh."

But immediately after, He Feng Yang's expression changed.

"He's still continuing? He's already thrown a few square kilometers worth of land! He is really bold, no wonder he managed to snatch the inheritance."

But a few moments later, He Feng Yang's expression turned ugly.

"It seems that this earthly calamity is very dangerous this time. But how much land is he going to give up? He has already thrown tens of square kilometers of land away. This wastrel!"

Chapter 420: Meeting of Brothers

On Tian Ti mountain, loopholes appeared one after another with increasing frequency.

Not only were Immortal Crane Sect's elite disciples watching carefully, many Gu Immortals were also keeping watch behind the scenes.

During this period, Fang Zheng tried three times, finally managing to send the lightning symbol paper crane Gu into the blessed land.

A green bird spread its wings and flew into the loopholes as well, reaching the Hu Immortal blessed land.

"This is a letter sending green bird Gu! What is Feng Jiu Ge trying to do?" He Feng Yang saw this and his expression turned dark.

But at the next moment, his pupils shrunk to pin-size, his mouth opened wide as he shocked an extremely flabbergasted expression.

"My god! He's discarding such a big area of the blessed land?!"

He Feng yang was tongue tied, he was stunned like a statue.

Fang Yuan discarded 600km2 worth of land, Tian Ti mountain waist was full of the blessed land's projected image, grassland filled everyone's vision.

A Gu Immortal was the first to react, appearing with the flash of a sword.

"Hahaha, what a big piece of blessed land, it is mine, don't even think of snatching it from me!" Jian Yi Sheng shouted, wanting to pull this piece of land into his blessed land, expanding his territory.

But at this moment, a lightning flash appeared.

"F*ck!" Jian YI Sheng was caught unguarded, he shouted profanities as the blue charm lightning shadow sent him flying like a cannonball.

But Jian Yi Sheng was not to be trifled with, he immediately engaged in battle with blue charm lightning shadow.

They created a huge commotion, the earth rumbled as Immortal Crane Sect's elite disciples watched in shock.

The more shocking thing was, over a dozen people appeared next, taking a piece of this 600km2 land at lightning speed like a pack of hungry wolves.

"You goddamn bastards!"

"I lured the monster away, I made the most effort, but you guys didn't even leave me a piece of the land!"

"I f*ck all your ancestors!"

"I curse you all to have constipation, all your children will be born with a chicken's tail!"

Jian Yi Sheng shouted angrily, he had never suffered such a great loss in his life, getting thrashed by the blue charm lightning shadow so pathetically.

"And there is that little rascal Fang Yuan, he is really evil and daring, scheming against me like this! Fight me fairly if you have guts!" He sent out the flying sword letter Gu.

Flying sword letter Gu was extremely fast, it could tear through space, even without a loophole, it could enter the blessed land.

Immortal Crane Sect's gang was in a daze.

This, was this the mannerism of a Gu Immortal?

"This Jian Yi Sheng is a complete disgrace to us Gu Immortals..." He Feng Yang covered his face in shame.

At this time, a bright white-gold light appeared.

There was a red door in the light, 30 meters tall, it had a rainbow colored plaque.

Pink colored clouds gathered, as the rainbow light shone on Fang Zheng's body. In the blink of an eye, Fang Zheng vanished on the spot.

Sending blue charm lightning shadow or the desolate beast swamp crab out of the blessed land was beyond little Hu Immortal's abilities. But to transport one Fang Zheng, it was easy.

"He got in!" Seeing this, He Feng Yang's heart eased.

A flash of lightning bolt descended from the sky, it was the blue charm lightning shadow. But the white-gold light moved the red door away in time.

By a hair's breadth, the blue charm lightning shadow's intention of entering the blessed land was thwarted.

Fang Zheng felt his surroundings turn blur before he regained his sight, and the environment around him had changed completely.

He was standing on a grassland, grass was all around him. There were clouds above him, extremely thick and dark clouds. Not far away, there are several lakes with ripples on the surface.

"I reached Hu Immortal blessed land." Fang Zheng quickly reacted, all his Gu worms were sealed now, it was the same as during the competition.

A smoky lump of shadow appeared before him, expanding into the size of a mirror. Fang Yuan's figure appeared in the mirror, he was sitting with his back leaning on the chair. He was crossing his right leg over his left leg as his left hand was placed on his knee, while his right hand was holding his chin softly on top of the chair handle.

His black hair was casually hanging over his face as his eyes squinted, showing a lazy and casual demeanour, but also gave people a sense of danger, dark and mysterious.

"My cute little brother, to think I would see you again in Central Continent." Fang Yuan spoke.

His voice was so foreign, yet so familiar to Fang Zheng.

Fang Zheng's body shuddered, his eyes burst forth with intense rage as he growled: "Gu Yu Fang Yuan, you crazy and hopeless demon, you murdered your entire clan! I will kill you personally!"

Saying so, he rushed towards Fang Yuan.

But this 'Fang Yuan' was only a projection from the smoke, after Fang Zheng charged towards it, it dissipated, but quickly gathered back into a perfect image of Fang Yuan again.

Fang Zheng pointed at Fang Yuan, shouting: "Fang Yuan, you don't even have the courage to face me? You coward! Shameless traitor, you are an inhuman animal. So what if you died, to think that you murdered your entire clan just to preserve your life. Such an outrageous act, how could you do it? Are you still human?!"

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan laughed heartily, casually leaning on his chair: "My cute little brother, you are still stupid as ever. Regardless of whether I did anything, they were going to die. If that is so, why can't I live? If not for my counterattack, do you think you would be brought back to Central Continent? In fact, I saved your life. I am your benefactor."

"Dog shit! You are distorting the truth, you are unbelievably shameless!" Fang Zheng heard Fang Yuan's words, and was extremely angered by it.

Fang Yuan's laughter came to a stop, he sighed: "Fang Zheng, my brother, you are a huge disappointment. All these years, you have not improved one bit. No matter how high your cultivation is, you are just a pawn piece. Alright, let's talk business. I've seen Immortal Crane Sect's letter, don't bother mentioning those ridiculous promises like making me an elder. We can however, go through with the transaction and deals."

Fang Zheng's chest was moving up and down, his breathing was heavy as he stared at Fang Yuan's image with hatred.

This pair of twins, they looked almost identical, and had closest blood relation in them. Unfortunately, they were life-and-death enemies.

Fang Zheng took a few deep breaths, holding in his killing intent towards Fang Yuan, thinking of the clan's instructions: "Within Hu Immortal blessed land, our sect is not interested in the fox groups or Gu worms. But the gutstones on Dang Hun mountain have some value. We will send disciples here by batches, you will bring them to Dang Hun mountain..."

"Stop." Before Fang Zheng finished speaking, he was interrupted by Fang Yuan: "I do not believe your Immortal Crane Sect's sincerity."

"This is what I want, prepare it for me as soon as possible, and hand it over to me. I do not have primeval stones, but I have the swamp crab's corpse to trade instead. The details are in the letter, go back and consider it."

Once he finished speaking, a small lightning bolt flew and landed in Fang Zheng's hand.

It was that lightning symbol paper crane Gu.

This lightning symbol paper crane Gu had already been refined by Fang Yuan, and was now used by him. The contents included the Gu worms and materials Fang Yuan wanted, as well as details on the swamp crab's blood, meat, bones, and shell etc.

Fang Zheng raised his head, and wanted to speak, but he saw the scene before him change — he had been transported out already.

"Check around, are there any suspicious things?" After Fang Zheng left, Fang Yuan did not relax, but instead gave instructions to land spirit.

The blessed land could not restrict Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan did not meet with Fang Zheng personally because he was worried about him bringing an Immortal Gu.

Immortal Crane Sect had a lot of resources, they had quite a lot of Immortal Gu.

Although Fang Zheng's aperture was not able to carry Immortal Gu, as the aura would easily leak, all sorts of things could happen in the Gu world, there were definitely methods to conceal an Immortal Gu's aura. Fang Yuan had to guard against this.

The land spirit checked for a few times and there were no problems, at this point, Fang Yuan finally relaxed.

"After the earthly calamity, will the situation improve from here?" Fang Yuan squinted his eyes, considering his current predicament.

The current situation was way more advantageous for him than he expected.

In order to devour Hu Immortal blessed land alone, Immortal Crane Sect shield him. Such guts, it was expected of one of the ten great sects of central continent!

Benefits above everything, enemies and friends were all built on this basis.

Using common words, it was the foresight of a 'big picture'. Restricted by the sect system, and under the pressure of the 'big picture', so what if Fang Zheng hated him? He still had to come over and discuss the transactions.

"Once they realize that they could not capture me so easily, that being forceful would just destroy everything, Immortal Crane Sect would naturally come to negotiate with me, to make transactions. Even if outsiders find out, there would be no rumors of 'allying with the demonic path'. That is because, Immortal Crane Sect had already admitted that I am a part of their sect! It was a meticulous decision."

"But this is what I needed too. Even if this disciple identity is so fake, it is enough to drive away the other forces. Looking at Jian Yi Sheng and Feng Jiu Ge's letters, one can easily tell how precious this identity is." Fang Yuan thought about it, he did not mind this.

The truth is, he is still in the demonic path, he is still alone, doing things his way, no one could restrict him.

But at the same time, he could do transactions, and exchange for resources he needed.

"Originally, I wanted to go to Lang Ya blessed land and snatch connecting heaven Gu. But now that I can deal with Immortal Crane Sect, I do not need to do that. Although, with Hu Immortal blessed land being in my possession, Immortal Crane Sect would not let this go, they are making deals at this point because of wariness, and that they have no choice for now. I cannot be careless and give them a weakness to exploit."

Fang Yuan reminded himself. As for his brother Fang Zheng, that was secondary.

Killing him would only be for the blood skull Gu, to raise the aperture's aptitude by a little. The problem it would bring is making an enemy out of Immortal Crane Sect, and putting himself into grave danger.

Killing his own brother is a pure demonic act, if outsiders find out, it would be interpreted as Fang Yuan betraying Immortal Crane Sect. At that point, the ten sects and numerous demonic Gu Immortals would place their greedy gazes towards Hu Immortal blessed land.

There is no such thing as an absolute secret, once the matter is exposed, even if Immortal Crane Sect wanted to continue acting, they would not be able to.

Fang Yuan's current situation was, raising aptitude was less important than his other objectives.

Even if his aptitude was raised, he still needed resources to cultivate.

The most important point now was to stabilize the situation and make full use of the blessed land's resources to convert them into his own strength!

Chapter 421: Development of the Rockmen Tribe

He Feng Yang carefully read the detailed content of the lightning letter.

Fang Yuan only made three types of requests; primeval stones, Gu worms and materials.

"Requesting for five million primeval stones? No problem! Let alone five million, it is no issue even if he wanted ten million or fifty million." He Feng Yang grinned.

When one reached the Gu Immortal realm, their attention was on immortal essence. They could have any amount of primeval stones they wanted, it was simply not a thing of concern.

"Huh? Five spring egg Gu?" He Feng Yang was slightly dazed.

Spring egg Gu was a rank five Gu that had the appearance of a white goose egg; it was obtained from killing specific eggmen.

Placing spring egg Gu deep underground could form a spirit spring eye. That means, it could grow a spirit spring.

Every spring egg Gu represented a small scale spirit spring.

Every small scale spirit spring could produce at least a hundred million primeval stones from the moment they formed till they disappeared!

However, spring egg Gu's price was much higher than hundred million primeval stones. Gu Immortals would frequently buy it and plant it in their blessed land to form spirit springs and provide spiritual essence to all living beings.

Sufficient spirit springs meant the primeval energy in the blessed land would be thicker and be beneficial to the cultivation and nurturing of Gu worms.

Conversely, if there were no spirit springs, the primeval energy in the blessed land would be created by diluting the immortal essence.

From a certain aspect, spirit springs could cut down the use of immortal essence.

"To think this Fang Yuan, a mere mortal, also knows the importance of spring egg Gu. But this Gu, even Gu Immortals have a lot of demand for it, how could we give you five of them? Three is enough, the Hu Immortal blessed land you are managing will sooner or later become our Immortal Crane Sect's property."

He Feng Yang's gaze moved over the list.

Below, Fang Yuan had mentioned many Gu worms.

"What does he want so many low ranked Gu worms for?" He Feng Yang felt some doubts.

If Fang Yuan demanded those rare and powerful rank five Gu worms, it would be understandable. However, what he was requesting for were some rank two and rank three Gu worms. Although he mentioned some rank four Gu, it was just a few.

"Hmph, I understand. This kid has strong vigilance! He is afraid that if he directly asks for rank five Gu, we would tamper with it, and so he intends to refine the Gu himself. Gu refinement process involves many subtle details, if the Gu worms had been tampered with, it would definitely destroy the whole refinement process. Conversely, a successfully refined Gu would be completely clean and secure."

He Feng Yang felt somewhat irritated.

He originally had such an intention, but now he knew that this scheme could not be implemented and was already useless.

"This kid is not easy to deal with... but, how would he know so many Gu refinement recipes? His background is definitely not simple!" He Feng Yang felt some apprehension inwardly.

He thought for a while more and laughed.

"This Fang Yuan doesn't know what's good for him! Are Gu so easy to refine? Every Gu refinement needs huge resources. The higher the rank of the Gu to be refined, the higher the chances of failure and higher the losses. You kid, just how old are you? Gu refinement cannot succeed just with innate talent, even more importantly, you need experience and accumulation."

He Feng Yang did not know the exact details of Fang Yuan, and even more importantly he did not know that fixed immortal travel Gu was refined by Fang Yuan. If he knew, he would definitely not be able to laugh.

He Feng Yang continued to read.

"Huh? He has requested relic Gu too. A yellow gold relic Gu and three purple crystal relic Gu?" He Feng Yang's gaze paused as he understood Fang Yuan's scheme.

Fang Yuan had rank four upper stage cultivation, this was already noticed by the ten sects' Gu Immortals and was not a secret.

If Fang Yuan used a yellow gold relic Gu, he would be at rank four peak stage. After advancing to rank five initial stage, he could use the three purple crystal relic Gu one by one and directly jump to rank five peak stage.

Immortal Crane Sect was one of the ten great sects of Central Continent and had abundant resources, it naturally had these relic Gu. Every year, there would be disciples and elders who would contribute the relic Gu they obtained to the sect in exchange for contribution points. And the sect would place these green copper to purple crystal relic Gu as rewards for sect missions.

He Feng Yang could easily bring out these relic Gu, but letting Fang Yuan advance to rank five so fast did not sit well with Immortal Crane Sect's benefits!

"Hehehe, I will first hand over one purple crystal Gu to create envy in this kid. These relic Gu are the things he wants the most, we will use it to get a hold on him and make him exchange them with guts Gu!"

He Feng Yang continued to read the letter, after the Gu worms were names of some materials.

These materials were also common for the most part. Although there were some precious Gu refinement materials listed, they were few in number.

"It seems this kid's main plan is to refine Gu. Hmph, you want to refine? Go ahead. But why does he need star heron bile, toad stones, ascension wine, and these other extremely uncommon materials?"

There were very few recipes that included the use of these materials, some of these materials had value that could compare to parts of a desolate beast. Even He Feng Yang would have to expend some effort to get these things.

"Whether this kid is deliberately mystifying it to scatter my attention or is really refining some rare Gu, I cannot give all these materials to him at once. I need to make him feel anxious to probe out his true intent. Hmm, for this transaction, I will give him a vat of ascension wine."

This ascension wine was a top quality wine brewed by Immortal Crane Sect's supreme third elder. Over a hundred years ago, He Feng Yang had officially sided with the third elder. In the banquet, the supreme third elder was in a great mood and rewarded him with three vats of ascension wine.

Supreme third elder liked drinking wine and it was one of his hobbies. However, He Feng Yang did not like to drink and ascension wine was worthless to him.

He Feng Yang saw each part of the desolate beast listed at the end of the letter.

He licked his lips.

This was a desolate beast, an existence that could be compared to Gu Immortals!

"Such a complete desolate beast corpse, looks like the earthly calamity this time was the desolate beast calamity. This kid's luck is really good, using Dang Hun mountain to destroy the swamp crab's soul and obtain such a complete corpse."

He Feng Yang instantly guessed the details of the earthly calamity.

"We can completely procure this swamp crab, but why has he not requested rockmen? Could it be that he does not know of the rockmen because of limited knowledge? Or is it because the group that migrated at that time is still alive? There is too little information."

What was the situation in Hu Immortal blessed land, how did Fang Yuan obtained fixed immortal travel Gu, who was behind him; He Feng Yang did not know the answers to any of these questions.

The five great regions - central continent, southern border, northern plains, western desert and eastern sea - were mutually independent, separated by barriers and each of them were incomparably vast.

Immortal Crane Sect had yet to grasp the whole central continent, let alone make contact with every region of southern border.

However, after Fang Yuan seized Hu Immortal's inheritance, Immortal Crane Sect had already sent elders to southern border to investigate.

　　...

Several days later.

"We're here, plant the spirit spring at this location." On the grassland, Fang Yuan stopped walking and said to little Hu Immortal following behind him.

Little Hu Immortal nodded her little head and raised her palm upon which a spring egg Gu flew out.

Spring egg Gu landed on the ground and drilled deep underground. Within moments, Fang Yuan felt the ground shake and could hear the sound of flowing water becoming louder rapidly.

And then, a fountain of spring water spurted out of the ground and flew as high as twenty to thirty meters.

The spring water was milky white and produced water vapor. After a few breaths' time, Fang Yuan could feel the primeval energy in the air becoming very dense.

"Primeval energy is the origin energy of all living beings; with the increase in primeval energy, the land will become more fertile, vegetation will flourish and beast groups will prosper even more, there will be a lot of benefits to the rockmen as well." Fang Yuan nodded his head in satisfaction.

The transaction with Immortal Crane Sect was a success. Fang Yuan sold the whole swamp crab's corpse and in return obtained most of the things he needed.

Among them were three spring egg Gu.

This spring egg Gu was a rank five Gu and was a one time expendable Gu that could turn into a small scale spirit spring.

It had a high demand on primeval essence to be activated and even rank five upper stage Gu Masters would have to exhaust all their primeval essence to succeed in activating it.

Fang Yuan was only at rank four upper stage and was absolutely unable to activate spring egg Gu. But fortunately, he had the little Hu Immortal land spirit as his helper.

Fang Yuan buried these three spring egg Gu near the rockmen tribes.

After the trial of the sixth earthly calamity, there were only a few pitiful fox groups left in Hu Immortal blessed land and were not worth nurturing. Fang Yuan thus put all his attention on the rockmen tribes.

Now, there were only a few hundreds rockmen left, much lesser than the foxes. However, with Dang Hun mountain and these three spirit springs, the rockmen tribes could rapidly grow and develop.

"Hehehe, Master, this is awesome! With three spirit springs, our green grape immortal essence expenditure will greatly reduce." Little Hu Immortal looked at the spurting spring water and narrowed her eyes in happiness.

"These three spirit springs can produce at least three hundred million primeval stones and can last for fifty to sixty years. But if we look at the whole blessed land, it is far from enough. It is lacking even for the southern area of the blessed land." Fang Yuan calculated.

Spirit springs were classified into small scale, mid-scale and large scale.

Small scale spirit springs could last for fifty to sixty years; mid-scale spirit spring could last for about a hundred years and more; large scale spirit spring could last for centuries.

The spurting spring water loosened the surrounding soil and the spring mouth gradually enlarged. The force of the spring water was not enough and its height slowly reduced.

In four to five days, the spring mouth would form and the spirit spring would start flowing, spreading to the surrounding soil. In several months, the dense primeval energy would condense into the first batch of primeval stones.

"Let's return. The rockmen tribes should be having the time of their lives now." Fang Yuan commanded the land spirit.

The next moment, the two teleported to Dang Hun mountain.

"Heavens, so many gutstones!"

"The place is in a mess, there definitely was a huge battle here. Maybe that male immortal is already dead."

"Our rockmen tribes' glorious days are coming!!"

"We will have endless offsprings. Tribe leader Yan Yong, we can establish the world's largest rockmen tribe!"

The rockmen cheered and shouted, indulging in this moment of happiness and fortune.

Dang Hun mountain was filled with gutstones. There was one every five steps.

The rockmen struck the gutstones in a frenzy and strengthened their soul.

There were many young rockmen who also struck the gutstones and rapidly strengthened their newborn souls, allowing them to control more rocks as their body.

There were only a few hundreds rockmen at first, but in only a day, their population expanded by ten times!

The more the population grew, the faster they multiplied.

On the morning of the second day, their population broke ten thousand. On the evening of the third day, their numbers reached three hundred thousand.

All the gutstones on Dang Hun mountain were plucked clean.

On the fourth day, Dang Hun mountain started emitting pressure and the rockmen could only reluctantly leave the place, majestically returning to their homes.

There were unexpected gifts, the new three spirit springs, waiting for them there.

Chapter 422: Spectral Soul Demon Venerable

Blub blub blub blub...

In a huge five-man-tall cauldron, green-blue colored liquid was bubbling inside.

The liquid seemed to be boiling, but cold air was emitting from it, even a rockman's hand would turn into an icicle if he placed it in.

Fang Yuan stood before the large cauldron, multitasking as he controlled it while taking out a primeval elder Gu.

He multitasked, activating primeval elder Gu as primeval stones flew out from within.

Plop plop plop...

Primeval stones caused a splash when they entered the cauldron.

Primeval elder Gu was a rank three storage Gu, it could hold up to a million primeval stones. It was shaped like a crystal ball, half transparent with clouds forming into an old man inside. The old man smiled when there were a lot of primeval stones inside, and cried when there were few primeval stones.

As large amounts of primeval stones were thrown in, the old man's smile turned into a bitter expression.

Fang Yuan expended around half a million primeval stones for this refinement.

If it was the past, he would not be able to afford it. But now, he is affluent, after he sold the desolate beast swamp crab and bought quite a bit of things, he had around six million primeval stones left.

As primeval stones were thrown in, a large spiral formed inside the cauldron, causing the liquid to flow faster. The cauldron was slightly shaking.

At this crucial moment, Fang Yuan invested all his concentration into it, he could not be distracted anymore.

Sweat quickly formed on his forehead, he could only call out: "Land spirit."

"Yes!" Little Hu Immortal responded quickly, throwing pieces and pieces of silver ingots into the cauldron.

The ingots entered the liquid, causing the spiral to slow down.

One by one, the ingots fell in until the surface of the cauldron became still, forming into silver colored ice.

Eventually, all the liquid inside was frozen, large amounts of silver colored mist flew out, freezing the entire cauldron, in fact, it extended five steps from the cauldron, dying the ground silver.

Fang Yuan breathed heavily: "After refining Gu for three days, it's finally done. Up!"

Silver colored ice broke apart, and Gu worms flew out.

These Gu were all rank three, they were shaped like little cups, while also resembling trumpet flowers. Three of them could fit on one palm.

They were silver in color, used to hold liquid or store Gu worms.

Little Hu Immortal counted, smiling brightly, clapping her hands: "Hundred and thirty seven, hundred and forty-six, hundred and fifty-nine! Master, you are amazing, refining a hundred and fifty-nine rank three Gu worms at once. We can sell these for quite a sum, what are these Gu worms?"

"Hehe, these are silver cup Gu, we have to use them to refine Gu, they are not for sale." Fang Yuan smiled.

Three hundred and eighty years into Fang Yuan's previous life, these silver cup Gu were created by a Gu Immortal. Continuing to refine them until they were rank five, that was the Gu Fang Yuan needed.

Of course they could not be sold now.

"These days, I used a large number of guts Gu to raise my soul to fifty-two times of a normal person. Thus, I did not feel much fatigue, and was able to refine so many Gu at once." Fang Yuan was extremely pleased with the results of this refinement.

The benefits of having a strong foundation in his soul was shown here.

If He Feng Yang saw this, he would no longer underestimate Fang Yuan. Fang Yuan's ability at refining Gu had already greatly exceeded his own.

But his head was still dizzy.

Every Gu refinement caused a strain on the soul, it used a lot of mental energy, not to mention Fang Yuan's large-scale refinement.

If it was before, Fang Yuan could only sleep to rest his soul. But now, he had a better method.

"Land spirit, this cauldron is useless now, get rid of it, I am going outside to walk."

"Yes master." Little Hu Immortal immediately got to work.

Three to four days had already passed, large numbers of gutstones had formed on Dang Hun mountain.

Fang Yuan casually stepped on a few pieces, the guts Gu that flew out recovered his soul, even strengthening it.

Fang Yuan instantly felt the dizziness go away from his head, he could think at lightning speed.

He laughed heartily: "This guts Gu is truly a divine Gu, the effect is so amazing. In that case, I shall strengthen my soul to the limit today."

Sixty-eight times! Fang Yuan felt refreshed, his movements were extremely fast and light.

Seventy-seven times! Fang Yuan could think at lightning speed, every thought moved like a spark.

Eighty-five times! Fang Yuan's soul had already vaguely hit his body's limit.

Ninety-two times! Fang Yuan could clearly feel his own soul. In his perception, his soul was grey-white color, its outer appearance was just like Fang Yuan's appearance, except it was extremely strong, muscular and had a bear-tiger like body. As for Fang Yuan, although his body was muscular, he only had muscular shoulders with a thin waist. His soul was quite squeezed inside this body.

Was he at his limit?

Ninety-three times! Fang Yuan used one more guts Gu, his soul strengthened once again. This time, Fang Yuan felt an unprecedented feeling, it was amazing and comfortable. It felt a hundred times better than taking drugs, eating good food, or having intercourse! It made a strong man like Fang Yuan groan out in pleasure.

An indescribable sensation of comfort and addiction made him savour this feeling, unable to forget it.

Fang Yuan's eyes shone in a cold light, his heart became alert.

He stepped on a few more gutstone, and his soul got stronger again. The feeling of comfort this time was much more intense than before!

Ninety-seven times, ninety-eight times, ninety-nine times!

The feeling came from deep within his soul, it was so intense that Fang Yuan's body shuddered, his bones felt like they were melting and his muscles were twitching, it could not be described with words.

A hundred times!

The intense sensation and addiction assaulted like a tornado, Fang Yuan almost fainted from this.

"This is the limit, I cannot use the guts Gu anymore!" Fang Yuan bit the tip of his tongue, using the pain to keep himself conscious, not falling into addiction.

Normal people could only strengthen their soul by a hundred times, it was called hundred man soul!

This was also the extreme limit. If the soul strengthened just a bit more, it would explode in a loud bang. Like a stomach that burst from overeating.

But the explosion of the soul was many times more severe than the bursting of a stomach. The soul would complete disperse in the air, completely destroyed, the flesh would be preserved for a while before rotting away, revealing the white skeleton.

If Fang Yuan indulged in the feeling, and used one more guts Gu, he would not even have the time to use Spring Autumn Cicada, he would die immediately, wiped off from this world.

Too bad I don't have Luo Po valley, inside it, there is the bewilderment fog that can loosen the soul. There is also the Luo Po wind that can cut the soul. After torture and trials, the soul will become more refined and condensed." Fang Yuan sighed in his heart.

Simply strengthening the soul was a quantitative advantage. Only through refinement and purification can there be a qualitative advantage.

In this world, there were many Gu Masters who cultivated their soul, they were called soul path Gu Masters. Soul path and strength path were at the same level, glorious during the ancient times. Except, strength path was now at its lowest point, while soul path was staying strong, it was the largest path in the current world.

The Gu Master who created the soul path is renowned in the entire world's history.

He is Spectral Soul Demon Venerable!

Rank nine Gu Master, standing at the top of the universe, looking down at mortals plainly, he was truly invincible, a legend who dominated his era.

At the same time, he was the rank nine Gu Immortal with the greatest killing nature.

Among all Immortal Venerables and Demon Venerables, he killed the most people. During his dark era, he made the five regions into his personal slaughterhouse. All living beings were his livestock, they had no way to resist.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable once said: In this huge world, Dang Hun mountain is the best at strengthening soul, and Luo Po valley is the best at refining soul. One mountain and one valley, if one had both, they would achieve great success in the soul path, and they would be able to dominate the world.

Thus, Dang Hun mountain and Luo Po valley were the two sacred lands of soul path Gu Masters.

Fang Yuan obtaining Dang Hun mountain was a huge blessing, he got a great deal from his rebirth. If he wanted to get Luo Po Valley, there was little hope, he did not know where it was.

"But, even without Luo Po valley, I can use other soul path Gu worms to replace it. Divine soul Gu, dragon soul Gu, ice soul Gu, dream soul Gu, moon soul Gu, general soul Gu, grudge soul Gu, poem soul Gu and others, they can all refine my soul and allow me to continue strengthening my soul, to break through hundred man soul, to reach thousand man soul, or even ten thousand man soul."

He could not get these Gu from Immortal Crane Sect. That is because these Gu that were directly used on the soul, if Immortal Crane Sect did something to them, it would be too dangerous.

But Fang Yuan knew very little of these Gu worms' recipes. Most importantly, he has not decided on which Gu would suit him the most.

"For now, hundred man soul is sufficient to deal with my problems, I should place my energy on how to trade rockmen." Fang Yuan's train of thought came back to the matter at hand.

He had already sold swamp crab, but next, he did not intend to sell the gutstones.

If he sold gutstones, that would strengthen Immortal Crane Sect, that was not favorable.

For the following days, Fang Yuan continued to refine Gu while cleansing his aperture.

A month passed quickly, with the nine eyes liquor worm's help, Fang Yuan successfully advanced to rank four peak stage.

At the same time, he refined a hundred and fifty-five gold cup Gu.

Gold cup Gu and silver cup Gu were about the same, they were rank three Gu used to store fluids.

Next, he used both silver cup Gu and gold cup Gu in refinement, after seven days and six nights, his luck was not bad, he obtained three rank four gold and silver cup Gu.

He put down his work at hand, and turned his attention to the rockmen: "So many days have passed, the rockmen should've reproduced already."

In a rockman's life, most of the time was spent on sleeping.

Normally, when a rockman reaches three hundred years old, his soul would accumulate to a degree, and he would produce an offspring. Next, every two hundred years, he will produce one young rockman.

Without accidents, a rockman can live to a thousand years, and they would have four offsprings when they die.

But because of the gutstones, the rockmen tribes expanded rapidly, they had around three hundred thousand tribesmen now.

The increased numbers caused the internal conflicts among rockmen to increase, intensify, and erupt.

Rockmen's social system was very relaxed, it could at most govern a hundred thousand people. As expected, after some political strifes, the rockmen split into three groups, each with around a hundred thousand people, each occupying one spirit spring, making their new homes there.

Fang Yuan took out the new slavery Gu that he made and handed them to the little Hu Immortal.

Slavery Gu, ranged from rank one to five. Fang Yuan refined rank three slavery Gu only, it was enough to enslave the rockmen tribes.

Little Hu Immortal teleported the slavery Gu for about ten thousand miles away, using them on the most crucial rockmen.

The rockmen's soul were not Fang Yuan's match, they were easily enslaved.

In the blink of an eye, Fang Yuan controlled three rockmen tribe leaders including Yan Yong, as well as over a dozen rockmen tribe elders.

At once, the three hundred thousand rockmen were under his control.

Governing many lives and making great changes with just a wave of his hand, this was already showing the ability of a Gu Immortal!

Chapter 423: Fang Yuan you little bastard!

"Not selling gutstones, but selling rockmen instead?" He Feng Yang looked at the letter in his hand with a grim expression.

In Hu Immortal blessed land, the guts Gu from Dang Hun mountain was the thing Immortal Crane Sect needed the most. Once they had the guts Gu to raise the foundation of their disciples' soul, Immortal Crane Sect's strength in terms of disciples would rise by thirty percent.

Furthermore, gutstones could not leave Dang Hun mountain, they could only be used on the spot. Thus, with this reason, Immortal Crane Sect disciples could freely enter Hu Immortal blessed land. As time passed, Fang Yuan's alertness would gradually fall, and Immortal Crane Sect would be free to set up some traps inside the blessed land.

But Fang Yuan adamantly refused to sell the gutstones, He Feng Yang was very troubled: "Since when did great Gu Immortals like myself have to be subjected to such difficulties from a mere mortal rascal?!"

He gritted his teeth as he thought, his handsome young face distorting with anger.

He had battle strength, but he could not display them. Fang Yuan was hiding inside the blessed land like a tortoise, he also had fixed immortal travel Gu and could leave at any time. He Feng Yang, and even the entire Immortal Crane Sect were afraid of his trump cards, and thus did not dare to attack.

"It seems the rockmen that Hu Immortal brought into her blessed land are still alive. But this Fang Yuan is selling so many of these rockmen now, just how many guts Gu did he use to create them!"

Thinking of this, He Feng Yang's heart was bleeding.

Several months had passed since the last transaction. The time in Hu Immortal blessed land was five times faster, thus he had around a year or so.

Fang Yuan nurtured so many young and strong rockmen, if these expended guts Gu were given to Immortal Crane Sect, and used to nurture disciples, how good would that be?

But this rascal Fang Yuan, he would rather nurture rockmen than give these guts Gu to Immortal Crane Sect. His motives are execrable, execrable!

What made He Feng Yang most furious was not just this. Most importantly, he was angry at himself — these rockmen that Fang Yuan was selling, even if he was a Gu Immortal, his heart was moved.

In a blessed land, if there were ample rockmen, Gu immortals could develop their underground land and excavate large amounts of resources.

All sorts of metals, gems, ore, as well as Gu worms, underground animals, they could be endlessly obtained.

Other than that, if they had enough rockmen, they can build an underground city, this was, in a way, expanding the blessed land's territory.

If there was no manpower in the blessed land, the resources Gu Immortals excavate would mostly be from the surface, it was limited. But if they had rockmen, and could even use the resources underground, the profits would be many times more than before.

Thus, in the market, rockmen were in high demand and low supply.

A rockman's life is mostly spent on sleeping. An ordinary rockman lives to a thousand years old, in one life, they have four children.

It was not impossible to use soul path Gu worms on them to raise their soul's strength, many Gu Immortals tried it, but none succeeded.

There was only one reason, cost.

The value of a soul path Gu worms greatly exceeded a single rockman.

Unless a Gu Immortal has a special need for rockmen, they would never profit from this.

In this world, only Fang Yuan who controlled Dang Hun mountain could nurture rockmen on such a scale.

Furthermore, the price Fang Yuan quoted in this transaction was also very appealing. Even if Immortal Crane Sect did not need it, they could resell it and earn at a huge profit.

But because this was such a good deal, He Feng Yang felt extremely troubled.

He knew this was bait from Fang Yuan.

Not afraid that you aren't moved, just afraid you won't take the bait!

Just as Fang Yuan had expected, He Feng Yang was already inclined towards the deal, not just him, Immortal Crane Sect would also be moved, and other Gu Immortals would also want this deal. The rockmen trading business could flourish for at least a hundred years.

"This wicked little rascal Fang Yuan, he is really devious. But with this batch of rockmen, I could show some results to supreme grand elder, second elder, and third elder, I can also make Lei Tan shut up. I can catch a breather in that case." He Feng Yang breathed heavily, calming his mind.

He squinted his eyes, his mouth curling into a cold smile: "But don't be too smug Fang Yuan. Tit for tat, if you don't sell guts Gu, I will not sell relic Gu. Didn't you want yellow gold relic Gu and purple crystal relic Gu? No way in hell!"

　　...

Fang Yuan laid on his chair, looking at Immortal Crane Sect's reply.

Because blue charm lightning shadow was still guarding Tian Ti mountain, little Hu Immortal did not dare to open the blessed land's doors, thus Immortal Crane Sect used the flying sword letter Gu this time.

Fang Yuan took a look and understood the content.

In He Feng Yang's letter, other than agreeing to the deal, he also stated his objective: to buy guts Gu. For the guts Gu, he could sell relic Gu, or even lend a hand to help survive the seventh earthly calamity.

Fang Yuan chuckled continuously.

Letting He Feng Yang into Hu Immortal blessed land was a greater danger than the calamity itself, that was impossible.

As for the relic Gu, did he think that threat would be Fang Yuan's weakness? What a laughable idea.

"I will definitely not sell the guts Gu, but I can sell rockmen, I have no worries about attracting Immortal Crane Sect. But I cannot just deal with Immortal Crane Sect alone, I also need to expand my business further." Fang Yuan considered.

With his five hundred years of experience, Fang Yuan knew that his sale price was lower than the market value.

Immortal Crane Sect would definitely profit from this trade.

But this was also arranged by Fang Yuan.

That is because at the moment, he needed his identity as an Immortal Crane Sect disciple, thus he also needed to maintain and sustain this fictitious relationship.

"With this profit, He Feng Yang's pressure would be lifted off him, he wants my blessed land, but I also need time to grow. After I become a Gu Immortal, would I still be afraid of Immortal Crane Sect?" Fang Yuan laughed plainly.

He looked at the letter again, at the end of it, He Feng Yang decided on a time, and requested Fang Yuan to open the door, to send in the hole earth Gu.

This was a very large scale transaction, Fang Yuan was going to sell sixty thousand rockmen. But these rockmen could not leave from the blessed land's doors.

At the moment, that blue charm lightning shadow was still moving around Tian Ti mountain. If the doors were opened, and it managed to rush in, Fang Yuan would be in huge trouble.

Thus in this situation, he needed to use hole earth Gu.

This Gu was rank five, and consisted of two Gu, the main Gu and the sub Gu.

Its biggest use was to connect the two places with one tunnel. The Gu Master will enter from the sub Gu, and come out from the main Gu, similarly for the opposite direction as well.

Hole earth Gu was often used to connect two blessed lands. Normally, hole earth Gu was used to transport and send resources. During war or battles, reinforcements could be sent in via the hole earth Gu, assisting immediately.

"To undergo the transaction and send these rockmen away, hole earth Gu has to be used inevitably. But I am worried that your hole earth Gu might have some traps in it, I'd rather refine it myself."

Fang Yuan thought about this and leaked the Spring Autumn Cicada's aura, refining the flying sword letter Gu and rapidly writing a letter back to He Feng Yang.

Half a day later, He Feng Yang received the letter, looking at it only to find large amounts of Gu worms listed in it, and all sorts of ingredients.

"Oh? You don't want to use my hole earth Gu, but you improved on the recipe and want to refine the new version yourself?" He Feng Yang was furious.

"Bullshit! Hole earth Gu has already been used for five hundred years, the recipe is known by all Gu Immortals, you think you can refine it further? Fang Yuan, this rascal's alertness is too high, he wants to use this chance to extort me, so that I would not dare to reject his deals again. I don't need to see to know that the relic Gu or spring egg Gu or some rare Gu worms in the strength path is included... eh? None?"

He Feng Yang gave it a glance, but did not see any relic Gu, spring egg Gu, or any strength path Gu listed.

But there were a lot of uncommon Gu, and even some low ranking Gu worms. The highest was rank five Gu worms, the earth path build a mountain Gu, normally used to increase the success rate of Gu refinement. Other than that, he requested a lot of rank four Gu, the commonly seen moving form Gu, and the very useful another perspective Gu.

He Feng Yang wavered: "Looking at this list, it seems he really is going to refine Gu. As long as his luck is okay, the materials are enough to refine three hole earth Gu. Don't tell me, he really improved the recipe of hole earth Gu? No, Fang Yuan is a mere mortal, how can this be? But what if he has a Gu Immortal behind him?"

If it was an improved recipe, then the new Gu would definitely be far stronger than hole earth Gu.

He Feng Yang's heart wavered.

Even if he could not get the recipe, after Fang Yuan succeeds the refinement, he would have to give the sub Gu to him. By then, he as a Gu immortal would be able to infer many details about the Gu from that sub Gu, and he has a high chance of recreating the same recipe.

Two days later, Fang Yuan received the letter.

Fang Yuan opened it and looked, just as he expected, He Feng Yang made all sorts of excuses inside the letter, intentionally reducing the amount of many materials and Gu worms, his motive was clear, he wanted to probe Fang Yuan's true recipe.

Fang Yuan laughed and shook his head while sighing, this He Feng Yang was too meticulous in this thoughts, this was both a strength and a weakness.

Although they had interacted for merely a few times, Fang Yuan had already seen through him.

Fang Yuan replied blandly that He Feng Yang was not to reduce any of the materials, otherwise the refinement would fail.

But He Feng Yang continued to argue and bargain, he said so much garbage that he almost believed his own excuses.

After a few times, Fang Yuan "helplessly" chose to give in, writing another list.

"Lad, you are too young to compete with me." He Feng Yang saw this letter than handed over a portion of the materials, while finding excuses to delay the others.

With the constant stalling, they wasted about eight to nine days.

Only until Fang Yuan showed an extremely helpless and angry attitude did He Feng Yang stop, realizing that the time was ripe, using the sixth list which had far less materials to do his research.

But his Gu refinement skills were not good, even after researching it thoroughly, and trying a few times, he did not get any results.

Half a month later, in central continent's time, he received the hole earth Gu from Fang Yuan.

He received it like a treasure, going into deep research again.

But this time, he spent three days before successfully reverse-engineering the recipe.

Looking at this recipe, He Feng Yang screamed: "Fang Yuan, you little bastard! This is the normal recipe for hole earth Gu!"

Immediately, he screamed and scolded Fang Yuan calling him shameless, unscrupulous, devious, vile, and his insults even extended to Fang Yuan's ancestors.

Chapter 424: We are going to slay an Immortal

The west area of the blessed land was a vast grassland.

It was a scene of green that extended all over the place. A newborn fox was having fun playing with a fluttering butterfly.

In Hu Immortal blessed land, foxes were the strongest predator and thus had worry-free lives.

Although they suffered an extreme grave loss during the sixth earthly calamity, they did not die out completely. On the vast grassland, the fox groups were slowly but surely growing.

Suddenly, the space rippled and two figures appeared scaring the little fox away.

One was a man wearing a black robe, he was tall and valiant with black hair and eyes as deep as abyss. The other was a cute and young girl who was wearing colorful clothes, her eyes shone like stars and she had a snowy-white soft fluffy tail, the thin and long fur on her tail slightly shook with the wind.

They were none other than Fang Yuan and little Hu Immortal land spirit.

"The position is good, it should be here." Fang Yuan looked around before taking out a hole earth Gu from his aperture.

This Gu looked like a walnut with a wooden and uneven surface, and was as large as a watermelon.

Hole earth Gu was a rank five Gu and required at least a rank five peak stage Gu Master to activate it with all his primeval essence.

Fang Yuan naturally could not do it, thus he gave the Gu to the land spirit.

After little Hu Immortal activated it, the hole earth Gu immediately burst out with intense scarlet rays of light before piercing into the ground.

In an instant, red light shot to the sky and 50km of ground shook.

The red light abruptly dissipated and a crack as big as two hundred and seventy feet appeared on the ground.

The soil around the crack bulged up and if one were to look from above, it would look like a person's lips.

Immediately following, the two sides of the cracks slowly opened up and revealed two rows of compact cube blocks of rocks resembling human teeth.

The 'teeth' also opened up and revealed an eerie large cave.

"Master, I'm hungry..." The lips-like crack opened and closed, unexpectedly speaking in a loud voice, causing the nearby ground to shake.

Fang Yuan smiled and took out a primeval elder Gu.

He sent his primeval essence and the amiable looking old man's happy expression gradually disappeared because large amounts of primeval stones were being taken out and thrown into the huge lips like crack.

After throwing in as much as two hundred thousand primeval stones, Fang Yuan stopped and put back the primeval elder Gu into his aperture.

The huge lips like crack slowly closed, its two rows of giant stone teeth started grinding the primeval stones into powder.

'Gulp', there was a loud sound like that of a person swallowing food, it echoed and shook the ground.

After swallowing these primeval stones, the lips-like crack calmed down and made no more noise.

At this point, the hole earth Gu could be said to have succeeded.

It could not be moved now, they would have to wait for He Feng Yang's sub Gu to activate before the two sides could link.

Feeding the hole earth Gu was an extremely huge expenditure. It would have to be fed two hundred thousand primeval stones yearly. And a large amount of primeval stones needed to be used every time it was activated.

Which ordinary Gu Master could use it alone? Besides the large sects and clans, only the Gu Immortals with huge resources could raise it and activate these hole earth Gu.

"Land spirit, this place needs to be strictly guarded from now on. Enslave some fox groups and place them here." Fang Yuan said while looking at the large lips-like crack.

"Yes, master."

　　...

"To protect our homes, we need to fight!"

"That damned immortal has come back stronger, we need to advance against this hardship. For a beautiful future and for our tribesmen, raise your fists!!"

"Although there are some grudges between us and the other two clans, they are all small conflicts within our rockmen tribes. This time, our three tribes will each send twenty thousand warriors to form an army to march west and attack the immortal's nest."

"This is a huge war, everything is for our people."

"Our parents and ancestors gave their lives and souls to defeat the immortal, and create this peaceful life we are enjoying now. We need to follow the footsteps of our elders and advance courageously in this war!"

The land spirit mobilized fox groups to appear near the rockmen tribes. The higher ups of the rockmen tribes took advantage of this to quickly form an allied army.

The majestic allied army marched towards the west area.

On their way, they had five to six small scale fights; they all ended in the rockmen army's victory while the fox groups had to retreat bit by bit.

"Look there! That is the demon's nest!" Yan Yong walked in front towards the hole earth Gu.

"Oh Mother Earth, you are our mother and have nurtured us rockmen. Why do you shield such an abominable immortal?" Yan Yong shouted in deep pain.

The huge crack slowly opened and little Hu Immortal spoke after using a Gu worm to change her voice.

The rockmen heard the gentle voice of a woman: "Oh rockmen, my children. I did not want to shield that immortal, but he entered my stomach and is hiding in my heart, threatening me to protect him. I will open my mouth, please come in and eliminate him, I will give you my blessing!"

The rockmen were astonished at first before they started shouting enthusiastically.

"Mother Earth spoke!"

"We are the warriors blessed by Mother Earth!"

"How despicable is this immortal, actually threatening our benevolent and gentle Mother Earth. We will definitely cut him into a thousand pieces!!"

The allied army of the rockmen felt their morale rising to the limit.

The large lips like crack opened wide. Yan Yong took the lead and shouted: "Rockmen, charge!"

He then jumped into the cave.

"Charge, we can't let our tribes' hero fight alone."

"Charge, we are fearless, we are omnipotent, we will kill the immortal!"

"Mother Earth is on our side, this battle will be our win!"

The rockmen jumped like dumplings into the large crack.

They fell down the dark tunnel for a while before they landed on the ground.

"Where is this? It is completely dark."

"This is even darker than underground, we can't see anything."

"How can we fight if we can't see?"

The rockmen were feeling doubtful when suddenly there was a huge coughing sound. A ball of light suddenly burst open above their heads. Rapid airflow instantly formed and carried them, as they were shot out.

"Two hundred thirty, two hundred forty..." Immortal Crane Sect's disciples were standing beside the hole earth Gu's sub Gu and were meticulously counting the rockmen that were shot out.

After the rockmen were shot out by the huge lips-like crack, they were immediately restrained by Immortal Crane Sect's disciples when they fell on the ground, unable to resist and unable to move.

Yan Yong and some rockmen elders stood at the side, looking at this scene in fear and their heads were lowered.

He Feng Yang had been furious after being played by Fang Yuan, but he eventually took consideration of the whole situation and did not smash the hole earth Gu's sub Gu under his anger, but instead planted it on Fei He mountain.

As for the rockmen...

Fang Yuan used their belief in Mother Earth and then used the fox groups and the rockmen higher ups to smoothly entice sixty thousand young rockmen into Fei He mountain and sell them.

Man is the spirit of all living beings.

In this world, apart from the humans born from Ren Zu's proper bloodline, there were also variant humans.

Variant humans might be more intelligent compared to other lifeforms but they were far from having human wisdom. Hairy men were ignorant, eggmen were innocent and rockmen were naive and barbaric...

Even a smart seven or eight year old child could deceive them. Whether it was Southern Border or Central Continent, such things often happened - some kids would bump into hairy men or rockmen at some place and deceive them all the way to the market. The variant humans would be ignorant even after being sold off, still the counting the money for them.

With this transaction Fang Yuan earned over one million six hundred thousand primeval stones.

Although each of the sixty thousand rockmen were young and energetic, they could not match the value of a swamp crab. On top of that Fang Yuan had to pay for the Gu refinement materials and there was the loss of sixty-five thousand primeval stones to use the hole earth Gu, and he also bought some common materials.

He Feng Yang had raised the price by ten percent as revenge, and also decreased many things Fang Yuan requested.

Fang Yuan did not care, the things he really wanted were already in his hands.

After the transaction was over, Yan Yong and the other rockmen elders followed the hole earth Gu back to Hu Immortal blessed land. Fang Yuan had already arranged a proper explanation to them and was sure the rockmen tribes would not rebel. Even if there was a rebellion, he could kill them and raise another batch. In any case, there were still a lot of gutstones on Dang Hun mountain.

Fang Yuan calmed down in his mind and continued his cultivation.

However, at rank four peak stage, nine eyes liquor worm had lost its use.

Liquor worm could purify the quality of the primeval essence, but only by a small realm. Fang Yuan was now at rank four peak stage and possessed the peak stage true gold primeval essence. Another step forward would be rank five initial stage light purple primeval essence.

Fang Yuan sealed the nine eyes liquor worm.

This Gu worm had accompanied him since Qing Mao mountain. From rank one liquor worm to current rank four nine eyes liquor worm, now it could finally retire.

By simply relying on true gold primeval essence to nurture his aperture, Fang Yuan's cultivation had become slower.

Naturally because he was at Hu Immortal blessed land, his cultivation speed was at least five times faster than the ordinary Gu Masters in the outside world.

"With this speed, I will have at least rank five middle stage cultivation or even near to upper stage by the time the seventh earthly calamity strikes."

Fang Yuan possessed A grade aptitude now, breaking through to rank five was not a problem. However, the higher the Gu Master's cultivation, the more time it would take for them to advance.

He had taken the purple crystal relic Gu into consideration when he said rank five middle stage.

Such speed compared to the five hundred years of his previous life was countless times better. Now, he was just slightly above thirty and was already at rank four peak stage. While in his previous life, at this age, he was still struggling at rank two realm.

"But this speed is still slow. There is the seventh earthly calamity outside in the blessed land while I have a great internal threat called Spring Autumn Cicada!"

Fang Yuan calculated that he would have to leave the blessed land in at most three years and go through a series of adventures. At least, he needed to find smooth success Gu or immediate success Gu to use on Spring Autumn Cicada and obtain a greater opportunity to live.

"Sigh! How I hope I could just keep on cultivating in the blessed land like Feng Jiu Ge and roam the world after reaching Gu Immortal realm."

Spring Autumn Cicada's ability to let the Gu Master rebirth was not fake, but there were too many restrictions. Even if the rebirth succeeded, the Gu Master would have to guard against it bursting their aperture. If there was not such a great fault, Fang Yuan's cultivation would be many times easier.

"For the next three years, I will have to refine Gu, use gutstones to expand the rockmen population and sell them for all kinds of resources."

However, while Fang Yuan's plan was near flawless, it could not compete against fate's prank.

Merely a month later, a huge change occured that gave him no choice but to leave the blessed land to an earlier date.

Chapter 425: Immortal Gu Gruel Mud

Crack.

Fang Yuan crushed a gutstone in his hand, immediately, mud flowed out, staining his palm.

Fang Yuan's gaze was solemn, he picked another rock on the mountain and held it in his hand.

His hand was stained with yellow mud, with a slow speed, it was slowly disintegrating the rock, turning the hard rock into more mud.

A moment later, Fang Yuan could distinctly feel the rock shrinking.

After ten minutes, the rock completely turned into mud, vanishing.

The yellow mud flowed down the space between Fang Yuan's finger, flowing onto Dang Hun mountain and continuing to cause damage to the mountain.

Fang Yuan was quiet for a moment before speaking, asking: "How severe is the situation?"

Little Hu Immortal wiped her tears as she sobbed, answering: "Most of Dang Hun mountain had been affected by the mud. Six out of ten of the gutstones below the mountain waist is turning into mud. Master, what do we do? Dang Hun mountain is going to perish... sob sob, it is my fault, I did not notice it earlier."

Fang Yuan patted little Hu Immortal's head, consoling: "This is not your fault, you do not need to blame yourself. The culprit is that swamp crab, as expected of a desolate beast, as expected of an earthly calamity!"

Land spirits' abilities are all different, they all differed and were greatly dependent on the Gu Immortals and their blessed lands.

He sighed, continuing: "I was still rejoicing earlier that the desolate beast did not have an Immortal Gu. It turns out this swamp crab used an expenditure type Immortal Gu and hid the Gu's power inside this mud. Nothing happens if it comes into contact with flesh, but all mountain rocks would be turned into mud upon touching it."

During the calamity earlier, the swamp crab spewed out large volumes of mud, and the crab army appeared from within the mud.

Fang Yuan killed an immense number of crabs, but little did he know, the real trump card was the mud itself.

Fang Yuan guessed that this is the effect of the rank six gruel mud Gu.

Gruel mud Gu was a naturally formed Gu, very commonly seen as rank one and two, and still rather popular as rank three and four. It was often used by Gu Masters to build cities. As rank five Gu were rare, many rank five Gu Masters would choose to temporarily use this gruel mud Gu when they did not have a good rank five Gu. When this rises to rank six, there would only be one in the world, and this Gu was a one time expenditure type.

Gruel mud Gu can only be used on mud, evidently, the swamp that swamp crab used to live in was created from the effects of gruel mud Gu. The swamp crab ate and defecated mud in the swamp every day, thus it was able to bring the ability of the gruel mud Gu into Hu Immortal blessed land.

After the swamp crab died, although the battlefield was cleaned up, large amounts of mud had already seeped into the mountain, moving deep underground.

Gruel mud Immortal Gu's ability was so hidden, and there was no Immortal Gu aura in the yellow mud, if Fang Yuan had not ordered the rockmen to crush the gutstones, he might not have found out at all.

But even if he found out early, he had no ability to stop this during the calamity.

Fang Yuan's expression was still as water.

Dang Hun mountain was being corroded by an Immortal Gu, slowly turning into yellow mud, this was a great nightmare!

The last valuable thing in this blessed land was this mountain. He wanted to rely on this mountain to nurture and sell rockmen. In the future, his own soul strengthening will also depend on this mountain. He could not sit around and watch the situation worsen.

At once, Fang Yuan ordered little Hu Immortal to clear out as much yellow mud as possible.

This way, the danger was greatly slowed.

But Dang Hun mountain's interior was also corroded, this method could not cure the root of the problem. This was the power of the gruel mud Immortal Gu, to remove it, he needed to use an Immortal Gu's power!

"I took such a huge risk to obtain this sacred land for soul strengthening. Even after I become an Immortal, this mountain is still extremely valuable. I cannot let it be destroyed. Heaven does not want this sacred land to end up in the hands of men, thus it sent such a calamity, but I will defy heaven. Hehe, competing with men, competing with heaven, this is the fun of life, that's all there is."

With Fang Yuan's knowledge, he was not helpless and without a solution.

He thought of more than ten ways to solve this, after eliminating half of which were not feasible, and removing those which were too hard, he was left with three solutions.

The first solution was the earth path rank six turn rock Gu. This Gu was in western desert, held in the hands of rank six Gu Immortal Sun Cu. Sun Cu is a righteous path Gu Master, he used this Gu to turn sand into rocks, in order for people to build structures in the desert, he was very popular and received gratitude from the people. He was kind hearted but not resolute, he loved his family and doted on his granddaughter the most, if Fang Yuan could hold her hostage, he would definitely comply.

The second solution was another earth path rank six Immortal Gu, called 'Rebuilding Mount Dongshan'. This Gu had already been refined, it was hidden in eastern sea's Hai Shi blessed land, Fang Yuan could enter the blessed land and use an Immortal Gu to exchange for this Gu.

The third was the time path rank six Immortal Gu 'Landscape As Before'. This Gu had not existed yet, it was not naturally formed. Its owner is Tai Bai Yun Sheng, he was still a rank five Gu Master in northern plains at the moment.

"In southern border on San Cha mountain, I refined fixed immortal travel Gu in public, it is obvious without a doubt that southern border is already in a huge commotion over it. A mortal that possesses an Immortal Gu, I'm afraid all those Gu Immortals in southern border are all notified now, and are looking for me all over the continent."

Until Fang Yuan becomes a Gu Immortal, he was not going to step into southern border again.

"Although the five regions are isolated, the super clan Yi clan has a relationship with a mysterious organisation in eastern sea. It will take at least two to three years until the news of me refining an Immortal Gu reaches central continent, but that might not be the case for eastern sea."

Fang Yuan eliminated eastern sea.

"As for western desert, it's the place where caravans flourish the most. Cities after cities, surviving using the oasis in the desert. If I can sell the rockmen there, I would earn a ton of profits. Unfortunately, a flourishing caravan trade means that information also travels fast. As a southern border Gu Master, I am an easy target. Once I reach there, I'd probably be marked the moment I enter a city."

In Fang Yuan's previous life, he roamed around all five regions during the five hundred years, finally choosing central continent to settle down, and become a Gu Immortal. Thus, he had a clear understanding of western desert.

"Compared to western desert, northern plains is a huge grassland, all sorts of tribes graze their livestock, migrate, battle, and procreate there. There is high mobility and some small-mid tribes have chaotic management, I can easily blend in with them."

Western desert was different from northern plains.

In western desert, humans relied on oasis to live, thus people are always gathered together. As long as the oasis is intact, nobody would make life difficult for themselves and go to another living area by making a dangerous and arduous desert journey.

But in northern plains, tribes have to move around often, finding rich and fertile land to relocate to. The weather there is ever-changing, strong weather conditions can destroy homes in a night, tribes have no choice but to move. Because of this, the high mobility among tribes also cause conflicts to occur often, and battles often takes place. Thus, the number of Gu Masters in northern plains is the highest, and they are also the ones most skilled at fighting among the five regions.

If Fang Yuan chooses western desert, abducting a hostage and threatening a Gu Immortal would cause a huge and lasting impact on the stability of western desert.

But if he chose northern plains, even if he killed the rank five Gu Master Tai Bai Yun Sheng, it would only be a mild commotion. In a few months, people will forget him.

Fang Yuan thought it through, and decided that the chaotic northern plains is most suitable for his actions.

Sun Cu in western desert is already a Gu Immortal, while Tai Bai Yun Sheng in northern plains is still a rank five peak stage.

After deciding on his destination, Fang Yuan started to think hard, compiling all the important information he had in his memories, to organise his plans for northern plains.

Plans do not keep up with changes, ever since rebirth, his plans had been changing continuously.

The first time was on Qing Mao mountain when he became A rank aptitude, it was a huge breakthrough and thus caused a shift. San Cha mountain was the second change, Fang Yuan soared to the sky in a single step, making all his plans unusable.

Although there were still benefits in the great battle of Yi Tian mountain, he could no longer stay in southern border.

As for central continent, that would be even worse.

He was a mortal, the ten righteous sects, the whole of Immortal Crane Sect, and all the demonic Gu Immortals on Tian Ti mountain were looking at him.

As long as he did not reach Gu Immortal realm, he would have to stay inside the blessed land, unable to come out.

He had also planned to do that, growing his strength inside Hu Immortal blessed land.

The blessed land had ample resources, Fang Yuan wanted to be like Feng Jiu Ge, cultivating in secret until he reached Gu Immortal realm, and get rid of the biggest problem called Spring Autumn Cicada.

Although Fang Yuan was a risk-taker, and liked to make profitable gambles, often struggling at death's door, it did not mean he rejected a peaceful and stable life.

Refusing to stay in a safe environment, and wanting to go around and create trouble for himself, taking risks and getting himself into danger, that is a fool.

Loneliness, solidarity, boredom, those were not obstacles to Fang Yuan's cultivation.

If he did not have the nature to endure these, how could he walk on the road to success?

But the world never goes your way, problems often find you when you least want it.

Fang Yuan wanted to cultivate in secret, developing the blessed land as he lived in peace. Although Immortal Crane Sect was trouble, Fang Yuan kept the initiative the entire time, although the other party is strong, they cannot do anything to him at the moment.

The future prospects were great, his life was going smoothly, everything had changed for the better. But at this moment, a problem happened to Dang Hun mountain!

To Hu Immortal blessed land, Dang Hun mountain's importance is insurmountable. If anything happens to this mountain, Fang Yuan's transactions would crumble, and his cultivation plans would turn into a mere dream.

Thus, Fang Yuan had to change his plans, leaving the blessed land and entering northern plains.

"Thankfully, I planned in advance, and made a few backup plans, otherwise, I would be extremely caught off-guard now."

For the next few months, Fang Yuan spent all his efforts on Gu refinement.

He used the rank four golden and silver cup Gu, combining with rank four another perspective Gu and rank four moving form Gu to refine the rank five moving perspective cup Gu.

Next, he refined dusty Gu, bright pearl Gu, dark toss Gu and earth treasury flower king Gu.

"Land spirit, during the days I'm gone, follow my instructions." Before leaving, Fang Yuan instructed.

Little Hu Immortal's eyes were red as she said reluctantly: "Master, I am waiting for you here, you have to return quickly."

Saying so, she used the green grape immortal essence and injected it into fixed immortal travel Gu.

With the burst of a jade-green light, Fang Yuan vanished on the spot.

Chapter 426: Stepping into Northern Plains

Howl!

In the night sky on the grassland, poison beard wolf king raised its head, howling loudly for a long time.

The ears of the few hundred poison beard wolves near it twitched, as their bodies shot out like arrows.

The wolves split into two, moving in a tight army-like formation.

The young girl Ge Yao ran for her life.

But her horse had already died, as her small red shoes stepped on the mud, she felt like her legs were tied with lead, extremely heavy.

The sprinting poison beard wolves successfully encircled her, and the two ends met. They were afraid of the young girl's Gu worms, thus they only circled around her and did not attack immediately.

All of a sudden, a poison beard wolf lost its patience and jumped out. Moving quickly, its body turned into a lump of black shadow as it charged towards Ge Yao.

Ge Yao shouted, using her Gu worms. As she pointed her finger, a light blue water arrow flew out.

The water arrow pierced through the poison beard wolf's head accurately while spiraling.

This courageous wolf died on the spot, its corpse fell on the slightly rotten grassland as it tumbled backwards, until it stopped moving forever.

Bright red blood quickly flowed out of its wounds, staining the grass nearby.

The restless wolves stopped momentarily, but soon the smell of blood spread in the air and the wildness and savageness of the wolves were brought out.

At once, hundreds of poison beard wolves started howling.

Ge Yao's beautiful face was full of regret and despair.

She should not have come out alone, to this poison grassland, trying to find some spirea. Now she was in a deadly situation, about to be torn apart and eaten by wolves.

"Sorry father, I am not longer able to take care of you!"

"Daughter knows that you arranged a marriage for my own good. But daughter does not want to marry..."

"Oh our ancestors in longevity heaven, if you can hear me, listen to my prayer and send a courageous warrior to save me."

The attack earlier had expended Ge Yao's last bit of white silver primeval essence. Ge Yao could only pray now.

The wolves lost their patience, the wolf king howled, and all the poison beard wolves charged towards the girl at the center, giving off an impressive aura.

"I am going to die!" Ge Yao's expression paled, she looked at the wolf group in a daze, she was helpless.

Right at this moment, a bright jade-green light flashed.

The poison beard wolves shut their eyes due to the light, howling in pain. The wolves that charged ahead knocked into one another, falling and causing a chain reaction, as their assault failed and the scene turned into chaos.

"What happened?" Ge Yao was shocked, ignoring her tears, she looked over.

From the jade-green light, the silhouette of a young man could be seen.

After the light faded, a naked man appeared in front of Ge Yao.

"A... a man?" Ge Yao's eyes were wide open, her mouth formed into an 'o' shape, she had an unbelievable thought: "Did my ancestors in longevity heaven listen to my prayers and send a savior to me?!"

But why was this savior naked?!

A huge question appeared in Ge Yao's mind.

"I reached northern plains?" Stepping on the grass barefooted, Fang Yuan looked around quickly.

"Oh? Why is there a human here... and wolves?" Fang Yuan squinted, to think that an accident occurred the moment he reached northern plains.

This trip to northern plains had to be kept secret, to think that he was exposed so quickly.

The wolf king howled, turning around as it opened its mouth, attacking Fang Yuan with its sharp and pointy teeth, targeting his neck.

"Hmph, a mere hundred beast king..." Fang Yuan's eyes shone with cold light, as a golden dragon appeared before him.

Rank four golden dragon Gu!

Roar!

The four clawed golden dragon roared, brandishing its claws as it flew towards the poison beard wolf king, crashing into it.

This hundred beast king's body was completely smashed, all its bones broke as it was sent flying like a rag. After crashing onto the ground, it struggled, but could not get up.

Fang Yuan frowned slightly, using another golden dragon to finish off the wolf king.

After the wolf king died, the wolf group broke down as they all escaped several miles away in a few breaths' time.

Only the wolf king's corpse was left, and also the young girl Ge Yao who was staring at Fang Yuan blankly.

Fang Yuan directed his dark eerie gaze towards this young girl.

The young girl was wearing a leather robe exclusive to northern plains, the robe was blue and white, with golden rims at the edges, showing off elegance and purity.

There was a purple gold belt at her waist, and also many beautiful and small accessories on her black lustrous hair.

She also had bright red leather shoes.

Her skin was slightly dark, but still had a pinkish tone, it was the unique skintone of northern plains natives. Her body was slim and strong, like a cute little deer.

Ge Yao retreated one step after Fang Yuan's stare, and she asked curiously: "Who are you? Are you sent from longevity heaven, the hero who is tasked to save me?"

Before waiting for Fang Yuan's reply, she continued: "I am a member of Ge tribe, my name is Ge Yao. My father is the tribe leader of Ge tribe, young warrior, you saved my life, you will be most welcomed in Ge tribe. Oh, I have not asked for your name yet."

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Beautiful lady of the grassland, just call me Chang Shan Yin. Longevity Heaven is Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's place of residence, how could I have come from there, I am but a mere Gu Master."

Saying so, he took out a wine cup from his aperture.

The top half of this cup was gold, the bottom was silver. It was rank five and was used as storage, it was the moving perspective cup Gu that Fang Yuan refined in the blessed land.

After Fang Yuan injected primeval essence into it, he took out a set of clothing.

This was a set of black tight-fitting battle attire, after wearing it, Fang Yuan gave off a sturdy and valiant aura.

During the process, Ge Yao stared at him fixatedly, her heart pounding as her face turned red.

The young women in the grassland were this open about their feelings.

After Fang Yuan wore his clothes, he walked towards the corpse of the poison beard wolf king.

Poison beard wolves were commonly seen in northern plains. But different from other wolves, they did not have a strand of fur, instead their bodies were black and their skin looked it it was covered in a layer of enamel. They did not have ears, only two long moustaches that were five inches long. When they ran, their moustache will sway along the wind, beside their bodies. When they fought, the moustache will stand up straight.

Fang Yuan searched but did not gain anything.

This poison beard wolf was a hundred beast king, it had rank two Gu worms in it.

There were two rank two Gu worms on this wolf, acid Gu and poison needle Gu.

Acid Gu could allow it to shoot out green acid from its mouth, corroding flesh or even steel and rocks. Poison needle Gu shot out poison needles, it was an offensive technique.

But unfortunately, Fang Yuan only got fragments of these two Gu.

There were no defensive Gu on this wolf king, no wonder it was so easily killed by Fang Yuan.

Normally, beast kings could have enslavement Gu in them. For example, on a dog king, there might be dog enslavement Gu, on a wolf king, there might be wolf enslavement Gu.

Even if it was a rank two wolf enslavement Gu, Fang Yuan needed it now.

Just as Fang Yuan was searching the wolf corpse, Ge Yao walked over: "Chang Shan Yin, your name sounds familiar. Are you a member of Chang tribe? But looking at your clothes, you seem to be an outsider? Are you from eastern sea? Central continent? Or western desert?"

Fang Yuan stood up: "I am from northern plains."

The young girl pouted, showing her white teeth as she laughed: "Liar! We northern plains natives do not have an accent like yours. Warrior Chang Shan Yin, don't worry, you saved my life, you are a benefactor of the Ge tribe, we will not ostracise you."

Be it central continent, southern border, or northern plains, as long as it is an outsider, they will be ostracised.

Before waiting for Fang Yuan's reply, the bubbly girl pointed at fixed immortal travel Gu on Fang Yuan's shoulder, asking: "Warrior Chang Shan Yin, this Gu on your shoulder is so beautiful, what Gu is this? Did you bring this Gu over?"

Fang Yuan's gaze concentrated, observing this young girl's expression. She was not acting or pretending, she really had shallow knowledge, she did not know this fixed immortal travel Gu, this made Fang Yuan slightly relieved.

The killing intent in his heart surged, but he showed an honest and sincere smile on the outside: "Beautiful young girl, are you a lark? Why are you constantly chirping non-stop. Hehehe, alright, I have to go, until we meet again!"

Fang Yuan raised his head, looking at the stars in the sky, trying to determine the direction.

Next, he walked past Ge Yao, towards the deeper parts of the poison grassland.

The young girl quickly caught up: "I am not a lark, it's your fault for being so mysterious, and appearing so suddenly. Heyheyhey, don't go there. This direction is the way out of poison grassland."

"I am going inside." Fang Yuan replied without turning around.

"Why are you going in? The deeper you go into the poison grassland, the more dangerous it gets. Although you are rank three peak stage, your fists cannot rival an entire wolf pack." Ge Yao sprinted towards Fang Yuan, urging him.

The five regions of the Gu world were independent, when Gu Masters cross regions, their battle strength will be suppressed by one rank.

Fang Yuan was a southern border Gu Master, when he is in northern plains, he will be suppressed when battling. Although his aperture still has rank four peak stage true gold primeval essence, the effectiveness was only at rank three peak stage snow silver primeval essence.

Thus, Ge Yao felt that his aura was rank three peak stage.

In addition, the rank four golden dragon Gu from southern border could only display the strength of a rank three Gu.

If this was southern border, one blow from the golden dragon Gu would have killed this poison beard wolf without doubt. But here in northern plains, Fang Yuan had to use it twice to kill the wolf king, and the wolf king's corpse was still intact at the end.

Fang Yuan's steps halted, as he looked at Ge Yao with a solemn expression and a determined gaze: "I am going into poison grassland for my own reasons."

Ge Yao was stunned by this aura, reacting only after Fang Yuan had walked a few steps away.

The girl quickly chased him: "Warrior Chang Shan Yin, I'll go with you, we can take care of each other."

"Got her." Fang Yuan's lips curled into a smile.

His currently battle strength was only rank three peak stage, it was insufficient to charge into poison grasslands' deepest part. Thus, he needed northern plains Gu worms to arm himself.

But even if he killed Ge Yao, he might not get her set of Gu worms. Thus, Fang Yuan set a little trap, purposely acting distant, easily tricking the young girl into joining him.

Chapter 427: Just take me

Although this was Fang Yuan's motive and Ge Yao took the initiative to join him, Fang Yuan still asked her: "Take care of each other? What do I need you for?"

Saying so, he ran his eyes over her, his tone carried a hint of arrogance.

The girl immediately raised her head: "Don't you know the poison grassland is filled with purple poison fog and you will be poisoned if you breathe it for a long time. I have detoxification Gu worms with me. Also the deeper you go, the denser the poison fog will become as ghosts and spirits will also appear. At that time, you won't be able to distinguish the direction, and only my return heart Gu can point out the correct way back."

Guuuu...

As the girl said this, her stomach suddenly let out a hungry rumbling sound.

Fang Yuan glanced at her stomach and the girl immediately felt her face go red.

She explained while stammering: "This... my big stomach horse was eaten by the poison beard wolves. My primeval stones and rations were all stored there."

Big stomach horse was a mount that was extremely popular in northern plains. It had two stomachs; one was used to consume food and another was used to store goods.

The Gu Masters of northern plains usually used this type of big stomach horse when relocating their homes.

Fang Yuan curiously asked: "Since your father is Ge tribe's tribe leader, why are you - his own daughter - using such a common mount?"

"Sigh, he kept my Gu away from me. Being able to escape alone with a big stomach horse and preparing so much resources was already amazing!"

Ge Yao spoke frankly but right after saying it, she felt something wrong and her expression turned sluggish as she realized what she had said.

"Escaped? Could it be that you are escaping from marriage?" Fang Yuan raised his brows.

The little girl exclaimed in surprise and looked at Fang Yuan with wide eyes: "Do you have mind reading Gu? How did you know?"

Fang Yuan laughed, he was only guessing but it was not without any evidence.

In northern plains, the position of women was much lower than that of men, even being treated as goods and casually sold in markets. In southern border, there were female clan leaders, but northern plains had no such precedence and women were not allowed to be in power.

Why was that so?

This tradition dated back to the era of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

In Fang Yuan's memories, during these three years, many great heroes would fight for supremacy in northern plains and a great storm would blow. Eventually, Hei tribe leader Hei Lou Lan succeeded and became the lord of the imperial court for ten years. He was also the most controversial lord of the grassland in future generations.

Hei Lou Lan was extremely lecherous, and after becoming the ruler of the grassland, he made beauties of many tribes part of his harem. But on other hand, he made a new policy to raise women's status and attempted to create gender equality.

This gravely infringed upon all forces' interests and led to conflicts, causing an institutional turmoil among all northern plains tribes.

Thus, Hei Lou Lan had only been the lord of the grassland for two years when he was deceived by his own tribesmen to go outside the imperial court and was killed secretly. Immediately following, all tribes allied to overthrow Hei tribe's rule and again contended for the position of the ruler of the imperial court. The bloodshed and war lasted for an entire five years before it settled.

After this chaotic war, every tribe of northern plain suffered great losses. And in the future, when Central Continent attacked the four other regions, this became the greatest weakness of northern plains.

A lot of northern plains women thus choose to run away in order to avoid marriage. This girl standing before him had come alone to poison grassland even though she was the daughter of the tribe leader. Fang Yuan naturally made such a guess.

Fang Yuan took out food from moving perspective cup Gu and gave them to Ge Yao.

This girl seemed to be very hungry; she wolfed down the food and rolled her eyes, slurring her words: "It was Man Duo of Man tribe who wanted to marry me. He is Man tribe leader's third son and is thin and small, like a monkey. Moreover, he is suffering from illness and only has rank two cultivation. Usually, he would rely on his father to act tyrannically in his tribe. He has not the slightest bit of heroic spirit! I don't want to marry to such a good-for-nothing."

"But Man tribe was a huge force while our Ge tribe has just migrated over with greatly reduced strength. Man tribe's betrothal gift was also very grand and they also promised to give a piece of fertile grassland to my Ge tribe. Father wanted these gifts and tried to marry me off. And so in my fury, I fled. Warrior Chang Shan Yin, how about you snatch me?"

Northern plains had simple and coarse customs. One of their customs was bride kidnapping.

The snatched bride was often more precious than an officially married wife.

Fang Yuan laughed: "I have no interest in you, eat quickly, we will leave after you are full."

Ge Yao's dark pupils darted around: "There is another method, that is, you can marry into my Ge tribe. According to the grassland customs, only a brave warrior can possess beauties. Even if Man tribe wants to find trouble, it has to be done according to the customs; Man Duo, that skinny monkey would have to challenge you to a fight. Warrior Chang Shan Yin, you are so strong, you will certainly beat that Man Duo to a pulp!"

Fang Yuan stopped smiling: "I said I don't have any interest in you."

Ge Yao, however, became even more passionate and displayed northern plains women's characteristic boldness and wildness: "Why don't you have any interest? Could it be that I am not beautiful? I am the flower of Ge tribe, that kid Man Duo glanced at me from afar and fell for me at first sight, asking his father to propose the marriage! Warrior Chang Shan Yin, there are benefits for you as well in living with my Ge tribe. You are an outsider, if you don't marry into the tribe, others will not take you as one of their own and you will suffer exclusion and vigilance in northern plains."

Fang Yuan said with a solemn tone: "I said I am a northern plains native."

Ge Yao gave a sweet smile: "Warrior, you can't deceive me. Your accent revealed your background, and your food is also not the northern plain's biscuits and dried meat. Just take me, don't you think our encounter is the arrangement of longevity heaven?"

Fang Yuan lowered his head to cover the cold light that was vaguely flashing in his eyes as the smile on his face became deeper.

"Let me consider it for a while, don't be in such a hurry to decide." Fang Yuan said and gave some primeval stones to Ge Yao.

Ge Yao nodded: "You have to think about it properly... properly."

She took the primeval stones and said with a cautious tone: "I will return these primeval stones to you in the future."

Fang Yuan nodded.

Ge Yao did not speak anymore and concentrated on absorbing the primeval stones to replenish her primeval essence and recover her strength as fast as possible.

As they continued moving deeper into the poison grassland, the thin poison in the air gradually became denser. They were unnoticeable before to the naked eyes, but now one could clearly see the light purple color.

"Stop, there is a wolf pack!" Ge Yao suddenly stopped, her gaze revealing panic.

Clearly, the battle with the poison beard wolves had left a deep impression on her.

Fang Yuan stopped, and after three breaths of time, he discovered the tracks of the wolf pack with his investigative Gu worm.

He could not help but glance at Ge Yao, indeed as a tribeswoman, the investigative Gu worm on her was great.

Fang Yuan had refined this rank four investigative Gu in Hu Immortal blessed land. But in northern plains, it was suppressed and could not compare to Ge Yao's rank three Gu.

The wolf pack's excited howls got louder and louder.

Soon, hundreds of poison beard wolves appeared in their vision.

"So many wolves!" Ge Yao's face turned pale and her delicate body trembled as she took in a breath of cold air. The wolf pack's numbers were many times higher than the previous ones, reaching close to a thousand.

The stronger the beast king, more the number of beasts they could control; this hundred beast king was clearly much stronger than the previous one.

"Hmph, what are you panicking for? Just protect yourself." Fang Yuan snorted and fiercely stomped his foot, charging forward.

Ge Yao exclaimed in shock at this, she wanted to call out to Fang Yuan but he had already entered the wolf pack.

Many poison beard wolves ran and charged at Ge Yao.

The girl shouted in her delicate voice: "Water armor!"

Immediately, water vapor condensed and formed into a layer of light blue armor that covered here whole body.

"Spiral water arrow Gu!"

She extended her finger and a spiral water arrow flew out.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!

She killed three poison beard wolves instantly while injuring five or six more.

But at the same time, a dozen poison beard wolves came charging at her.

The girl panicked and retreated, responding in a flustered manner.

"Water dragon Gu!" She pushed with her palms and a three clawed water dragon whistled out and swept through the surroundings, increasing the water vapor in the air.

With the appearance of the water dragon, Ge Yao was able to control the situation.

"Warrior Chang Shan Yin, don't die!" The girl immediately looked at the center of the wolf pack.

She was almost stunned at the sight.

The scene she saw was not what she had expected, she only saw Fang Yuan charging all over the wolf pack, every collision would send large numbers of poison beard wolves flying.

The ferocious poison beard wolves seemed to be weaker than sheep in front of him.

His whole body was covered in a layer of bright golden light armor, and a golden dragon came out occasionally, sweeping through the surroundings. There were so many poison beard wolves, but they could not subdue him.

He was fierce and fearless, his fighting style was extremely valiant, his every move would cause the wind to scream. His strength was so huge that as long as a poison beard wolf came into contact with his fists or kicks, their skeleton would definitely shatter and they would howl with pain, no longer able to stand up.

Not only that, he was also fighting an intense battle with the wolf king.

This poison beard wolf king was indeed very strong. Lightning flickered arounds its whole body, and it occasionally shot out green venom. Its movement speed was so fast that it created an afterimage when it ran.

"This wolf king has at least three wild Gu." Ge Yao's heart sank as she learnt this, becoming worried for Fang Yuan.

Soon, the girl let go of her worry and admiration towards Fang Yuan rose in her heart.

Fang Yuan fought in a smart manner, he was continuously on the move and did not blindly engage with the wolf king, instead using the ordinary poison beard wolves to hinder the wolf king's movement.

The wolf king had movement Gu but it was restrained by the wolf pack and could only passively take a beating.

Fang Yuan's fists attacked its targets with high power; Ge Yao's blood boiled at the scene.

"This is a true man!" She exclaimed in her mind and after disposing of the poison beard wolves around her, she shouted loudly and sent the water dragon to kill the wolf pack.

She was after all a rank three middle stage Gu Master, she was not to be underestimated. The wolf pack immediately turned chaotic from the attacks and a large portion of them rushed towards her.

Fang Yuan's expression changed as he shouted: "Who told you to come? Move to the side!"

The girl's face turned pale at the wolf pack's counterattack and immediately retreated.

Fang Yuan continued to attack with boundless vigor and after spending a huge effort, he finally turned the wolf pack's attention back to him.

After some time, he suddenly activated a beast phantom and smashed the wolf king's defense.

Taking this chance, he got close to the wolf king and pressed its skull down to the ground, then he ruthlessly smashed it.

It was a brutal scene. This wolf king that was on the verge of becoming a thousand beast king was beaten to death by Fang Yuan.

Chapter 428: Sea of Ghost Face Sunflowers

With the death of the wolf king, the wolf pack's morale collapsed and they all started fleeing in disorder.

A fierce battle ended so abruptly.

"You got injured?!" Ge Yao came running and looked with a concerned gaze.

"It's nothing." Fang Yuan's injuries looked terrifying but it was all under his control. He activated self-reliance Gu on the spot; the wounds started closing and healing.

Self-reliance Gu was a rank three Gu but could only show the effects of a rank two in northern plains. After Fang Yuan's injuries healed a little, its effects immediately weakened.

"Warrior Chang Shan Yin, let me heal you." Ge Yao waved her hand and water vapor rose, forming a green-blue cloud above Fang Yuan.

Light rain started pouring down from the cloud and splashed upon Fang Yuan's body, healing his wounds.

"This is spring rain Gu?" Fang Yuan furrowed his brows, "This Gu has a huge healing range, isn't it a waste to use it on just me alone? Deactivate it."

After saying so, he activated golden breeze Gu.

This Gu was obtained from Tie Mu Bai and was a rank four healing Gu but now it only showed the efficiency of a rank three. However, it was still a top quality Gu.

Ge Yao saw a golden whirlwind form beside Fang Yuan; after it spun around him several times, all his wounds disappeared.

"What Gu is this?" The girl asked curiously.

Fang Yuan did not reply, but turned around and crouched down, searching the wolf king's corpse carefully.

Ge Yao followed behind him and bent her back to look at him, exclaiming in praise: Warrior Chang Shan Yin, you are a true expert. Father has always told me that going into battle by just relying on one's cultivation is stupid. I saw you charging into the wolf pack, it was such a dangerous situation, but you moved skillfully like it was a simple task. I finally understood that what father said was true."

Fang Yuan snorted and stood up.

With his five hundred years of battle experience, it was rather easy for him to do this. If not for the region's restriction, how could he take so much time to deal with this puny wolf pack?

After searching, he found out that the wolf king had three wild Gu, but they were all dead.

Fang Yuan's expression turned unsightly at the lack of loot, he glanced at Ge Yao and said gruffly: "Stupid? Do you think you are just stupid? You are utterly stupid!"

Ge Yao was immediately stifled: "Hey! Why are you so blunt!"

"Hmph, earlier, your careless attack attracted most of the wolf pack and almost screwed up my control of the situation. Do you have the brains of an ox?" Fang Yuan snorted and blamed.

Ge Yao knew that it was her mistake, her aura immediately weakened and she lowered her head, looking at her feet: "I know you attracted most of the wolf pack away for me. But I also wanted to help you."

Fang Yuan heaved a sigh: "Forget it, I will let it go this time. I will try to make an effort to teach you what you have to do to, so that you will not impede me again in the future."

"Who needs you to teach?" Ge Yao turned around and snorted with dissatisfaction. …

""You need to be calm when activating spiral water arrow Gu. If you just recklessly shoot them, you would simply be wasting your precious primeval essence rapidly."

"Water dragon Gu wastes a lot of primeval essence, don't use it if it is not necessary. This is why you are always running out of primeval essence!"

"Don't use spring rain Gu, that is a large scale healing Gu that is not worth it for just the two of us."

As they continued on their way, Fang Yuan gave many tips to Ge Yao.

The girl's words before were just said in a fit. Although, she did have a young missy's temperament, this was something that concerned her deeply, so she earnestly listened to the suggestions and absorbed the knowledge, improving rapidly.

The two continued moving through poison grassland and ran into several waves of wolf packs, and Ge Yao's performance also became better each time.

"Haha, are you afraid? You abominable poison beard wolves, get lost." After repelling a poison beard wolf pack again, Ge Yao stood with her hands on her hips as she said proudly.

"Truly a naive girl." Fang Yuan looked at her back with a cold light flashing across his eyes.

Naturally, the reason he guided Ge Yao was not purely to raise her battle strength, more importantly it was to probe out her Gu worms.

The result was, the girl revealed all her trump cards to Fang Yuan.

Ge Yao was a water path Gu Master with rank three middle stage cultivation.

Rank three fog sparrow Gu as the investigative Gu; three claw water dragon Gu and spiral water arrow Gu for attack; water armor Gu for defense; water trace Gu for movement; and spring rain Gu for healing.

She did not have a storage Gu, the big stomach horse she used to replace this aspect had already died by wolf pack's claws.

Besides these, she also had cleansing Gu for detoxification; and return heart Gu for discerning the direction.

This set of Gu worms was very appropriate given her identity.

Fog sparrow Gu was a very precious investigative Gu among rank three which could condense fog into sparrows that could fly to scout the area and had a very huge range.

Her attack and defense Gu were also of top quality.

Water trace Gu's ability to raise the speed could almost rival some rank four Gu. The only disadvantage was that the water trace would leave behind footprints that were easy to track. At the same time, it would make the shoes wet.

This Gu had the potential to be nurtured. At rank four, it could become wave trace Gu which had an even stronger effect.

For rank five, it had two different refinement directions. One was wandering wave trace Gu that had instant evasion properties; and another was the river wave trace Gu that allowed the Gu Master to run quickly on water surfaces.

At rank six, it would be the extremely famous worldly wave trace Gu.

All of these Gu were the best among rank three. Along with Fang Yuan's meticulous guidance and the wolf packs' pressure, it was no wonder Ge Yao was improving rapidly with her battle strength rising step by step.

"Warrior Chang Shan Yin, you are a sage. Your guidance is much more amazing than my tribe's three top elders. Even if you don't take a fancy upon me, I want to invite you to be a guest of our Ge tribe. If you are interested, I will do my best to persuade father to make you an external elder!"

Ge Yao turned around and walked to Fang Yuan's side, and invited him with a sincere expression.

She was after all the young missy of Ge tribe, her foresight was extraordinary. She realized Fang Yuan's worth; not only his bravery, but more importantly his ability to educate others. This was the strength of wisdom, if he educated the tribe's next generation, the whole tribe could flourish.

"I can become a guest of Ge tribe, but I don't have any interest in becoming an external elder." Fang Yuan walked forward while shaking his head to refuse.

Ge Yao persuaded him several times, but Fang Yuan's attitude was firm.

The girl sulked and followed behind Fang Yuan, looking at his back with an angry gaze.

"Do you think you are amazing just because you can teach? Hmph. I used such an urging tone, yet you remain unmoved. No interest to become my Ge tribe's external elder? Are you looking down on my Ge tribe?"

"Chang Shan Yin, you scoundred!"

Ge Yao gritted her teeth in hatred while having a doubt in her mind: "But this name Chang Shan Yin, it is really familiar, where in the world did I hear it?"

Poison grassland was covered with dark clouds all year round, and in this dusky light, the two walked for some distance.

Fang Yuan stopped.

In front of him was a large field of sunflowers.

Each of these sunflowers had a dark purple stalk and large pitch-black petals. Its basin-sized stamen showed a pale human face.

Ghost face sunflower!

This sight caused Ge Yao to immediately hold her breath and grab Fang Yuan's sleeve, whispering in a very soft voice: "A lot of people definitely died here, with many ghosts wandering around, it led to the growth of so many ghost face sunflowers. Every ghost face sunflower is a ghost that died unjustly. Let's detour around this place, there are definitely many ghost cry Gu living in these ghost face sunflowers and there could even be ghost face Gu."

Ghost cry Gu was a rank three soul path Gu which could let out a mournful wail that could cause the soul to shake.

Ghost face Gu was a rank four soul path Gu that could create a tremendous impact on the soul.

"It is such a large field of ghost face sunflowers, how long will we take to make a detour?" Fang Yuan concentrated on this sea of sunflowers, he did not show any expression on the surface but was actually very happy inside.

This confirmed the direction he was walking towards was not wrong.

As long as he walked along this direction, he will find that battlefield twenty years ago and obtain the Gu worms left behind on the battlefield.

Northern plains was different from southern border.

Southern border had lots of mountains and one could distinguish their general direction; while northern plains was grassland as far as the eye could see and was very easy to get lost.

Thus, Ge Yao carried return heart Gu with her for support. Return heart Gu would always point towards the direction of the home in the Gu Master's heart.

However, return heart Gu could only indicate the direction and not the position.

If Fang Yuan wanted to ensure that he was moving in the correct path, he would have to take the risk of moving through this field of sunflowers.

Fortunately, he was already prepared.

He lightly removed the girl's hand on his sleeve and squatted down. He put his palms on the ground and then activated a Gu in his aperture.

Soon, green underbrush grew out from the ground.

The lush underbrush rose little by little and the slender grass and leaves coiled around each other, gradually forming into a puppet.

Enslavement path, rank three grass puppet Gu.

This Gu worm was something only Southern Border had; Ge Yao looked at each grassman puppet with astonishment, they continued to grow and soon formed a group.

These grassman puppets were short and thin, the leaves tightly weaved together, they held a bamboo blade in one hand and a rattan shell shield in the other.

This was the rank three rattan shell grass soldier.

Previously when Fang Yuan had fought one against seven at San Cha mountain, Tie Ruo Nan had used such a Gu. Later, Fang Yuan obtained a grass puppet Gu in three kings blessed land from one of the people he killed.

Grass puppet Gu was rather common in Southern Border. Rank three grass puppet Gu could could create an army of rattan shell grass soldier that had the strength to kill rank one Gu Masters. Rank four grass puppet Gu could create grass sword elite soldiers which possessed even stronger battle strength.

However, in the northern plains, the grass puppet Gu also suffered from the restriction and the rattan shell grass soldiers it created were weak.

However, Fang Yuan created these rattan shell grass soldiers not for battle and was indifferent about them.

After a while, close to a thousand rattan shell grass soldiers started clearing the way in front of him.

Fang Yuan pulled Ge Yao's hand and under the protection of another hundred rattan shell grass soldiers, they walked into the sea of ghost face sunflowers.

"Yaaa—!"

"Mieee~~~"

"Dieee…"

Every ghost cry Gu let out a sharp screech; the rattan shell grass soldiers ahead collapsed. The voices the ghost cry Gu let out were not the same. Some were sharp frightened sounds; some were like the bleating of sheep; and some seemed to be recounting hidden bitterness.

"Ghost… ghost faces are rising." The girl shook as she looked at the pale, terrifying ghost faces fly out from the sea of sunflowers.

Fang Yuan gently patted her hand and then calmly organised the puppets.

Soon, some rattan shell grass soldiers left the main group and sacrificed themselves to lure the ghost faces away.

Chapter 429: Shadow Crow

The two got through sunflower sea safely.

Ge Yao looked behind her, breathing out deeply, her worried heart finally settled.

"To think that we got past the sea of ghost face sunflowers so easily."

After regaining her composure, the young girl looked at the grassman puppets around her.

There were only a few dozen puppets left, forming a weak defensive layer around them.

Ge Yao had never seen such a Gu in her life, this was an eye-opener.

"These Gu, although they do not have high combat strength, the greatest advantage is to use them as fodder. Chang Shan Yin came prepared indeed." Thinking so, the young girl diverted her gaze towards the person beside her.

The more she spent time with Fang Yuan, the more curious Ge Yao got, and the greater her determination to find out more about him.

"What sort of person is he? Entering poison grassland, what motive does he have? Chang Shan Yin, Chang Shan Yin... this name is so familiar, I've heard it before. Ah!"

The young girl's face turned red.

When they had crossed the sunflower sea earlier, Fang Yuan held her hand. Those ghost cries and scary ghost faces made her frightened, she got closer to Fang Yuan and was almost hugging his arm, but she did not notice.

Ge Yao quickly let go of Fang Yuan's arm, getting free of his hand.

After she got to a safe distance, Fang Yuan slowly stopped his steps, turning to look at these sunflowers.

"These ghost cry Gu and ghost face Gu are decent Gu, but I do not have the specialized Gu worms needed to catch them."

Catching a wild Gu worm requires specific methods. These two Gu worms were soul path Gu, the Gu needed to catch them were even more peculiar.

"It is time." Fang Yuan's gaze concentrated, discarding his mild regret as he turned his gaze towards fixed immortal travel Gu on his shoulder.

Immortal Gu have overbearing aura, they could not be stored into mortal apertures. Spring Autumn Cicada could barely be kept in the aperture due to its weakened state.

Even if Fang Yuan ordered fixed immortal travel Gu to stay on his shoulders and not move about, the Immortal Gu's aura would still leak, if a Gu Immortal senses it, it would invite grave danger!

But thankfully, Fang Yuan had measures against this.

He took out bright pearl Gu.

"Go." He injected his primeval essence, and the bright pearl Gu turned into a warm white light, floating onto fixed immortal travel's body, covering it completely.

Bright pearl Gu is a rank four storage type Gu, mainly used to seal Gu worms and cause them to go into deep slumber and be easily stored.

Fang Yuan expended almost all his primeval essence before he successfully sealed the fixed immortal travel Gu.

Fixed immortal travel Gu was like a jade butterfly, sealed into a fist-sized pearl. But it was an Immortal Gu, its aura still leaked out through the pearl.

Except, it was much weaker now.

Fang Yuan was not surprised, this was only step one.

The following journey was much smoother.

Perhaps due to that sunflower sea, not a single poison beard wolf appeared.

The two continued to venture deeper, as the poisonous fog on the grassland became thicker, until one could clearly see the purple fog in the air.

When the two started coughing, they would stop moving and take out their Gu worms respectively, getting rid of the toxins that accumulated in them.

The deeper they went into the grassland, the thicker the fog, and the more often the two of them stopped.

Ge Yao who was active and lively also started keeping quiet in order to avoid breathing in too much of the poison fog.

Eventually, the purple fog started to obscure their vision.

"How much deeper are we going?" Ge Yao could not help but ask.

The deepest part of the poison grassland was a forbidden area for living beings. The deeper they go, the stronger the wild beasts inside. Many experts who went to explore lost their lives here, none returned. Among them were rank three peak stage experts, and even rank four.

"Soon." Fang Yuan replied plainly as he walked slower, until he stopped.

"Are we there? It's here?" Ge Yao asked happily.

Fang Yuan did not say a word, he squatted down and moved away some poisonous shrubs that had a weird appearance, as a hole that was hidden by the bushes appeared before him.

This hole was the size of a large bowl, it has a smooth edge. Inside the hole was pure darkness.

Ge Yao saw this and her eyes were fixed on the hole, breathing roughly: "This, this is a hole dug by a earth spike rat. They live together in thousands and even ten thousands, forming into a huge group. They live under the grass inside the soil, as long as there are vibrations in the ground, they would attack from below. Their heads are like steel spikes, once they shoot out, it can pierce a person's feet. Even a horse's hoofs can get pierced."

"We cannot go forward anymore. Once we get encircled, there will be no way to survive. We will be submerged by endless rats. Along the way, we met no poison beard wolves, this shows that the earth spike rats are the lord of this area. Who knows, the earth spike rat king might be a myriad beast king!"

The young girl had lived in the grassland since young, she knew clearly how powerful the earth spike rats were.

"No, my destination is further ahead." Fang Yuan stood up.

"Chang Shan Yin! Excessive bravery is courting death. You cannot walk over this. In fact, in just a few steps, you will get attacked by the rats." Ge Yao quickly explained.

But Fang Yuan smiled lightly: "Who said I am going to walk over?"

Just as he said so, pitch-black wings grew on his back.

"This..." Ge Yao stared with wide-opened eyes, before she reacted, Fang Yuan already carried her up.

As the girl screamed, Fang Yuan flapped his wings and flew above the ground.

Ge Yao felt like her heart was stuck in her throat, the wind was blowing at her ears as she felt herself on swimming in clouds, her legs could not touch the ground thus she subconsciously grabbed Fang Yuan's neck.

After a while, the young girl reacted, and laughed heartily in Fang Yuan's arms: "Chang Shan Yin, to think that you can fly. Father has a flying cloud Gu, he used to bring me to play in the sky when I was young. Sigh, sadly flying cloud Gu is a rank four Gu, I cannot use it. But even if I could, father would not allow it, he would be afraid of me falling from the sky."

Ge Yao recalled, before asking curiously: "Chang Shan Yin, what flying Gu is this? Why have I not seen it before?"

Fang Yuan did not answer.

The young girl did not give up: "This is the rank three eagle wings Gu? Such speed and altitude is similar to eagle wings Gu, but this does not look like it."

Fang Yuan sighed: "You ask too many questions. Rather than asking me useless questions, why don't you spend your effort on the shadow crows ahead of us."

"Shadow crow?" The young girl reacted, seeing three shadow crows in front flying towards them soundlessly.

The shadow crows were large as an eagle, their bodies were black and they moved without sound. In this foggy poison grassland, they were even more stealthy.

The young girl's expression paled, her voice trembling: "Chang Shan Yin, how good is your flying technique? If you are not good, let's land and defend on the grassland."

"No worries." Fang Yuan's voice was emotionless: "I'm carrying you, I cannot attack. Next, it will depend on whether your spiral water arrow is accurate."

"What? Ah!"

The young girl had not understood what he said, when Fang Yuan flapped his wings fiercely and charged towards the three shadow crows.

Fang Yuan used his actions to reply Ge Yao.

"This is too insane! He did not think of running away, but instead wants to kill these three shadow crows!" Ge Yao was shocked, in her panic, she shot out two water arrows.

But these two water arrows, one missed completely while the other grazed the shadow crow's wing.

"Too slow, again!" Fang Yuan made a perfect turn as he flapped his wings towards the shadow crows again.

"What? Hey, wait, don't fight them. We are not on the ground, our opponents are the shadow crows famous for speed!" Ge Yao shouted.

The two humans and three birds charged towards each other in the air, as they got closer and closer.

Ge Yao could see a shadow crow enlarging quickly in her vision, as they got close, the shadow crow brandished its dagger-like sharp claws.

Seeing that the sharp claw was about to hit her, Ge Yao's body turned cold from fright, her fingers and legs were stiff as she was immobilized.

"We're going to collide, I am going to die!" Just as she had this thought, Fang Yuan kept his wings and they descended quickly, narrowly avoiding the shadow crow's claw.

Next, he stretched out his wings and flapped hard, making a zigzag turn, flying up and chasing behind the shadow crow.

"Fire quickly!" Fang Yuan shouted.

Ge Yao's body reacted to his voice and subconsciously shot out a spiral water arrow.

Fang Yuan's flying technique was too profound, he directly flew behind the shadow crow, its back was completely exposed to Ge Yao.

The spiral water arrow shot the shadow crow, piercing its body and causing a trail of blood.

The shadow crow was killed on the spot, like a kite with its strings cut, it fell onto the ground with a loud thump.

The grassland was silent for a moment before the ground vibrated, as numerous earth spike rats popped up from underground.

That shadow crow corpse was immediately dismembered and dragged into the holes made on the ground piece by piece.

The large shadow crow vanished in an instant, leaving behind a pool of blood, as well as some small pieces of intestines.

The young girl became overwhelmingly nervous after seeing this. If she really fell, she would immediately get attacked by the earth spike rats, she would definitely die!

"What are you thinking? Shoot them!" Fang Yuan chided, interrupting the girl's thoughts as she hurriedly attacked, shooting over ten arrows before killing the two shadow crows.

The two shadow crows landed on the ground and were immediately taken by the earth spike rats, Ge Yao looked at this as cold sweat appeared on her face.

"Your accuracy is terrible, quickly use primeval stones to recover your primeval essence!"

As Fang Yuan scolded, Ge Yao took out one primeval stones, but because she was flustering, this primeval stones fell out of her hand and landed on the ground.

"You idiot!"

"So... sorry!"

The young girl apologised in a sobbing tone.

"Focus, calm down! Display your usual ability, there will be many shadow crows later, I have to depend on you." Fang Yuan's voice became more gentle.

"Yes, yes." Ge Yao nodded her head in succession, after Fang Yuan consoled her, her mind slowly returned to a calm state.

Chapter 430: White Bone Chariot

An entire hour later.

Fang Yuan carried Ge Yao as they safely landed on the ground.

Ge Yao's legs went soft, her expression was pale and she had to catch her breath after getting back to the land, recovering slowly.

During the flying process, she had killed at least a hundred shadow crows, she had felt that she was struggling at death's door during the process.

During the process of flying, they were in great danger, facing the assault of many waves of shadow crows, and even attracted the attack of the earth spike rats.

Not only were there an endless number of shadow crows in the sky, numerous earth spikes would shoot up from the ground at times; it was a truly precarious situation.

Fang Yuan spread his wings, twisted and turned, circled, dived, and rose into the sky under such attacks. Finding impossible opportunities, he managed to find a way out of the rain of attacks.

"I actually survived from facing such an insane number of enemies?" This was Ge Yao's first thought when she landed.

The relief of surviving an ordeal, an unbelievable feeling of happiness, and the after-fear of recalling the situation, after she had experienced all these, Ge Yao looked at Fang Yuan with a complicated expression, as he was healing the injuries on his body.

Even if the girl was ignorant, after such an experience, she knew that Fang Yuan was a grand expert in flying.

Moreover, Ge Yao was not an ordinary young girl from the grassland, her father was the leader of a tribe, in her entire life, she had been greatly influenced by him, her horizons were expanded and she knew much more than her peers.

"The man before me, he has such skilled flying techniques, he is so strong. Inside that strong body of his, is there a flying eagle's soul? Such flying technique can compete with 'Lightning' Dong Po Kong, 'Water Immortal' Song Qing Yin, and 'Green Bat' Wu Ye! This is a first-rate flying technique in northern plains! Chang Shan Yin, Chang Shan Yin, what kind of person are you..."

Fang Yuan quickly took care of his injuries.

Facing a storm-like attack, even if his flying technique was top-tier, he could not avoid getting hit sometimes.

Most importantly, the rank four bone wings Gu only had rank three effectiveness in northern plains. At the same time, he was carrying a person, with the increase in weight, it affected his agility.

"But, having Ge Yao's help, the advantage was greater than the disadvantage. If she did not use water arrow and water dragon to kill the crow groups, or if she did not use water armor to defend us, my primeval essence might not be enough." Fang Yuan thought.

"As a southern border Gu Master, when I am in northern plains, my cultivation will be suppressed, but thankfully, as time passes and I slowly assimilate into northern plains, this suppression will decrease."

Man is the spirit of all beings, they had great adaptability with the environment they were in.

Of course, when Fang Yuan completely mixes in with northern border, and his cultivation returns to normal, when he returns to southern border, he will face suppression again, and would need to adapt and assimilate once again.

"Man can adapt to the environment, but Gu worms cannot. Southern border Gu worms will continue to face suppression, all my Gu worms still expend the same amount of primeval essence but their use is greatly reduced. Rank four Gu worms in southern border are inferior to rank three northern plains Gu worms here."

But if he killed Ge Yao, he only had a very small chance of getting her Gu worms.

Ony by using her like this, can this rank three middle stage Gu Master's worth be fully displayed.

"If not for Ge Yao, I would not be able to advance so quickly. Although her Gu worms are good, I have no way of taking them. These southern border Gu worms, I need to change them out, other than considering their battle strength, they are also the greatest flaw in hiding my identity. I have to get to that battlefield."

Fang Yuan sighed internally, taking out bright pearl Gu.

Fixed immortal travel Gu is sealed inside bright pearl Gu, like a beautiful amber.

In front of Ge Yao, Fang Yuan took out bright pearl Gu forthrightly.

Dusty Gu was like a cocoon, its body was dark grey, and felt like sandpaper. Fang Yuan injected primeval essence, and dusty Gu exploded lightly, turning into a grey smoke cloud.

The grey smoke moved towards bright pearl Gu as if it was sentient.

The originally shining bright pearl Gu was covered by this dust cover, and dimmed. The fixed immortal travel Gu's aura diminished once again.

This became a dusty pearl.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, when he got to central continent and caused the five region chaotic battle, some Gu Masters slipped into other regions to battle, and in order to hide their identities and conceal their aura, they created this method.

"What are you doing?" Ge Yao asked curiously.

Fang Yuan did not answer her, he kept the dimmed pearl into his pocket and continued on his journey.

The two continued to advance, as the poison fog in the air became thicker, the thick purple color fog started to affect their vision.

The two had to stop more frequently, using Gu worms to eliminate the poison in them.

Crack...

A crisp sound came from the below their feet, like they had stepped on some twigs.

Ge Yao directed her gaze over in suspicion, before screaming and jumping back like a rabbit.

"Wh... why is there a human skull here?" She said with a trembling voice.

"Because this is a battlefield." Fang Yuan walked ahead of her, not turning back but instead walking even faster.

"Battlefield? Hey, wait for me, don't go so fast!" Ge Yao quickly followed after Fang Yuan.

The more she walked, the more shocked she was.

Before, the thick purple fog was covering her vision, but now that she got close, she could see many skeletons on the rotting grassland, skeletons of both humans and wolves.

There were deep pits and trenches in the ground, evidently, a fierce battle had taken place here.

"So many people died, who engaged in such a brawl here? But the trenches and pits have already been outgrown by poisonous grass, looking at the other traces, this battle took place at least twenty years ago."

Ge Yao was behind Fang Yuan, seeing him search continuously, like he was trying to find something, she understood.

"So Chang Shan Yin's purpose for entering this poison grassland is this battlefield. What is he looking for? Wait, twenty years ago, in the poison grassland, there was indeed a huge battle. Father had spoken with someone about this, I was beside him at that time..."

A memory surfaced deep in Ge Yao's mind.

Back then, Ge Yao was still young, she was only four or five years old. Her father invited an esteemed guest, and brought her along with him.

In the tent, the adults were talking about the heroes in the grassland.

"Speaking of which, Chang tribe has an amazing person!"

"You mean the Wolf King?"

"That's right, this person is an enslavement path Gu Master heavily nurtured by Chang tribe, he moved like the wind and attacked like the rain, he could alter his battle formations as he wished, he has great abilities. Most importantly, he is a righteous figure, he is extremely filial to his mother. This time, because his mother was poisoned by a unique poison, it can only be cured by the snow wash Gu inside the spiraea. He ignored all opposition and ventured into poison grassland alone."

"Sigh, that is exactly why Wolf King died."

"Yes, this matter was a huge scheme from start to end. Wolf King's enemy Ha Tu Gu planned this. Ha Tu Gu wanted to kill Wolf King, but he was not to be trifled with, killing all of the bandits with Ha Tu Gu and eliminated a huge pest for the grassland."

"But it is a pity for this hero, Wolf King Chang Shan Yin, he lost his life at poison grassland."

　　...

"Chang Shan Yin? You are Wolf King Chang Shan Yin!" Thinking of this, Ge Yao opened her mouth, staring at Fang Yuan fixatedly.

"Oh? You know about Chang Shan Yin too?" Fang Yuan replied lightly as he continued searching.

But Ge Yao quickly shook her head: "No, no way. Looking at his age, by now, if Chang Shan Yin is alive, he should be at least forty years old. How can he be as young as you. Furthermore, your appearance and accent are completely different. You are not Chang Shan Yin!"

"Hehehe, if I am not Chang Shan Yin, who am I?"

"Oh right, who are you? Why are you impersonating a dead Gu Master?" Ge Yao's mind was full of questions.

Suddenly, her eyes brightened up: "Wait! Although after Chang Shan Yin died, his mother also died of poison. But he was already married and had kids. His son is already grown up, and is quite a talented person. Don't tell me... you are Chang Shan Yin's son?"

Fang Yuan laughed, just as he was about to answer, he heard a strange sound near his ears.

This sound was like old wheels rolling on the ground.

Following this sound, a large white bone wheel appeared in the purple fog.

It was as tall as two men, 1.5m in width, its body was made of white bones. On the surface of the carriage, sharp bone spikes were protruding out. At the spoke of the wheel, there was a large skull. The skull's horrific eye sockets were burning with blood-red flames.

"Careful, this is Ha Tu Gu's rank five Gu — Battle Bone Wheel!"

Fang Yuan had just warned, when the wheel accelerated, crushing over with an imposing aura.

Golden dragon Gu!

Fang Yuan pushed with his hand, and the dragon roared, smashing on the wheel.

The wheel vibrated, easily smashing the golden dragon to bits and continued to attack Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan quickly spread his bone wings and flew into the sky.

But the wheel also lifted off from the ground, flying into the air.

Golden coat Gu!

Fang Yuan knew he could not dodge and decided to face it head on.

Bam, he was sent flying, landing on the ground, causing his body to be covered in rotten grass.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!

Three spiral water arrows shot the wheel consecutively.

The white bone wheel landed on the ground, causing mud to splash. It gave up on Fang Yuan, turning its target to Ge Yao, rolling over.

Ge Yao quickly activated the water trace Gu, summoning her water armor and dodging while attacking back.

Fang Yuan also arrived quickly and started to assist her.

This was a tough fight.

The opponent was a rank five Gu, it was Ha Tu Gu's core Gu. After Ha Tu Gu died, it became a wild Gu, and ate white bones as food.

White bone wheel's attack was fierce, it often crushed its opponents into meat paste.

Fang Yuan was suppressed, and his battle strength was lowered, he also did not bring a rank five Gu, he could not face the white bone wheel directly.

His original plan was to avoid the white bone wheel and find Chang Shan Yin's corpse.

But with Ge Yao to assist him, he changed his plans and decided to battle.

After fighting for four hours, using the kiting tactic devised by Fang Yuan, the two bullied the white bone wheel's lack of intelligence, taking breaks in turns and eventually caused the white bone wheel to fall over.

Once the battle was decided, Fang Yuan placed both hands on the white bone wheel, sending his will and primeval essence into it.

White bone wheel was a rank five Gu, even if he had the rank six Spring Autumn Cicada and fixed immortal travel Gu, they could not help him to instantly refine it.

But the wheel was full of cracks, it was almost going to break apart, it was a step away from being destroyed. With Fang Yuan's hundred man soul, he had ample mental energy and with his firm will, he continuously injected primeval essence into it, after spending fifteen minutes, he finally subdued it.

Rank five Gu obtained!

Chapter 431: Chang Shan Yin’s death

Fang Yuan's mind entered his aperture.

After the white bone wheel entered his aperture, it floated along the waves of his true gold primeval sea, half sinking and half floating, showing a lifeless appearance.

Gu worms naturally get hurt, damaged, or even die.

"This white bone wheel is already on the verge of destruction and can no longer be used, unless I can find the bone bamboo Gu and combine it with the ghost fire Gu to repair it." Fang Yuan thought in his heart.

There are many healing Gu which are not intended for human bodies.

Some Gu, such as wolf smoke Gu, are specifically used to treat the injuries of wolves, while other Gu, like pig iron Gu are used to treat chainsaw golden centipede.

Bone bamboo Gu, combined with ghost fire Gu, can repair the damage of the white bone wheel, so that it can function again.

"Speaking of the battle bone wheel Gu, it's actually quite famous, since it was used by the rank eight Demonic Gu Immortal Shen Jie Ao. He was also known as the Proud Bone Demon Lord. His talent was outstanding and shocking. When he became a rank six Gu Immortal, he lacked a rank six Gu. He came up with a killer move known as White Bone Chariot. The white bone chariot consisted of many rank five Gu, such as the white bone wheel, and had power comparable to a rank six Gu!

"By the virtue of his ingenuity, Shen Jie Ao reached rank eight realm, and made his killer move 'White Bone Battlefield' famous in the world; it was a killer move that combined three Immortal Gu's power, it was even more powerful than before. He used this to dominate the world, killing an uncountable number of Gu Immortals, his fierce name spread wide as he caused the righteous path to be helpless. Sigh, when can I reach such a stage?"

In his past life, Fang Yuan lived for about five hundred years, and became a rank six Gu Immortal, one step away from rank seven. When he later refined the Spring Autumn Cicada, he was attacked by the righteous path and consequently self-detonated.

Every time he thought about Blood Sea Ancestor, Proud Bone Demon Lord, Soul Specter Demon Venerable, all of them were amazing characters, Fang Yuan could not help but be impressed.

"As a man living in present age, I should be like this, unrestrained by the mortal realm, doing things without worry, killing whoever I dislike. When my heart is evil, I slaughter all beings, and when I am virtuous, I bless the world. The world moves according to my emotions, I dominate everything, any enemy who resists me are trampled underfoot. Oh, this is a true freedom, a cheerful and carefree life!"

Fang Yuan let out a heartfelt sigh and took out a bright pearl Gu from his pocket.

Bright pearl Gu was already dusty, its light was dim. Sealed inside was fixed immortal travel, the aura of the Immortal Gu was also fading.

Fang Yuan took out the dark toss Gu.

This Gu and dusty Gu looked almost the same, a silkworm cocoon like shape, except it was deep black in color.

Fang Yuan transferred his primeval essence, the black silkworm cocoon wiggled up, ten tendrils twisted out, twisting like snakes, and climbed on the bright pearl Gu.

In just a short moment, the bright pearl Gu was enveloped by a black silkworm cocoon.

This was known as "tossing pearls in the dark", it was developed during the battle of the five regions, to completely conceal the aura of Gu worms.

Because of this, fixed immortal travel's aura was even fainter now.

"Warrior Chang Shan Yin, you are trying to seal this beautiful jade butterfly?" Ge Yao stood to the side and gradually understood Fang Yuan's intention.

Fang Yuan gave her a mysterious smile and kept the dark pearl into his pocket and continued to be buried in his research of the battlefield.

This battlefield was created twenty years ago, after the battle between Chang Shan Yin and Ha Tu Gu.

Chang Shan Yin was a rank four peak stage Gu Master, while Ha Tu Gu was already a rank five initial stage Gu Master who also lead a large band of subordinates.

The two were originally childhood friends, but they fell in love with the same woman. The woman ultimately chose Chang Shan Yin, and from then on Ha Tu Gu became filled with a jealous rage. This led to an unceasing hostility growing between the two of them, a hatred that could only be washed away with the blood of the other.

After Ha Tu Gu poisoned Chang Shan Yin's mother, in order to find the snow wash Gu, he lead the wolf packs deep into the poisonous plains.

When he reached the plains, Chang Shan Yin set up an ambush there. When Ha Tu Gu brought his gang of bandits and came, as large groups of wolves attacked from all directions.

This was a bitter fight to the death, until the sun went down.

Eventually, the wolves were all killed, along with all the horse bandits, who were either killed or fled. Chang Shan Yin was at his limits, and Ha Tu Gu's primeval essence was exhausted. The two resorted to fighting with their bare hands.

Both men fought till their eyes turned red and made use of everything in their surroundings to gain the advantage.

They wrestled together, biting with their teeth, clawing with their hands, until they finally expended all their strength, and collapsed to the ground, with barely enough strength to breathe.

The life and death enemies, once incomparably close friends, were only two or three steps away from each other, but all they could do was gasp for air and stare at each other.

They were powerful Gu Masters, one a righteous hero, the other a demonic devil, yet both had lost their strength. At this moment, both were as fragile as a child, if a rabbit came running and blocked their face, they would suffocate to death.

They were at a deadlock, when suddenly Ha Tu Gu suddenly burst into hearty laugh. He was, after all, a rank five Gu Master, and his primeval essence recovery rate was quicker compared to Chang Shan Yin's.

His primeval essence recovered first, enough for him to cast a poisonous bone spear.

Seeing the bone spear being shot towards him, Chang Shan Yin's eyes widened, as a miracle burst of strength emerged in him.

Using all his strength, he managed to turn half his body, but the poisonous bone spear, which had been aimed at his head, still pierced his chest.

The intensity of the pain made Chang Shan Yin roar, but by relying on the wolf strength Gu to increase his strength, he managed to break the bone spear and clutched it tightly in his hand. Slowly, he dragged his body towards Ha Tu Gu's side.

In the end, Chang Shan Yin took the poisonous bone spear and stabbed it into the eyes of Ha Tu Gu, ending the life of his mortal enemy.

Although Chang Shan Yin had won, the poison of the bone spear had already spread throughout his whole body.

By utilizing all the primeval essence that he had just recovered, he activated the wolf fetus burial Gu.

This Gu utilized a hundred and eight different species of pregnant female wolves, and its specialty was to save a life. If long as they had one breath left, the user could be saved.

Chang Shan Yin used the Gu, drilled into the ground, and fell asleep.

About thirty years later, a rank three Gu Master, Ma Hong Yun, was chased to the battlefield by a pack of wolves. In his desperation, he coincidentally managed to find the buried Chang Shan Yin.

After Ma Hong Yun saved Chang Shan Yin, the latter not only helped him repel the wolves, but also helped him become one of the four great generals. In the future struggle for power in the grassland, Chang Shan Yin contributed countless merits, and Ma Hong Yun who was born as a slave became the lord of the imperial court.

Chang Shan Yin experience both ups and downs of life, his tale was quite legendary. His story spread widely throughout the north, it was no secret.

Later, with the aid of Ma Hong Yun, he became a rank seven Gu Immortal, receiving the title of "Sky Wolf General", gaining even greater authority.

Ultimately, while resisting the invasion of the Central Continent, he died in battle, and his descendants passed down his biography — this is also why Fang Yuan was so knowledgeable about his history.

"Hmm? I found it!"

His long search had finally come to an end.

Fang Yuan stepped forward and found a huge wolf tail on the grass.

The wolf tail, covered with mud, was covered by poisonous grass and could hardly be seen. If it wasn't for Fang Yuan's persistence and careful search, it would have been impossible to find.

"Originally, while Ma Hong Yun was escaping, he tripped on this wolf tail. When he pulled on the wolf tail, he saved not only Chang Shan Yin, but also himself."

Fang Yuan was feeling overwhelmed by emotions, he grabbed the wolf tail and forcibly pulled it out.

Suddenly, the land writhed, and a huge female wolf's body appeared out of the ground, its eyes were closed, the whole body covered in purple fur, with a white belly.

It was humongous; even while it was lying down, it was taller than a person.

Ge Yao hurriedly ran over, her face flushed with surprise: "What wolf is this, why is it so big? Ah, it looks like a female wolf, look at its belly, it must be pregnant!"

"It's not a wolf, it's a Gu." Fang Yuan said, taking out a sharp knife from moving perspective cup Gu.

He sliced open the belly of the wolf, causing a long gash to appear.

Immediately, the wolf's bulging belly was torn open, and a large amount of amniotic fluid, mixed with blood, spewed all over the ground; the lower part of Fang Yuan's body was soaked.

Ge Yao saw what was happening, and hurriedly jumped out of the way to avoid becoming a victim of the filth.

She then widened her mouth in surprise, crying out, "Why is there a man inside the wolf's womb?"

As the amniotic fluid continued to flow out, a person also came out. It was the true Chang Shan Yin!

His eyes were closed, and his body was full of injuries, especially the part with the half-bone spear sticking out. He was covered in thick amniotic fluids, his expression showing great pain, and his skin was green.

Fang Yuan quickly squatted down and extended his hands. It looked like he was observing the injuries of Chang Shan Yin, but in fact, he secretly pinched the neck of Chang Shan Yin.

Poor Chang Shan Yin, a hero who succeeded in killing his enemy, and lived for another twenty years using his Gu worm. After another ten years or so, his fated lord appeared and saved him. But now that Fang Yuan had stepped in, the future of this man, the famous 'Sky Wolf General' and the future rank seven Gu Immortal was killed.

Chang Shan Yin died while he was unconscious, unable to resist, letting out only a faint breath.

When Fang Yuan killed him, his body did not even tremble. Needless to say, since he was unconscious, he could not self-detonate his Gu worms.

Fang Yuan's mind entered his aperture and immediately found several tortoise breath Gu inside.

Tortoise breath Gu was a storage Gu, like the bright pearl Gu, it was used to seal Gu worms.

Before Chang Shan Yin entered the belly of the wolf, to prevent his Gu worms from starving to death, he seal his Gu worms one by one in the tortoise breath Gu.

They were rank four Gu, shaped like oval stones, and were slightly larger in size than a fist. The surface of the stones was covered with markings, similar to that of a tortoise shell.

By leaking the aura of the Spring Autumn Cicada, Fang Yuan instantly refined these tortoise breath Gu.

He took all the tortoises out, and under the watchful eyes of Ge Yao, he crushed them all one by one to reveal the Gu inside.

There were a total of eight Gu from the enslavement path, all of which were precious rank four Gu worms. Some of them were even more precious than ordinary rank five Gu. Chang Shan Yin meticulously arranged this collection, and with this set of Gu, he made a reputation for himself in northern plains. Using this set of Gu, he killed rank five Gu Masters before.

And with the help of Spring Autumn Cicada, all of them became Fang Yuan's possession.

"And now, I finally have an excellent set of rank four Gu from northern plains!" The corner of his mouth curled into a faint smile.

Chapter 432: Human Skin Gu

But merely retrieving the Gu worms was not the whole purpose of Fang Yuan's journey.

After placing all of the Gu worms into his aperture, he turned his attention to Chang Shan Yin's corpse.

He started using Gu worms, helping the body to detoxify.

"Isn't he already dead?" Ge Yao asked by his side, looking confused. Detoxifying a living person made sense, but what was the point of detoxifying a corpse?

Fang Yuan did not bother turning to answer her, but told her: "Stop looking, use your cleansing Gu and help."

Fang Yuan and Ge Yao worked in turns; gradually, Shang Chan Yin's corpse was losing its toxicity.

"Don't tell me... is he Chang Shan Yin? He's your father?" Ge Yao had a sudden realization, and sent a look of inquiry towards Fang Yuan, "No, Chang Shan Yin's son is a native of northern plains. Looking at your appearance, you're obviously a foreigner."

Fang Yuan let out a cold grunt, saying expressionlessly: "I told you, I am Chang Shan Yin."

As the toxins in his body were purged, the surface of Chang Shan Yin's skin gradually returned to it's natural complexion, losing the wretched green color that came as a result of the poison.

Fang Yuan, upon seeing that the cleansing was almost complete, asked the girl to step back. He stripped Chang Shan Yin of his clothes, and rinsed them with water.

"You... you want to bring his body back?" Ge Yao surmised.

However, Fang Yuan's following actions immediately overturned her conjecture.

She saw Fang Yuan retrieve a regiment of black ants from his aperture.

Fang Yuan injected his primeval essence, and the black ants immediately rushed towards Chang Shan Yin's pale and naked corpse and began to consume it.

The black ants crawled all over Chang Shan Yin, swallowing all of his skin into their stomach, turning the corpse into a mess of fleshy tendons, and leaving the body beyond recognition.

Ge Yao saw what was happening, and resisted the urge to vomit.

Fang Yuan collected the ants once they were done, took out a seed, and planted it into the ground.

As he poured his primeval essence, the seed began to grow at a visible rate: rooting, germinating, and blooming into a beautiful flower.

The flower was in full bloom, yet it was quite strange in that it appeared as if it was covered in a membrane of skin, like the inner flesh of a mouth. The inner petals also had a row of tiny jagged sawtooth.

The black ants converged into a group, climbing up the flower, and entered the core of the flower.

The flower then closed again, its jagged teeth whirling wildly, as the teeth rubbed against each other, it made a humming sound, and made the whole flower tremble.

Fang Yuan took out another Gu worm, which Ge Yao failed to recognize. The Gu turned into a multi-colored blaze, and attached itself to the top of the flower.

The flower twisted wildly while it burned in the flame, giving off a sharp shriek.

The shriek of the flower was so sharp that it forced Ge Yao to cover her ears and move backwards several more steps.

At this point, the girl realized that something was amiss, this strange method reeked of the demonic path. Ge Yao's complexion paled, and when she looked at Fang Yuan, she saw that his face had not changed, standing on the spot, both his eyes were shining as he paid attention to the flower.

"Open." Suddenly, both of Fang Yuan's eyes emitted an explosion of light as he shouted loudly.

The corolla of the flower opened up a small slit, allowing the multi-colored flame to enter. Afterwards, the whole flower suddenly exploded and a Gu worm flew out.

The Gu Worm had a multi-colored tint, constantly transforming; occasionally yellow-green, and occasionally blood-violet. Like a smokey fog that was rising upwards.

"Human skin Gu, the refinement has finally been completed." Fang Yuan, upon seeing it, let out a sigh of relief. Next, he willed, retrieving an old removal Gu from his aperture, as it turned into a cooling breeze.

The breeze flew out of the aperture, flowing all over Fang Yuan's body, permeating his skin, tendons, and bones.

Fang Yuan had originally used three Gu; ancient bronze skin, essence iron bones, and golden steel tendons, to modify his body, and now it was all washed away.

Then, from the moving perspective cup Gu, he took out a sharp dagger.

"The following scene is going to be a bit bloody, you should close your eyes." With his hand clutching the dagger, he gave his warning to Ge Yao.

Ge Yao hurriedly took a breath, looking at Fang Yuan in confusion, unable to speak a word.

Then at the next moment, the girl's pupils shrank, both of her hands covered her mouth, unable to suppress her alarmed yelp.

Under her horrified gaze, Fang Yuan pointed the dagger to his chest and softly sliced it.

Swish!

He had cut from himself from the neck down to his abdomen.

Yet strangely enough, his blood did not flow out, he had prepared a staunch bleeding Gu in advance.

After that, Fang Yuan expressionlessly slit the dagger along the middle of his body, then he stretched out his hand and ripped the skin off of his chest.

The girl, upon seeing this horrifically violent scene, could not help but repeatedly step backwards again, her entire face had turned pale like paper.

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth to endure the pain, and under the urging of his mind, the colorful smoke that was in floating in midair covered his whole chest.

Sizzle...

In the midst of the strange sound, Fang Yuan's bare and bloody chest was covered by a new layer of skin.

The peculiarity of it was, although the skin had just grown, it did not have the expected baby-like tenderness; instead it had the pale solidity of old skin.

Then, Fang Yuan repeated the process, peeling the skin of his arms and his legs, completely removing them, to grow a new layer of skin.

"This, don't tell me..." Ge Yao could gradually see what was happening, and was flabbergasted.

When he was peeling the skin of his back, Fang Yuan was somewhat troubled, but under his strenuous effort, he managed to succeed.

Eventually, it was time for the most critical part, the face.

Fang Yuan stop for a moment, taking a quick rest, then, lifting up his dagger, he aimed at the tip at his eyelid.

Ge Yao watched with her whole body trembling, yet Fang Yuan's hands were steady like they were cast iron, each of his actions were precise and minute. He first cut his eyelids off, followed by his eye sockets, the knife tip curved out and reached his ear, and moved from his cheek to his chin.

Turning around at his chin, he did the same to the other side, and ended up completing a circle.

Next, Ge Yao saw Fang Yuan removing his own face; her heart pounded furiously, and her legs felt weak.

The colorful smoke then flew over again, and grew a new layer of skin.

Subsequently, Fang Yuan did the same to the skin on his neck, ears, and scalp.

When he turned his face to look at Ge Yao, he had already changed into a new person, sporting the appearance of Chang Shan Yin.

"I told you, I am Chang Shan Yin." He said in a bland tone.

Ge Yao looked at Fang Yuan in disbelief, he had actually spoken in a perfect northern plains accent.

Of course Fang Yuan could speak in the northern accent, he just chose not to earlier.

"You, you!" Her finger was pointed at Fang Yuan, her body trembled violently, her face had turned pale, and her expression was filled with horror.

Fang Yuan laughed in disdain internally: the human body is merely a sack of flesh, I was just changing the sack, what was the point of making such a fuss? The so-called beauty and ugly are superficially and weak things. If this is Earth, people have no powers and the immortal path is cut, then so be it. But in this world, only eternal life is worth pursuing!

This human skin gu, hundred of years later, it would be developed by Gu Masters during the five region chaotic battle. It could be used by Gu Masters to cleverly disguise themselves as another person, with their face being identical.

Many of central continent's Gu Masters, using human skin Gu, were able to penetrate deep into enemy headquarters. Allowing for secret assassinations and mass destruction, it had greatly augmented the military power of the central continent, making the four other regions panic and doubt each other.

Not paying any attention to the pretty lady who was scared out of her wits, Fang Yuan stood where he was and brought his hands to eye level to observe them.

By now, his hands had completely changed.

His fingerprints and palm prints were exactly the same as Chang Shan Yin's.

Next, he felt his chest.

His chest was originally smooth and flat, but now it sported chest hair that extended downwards from his throat to his crotch.

He felt his own nose, a northern man's stiff nose, then he felt his rough cheeks. He took out a mirror and observed his features, his face had already become that of Chang Shan Yin, going to the extent that he had begun to grow hair in the same style. Even the grey hair that came with old age were completely replicated.

Human skin Gu, it referred to the fact that human skin was the main ingredient of the Gu worm. In addition, the transformation was a complete transformation. Not just skin, but hair, eye color, the shape of his bones, and even old injuries were completely replicated

　　...

Ge Yao looked at Fang Yuan, it felt like a dead man had just resurrected.

"You, who the hell are you?" She stared at Fang Yuan, full of vigilance and alertness.

Fang Yuan gave her a smile, saying gently: "I told you, I am Chang Shan Yin."

"Do you think I'm a fool? Just a moment ago, I saw the whole thing, I saw it first-hand till the end. Also, you are an outsider, stop using our northern accent to speak!" The girl shrieked, her expression looked almost deranged.

Fang Yuan looked at her with a considerate gaze, his face showing great wisdom that came with age, he let out a sigh filled with great emotion: "Little lady, rest assured, I mean you no harm, I am Chang Shan Yin, from the beginning to the end, I did not lie to you."

"So, so how do you explain what just happened?" The young girl asked.

Fang Yuan's eyes glanced upwards, ignoring the girl, and looked at the sky, his expression was in daze as he spoke in a reminiscent tone: "Little lady, have you ever heard of soul seizure?"

"Soul seizure?" Ge Yao had a blank look, her eyes flickered with confusion, and her tone was uncertain, "You mean, when a body is taken over by another soul?"

Fang Yuan slowly and gently explained: "It seems you have heard about it before. Yes, you're right, I was on the verge of death, with no one to rescue me, so I had no choice but to escape with my soul. In poison grassland, it is cloudy all year round, and the sun isn't visible, which allowed my soul to wander freely. I wandered for a whole twenty years, until I was able to seize the body of a foreign Gu Master. While I teleported back with my Gu worm, I met you coincidentally."

"Really? Is what you are saying really true?"

"Hehehe, if I meant you harm, I would have killed you long ago, there would have been no reason to allow you to accompany me here, or even teaching you how to battle right?."

"That's true but..."

"If I wanted to guard against you, I wouldn't have let you witness these things. You are a northern plains native, and I am the great Chang Shan Yin, I wouldn't do despicable things to a girl such as yourself. Why was it that I only managed to seize a body after twenty years? It was because I did not want to slaughter a northern plains native for my own selfish reasons. Little lady, will you attack me because of an outsider?" Fang Yuan's smile was bright as the sun, speaking in a righteous tone.

Chapter 433: Snow Wash Gu

Ge Yao gradually let her guard down: "Your words are reasonable. If you truly are Chang Shan Yin, then you would be the great hero of our northern plains! For a mere outsider, I definitely wouldn't make things difficult for you. Yet how can you prove your identity?"

Fang Yuan chuckled and his expression changed, revealing a trace of the arrogance that belonged to a senior expert: "I, Chang Shan Yin, will neither change my name or surname, I am me, why would I need to prove myself? Little girl, if you want to leave now, I will definitely not stop you."

Fang Yuan's statement of allowing her to leave succeeded in shaking Ge Yao's doubts, creating enormous hesitation in her heart.

Fang Yuan did not miss this chance: "Little girl, it's alright to be on guard, but just think, how many opportunities did I have to kill you on the way? There is no need to mention anything else, just think of the time we spent flying. I just had to release my hands and you would have fallen into the earth spike rat group, your death would have been certain. But didn't I do that? Our meeting was fated; since you had the courage to flee your marriage, why don't you have courage to face me?"

Ge Yao fell into silence.

Fang Yuan observed her expression and knew the time was ripe, finishing off his explanation: "Come with me, you are still young, it is not safe for you to wander around the depths of poison grassland alone. Didn't you tell me you were searching for the snow spirea? You want to find a snow wash Gu in the snow spirea, and bring it back to the clan to earn great merit, allowing you to cancel your marriage, correct? Honestly speaking, that line of thinking isn't realistic; one or two snow wash Gu won't change your situation."

"It just so happens I also need a snow wash Gu. I will bring you along to search for the snow spirea and capture a few snow wash Gu, then I will take you back to your tribe and personally persuade your father. What do you think?"

"Really?" Ge Yao's eyes immediately shone brightly: "I remember that father idolizes you, saying that you were a great hero. Father will definitely listen to you. But what do you still need the snow wash Gu for? Your mother has already passed away..."

"Sigh!" Fang Yuan's voice was melancholic, his expression lonely; he lowered his head before smiling bitterly, "I already know my mother passed away due to poison over twenty years ago. I could not find the snow wash Gu and return in time, I was unfilial. Do you know, since then, snow wash Gu had already become my obsession? I must definitely capture one and kneel in front of my mother's tomb to repent."

Tears fell down Fang Yuan's cheeks as he spoke of this.

The girl looked at Fang Yuan's tears and was thoroughly convinced by Fang Yuan's lies. Her heart ached and consoled: "Senior Chang Shan Yin, this is not your fault. Everything was because of that damned Ha Tu Gu!"

"Don't speak anymore, let's go." Fang Yuan waved his hand and walked forward.

"I am sorry, I was wrong. I should not have doubted you." Ge Yao felt a twinge of guilt, immediately following behind Fang Yuan to apologize.

Fang Yuan consoled the girl, causing her inner guilt to become even heavier.

The two continued to walk to the depths of poison grassland; the purple fog continued to become denser and even poison resistant wild beasts like poison beard wolves rarely appeared.

After walking two to three hundred li, Fang Yuan and Ge Yao had no choice but to use their Gu to detoxify themselves. After walking another five to six hundred li, the poisonous purple fog became so dense that they could not even see their own hands.

Ge Yao's fog sparrow Gu had already lost its use in such a situation. However, Fang Yuan was already prepared and could still scout the distance of a thousand steps.

"Senior Chang Shan Yin, we should return. We can still go in another direction, maybe we can find the snow spirea there. If we go any deeper, I'm afraid..." Ge Yao's face was suffused with a purple color, she had already reached the point where she could endure no more.

But Fang Yuan shook his head and refused to accept her suggestion, persisting on moving forward.

The girl did not understand, but Fang Yuan was understood that snow spirea grew in very poisonous environments.

And this poisonous grassland also had a lot of history.

In the deepest part of poison grassland, there was a blessed land where rank the seven Gu Immortal Zi Yan Ran, titled Lady Poison Scorpion, resided.

An uncountable number of poisonous grass grew on her Zi Du blessed land with many large poisonous swamps and marshes. Large amounts of poisonous beasts and poisonous Gu lived on her blessed land.

The toxins of these poisonous beings accumulated to such an intensity that even the blessed land could not endure it.

Thus, every few years, the blessed land's entrance would open to release the dense toxic gas outside.

Most of the toxic gas formed into the purple poison fog in the poisonous grassland.

Some creatures at the lowest rung of the blessed land also took this chance to sneak out. Thus, there were large numbers of poison beard wolves in the poisonous grassland.

After a long period of this cycle, a complete change occurred to the surroundings of Zi Du blessed land. Dark clouds covered the surroundings all year round, creating a world devoid of light. Purple fog lingered and tormented all living beings. Large numbers of poisonous grass grew, and the poison beard wolves rampaged around outskirts of the poisoned lands. The grassland had become a forbidden zone for living beings and was named the poisonous grassland by the mortals out of fear.

Zi Du blessed land was at the center of the poisonous grassland, and the place Fang Yuan was currently at was around the center.

In the depths of the grassland, dense poisonous fog lingered all year round, encouraging the growth of a large number of snow spirea. Fang Yuan knew if he persevered in moving forward a little longer, he would definitely see the snow spirea.

Sure enough, as he had expected, after walking forward another few hundred steps, Fang Yuan discovered a snow spirea.

The snow spirea was twenty feet tall; it had numerous branches and leaves on a pitch black trunk, contrasted by the countless drooping spirea branches that were pure white. Within the dense purple fog, it appeared sacred and noble.

Fang Yuan walked to the snow spirea with Ge Yao, who immediately let out a shout of joy.

The two began to carefully observe the snow-white leaves on the spirea branches.

Soon enough, Ge Yao discovered one leaf that had already turned into a Gu.

It was a snow wash Gu, an invaluable rank four Gu. Snow wash Gu's detoxification ability was extraordinary, widely acknowledged by the northern plains' Gu Masters.

The two searched for a long while and found three snow wash Gu.

Fang Yuan only took one and gave the other two to Ge Yao, causing the girl to inwardly feel grateful.

After he acquired the snow wash Gu, Fang Yuan took out a dark pearl.

The Immortal Gu, fixed immortal travel, was sealed inside, and at that moment, it quietly let out a slight amount of it's immortal aura. If this aura persisted, it would easily be discovered by Gu Immortals.

"It is time." Fang Yuan willed and summoned a Gu from his aperture.

He poured his primeval essence towards the Gu at once, turning the Gu into a red iron cabinet, which then firmly sealed the dark pearl.

Immediately, the Immortal Gu aura was cut without the slightest bit leaking out.

This was the Gu worm Fang Yuan captured on San Cha mountain, unique to Tie clan - iron cabinet Gu.

Fang Yuan carried the iron cabinet on his back and walked back the way they came with Ge Yao.

After walking around two to three hundred li, Fang Yuan stopped and took out earth treasury flower king Gu, stored the iron cabinet in its stamen, then planted it deep under the ground.

This Gu was a rank five Gu and Fang Yuan had to spend quite some effort to plant it. His primeval essence was not enough, thus for a period, he had to pour primeval essence slowly while he absorbed primeval stones.

It took him whole four hours before he finished.

At Qing Mao mountain, Fang Yuan had obtained Flower Wine Monk's inheritance. The Flower Wine Monk had hidden his Gu worms into earth treasury flower Gu.

Earth treasury flower Gu was only a rank two Gu, and only after it advanced again and again, could it become a rank five earth treasury flower king.

When earth treasury flower king bloomed open, it was ten times larger than earth treasury flower. It had huge dark golden petals that were as soft as silk and in the depths of its stamen was dark golden floral liquid.

However, when earth treasury flower king closed shut, its whole size was smaller than an infant's fist.

It completely curled up in the depths of the ground, not leaking out the slightest bit of aura.

After planting the earth treasury flower king, Fang Yuan carefully destroyed all traces of it on the ground. At this moment, he had genuinely and completely hidden the Immortal Gu fixed immortal travel.

Fang Yuan's aperture could not store fixed immortal travel. He could only use this method to hide the Immortal Gu and retrieve it in the future.

In such a vast grassland, who would think an extremely precious Immortal Gu was buried here?

Yet the aura of the Immortal Gu had still been a problem. Its aura would persist for a long while and attract Gu Immortals.

Thus, Fang Yuan had intermittently sealed the Immortal Gu when he buried it; it was to guard against a Gu Immortal's search.

"Unless, the Gu Immortals that come possess an investigative Immortal Gu, capable of seeing through the ground and scouting hundreds of li deep into the ground, the possibility of its discovery is slim."

If fixed immortal travel Gu was truly discovered by some Gu Immortal and taken, Fang Yuan could only attribute it to his bad luck.

However, even if that happened, he would absolutely not bring fixed immortal travel with him. Compared to the Immortal Gu, he felt his own life was more precious.

The two continued moving through the grassland and returned to that battlefield.

When they reached the place, Fang Yuan looked for another direction and did not move along their original way, using Ge Yao's return heart Gu to point the direction.

The return trip was not smooth, Fang Yuan and Ge Yao encountered the attacks of wolf groups' time and again.

They even encountered thousand wolf groups three or four times; Fang Yuan could only grab Ge Yao and fly to the sky to avoid this calamity.

As the two got closer to the outer edge of poison grassland, the number of wolves and difficulty they encountered decreased.

　　...

About a hundred poison beard wolves pounced upon Fang Yuan and Ge Yao.

Fang Yuan laughed brightly, he was happy instead of shocked as he flew to the air and pointed down.

"Wolf enslavement Gu, go!"

A rank two wolf enslavement Gu turned into a lump of blue smoke and descended, enshrouding the hundred beast wolf king.

The hundred beast wolf king struggled intensely, its soul resisting strongly. But in front of Fang Yuan's hundred man soul, it failed utterly.

"Howl, howl."

When Fang Yuan landed on the ground, the hundred beast wolf king ran around Fang Yuan's feet with its tail swaying like a little puppy.

The wolf group it brought also remained motionless under its command, becoming Fang Yuan's minions.

This was already the second wolf group Fang Yuan had subdued.

As they continued, Fang Yuan's strength became stronger, the wolf group around him growing larger.

Their trip of death before had unknowingly become a leisurely outing.

When the wolf group following Fang Yuan increased to a thousand wolves, with four hundred beast wolf kings, poison grassland was no longer scary.

With this safety, Fang Yuan began to settle the Gu worms from southern border.

Northern plains natives were xenophobic; his original appearance would have made him suffer exclusion and vigilance wherever he walked, making it difficult for him to do things, and the southern border Gu worms were also enormous flaws which could expose his identity.

The innately cautious Fang Yuan would not allow these gaps to exist.

All the Gu worms on him that were not from northern plains must be dealt with.

Chapter 434: Chang Shan Yin, be my husband!

The wide and huge poison grassland became even darker at night.

Wind blew near the ears as the howling of wolves could be heard, resembling the cries of wandering spirits.

A fire was burning silently on the grassland.

Ge Yao got close to the fire, expelling the chill in her body.

There was a pot on top of the fire, and a meat soup was cooking in it, emitting a fragrant smell.

Ge Yao swallowed her saliva as her hunger intensified. Eventually, she gulped and asked Fang Yuan: "Senior Chang Shan Yin, can this meat soup be eaten already?"

Fang Yuan sat opposite the young girl, the two were separated by the fire.

"No rush, this dried meat has just entered the pot, it needs to cook to a boil. Wait a while more, when the meat is soft and juicy, it will be extremely delicious." Fang Yuan took out the moving perspective cup Gu as he said plainly.

"Oh, we still have to wait so long." Ge Yao pouted, her beautiful face was shining in the flame, together with her long robe exclusive to northern plains and her beautiful accessories, it showed a unique style.

But such a tranquil scene was not enough for Fang Yuan to take a second look.

His gaze was on the moving perspective cup Gu.

Moving perspective cup Gu was a rank five Gu, now that it was in northern plains, it was suppressed to rank four. Speaking of capacity, it was weaker than other rank four Gu. It was expensive to feed, one of the most expensive among the rank five Gu worms. It was also extremely heavy on primeval essence consumption. But why did Fang Yuan choose it specifically, expending his energy and resources to refine it?

That is because it originated from Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, he stole from heaven and robbed earth, he was the wealthiest venerable in history.

He spent his entire life's effort to find the rumored legendary space cave.

Space cave was first depicted in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, it was a forbidden ground on the same level as the river of time. In the river of time, there were large numbers of time path Gu worms. Inside the space cave, there were countless space path Gu worms.

It connected the five regions, hidden in a place no one knew. Pushing open a door from inside the space cave, one can reach any place in the world. The door that connected the space cave was also known as the space door. Space door was omnipresent, it could be in a narrow crack, or in the wide and boundless sky. Where there is space, there is a door into space cave.

But from the past until now, very little people could find the space cave, not to mention going inside. In the entire human history, only one person had managed to enter and exit it.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable discovered the recipe of the moving perspective cup Gu, his intention was to send this moving perspective cup Gu into the space cave, and bring out large numbers of wild Gu worms inside it.

But he failed, yet succeeded.

Four hundred years later, his blessed land was excavated, and all sorts of Gu Immortals competed for it. The recipe of the moving perspective cup Gu was also spread as a result, its strong effect quickly caused many Gu Immortals to recommend it, and it became famous throughout the regions.

Fang Yuan took out the golden dragon Gu from his aperture.

The rank four golden dragon Gu was suppressed into a rank three. After it flew out, it entered the moving perspective cup Gu.

Fang Yuan injected large amounts of primeval essence into the moving perspective cup Gu.

This cup with a gold top and silver bottom, immediately gave off a strong golden-silver light, floating in the air.

Fang Yuan pulled back his hand, and pushed the cup slightly forward.

The moving perspective cup Gu moved forward, until it vanished. First, the sides vanished, and then half the cup was gone, finally it vanished in mid air.

Ge Yao stood up abruptly, staring with wide opened eyes as she saw this strange scene.

At the same time, far away in central continent, Hu Immortal blessed land.

Little Hu Immortal suddenly had a feeling, immediately teleporting into Dang Hun palace's secret room.

In the secret room, a moving perspective cup Gu gave off a shining radiance as it floated in the sky. As if it was pulled by an invisible force, it moved forward slowly before vanishing in the air.

When moving perspective cup Gu completely vanished, Fang Yuan stretched out both his palms parallel to the ground as he activated his primeval essence again.

Suddenly, a golden-silver light burst out in his palm.

Immediately after, Ge Yao saw the rim of a cup appearing, gradually growing to become half the cup, and finally,the entire cup appeared from thin air.

When the light faded, the cup-like Gu worms landed in Fang Yuan's palms.

"Done." Fang Yuan muttered, seeing this cup, he knew that his plans did not go out of control.

"Senior Chang Shan Yin, what did you do? Eh, this Gu doesn't seem right." Ge Yao walked a few steps towards Fang Yuan and asked curiously.

"In what way?" Fang Yuan laughed lightly, taking out a primeval stone and recovering his primeval essence quickly.

Ge Yao did not speak, she only stared at moving perspective cup Gu, when suddenly her eyes shone, as she shouted: "This Gu is not the same, originally it was golden top and silver bottom, but now it is silver top and golden bottom."

Fang Yuan laughed.

That's right!

There was not just one moving perspective Gu, there were two.

These two Gu worms, one was golden top and silver bottom, while the other was silver top and golden bottom. The two together, made up the complete moving perspective cup Gu. Before Fang Yuan left, he brought one with him while placing the other in Hu Immortal blessed land.

When he injected his primeval essence, the two moving perspective cup Gu entered the space cave, and swapped positions with each other inside the space cave. The one that was in the blessed land thus came to Fang Yuan. As for the cup that held golden dragon Gu, it returned to Hu Immortal blessed land.

In the past, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable wanted to rely on the moving perspective cup Gu to steal the Gu worms inside space cave. He failed and did not achieve his goal. But the moving perspective cup Gu, in another way, was a great success.

Using the omnipresent space cave, a pair of moving perspective cup Gu could interchange in the space cave and transport resources between two places.

Most importantly, it was rank five, it was not a unique Immortal Gu.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, during the chaotic battle of the five regions, moving perspective cup Gu was a must-have Gu for all factions. Even Gu Immortals competed for it.

Fang Yuan took out a letter from this moving perspective cup Gu.

It was written by little Hu Immortal, stating the current situation in the blessed land.

Fang Yuan had only been in poison grassland for five to six days, but a month had already passed in Hu Immortal blessed land.

The letter stated that other than Dang Hun mountain, everything was going well. Immortal Crane Sect suggested another transaction, but according to Fang Yuan's instructions, little Hu Immortal rejected it.

If they did more transactions, Immortal Crane Sect would have a higher chance of finding out that Fang Yuan was not in the blessed land. Fang Yuan was in northern plains, but he was still concerned with the blessed land. Using the moving perspective cup Gu to exchange letters like this, he could control the situation behind the scenes, and other people's schemes would not succeed.

Fang Yuan sent a letter back after looking at the one he received.

Ge Yao was completely lost, she could not read central continent characters.

Together with this letter, Fang Yuan placed three rank four Gu inside, golden coat Gu, charging crash Gu, and bone wings Gu.

The more things were placed inside, the more primeval essence consumed by the moving perspective cup Gu. In contrast, the distance between the two cups did not matter.

This is because moving perspective cup Gu was created in a special way, it used the mystical forbidden passage of the space cave.

Fang Yuan's earlier attempt was a test run. After making sure that the moving perspective cup Gu was working fine, he started to send all his Gu worms that were from southern border into the blessed land, for little Hu Immortal to take care of them.

In the blessed land, little Hu Immortal sprawled on the table, staring at blank space with her large shining eyes.

The golden dragon Gu in the moving perspective cup Gu was already taken away.

Suddenly, moving perspective cup Gu started floating again, and entered the space cave. Afterwards, another cup appeared and landed on the table.

Little Hu Immortal took out the things inside moving perspective cup Gu, and saw Fang Yuan's reply, extremely elated as she shouted: "Master's reply!"

With just one cycle, the primeval essence in Fang Yuan's aperture were mostly expended.

He had to hold onto a primeval stone and replenish his primeval essence again.

Ge Yao stood at one side, gradually starting to understand. She, who was overwhelmed with curiosity, asked a few more questions again. But Fang Yuan only smiled plainly, not replying her.

"Hmph, acting all mysterious, it's no big deal." The girl pouted, sitting back at her original seat in displeasure.

She sat down, frowning as she stared at Fang Yuan angrily.

Fang Yuan completely ignored her, causing her to be even more angry.

She was doted on by her father since young, she was the beauty of her tribe, no one had ever dared to look down on her. But during this entire journey, Fang Yuan did not give her any attention.

Many youths had pursued her with great enthusiasm, causing her temperament to become even more arrogant.

Ge Yao stared at Fang Yuan for a while more, after he recovered his primeval essence, he started to use the moving perspective cup Gu again, completely forgetting her existence.

However this time, this northern plains young girl's displeasure vanished.

"He is after all Chang Shan Yin, he is not someone those young and immature brats can compare with. In his eyes, what am I? Just an unimportant junior I guess."

Thinking so, Ge Yao felt dejected, as she looked at Fang Yuan's face, she became dazed.

Fang Yuan used human skin Gu to change his appearance, with the features of a northern plains native, it matched her sense of beauty even more.

When Chang Shan Yin was young, he was one of the most handsome teenagers in Chang tribe.

His five features were proper, his nose was sharp, his brown eyes were deep, his thick lips showed his determined personality.

His sideburns were already turning white, it showed the experience and wisdom of a mature man. That was an intense attraction to a young girl.

As the light of the flame flickered, Fang Yuan's expression flickered along with it, his determined and mature disposure was strongly felt.

Ge Yao's thoughts drifted, she thought secretly, what kind of person was Fang Yuan?

The startle when they first met, the warmth when he smiled, the knowledge when he gave her pointers, the bravery when he fought, and the absolute calmness when he tore down his own skin.

All these scenes flashed in the young girl's heart, it was so vivid, like the memories were ingrained in the girl!

"What about his past?" Ge Yao thought again.

Chang Shan Yin's past was a heroic tale, it was widely spread in northern plains.

Numerous people respected him, love him, and thought well of him.

When he was young, his reputation was overwhelming, he was the future hope of Chang tribe.

He was famous very quickly, his first-rate wolf enslavement skill caused people to marvel.

Most importantly, he was righteous and just, forgiving and kind, he never oppressed the weak, was filial to his parents, and helped tribesmen in need. At the same time he had a great sense of brotherhood and loyalty, he placed his life on the line to protect his tribe, and performed great deeds for Chang tribe.

He married a beautiful wife, but gained the betrayal of his childhood friend. Fate toyed with him, causing this man to lose his mother, his sworn brother, his beautiful wife, and almost, his own life.

But he survived in the end.

Relying on his own hard work, he crawled up from the abyss of death, and created a legend that normal people could never imagine!

"This man shoulders endless pain and suffering, countless wounds and injuries are hidden within him." Ge Yao thought of this and had a strong urge to hug Fang Yuan, using her warmth to heal this injured lone wolf, the former Wolf King.

As the fire burned on, the wood was crackling under the flame.

Ge Yao's gaze towards Fang Yuan became more infatuated, she could not longer help herself.

Under the warm fire, a young girl's feelings were developing, and growing.

When Fang Yuan finished this round of cup exchange, and took out a primeval stone to recover his primeval essence, Ge Yao secretly made the most important decision in her life.

She suddenly stood up, shouting towards Fang Yuan: "Chang Shan Yin! Be my husband!"

The voice spread far and wide in the quiet grassland.

"What did you say?" Fang Yuan frowned, even with his five hundred years of experience, he could not anticipate this girl's change of heart.

After he reacted, he smiled: "Stop fooling around, young girl, I am your senior. Looking at our age, I am over twenty years older than you, my son will be a good match for you."

"No, Chang Shan Yin, I want you!"

Chapter 435: Don’t block my road to success!

"No, Chang Shan Yin, I want you!" Ge Yao's voice resonated in the grassland.

Under the illumination of the bonfire, her eyes shone brightly as she stared head-on at Fang Yuan: "Chang Shan Yin, you are the hero of this great plains, your reputation extends far and wide. You are the man I can entrust my whole life to! Age is not a problem. Back in the day, didn't old ancestor Giant Sun marry young women every year even after he was a thousand years old?"

Fang Yuan's expression turned dark: "Alright, don't make a scene."

Ge Yao stamped her foot and raised her voice: "I am not making a scene! Chang Shan Yin, I have already been deeply attracted to you along the way. Just earlier, I discovered that I had completely fallen in love with you. I am willing to give myself and everything to you, please accept me."

"Young girl, I already have a wife." Fang Yuan heaved a sigh and said with a complex expression.

Ge Yao immediately shook her head: "Your wife has already remarried. Even if you snatch her back, I don't mind. I don't intend to take your first wife's position, I am satisfied being your concubine. Old ancestor Giant Sun had hundreds of thousands of imperial concubines, but only had one empress."

However, Fang Yuan refused firmly: "I won't marry again. My heart is already still, just like this poison grassland. You are still too young and are unable to understand my mind. During the days I spent in the wolf's belly where I could not move at all, I felt extremely painful. When my soul floated over the vast plains, I wandered around aimlessly, but my mind gradually elevated to a greater height. I recalled my past, watched many people's life and death. The suffering or happiness of my former life were no longer able to enter my heart. I have been completely reborn, I am a new Chang Shan Yin, I also won't return to Chang tribe."

"Then, come to my Ge tribe." Ge Yao's eyes shone.

She invited with utmost sincerity, but Fang Yuan still refused and did not show any signs of being moved.

"Chang Shan Yin! Is your heart made of iron? You doubt me? Do you want me to take out my heart to let you check, just like those rockmen?" Ge Yao muttered, her eyes turned red and tears were on the verge of falling.

Howl!

Right at this moment, the howling of wolf groups signified that they were nearby.

A large group of poison beard wolves were attracted by the fire and rapidly approached Fang Yuan and Ge Yao.

However, there were large amounts of wolves resting beside the bonfire.

The two groups of wolves soon clashed against each other and an intense battle unfolded.

"This is a thousand beast group!" Ge Yao's attention was attracted towards the wolves, her expression becoming grave.

If it was before, they would choose to retreat when they came across such a scale of wolf group, but now Fang Yuan smiled coldly: "No matter, the situation is different from before, we also have a wolf group to help us. Ge Yao, I need to ask you to restrict the thousand beast wolf king. My primeval essence is exhausted, I will come assist you after I replenish it!"

The girl nodded her head but she did not immediately leave and instead looked at Fang Yuan with her bright gaze.

Fang Yuan looked at her: "Go."

Ge Yao pursed her lips, her gaze was firm as she still remained motionless.

Fang Yuan could only use a soft stance and said gently: "Alright, I will consider this matter."

"But I want the answer now!" Ge Yao immediately said.

A dark light flashed past Fang Yuan's eyes, but on the surface he heaved a sigh and proposed: "If you can kill this thousand beast king alone, I will agree and take you as my wife."

"Really?"

"Hehe, a promise that us northern plainsmen make can never be broken."

Ge Yao's eyes shone brightly at this reply: "Okay, then just wait!"

Battle intent filled the girl's heart and she charged towards the battlefield, directly taking on the thousand beast wolf king.

Gazing at her leaving, Fang Yuan's smile quickly disappeared, replaced by indifference.

He did not expect Ge Yao would be so attracted to him, the feeling of love had already taken his roots deep within her. However, when it came to love, this thing had always been unreasonable and was very difficult to deduce with common sense. Long long ago, Desolate Ancient Moon climbed Cheng Bai mountain and met with a rockman's pursuit.

According to \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> —

Ren Zu could not save his eldest son Verdant Great Sun, and at the final juncture of resurrection, he made a great mistake and was swept away by reverse flow river back into Luo Po valley.

His eldest daughter Desolate Ancient Moon heard of this and wanted to go rescue her father.

However, one must have the help of courage Gu and faith Gu to enter the life and death door.

But these Gu were with her father Ren Zu.

Desolate Ancient Moon was unable to enter the life and death door. She wanted to rescue Ren Zu but had no ways, so she asked for guidance from cognition Gu.

Cognition Gu gave her two methods.

The first method was to enter space cave, then open the space door to directly move to Ren Zu's side. She could then use the space cave to escape life and death door. However, this method could only rescue Ren Zu's soul and could not resurrect him.

The second method was to climb to the peak of Cheng Bai mountain and find the one and only success Gu. As long as she made a wish to success Gu, she could rescue Ren Zu and allow him to successfully resurrect.

Desolate Ancient Moon already knew of space cave's existence, but she had no idea how to find the space cave. Moreover, to let her father truly resurrect, she had to go to Cheng Bai mountain.

Cheng Bai mountain was not tall and was like a mound. It was peculiar as it was made from millions and millions of 'pebbles'.

These 'pebbles' were actually failure Gu. And there was only one success Gu; at the peak of Cheng Bai mountain.

Desolate Ancient Moon walked to the foot of the mountain and began to ascend the mountain.

Her movement woke up love Gu who was sleeping nearby.

Love Gu was very angry at having its sleep disturbed and wanted to take revenge against Desolate Ancient Moon. It used its unique power to awaken a piece of stone.

The stone gained life because of love Gu and became a rockman.

The rockman was tall and might, his body filled with gold, silver, copper and iron, looking very dazzling and gorgeous.

After the rockman was born, the first thing he saw was Desolate Ancient Moon. Her shocking beauty immediately conquered his heart.

He started following behind Desolate Ancient Moon, and as he looked at her fair back view, his heart was filled with love.

Finally, he could not endure it anymore and ran past Desolate Ancient Moon and blocked her, shouting loudly: "Beautiful lady, your appearance is so dazzling, your body is so elegant and your temperament is so noble. The very first moment I saw you, I was subdued by you. You are my love, please accept my love for you!"

The rockman's physique was huge, completely blocking Desolate Ancient Moon's path.

Desolate Ancient Moon slightly furrowed her brows and sized up the rockman before speaking coldly: "Love, what is that thing? You want me to accept your love, but where is it?"

The rockman immediately took off the iron pieces from his body and offered them to Desolate Ancient Moon: "Beautiful lady, this is my firmness. I give it all to you, this is my love."

Desolate Ancient Moon disappointedly shook her head; she had no interest in these iron pieces.

The rockman was dazed before taking out the copper pieces from his body and piling them above the iron pieces: "Beautiful lady, this is my obstinance. I give it all to you because this is my love."

Desolate Ancient Moon impatiently said: "Please move away, I have no interest in love, I need to rescue my father."

The rockman panicked seeing that the goddess of his heart was unmoved. He kneeled down and made up his mind, taking out all the silver pieces in his body and piling them above the copper pieces: "Beautiful lady, this is my dignity. I give it all to you, this will prove my love for you, right?"

Desolate Ancient Moon's furrowed brows deepened: "Listen, I don't have time to waste with you."

The rockman became more anxious and took out all the gold pieces in his body and put them above the silver pieces: "Beautiful lady, this is my self-confidence. I give it all to you, they represent my love for you."

Desolate Ancient Moon heaved a deep sigh: "Rockman, to express your love for me, you gave up your firmness, put down your obstinance, lost your dignity and even gave up your self-confidence. However, what I see is a very ugly rockman. Get up, I cannot accept your love, I have more important things to do."

After losing his gold, silver, copper and iron decorations, the rockman looked very small and weak, even appearing comical. It lost all the beauty and might it had before.

The rockman wept and begged Desolate Ancient Moon: "Then, how can I obtain your love?"

Desolate Ancient Moon was anxious, but the rockman kept on kneeling on the ground. She thought of an idea and changed her expression to show a smile: "Rockman, since you love me, take out your real heart for me to see."

The rockman opened his chest without any hesitation and offered his scarlet heart to Desolate Ancient Moon.

Desolate Ancient Moon took the heart and immediately kept it.

The rockman then said: "Now, I can obtain your love, right?"

Desolate Ancient Moon shook her head: "Even if you offer your heart, it cannot exchange for my love."

　　...

"Chang Shan Yin, look at this!" Ge Yao's whole body was soaked in blood and injuries, her breathing was rough as she walked towards Fang Yuan with the head of the thousand wolf king in her hand.

With the loss of their wolf king, the invading wolf group collapsed and fled.

Fang Yuan slowly stood up and nodded: "You killed the thousand wolf king."

Ge Yao showed extraordinary performance in the battle, but she suffered grave injuries, her whole face was stained with blood and her primeval essence was completely dried up. She looked at Fang Yuan with glittering eyes: "Chang Shan Yin, you are a hero, you won't go back on your words, right?"

"Of course I won't. Your love has moved me. From today onwards, you are my wife." Fang Yuan gazed at Ge Yao profoundly, then step by step, he moved closer and hugged her.

The girl relaxed her hands, the wolf king's head fell down on the ground, and she passionately hugged Fang Yuan back. Her breathing sped up and her heart thumped rapidly, this moment was even more nerve-racking than when she was fighting the wolf king.

In Fang Yuan's warm embrace, she felt happiness and her eyes reddened.

Chi.

A soft sound suddenly echoed.

The girl's face stiffened and she used all her strength to get out of Fang Yuan's embrace, then lowered her head to look at her chest.

There, a sharp dagger had pierced into it.

It was a fatal strike to both her body and mind.

"Wh... why?" Ge Yao gazed at Fang Yuan with disbelief, her delicate body shook, and her gaze was filled with anger, hatred, shock and doubt.

Fang Yuan looked at the girl and said, expressionlessly.

He spoke of the story in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> —

"The rockman was panicking seeing Desolate Ancient Moon had stored his heart away. He said: 'Heartless woman, your cold-heartedness has made me despair. Since I can't obtain your love, then please give back my heart. Without my heart, I will die.'"

"But Desolate Ancient Moon did not return the heart and watched as he slowly died."

"'Why? I love you so much, why are you killing me!' The rockman shouted before his death."

"Desolate Ancient Moon looked at him with pity, but her voice was tranquil: 'Rockman, I did not want to kill you. But you blocked my path to success.'"

"Path to success?" After Ge Yao heard this reply, she could no longer stand and collapsed on the ground.

The dense aura of death made her body increasingly colder.

The girl raised her small head, revealing her swan-like exquisite neck. She gazed at the dark night sky and laughed mournfully.

She laughed only for few seconds before tears fell down her face.

She looked at Fang Yuan, her gaze still expressing the deep love as before: "Chang Shan Yin! I don't know how I am blocking your path to success. But now, even if you kill me, I do not hate you. Maybe you are seeking revenge? I will leave all my Gu worms to you, I hope they can be of some use to you in your path to success."

"Cough cough..." The girl coughed out blood and begged Fang Yuan with a grieved smile, "I am going to die, but before I die, I have a small favor to ask. I hope you can hug me, I really want to feel your warm embrace..."

However, Fang Yuan did not move, his gaze coldly looking at the girl.

He looked at the girl and saw her expression becoming stiffer as vitality left her bit by bit.

Finally, the flower-like girl became an ice-cold corpse.

Fang Yuan fell into a long silence as he looked at Ge Yao's face.

Chapter 436: No regret even if I die along the way

Even if it was daytime, poison grassland was still solemn and dark. The thick dark clouds obstructed the entry of sunlight.

Behind a low mound, one hump wolf was lurking.

The hump wolf's size was as large as a war-horse. Its body had black and long fur, and two camel humps on its back. A pair of wolf eyes shone with eerie light in the darkness.

It was lying on the mound, completely still like a statue. Even its breathing was slow, if one took a glance, they would think it was a piece of steel.

Suddenly, the hump wolf's long ears vibrated.

Under its watchful gaze, a grey rabbit jumped out of a hole on the mound, starting to look for food.

Even though there were delicious grass near its hole, the grey rabbit did not care about them, it rushed out to look for grass far away.

Rabbits did not eat grass near their hole as it would expose the hole that they lived in.

The hump wolf saw the grey rabbit emerge, and its eyes drooped even lower, hiding most of its pupils, only leaving a small slit.

As the grey rabbit ate grass, its ears were standing high in the air. If there were any danger alerts, it would raise its head quickly and look around, extremely vigilant.

Hump wolf was extremely patient, watching the grey rabbit eat happily, it did not move, as if it was dead.

The grey rabbit continued to eat, indulging in its delicious meal.

When it was full, it started to return.

Just at this moment, the hump wolf struck. It jumped out of the mound and charged towards the rabbit.

Grey rabbit's return route was blocked by the hump wolf, in its shock, it turned around to escape.

Its speed was fast, as it sprinted, it resembled a white lightning swimming in the grass. The rabbit's speed was higher than the hump wolf, quickly pulling some distance between them.

But after sprinting for a while, it slowed down.

The grey rabbit has explosive speed, but its stamina was much less than the wolf.

The two ran and chased on poison grassland, engaging in a death chase. This was the most common scene in poison grassland — the game of survival between predator and prey.

The hump wolf got closer and closer, seeing the grey rabbit right before it, the wolf jumped and assaulted.

But at this moment, the rabbit's speed rapidly increased, as it jumped to one side. After dodging the fatal attack, it moved away from the hump wolf again.

This grey rabbit is very crafty, its fatigue earlier was just an act, it still had the ability to protect itself.

Hump wolf did not succeed in its attack, thus it had to continue chasing after the rabbit.

Soon, the distance between them shortened again.

The hump wolf jumped again, but missed once more.

After three to four times, the rabbit was exhausted, it was finally killed by the hump wolf.

The hump wolf breathed roughly, sprawling on the ground before getting up after a long while. In this cruel competition, the predator did not always have an easy time, they often faced much difficulty and suffering.

After catching this grey rabbit with much effort, the hump wolf did not enjoy this delicacy, but held it in its mouth as it returned to its home.

In the den, there was a female hump wolf and numerous newborn wolf cubs to feed.

But when this hump wolf got back to its den, it only saw blood traces and cold corpses.

Howl!!!

It abandoned the grey rabbit corpse, and howled angrily towards the sky. The fur on its neck stood up, as the intense hatred turn its eyes red.

A large group of poison beard wolves surrounded it from all directions.

Far away on a mound, Fang Yuan crossed his arms as he looked down, observing this battlefield.

"Hehehe, as expected, a male wolf came." He laughed lightly, feeling that his recent luck had finally improved.

Hump wolves were outstanding mounts in northern plains, although Fang Yuan had Chang Shan Yin's rank four wolf sprint Gu, it expended quite a bit of primeval essence. He would rather ride a hump wolf, it was quicker and easier.

When Fang Yuan accidentally found this wolf's den, he killed the weak female wolf and its cubs, obtaining a rank two wolf enslavement Gu.

He did not leave in a hurry, but instead used the poison beard wolves as ambush, awaiting the return of the male wolf.

The battle between hump wolves and poison beard wolves had just gotten intense.

The hump wolf had a large physique, together with the furious emotions it had, it battled even more fiercely. Using its claws, ordinary poison beard wolves were not its match.

But with Fang Yuan's manipulation, the poison beard wolves were very cunning, they did not fight it head on, but cooperated and worked with great teamwork, taking turns to drain the hump wolf's stamina.

After an hour, the hump wolf was breathing raggedly as it lost the ferocity it had earlier.

Around it, there were sixty or so poison beard wolf corpses, that was its greatest achievement. Of course, if Fang Yuan wanted to kill it, with his skill in enslavement path, he would only need to sacrifice thirty poison beard wolves. But Fang Yuan wanted it alive, thus when he battled, he was restricted in many ways.

"It's about time." Fang Yuan looked at the hump wolf's trembling limbs in the wind, he slowly walked down and got closer to the wolf.

Now, most of his Gu worms were sent back to Hu Immortal blessed land using moving perspective cup Gu.

When he was two hundred steps away from the hump wolf, Fang Yuan's finger pointed and a rank two wolf enslavement Gu flew out.

The wolf enslavement Gu exploded, turning into a light smoke that covered the hump wolf's body.

Hump wolf quickly jumped back to evade, but the light smoke chased after it. The hump wolf howled, charging towards Fang Yuan. However, the poison beard wolf pack stopped it with their full force.

In a few breaths' time, the smoke completely merged into its body.

Hump wolf lied down on the ground weakly, its body was covered in wounds that were bleeding, its bright red eyes no longer stared at Fang Yuan with hatred, but showed submission.

"Hundred man soul is really useful, if I did not use the guts Gu, I would need to spend a lot of effort to capture this hump wolf." Fang Yuan sighed in his heart, before activating wolf smoke Gu in his aperture.

Wolf smoke Gu flew out, turning into thick smoke as it engulfed hump wolf, as well as most of the injured poison beard wolves.

In a moment, the thick smoke dispersed, and hump wolf's injuries were fully healed, it even grew new fur. The injured poison beard wolves also regained their vitality.

However, even without injuries, their battle strength was not at their peak.

What affected the battle strength of beats was not just injuries, but also their hunger.

For wolves to display their full strength, they cannot be too hungry, as it leads to weakness. But they cannot be too full, as that would make them more sluggish.

Earlier, when the hump wolf hunted, why did it patiently wait for the grey rabbit to get full? It was the same reason.

Only when the wolves are half full and half hungry, could they have the will to fight, fighting most harshly and fiercely.

After battling for so long, be it the hump wolf or the poison beard wolves, they had lost a lot of stamina and were hungry.

Fang Yuan willed, and the poison beard wolves started eating the corpse of the dead wolves. Hump wolf ate that grey rabbit, and by the command of Fang Yuan, started to devour the dead female wolf and her cubs as well.

Fang Yuan stood on the spot, taking out his rations and consuming them.

Three days had passed since he killed Ge Yao.

Ge Yao had to die, the moment she saw fixed immortal travel Gu, her death was guaranteed.

Furthermore, she had first seen Fang Yuan step into northern plains naked, and then saw him bury the Immortal Gu, as well as using moving perspective cup Gu.

She knew too many things, in Fang Yuan's heart, she was a definite target to kill.

Except when Fang Yuan first came, his battle strength was low, in order to move around in poison grassland, he needed her assistance.

But Ge Yao could not be allowed to live, if her naivety could be used by Fang Yuan, others could naturally use it as well. She was such a burden, with her ordinary soul foundation, others only needed the mind reading Gu or recollection Gu on her to be able to completely expose Fang Yuan's plans, and divulge his secrets to the world.

This was a premeditated murder by Fang Yuan.

As they survived hurdles one after another, the ghost face sunflower sea, the earth spike rats, the shadow crows, as well as finding Chang Shan Yin and using his skin, to finding snow wash Gu and burying the earth treasury flower king Gu, her value and use was diminishing. At the same time, her threat was rising slowly.

Her love towards Fang Yuan also made him, who was disguised as Chang Shan Yin, feel like a dagger was placed at his throat, a great sense of danger.

A young girl in love would use all ways possible to understand the person she loves, not just the present, but also his past and future.

What happens when she finds out the truth?

Moreover, she had a tribe behind her, she was the young missy of her tribe.

Being loved by such a person, no matter how low-key Fang Yuan was, he would be at the center of attention.

Remember that there were many young masters in Man tribe who were infatuated with Ge Yao's beauty.

If Fang Yuan returned with Ge Yao, he would definitely be heavily watched by the two tribes. Why did he have to attract so much hostility for this burden?

Fang Yuan was not afraid of hostility, but his purpose in northern plains was not for a vacation. He had limited time, he was racing against time. Dang Hun mountain was nearing death, and Spring Autumn Cicada was recovering slowly, meanwhile his cultivation was only rank four peak stage.

He had to strive towards success, he could not fail. Once he failed, he would fall into the abyss, he would have no hope left.

On this road, he was destined to be lonely, there were only two outcomes. Either he succeeds, or he faces destruction!

Thus, when the two got close to the outer border of poison grassland, Fang Yuan used an opportunity when there were few people and it was convenient to kill to end her life!

After Ge Yao was killed, Fang Yuan ordered the wolves to devour her corpse. Her soul was obviously not spared, he used the burial soul toad to swallow it, it had already been sent to the blessed land and was crushed by Dang Hun mountain.

The area near the fireplace had already been carefully inspected, there were no traces or evidence left.

All in all, Ge Yao had been wiped off the face of this world. Her only remains, might probably be the faeces that the poison beard wolves excrete.

Hehehe.

This so-called beauty, in the end, she was just a pile of shit.

Ashes to ashes, dust to dust.

A beautiful young girl, in this heaven and earth, she was just like a flower. Either she gets trampled on at the roadside, or she wilters when her time is up, becoming an ugly fertilizer for the earth.

"Without eternal life, even the most beautiful thing is but the reflection of the moon in the water. The value of their existence is merely for that second of elegance." The more experiences that Fang Yuan went through, the more he understood the cruelty of this world. Without immortality, even the most valuable of things will become worthless.

"The so-called praised for a hundred years, or leaving a stench for ten thousand years, these are all superficial thinking of those cowards. The so-called immortality in spirit is merely a tool for descendants to make use of. Is it true that the existence of humans can only be affirmed through one another? So be it on Earth. But here in this world, if there is even a slight possibility, I want to pursue it!"

"Even if I die on the road while pursuing my goals, even if I die a million times worse than Ge Yao, I have absolutely no regrets..."

Fang Yuan was resolved for death from the start.

But only if he placed all his effort, and contributed his all towards the pursuit of his dream, could he die without a hint of regret.

Heh.

Who could understand the heart of this transmigrator plus reincarnator Fang Yuan?

The road he walked on was destined to be filled with endless darkness, he was destined to be lonely forever.

The direction he walked was towards the light in his heart — immortality — a possibility so slim that it was almost impossible.

In this world, nobody understood him.

But he...

Does not need anyone's understanding.

Chapter 437: Wind Wolf King

The wolf group finished eating. Fang Yuan rode on the hump wolf's back and resumed his journey.

"These days, I have been moving according to the direction Ge Yao pointed. I am almost at the edge of poison grassland. If I move further, I will see human habitations."

Hump wolf was a natural mount, its two humps formed a comfortable saddle.

Fang Yuan sat between the two humps, inspecting his aperture while moving forward.

There were only around ten Gu worms remaining in his aperture. Besides Spring Autumn Cicada and moving perspective cup Gu, they were all northern plains Gu worms.

The Gu that were from southern border and central continent were already sent to Hu Immortal blessed land. Fang Yuan did not keep even a single primeval stone.

Southern border primeval stones could be used in northern plains, but they had some differences with northern plains primeval stones. Ge Yao could not see it because she was too young and too naive. But generally, any Gu Master that had some experience and shrewdness could notice it.

"Unfortunately, moving perspective cup Gu - a rank five Gu - has been suppressed to rank four in northern plains and can only contain rank four Gu. If I could send fixed immortal travel to the blessed land with it, it would be perfect. Sigh, I hope my method is effective."

If some other Gu Immortal took fixed immortal travel Gu, it would be a heavy loss to Fang Yuan.

However, Fang Yuan could do nothing else as he had already done everything possible.

"Immortal Gu's aura lasts for about a month. If there are no problems during this period, then fixed immortal travel Gu will be safe."

"Soon, I will run into northern plains Gu Masters. I absolutely cannot be careless, it would be best if I can subdue a thousand wolf king during this period of time and raise the number of the wolves to over two thousand."

Sometimes, humans were more terrifying than wild beasts. A wolf group of over two thousand wolves could intimidate most of the small characters.

"Currently, I only have one rank three and one rank two wolf enslavement Gu, I must use them carefully. I will be moving using Chang Shan Yin's identity in northern plains, wolf enslavement should be the main priority. But there is an obstacle, I do not have the recipes for rank three and rank four wolf enslavement Gu."

Almost all the beast enslavement Gu were expendable Gu, and after they were used, whether it resulted in success or failure, they would disperse.

Rank three wolf enslavement Gu could enslave thousand wolf king. Rank four wolf enslavement Gu could enslave myriad wolf king or mutated beasts.

Without the recipe for these two Gu, Fang Yuan would not have many wolf enslavement Gu. Without these wolf enslavement Gu, Fang Yuan's wolf group could at have a most a few thousand wolves, it was not enough to enter the limelight.

With the hump wolf's pace, the following journey was sped up by three times.

Fang Yuan travelled day and night, the dark clouds hovering over his head also gradually thinned.

Two days later, he finally reached the edge of poison grassland.

In the sky, the dark clouds were dispersed here and there. Rays of sunlight passed through the gaps between the dark clouds and fell on the ground in the form of light pillars.

Looking from afar, the green grassland flourished under the light; flowers having the colors of blue, purple or yellow eagerly blossomed.

The low and gently sloping mounds were completely filled with greenery without any gaps.

A small river flowed gently beside the mounds and sparkled like a silver necklace under the sunlight.

"I am finally out." Fang Yuan felt moved. Riding on the hump wolf's back and surrounded by poison beard wolves, he slowly walked towards the sunlight.

The poison beard wolves were restless.

They were adapted to hunting in dark surroundings, the sunlight would greatly affect their battle strength.

Fang Yuan did not care, these poison beard wolf group were only temporary, they would be eliminated sooner or later.

Fang Yuan gazed back, poison grassland behind him was still covered with dark clouds, dusky sunlight and gloomy cold wind. On the corrupted land, there were dark purplish poisonous grass, bent into all kinds of shapes.

Compared to this side of the grassland which had sunlight shining over it, it showed a clear contrast, like they were two different worlds.

"Hu Immortal blessed land's eastern area is also covered in dense clouds. If they are not dealt with in time, that land would also develop towards the direction of poison grassland. Poison grassland... I will be back."

Just as Fang Yuan was mumbling, his body suddenly relaxed.

Since the time he entered northern plains, he felt uncomfortable, a formless restriction had covered his body.

Right now, this restriction slightly loosened and Fang Yuan immediately felt he was much closer to this vast land.

Subsequently, his aura rose and from rank three peak stage, it reached rank four initial stage.

A joyous feeling rose up involuntarily, causing Fang Yuan to laugh heartily.

With his body gradually adapting to northern plains, his cultivation also slowly recovered; this would be a great help to his following plans!

"Northern plains, I'm coming!" Fang Yuan shouted. He squeezed the wolf's belly with his legs, the hump wolf started running towards a distant location, leading the poison beard wolf group.

　　...

"Kill!"

Shouting resounded over a hill, dozens of Gu Masters were in an intense battle with over a thousand wind wolves.

The battle had already continued for fifteen minutes.

"This damned wind wolves!" The leader Ge Guang cursed with a malevolent expression, he waved the sabre in his hand, cutting off the head of a wind wolf.

But after cutting off the head, his sabre broke into two. The two halves of the sabre were also already filled with holes.

Howl!

A wind wolf suddenly leapt and charged towards Ge Guang.

"Young tribe leader, careful! Spiral water arrow!" A Gu Master behind Ge Guang anxiously shouted.

Hearing this shout, from a tacit understanding that came from fighting all year round, Ge Guang did not think and suddenly bent his waist; it looked like he took the initiative to send himself to the wolf's mouth.

The wind wolf that was in mid-air opened its mouth and revealed its sharp fangs. Just as it seemed like it was going to bite off Ge Guang's head, a blue water arrow shot out from behind Ge Guang with a strong rotational force.

This spiral water arrow ruthlessly shot into the wind wolf's mouth, sending it directly towards the afterlife.

Taking this chance, Ge Guang squeezed the wolf's belly, urging his hump wolf to retreat into the defensive range of his group.

Sabre Gu!

He put his palms together and squeezed out the final trace of primeval essence in his aperture, pouring it into the sabre imprint on his palm.

Whoosh!

A completely new sabre instantly formed; Ge Guang suddenly swung his right hand and tightly grasped it.

"Die!" He growled with an iron-like hoarse voice.

The new sabre was extremely sharp, cutting a cold light in the air and splitting a wind wolf into two.

But this was only a small victory, it was truly difficult to have an active influence on the whole devastating situation.

"Damn it, I don't have enough primeval essence!"

"There are at least over three thousand wolves, it's too many!"

"Young tribe leader, we are completely surrounded! There is no hope even if we fight to the death, it would be better to break through the east, the defensive line there is the weakest!"

The surrounding Gu Masters shouted one after another.

Ge Guang's fierce eyes shone and after thinking for a moment, resolutely refused: "No, there are puddles in the eastern side. The defense there looks the weakest, but it is actually a trap prepared by the wind wolf king. If we go in, we will be sending ourselves into its trap!"

"Then what should we do?"The surrounding people asked.

Ge Guang gritted his teeth and firmed up his mind: "Turn around, we will break through the west."

"But we have still not found lady Ge Yao. If we return like this, what will we say to lord tribe leader?"

Ge Guang snorted: "Although Ge Yao is my sister, for her own selfishness, she ignore our tribe's circumstance and fled the marriage. Sacrificing great men for a mere woman is not worth it! Spread the command, we will break through! Let those lowly slaves stay behind. It is time for them to offer their lives for their masters."

"Understood!" The surrounding people immediately transmitted the order.

Northern plains tribes would go on war campaigns all year round. Some defeated Gu Masters would become slaves. Slaves had very low status and when necessary, they would be treated as cannon fodder and abandoned.

Soon, Gu Masters divided into two groups.

A pair of slaves was to stay behind on the mound and use their lives to block the enemy. While the other group was led by Ge Guang to break through the west.

"Kill kill kill!" Ge Guang charged through the frontlines riding on the hump wolf, wielding his saber roughly and bravely.

"Protect young master!" The Gu Masters behind him were also tall and stoutly built men, they closely moved around Ge Guang on their hump wolves.

Whoosh!

Suddenly, a large three-leaf wind blade flew towards them.

"Master!" A loyal Gu Master warned loudly and was the first to react.

He did not have a trace of primeval essence left, he directly charged towards the front on his hump wolf and used his own body to obstruct the wind blade.

Nothing surprising happened, he was cut into two by the wind blade, immediately losing his life.

The wind blade was weakened to two-leaf but still moved towards Ge Guang.

Ge Guang reacted, immediately lifting his sabre to block it.

Bang!

The wind and the sabre collided; the sabre shattered into pieces, Ge Guang spurted out a large mouthful of blood and fell from the hump wolf's back.

"Young tribe leader!" The Gu Masters behind him immediately came over to protect him, but with this, their break through failed. Endless wind wolves came over from both sides and firmly surrounded them again.

The wind wolves quietly parted open a path; a young and vigorous wind wolf king slowly walked through the path and appeared before everyone.

Thousand beast king!

Its body was enormous like a warhorse. Brisk dark green fur covered its whole body and its eyes were like emeralds. Its alternating steps and unhurried pace unexpectedly gave an elegant and noble feeling to Ge Guang and the group.

Right now, the slave Gu Masters that had stayed behind on the hill were already killed. Large amounts of wind wolves came over after killing them.

The Gu Masters had already exhausted their primeval essence, the wind wolf king's appearance caused them to feel restless.

Someone pulled Ge Guang to retreat, but Ge Guang swung his arm and stood up with difficulty, he shouted: "What are you afraid of? I don't have primeval essence, but I still have my hands, legs and teeth! Warriors, don't let these beasts scorn you. We will use our blood to prove ourselves, we are the brave tribesmen of Ge tribe!"

Everyone was agitated by his words, their morale immediately rose and a will to fight to death emerged in them.

The wind wolf king was walking leisurely, when suddenly it turned its head to look at the eastern direction of the battlefield.

A large group of dark purplish poison beard wolves were rapidly closing in!

Chapter 438: Benefactor Chang Shan Yin

The poison beard wolves did not make any stops, they charged towards the wind wolves.

"It's the poison beard wolves!" Very soon, Gu Masters discovered the poison beard wolf pack and looked up.

"Strange, don't the poison beard wolves only move around in poison grassland, why are they outside?" Some Gu Masters felt perplexed.

"There's probably a Gu Master controlling them!" Ge Guang clenched his fists, seeing the approaching poison beard wolves, his eyes which showed despair started to shine with the light of hope.

"Young master is wise, look there, there's a person!" A few breaths later, a Gu Master pointed to a faraway place.

As everyone observed closely, Fang Yuan appeared before them while riding the hump wolf.

"We're saved!" Everyone cheered.

"Not necessarily..." Ge Guang's eyes squinted, he was very rational: "Less than a thousand poison beard wolves, we might not be safe, it'll depend on his wolf enslavement skill."

With this reminder, the Gu Masters started worrying.

"This person should be an enslavement path Gu Master, but he does not have many poison beard wolves."

"Not good, poison beard wolves are weaker under sunlight, they are slightly inferior to the wind wolves."

"Oh no, this enslavement path Gu Master does not even have a thousand beast king, he only has a few hundred beast kings, how can he block the assault of the wind wolf king?!"

Ge Guang suddenly said: "No matter, as long as this Gu Master can gather the poison beard wolves and charge all at once, he can break the encirclement and would be able to save us."

This greatly reduced the people's worry, but just as they felt hopeful, Fang Yuan willed, and the entire poison beard wolf pack spread out like pouring a basin of water.

"This, this, this!" Many Gu Masters were tongue tied.

"It's over, he's courting death!" Some closed their eyes.

"Idiot, wasting such a chance." Some Gu Masters were stomping their foot in anger.

They were extremely disappointed, they cursed and swore, some even started to hate Fang Yuan.

Ge Guang's expression paled, as long as there was a chance to live, who would want to die? Fang Yuan's appearance gave them hope, but he also destroyed their hopes single-handedly!

Wind wolf king howled, causing the entire wind wolf pack to attack.

Just as the two packs were about to engage in battle, Fang Yuan let out a loud howl.

He was human, but he emitted the cry of a wolf.

This call was desolate, it was wild, it was like a fire that was being blown by the wind in the night sky.

The wolf howl could be heard from eight hundred steps away, the poison beard wolves in this range turned frenzy upon hearing it, summoning twice their original battle strength!

"Ah, this is the rank four wolf howl Gu, it can increase the battle strength of wolf packs temporarily, it is a precious Gu. This person is a rank four Gu Master!"

Fang Yuan's howl was shocking, it changed the expressions of the Gu Masters.

Many pairs of despairing eyes gave off hope once again.

Rank three and rank four were two different concepts.

Rank three was elder, rank four was leader.

Even Ge Guang was only rank three upper stage.

After recognising Fang Yuan's cultivation level, nobody scolded him anymore. Although northern plains Gu Masters were brave, they were not arrogant, they were filled with respect for experts, and were humble towards strength.

The poison beard wolves were originally weaker than the wind wolves, but now their battle strength surged, and they quickly overwhelmed the wind wolves.

After just a short battle, the wind wolves retreated, and a large number of wind wolf corpses were left on the battlefield. Over a dozen wind wolves were sacrificed for the life of one poison beard wolf.

"What level of wolf enslavement skill is this!" Such a grand feat caused the Gu Masters to stare till their eyes fell out.

"Unimaginable! This is the attainment of an enslavement master, who in the world is this person?" Many people looked at Fang Yuan like he was a monster.

"I have never heard of such a hidden expert living in this area!" The gang was excited and shocked.

Fang Yuan's strength caused the wind wolf pack's attention to be placed on the poison beard wolves. They only surrounded the Ge tribe Gu Masters without attacking. This allowed these people to have a moment of rest under such circumstances.

"The wind wolf king is here!" Ge Guang said, as everyone became nervous again.

Wind wolf king had higher intelligence, it howled and gathered the elites of its pack.

Very soon, with wind wolf king as the arrowhead, these elites moved like an arrow, charging into the formation, straight into the center, and attacked Fang Yuan.

Enslavement path Gu Masters were most afraid of 'beheading the leader' tactic, this wind wolf king was a thousand beast king, as it led the group of elites in attacking, they were simply unstoppable. Meanwhile, Fang Yuan only had a few hundred beast king level poison beard wolf kings.

But Fang Yuan was overjoyed instead of afraid, as he smiled lightly: "It could not resist it."

Wind wolf king's intelligence was higher than other wolves, but it was still a wild beast, it could not compare with humans. Against other wolf packs, Fang Yuan needed to charge himself, but when battling the wind wolf king, Fang Yuan could create this formation to attract the wind wolf king to charge towards him.

Swoosh!

Wind wolf king who was sprinting opened its mouth and shot out three large wind blades.

The wind blades flew ahead and sliced through the wolf pack, creating a path as it targeted Fang Yuan.

"Careful!" A Gu Master on the mound could not help but scream, as the others were extremely nervous.

Fang Yuan did not move, he waited for the wind blades to get near him before manipulating the hump wolf to evade, easily and narrowly avoid them, as the green-blue wind blades passed right beside him.

"Expert!" Fang Yuan's calm and composed demeanor made the Gu Masters think of this word.

Fang Yuan willed and several poison beard wolf kings were already prepared, charging forward and forming a formation, blocking the Wind wolf king.

Wind wolf king's speed was fast, and had strong attacks with sturdy defenses, it was stronger than any of the poison beard wolf kings. And yet, it could not break through this barrier.

Fang Yuan's precise control allowed him to overcome a stronger foe, restraining the wind wolf king as it could only howl angrily and helplessly.

"Formidable! The great wind wolf king is being toyed by this man."

"This person's enslavement skill is on par with Jiang Bao Ya, Yang Po Ying, and Ma Zun. Northern plains has a new first-rate enslavement expert now!"

"If his wolf pack is stronger by a few times, he could take on a small-mid tribe single-handedly!"

"Who is this person? He looks rather old." Ge Guang was in a daze looking at Fang Yuan deal with the wind wolf king, feeling great admiration in his heart.

Everyone shook their heads, guessing among themselves, this gave Fang Yuan an aura of mystery.

"It is about time." Fang Yuan muttered.

He had the entire battle in his grasp, seeing that the wind wolf king was about to escape, he knew that its battle intent was gone.

"Rank three wolf enslavement Gu, go!"

Fang Yuan willed, and his sole rank three wolf enslavement Gu flew out and turned into a light smoke, engulfing the Wind wolf king.

Wind wolf king howled as it struggled, holding on as it did not submit to Fang Yuan's authority.

"Hmph." Fang Yuan's eyes shone brightly, he had a hundred man soul, he was not afraid of such competition between souls.

As expected, after a while, the wind wolf king could not resist anymore and submitted to Fang Yuan.

"This person's soul is extremely strong, he most likely has a hundred man soul!" Someone exclaimed.

"With such skill in enslavement, it is not strange that he has a hundred man soul." Someone rebuked: "Like Jiang Bao Ya, Yang Po Ying, and Ma Zun, they all have thousand man souls!"

After successfully planting the wolf enslavement Gu, Fang Yuan obtained his first thousand wolf king.

Wind wolf king howled, and the wolf pack stood its movement, the noisy battlefield turned silent.

The remaining thousand wind wolves obeyed the wind wolf king and joined Fang Yuan.

This way, Fang Yuan's wolf pack size doubled, reaching two thousand and four hundred wolves.

"I was lucky this time, if not for these Gu Masters restraining the wolves, I would have had a pay a bigger price to subdue this wind wolf king." Fang Yuan rode on the hump wolf as he gradually moved towards the mound.

Ge Guang and gang were holding their breaths, this person would decide their life and death.

As Fang Yuan got closer, Ge Guang stood out from the crowd and placed his right hand at his chest, bowing deeply at Fang Yuan, shouting: "Esteemed expert, your strength brings me great admiration and reverence. Now, our lives are in your hands. To live or to die, we will listen to your command, we will not have any complaints."

"Hehehe, young warrior, I saw your battle earlier. You are as brave as a stallion, it reminds me of myself in the past." Fang Yuan sat on the wolf's back, laughing as he looked at the people warmly: "You are the first batch of humans I've seen since I left poison grassland. I am very happy to return to this land, rest assured I, Chang Shan Yin, am not a cruel and wicked person."

Hearing Fang Yuan's words, the Gu Masters laughed as they relaxed.

They had little primeval essence left now, if Fang Yuan wanted to kill them, they had no way of retaliating.

Sometimes, men were more dangerous than wolves. If they met a demonic Gu Master, their outcomes would be even more tragic. Right now, everyone felt glad, they thought that they had met a righteous expert.

"Benefactor Chang Shan Yin, I am Ge tribe's young tribe leader, you saved my life, allow me to repay this debt. Let me invite you to our tent as a guest, I will do my best to make your stay an enjoyable one." Ge Guang invited earnestly.

Of course, gratitude was a part of the reason, but he was also looking at Fang Yuan's strength. The chance of become familiar with an expert was not just good for him, it benefited the entire tribe as well.

"Ge tribe?" Fang Yuan thought for a while: "Alright, I have already expended my primeval stones, and I also need to replenish my Gu worms, I do need to rest and reorganise."

He subtly expressed his needs and requests, it was a hint to Ge Guang.

Without disappointing him, this young clan leader's eyes shone as he memorised these words to heart, laughing heartily: "Benefactor Chang Shan Yin, thank you for accepting, then let me lead the way."

Chapter 439: Ge Tribe Camp

Fang Yuan followed Ge Guang and the others towards the west.

They had the hump wolf, the speed was not slow.

Along the way, the group's atmosphere was uplifting.

On the one hand, Fang Yuan was intentionally getting close to them, he had his motives. On the other hand, Ge Guang was doing his best to form a relationship with this expert, he had great respect for him in his heart.

Northern plains natives were brave and fierce, but they were also forthright and candid.

If you did not have the strength, they would look down on you, they were hard to talk to. But if you had a strong and tough fist, they would respect you. And when your personality matched theirs, their enthusiasm would make you understand what was 'to regret meeting too late'.

In just two days, Fang Yuan became very close to Ge Guang.

Fang Yuan intended to use this stepping board called Ge tribe to fuse into northern plains. After all, Chang Shan Yin had vanished for twenty years, now that he returned, it was hard for people to accept that fact.

At the same time, he had few primeval stones left, and he lacked a defensive Gu, he needed transactions to get them.

On Chang Shan Yin's corpse, Fang Yuan did not find any defensive Gu, most likely it was destroyed during the battle with Ha Tu Gu.

And Ge Guang was also very grateful, respectful, and curious about Fang Yuan,

Grateful because Fang Yuan saved his life.

Respectful because Fang Yuan's wolf enslavement skill was first-rate. With just a bit of guidance, Ge Guang's bottleneck was easily broken, it was truly the demeanour of a first-rate senior, the disposition for an expert.

Curiosity was because Fang Yuan spoke of the past, he often used a reminiscent tone and an old and wise gaze, he was obviously an expert with a deep story. Ge Guang had the desire to find out more, but he did not dare to ask excessively.

Five days later, the gang returned to Ge tribe's camp base.

The campsite was huge, there was a thick sturdy wall at the outer border of the camp, it was around 6 meters tall, green in color as vines grew and intertwined on it. Large numbers of leaves covered bunches and bunches of grape-like fruits.

These were obviously not fruits, but the wood path mind confusion Gu. When wild beasts attack, these grape-like fruits would explode and their juices would splatter on the beasts, causing them to go into confusion, and their bodies would shake as they lose their balance, unable to continue fighting.

After the great wall, there were tall watchtowers. Three Gu Masters were stationed on top of each tower, one defensive and two investigative Gu Masters taking turns to keep watch.

When the camp gates were opened, many Gu Masters came out to welcome them back.

"Young tribe leader is back, young tribe leader is back."

"Young tribe leader has only left for a few days, they're back already?"

"I heard they met with a wind wolf pack, and almost lost their lives, thankfully an enslavement path expert helped them out!"

"That middle-aged man? These wolves are all following him, he is amazing! But I wonder he is expert from which tribe in northern plains."

Before Fang Yuan and others reached the camp, they had already met with the investigative Gu masters patrolling the camp. Thus, the camp had already received their news before the gang even reached.

As the information spread, many people pointed fingers at Fang Yuan, extremely curious.

Some children were jumping and shouting, following behind the gang excitedly.

Fang Yuan was seated on the back of hump wolf, looking at Ge Guang wave his hand towards the tribesmen. Every time he waved his hand, there would be a loud cheer from the crowd. It showed this young man's important position in the tribe.

From their conversations along the way, Fang Yuan had already understood Ge Guang completely. He was the brother of Ge Yao, a typical northern plains native, forthright and had a strong sense of brotherhood, he placed glory above his life. He had both wisdom and strength, and had the traditional northern plains mindset of patriarchy deeply ingrained in him. He was extremely angry and disgusted at his sister for escaping the wedding.

But his negative emotions did not mean that their sibling relationship was cold.

In fact, if he knew that Fang Yuan was the murderer of his sister, even without any primeval essence, he would use his teeth and limbs to try and exact revenge on Fang Yuan.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, he had lived in northern plains, thus he had a deep understanding of their nature.

Along the main path, the gang moved towards the center of the camp.

All around them were tents, resembling the mongolian tents on Earth. These were the accommodation of mortals.

Many people heard the commotion and lifted their window flaps, as their expressions changed when they saw the wolf pack behind Fang Yuan. Upon seeing the young tribe leader, they used their right hand to cover their chest as they paid respects to Ge Guang, shouting loudly to greet him.

In southern border, mortals had to kneel down when they met Gu Masters. But in northern plains, the male warriors only kneeled to heaven, their ancestors, and family elders. Normally, they did not kneel even to the tribe leader or tribe elders.

These mortals wore fur robes. Some females with better family background would have some accessories, while the males would have golden or purple threads on their shirts. Those who were poor would wear tattered clothes, with holes covered by additional cloth.

But this was much better than slaves.

Along the way, the people Fang Yuan saw who were kneeling were all slaves.

These slaves wore barely any clothing, they were skinny and pale. In the northern plains, these slaves had very lowly status, and lived a pitiful life.

In the hearts of northern plains natives, keeping slaves was the same as rearing cows or sheep. Slave trade was the most flourishing business in northern plains.

In northern plains, mortals lived in tents. The tents were scattered at the outer ring of the camp, while the inner area was the residential area for Gu Masters.

If beast groups attacked the camp, the morals were the first to die.

After Fang Yuan and the others passed the tent area, they reached the Gu Master domain.

The Gu Masters on the grassland did not live in tents, but lived in Gu houses.

Gu houses were houses made of Gu. Simple Gu houses were made using one Gu. Complex Gu houses were made from a combination of many Gu.

In southern border, the large size caravans that travelled across mountains and forests had such Gu houses.

Back then on Qing Mao mountain, Jia clan brought a Gu house that was made using a wood path Gu worm, three star cave.

It was 18 meters tall, a truly tall tree. The roots were thick and strong, intertwining like coiling snakes, a small portion were exposed on the ground, while the rest were deeply buried underground.

The tree trunk had three layers, and on the surface, there were windows. The defensive power was on another level compared to the ordinary tents.

When used, the support Gu Master would plant the seeds, and inject their primeval essence for it to grow. When they wanted to keep it, the tree would turn back into a seed.

But in northern plains, ordinary Gu houses were not large trees like three star cave. Such a tall tree would be an easy target for lightning when it rained heavily.

Thus, the first Gu house that Fang Yuan saw was the most common house lizard Gu.

This was a rank two Gu, its outer appearance was like a lizard with many colors. The most commonly seen colors were dark green, sky blue, and milky white. They were huge in size, like the buses on Earth, the lizard had two eyes that acted as windows. The two sides of their body also had windows.

The lizard sprawled on the ground, opening its mouth to reveal a door.

After opening the door and entering, one would see a long passage. On the left and right, there were two rows of rooms. At the end of the passage, it was the toilet, the temporary area to store body waste.

When the tribe relocates, the lizard would get up and move with its four strong limbs.

When there was too much waste in the toilet, these lizards would defecate, lifting their tails to expose their anus, excreting all of the waste they had.

A family living inside a Gu house needed to have at least one Gu Master.

Such living environments were a level higher than the tent area.

At the door of the Gu house, there were often big stomach horses standing there, as their ropes would be tied to the lizard's huge teeth. A small number of families even had hump wolves.

Fang Yuan and gang moved past these lizard Gu houses and saw the mushroom forest Gu houses.

These Gu houses were formed by planting large numbers of mushroom Gu. Each house was a large mushroom, with a grey colored round top that can let rainwater flow away, they did not attract lightning from storms and were very stable when strong winds blew.

The mushroom had a strong and circular stem, the interior was white walls with windows on it.

A few mushroom Gu formed together to create a unique living environment. With dozens of mushroom Gu, the area turned into a small mushroom forest.

Those who lived in the mushroom forest were tribe elders or affluent Gu Masters.

Hearing the movement from Fang Yuan and gang, the windows of these mushroom houses opened, showing some women and children. Some lively children ran out to touch the wind wolves or poison beard wolves' fur, they were more bold than mortal family's children.

"Benefactor Chang Shan Yin, ahead is the king tent of our Ge tribe." Ge Guang said.

The gang came to the center of the campsite, and there were over a hundred mushroom Gu here.

An old man, with an amicable appearance, led a group of Gu Masters to welcome them.

Fang Yuan guessed that he was the Ge tribe leader, and to express his politeness, he got off the hump wolf.

Old tribe leader came before Fang Yuan, placed his right hand at his heart as he bowed deeply: "Esteemed expert, you saved my son, you saved the future of our Ge tribe. Please come in, we have already prepared high quality kumis, and the beef and lamb are also grilling right now. I will arrange for people to feed your wolf pack."

"Alright." Fang Yuan nodded, following Ge tribe leader into this largest mushroom forest.

In the mushroom forest, people sat in order of status in the largest mushroom Gu.

Fragrant kumis was placed in a leather water bag, presented before the people by young beautiful girls.

Large numbers of delicacies were placed on the table.

Soon, someone placed the grilled lamb and beef in the center of the room.

Old Ge tribe leader worked personally, he got to the center of the room and used a dagger to cut out the eyes of the cows and sheep, and also their back and chest meat, before placing them on a golden plate and bringing them to Fang Yuan with both hands.

"Benefactor, please." Old Ge tribe leader lifted his wine cup and stood before Fang Yuan as he toasted.

Northern plains natives respected honorable men the most, and were extremely hospitable. In the northern plains, if the host toasts a guest, and the guest drinks it all, then that is respect to the host. Similarly, if they did not drink it, that means they did not respect the host, or held disdain towards him.

When Fang Yuan drank the entire bowl of kumis, the room cheered as the atmosphere became more lively.

After Ge tribe leader toasted, Ge Guang followed, and Fang Yuan drank it all in one shot. Afterwards, the tribe elders started toasting him, and Fang Yuan drank them all, his grand attitude won the good feelings of everyone.

After the toasting ended, the atmosphere in the room was absolutely heated.

"Benefactor Chang Shan Yin, you name is very familiar, are you a member of Chang tribe? In Chang tribe, I have several friends, my second daughter is married to Chang tribe. We might even be relatives." Old Ge tribe leader placed his cup down as his slightly red face had bright shining eyes.

"Ge tribe leader, I know what you want to ask. I am a tribesman from Chang tribe Yuan Feng faction, a Shan generation descendant who is the sole child in my family. My father is Chang Sheng Dun, and my mother is Chang Cui." Fang Yuan sighed, replying in a solemn expression.

Old Ge tribe leader's eyes were wide as he stared at Fang Yuan in shock: "You, you are really Warrior Chang Shan Yin?!"

Chapter 440: Ten Year Interval of Wind and Snow

Ge tribe leader had some doubts when he heard Chang Shan Yin's name in his subordinate's report.

Now, when he received Fang Yuan's confirmation, he was very moved.

All the elders present there also cried out in shock.

"Chang Shan Yin?" Ge Guang was sitting at the side and said with some doubts.

"You are young, not knowing is normal." Ge tribe leader heaved a sigh and instructed, "Son, toast to Chang Shan Yin. He is not only your benefactor but more importantly, he is our northern plains' hero!"

"Old tribe leader." Fang Yuan gave a bitter smile and placed down his wine cup, "I am only a broken vagabond, not a hero. Maybe it was the blessing of longevity heaven, I was able to luckily escape from the edge of death. But I have slept for twenty years and when I woke up, everything seems to have changed. I am an unfilial child and have no face to return to my tribe..."

Tears dripped down Fang Yuan's eyes as he said this.

The elders sighed.

Ge tribe leader promptly consoled: "Benefactor Chang Shan Yin, what are you saying? If you are not our northern plains' hero, who can it be? Ha Tu Gu's group of bandits were so savage and who knows how many tribes were looted by them, the weaker ones were even wiped out and even the livestock were not spared."

"By killing them, you have eliminated a huge threat in our northern plains. Your mother was injured by a villain, it was not because you were unfilial. On the contrary, your morals and righteous conduct were widely spread and known by all of us. Your return is the fortune for our northern plains' righteous path."

"Lord tribe leader is correct!"

"So sir was actually Chang Shan Yin, it is really our honor for being able to see the hero."

"That's right, the return of hero Chang Shan Yin is a great fortunately event for our righteous path!"

The elders praised repeatedly.

Ge Guang's eyes shone, he only knew now that Fang Yuan actually had such a great origin and so many tales. This intensified his respect towards Fang Yuan.

"Let the past remain as the past. Everyone, our meeting is fate, let's drink to it." Fang Yuan did not want to talk of these; he understood the past of Chang Shan Yin, but it was best if he avoided the topic.

He showed a depressed and gloomy expression.

Everyone observed his expression and did not mention the topic again, only speaking of joyous events.

After confirming Chang Shan Yin's identity, Fang Yuan received much passionate treatment.

The banquet lasted all the way from afternoon to late at night. The elders were lying down after drinking too much, if not for Fang Yuan pretending to be drunk, he would not have been able to leave.

Next day, Ge tribe leader invited Fang Yuan to banquet again.

"Benefactor Chang Shan Yin, this is a small gift as thanks for saving my son's life. Please take it!" Before the banquet started, the old tribe leader gave a million primeval stones to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was somewhat surprised as he had not thought he would get such a big gift.

Ge tribe was only a small-mid scale tribe which was not in a good financial situation; it could be seen from the position of their camp and the clothings of the people.

Currently, Fang Yuan was in poverty; these northern plains' primeval stones could be used to resolve his current problems. He accepted the gift: "Ge tribe leader, I did not rescue Ge Guang for money. However, to be honest, I am currently out of primeval stones. I won't be polite then. I will definitely repay Ge tribe's kindness in the future."

Hearing Fang Yuan's final sentence, Ge tribe leader, Ge Guang and the group of elders all smiled.

Being able to make friends and connect to such a heroic expert like Chang Shan Yin was the thing that a small-mid scale tribe like theirs would dream about.

The banquet continued and the atmosphere was much more bustling than yesterday.

Yesterday was only a first meeting, and today, both sides were familiar with each other. Fang Yuan raised his cup and proposed to all the elders; he remembered all their names clearly.

This made all the elders feel overwhelmed, making them feel even more closer to Chang Shan Yin.

During the banquet, some people were inevitably curious of Fang Yuan's experiences.

Fang Yuan had already prepared a good tale and told it to everyone. It was the same thing he told to deceive Ge Yao, but compared to deceiving a young girl, he spoke more carefully this time.

He recounted his events and said his cultivation had fallen from rank four peak stage to initial stage due to injuries.

His words had no flaws, causing everyone to gasp, sigh and feel even more respect towards him.

And Fang Yuan just kept on sighing, not caring the slightest bit about his past accomplishments; his gaze showed the vicissitudes of time and his tone was melancholic.

Ge tribesmen realized the legendary hero also had a painful side to him; seeing such a sincere person, they grieved and sympathized with him, feeling even more closer to Fang Yuan.

On the third day, Ge tribe still continued the banquet with very high liveliness.

This time, a strange elder appeared in the banquet. He was in charge of Ge tribe's intelligence, and just as Fang Yuan had reached the camp, he had received an order to lead a group to search for Ge Yao.

"Sigh, it is all my fault. I have a crafty girl, I have spoiled her too much, she actually fled her marriage!" Ge tribe leader sighed.

"Right, big brother Chang Shan Yin, you returned from the poisonous grassland. Did you see my little sister on your way?" Ge Guang asked.

Fang Yuan calmly replied with no hesitation, his expression extremely natural: "I am sorry, I only had wolves as my companion on my way. You guys were the first humans I saw, so I felt even closer to you."

Ge Guang was also casually asking and did not have any expectations.

Besides, the poisonous grassland was so huge, Fang Yuan not running into Ge Yao was also normal. If they met each other, it would instead be a rare thing.

"This insensible little sister, I really don't know where she fled to without leaving behind any message. Sigh... it has become troublesome, Man tribe leader's third son Man Duo is the person who wants to marry her. Now, sister has fled the marriage, and because he failed to obtain her, Man Duo might take it out on Ge tribe."

Ge Guang sighed with a frown on his face.

The other elders also looked gloomy. Man tribe's pressure on them had been increasing these days.

None of them knew that Chang Shan Yin whom they had been enthusiastically entertaining for three days had already killed Ge Yao.

"Trees die when moved, humans live when they move. Brothers of Ge tribe, why are you reluctant to leave this place? There is only just over a year left until the great blizzard. You can migrate to the north, participate in the heroes assembly and rely on Huang Jin tribe. With this, you can hide in Wang Ting blessed land when the great blizzard comes." Fang Yuan persuaded.

The Gu Master world was a world of cruel environment and was not easy to survive in.

In southern border, humans made fortified villages which could defend against the beast tides, but northern plains had no mountains and the tribes would have to suffer the baptism of wind and snow.

Every ten years in northern plains, there would be a great blizzard that engulfs the entire northern plains.

It would last for months, the sky would be gloomy and snow would drift everywhere. Cold winds would whip around like blades and white snow would cover up the world. The whole vast plains would freeze into a world of ice and snow.

Every time the blizzard occurs, it would bring about a large number of deaths. Wolves, foxes, eagles, vegetations and humans; none could escape.

Especially during the blizzard, large numbers of strong wild Gu worms would appear.

Often, after the blizzard, the large scale tribes of northern plains would shrink down to mid-scale and mid-scale would shrink down to small scale due to the large numbers of casualties.

Ge tribe leader heaved a long sigh: "Brother Shan Yin, I am old and no longer have ambitions I had when I was young. If we seek refuge with Huang Jin clan, our Ge tribe will be dragged into the whirlpool of conflicts. It is good if we succeed, but the consequences for failure is too severe. Our Ge clan had been making progress with great difficulty, we won't be able to endure the loss."

"The struggle in the imperial court is not something small clans like ours can participate in. Actually, this environment is not bad, soil is fertile and there are abundant resources. There is even Hong Yan valley nearby where underground fire burns. During the blizzard, our tribe can move inside the valley and survive this disaster."

However, Hong Yan valley was firmly controlled by the overlord of this place, Man tribe.

Ge tribe would need to come in terms with Man tribe to enter Hong Yan valley.

Man Duo's marriage proposal to Ge Yao was an extremely good opportunity. For the whole tribe's benefits, sacrificing a girl's happiness for marriage was a very good deal to Ge tribe leader and Ge Guang.

Sacrificing an individual benefits for the whole, this was the most common scene in an organization.

However, Ge Yao fled the marriage with her whereabouts unknown. Man tribe has been pressuring them to hand over Ge Yao, but Ge tribe was not able to do that.

Fang Yuan immediately realized the intention of Ge tribe leader from his words, they wanted to seek refuge with Man tribe.

He understood this very well but felt some pity inwardly.

Heroes assembly was his next target destination. If he could make Ge tribe migrate, he would be able to journey smoothly without having to face the many dangers along the way.

After mentioning the blizzard and Man tribe, everyone's mood turned grim.

"Brother Shan Yin, are you really not going to return to Chang tribe?" Ge tribe leader asked.

"Of course I can't return. If I return, wouldn't it be easy for my impersonation to be exposed?!" Fang Yuan thought in his mind while speaking, "Sigh, in my current circumstance, I am unable to face my elders and tribesmen."

Ge tribe leader nodded his head, expressing his understanding and feeling some sympathy.

Chang Shan Yin slept for twenty years and after waking up, everything had changed. His mother had died, his wife had been remarried to his brother. Chang tribe had become his sore spot, it was a normal thing for him to not able to face these for a while.

In the previous banquet, Fang Yuan had mentioned he wanted to go to the heroes assembly and also recover his cultivation quickly.

"Brother, if you really want to participate in the heroes assembly, just relying on your current wolf group, it would not be enough for your journey. It will be better for you to rest for a few days." The old clan leader proposed.

Fang Yuan nodded and did not object: "I have the same idea. But this way, I will have to continue imposing on your tribe."

"Of course not, it is our honor that you are a guest here!" The old tribe leader laughed heartily, expressing his willingness.

Ge Guang also smiled: "A few days later, the surrounding few tribes will hold a market together. Uncle Chang can come take a look."

Like this, Fang Yuan stayed over at Ge tribe.

Several days later, Ge tribe decamped and moved towards the southwest, converging with several other tribes.

An enormous tribal market rapidly emerged.

Fang Yuan rejected Ge Guang's invitation and entered this hustling and bustling market alone.

Chapter 441: “Fortune Rivalling Heaven” Ma Hong Yun

"Come, have a taste of this fragrant rice cake."

"Selling tea, selling tea, this is top grade brick tea!"

"Ah Su family's kumis, we are a ten year old brand, anyone who drinks this will know."

　　...

There was a huge mix of small stalls on the ground as different smells entered the nose, shouting and bargaining noises were heard all over the place.

Fang Yuan walked among them, almost at a shoulder touching distance with the surrounding people, the festive mood was so intense.

Not only was food on sale, but clothing too.

Ordinary sheep skin robe, dog skin robe, or the higher quality bull skin robe. There were beautiful fox snow robes, or the wolf skin robe that had metal pieces in them which were often worn by warriors.

Children were having fun at the food stalls, while men were bargaining at the weapon stalls. Women were choosing gems, pearls, or gold and silver accessories.

As he walked in, Fang Yuan saw a square that was assembled casually.

On the square, there were large wooden cages filled with people.

Outside the cage, there were specialized Gu Masters guarding the place, as a fat man was shouting at the top of his lungs: "Selling slave, five male slaves for half a primeval stone!"

Fang Yuan took a look and knew that it was the flourishing slave trade in northern plains.

These people were from tribes who lost in battles, after being captured alive, they lost their freedom and became commodity.

Inside the cages, there were children who were thin and wore no clothes, there were also kneeling men who lowered their heads while locked by a steel chain. Of course, there were women too."

The fat man shouted for a long time, his forehead was sweating but the passersby were only watching. His eyes rolled as he thought of an idea, opening the wooden cage and letting a woman whose face was full of dirt walk out.

"Look, this is a top quality woman."

As he shouted, he ripped off the torn clothes of the woman, exposing her breasts.

"Look, what a plump breast she has!"

Next, he turned the woman to the other side and slapped her butt in public.

"Look again, such a huge butt, she can have many children. Buy her home to have kids, you can even use her for manual labor!"

During the process, the woman's expression was numb, she was like a wooden puppet that could be manipulated by anyone.

As the fat man shouted earnestly, some commotion finally occurred in the crowd.

Someone asked: "How much are you selling her for?"

"Three taels of primeval stone. Just three taels of primeval stone." The fat man raised three fingers.

Three taels of primeval stone, it was not even half a piece.

But the person who asked for the price suddenly shouted: "What, three taels! Is this robbery, I might as well save up two more taels to buy a big stomach horse, that is much more worth it!"

The fat man's oily face trembled as he spit on the ground: "Rubbish! You can buy a woman and ride her in bed, but if you buy a big stomach horse, although you can ride it, can it make babies for you? Poor miser, get lost if you do not want to buy!"

The fat man was a rank one Gu Master, and the person scolded was a mortal, he immediately shrunk his neck and walked away feebly.

Fang Yuan gave a few glances of interest before retracting his gaze.

The slaves that the fat man was selling were just mortals, they could not fetch a good price. But if he sold variant humans, they would be sold for a much higher price. If he sold Gu Masters, they would be high quality slaves, the price would be the highest.

Seeing these slaves, Fang Yuan could not help but think of Ma Hong Yun.

This person was born as a slave, but he had heaven defying luck.

First as a slave, he participated in battle. When his tribe lost, he saved the young tribe leader by pure luck when escaping for his life. Because of this huge merit, he was given the surname Ma, and was no longer a slave.

He became an ordinary mortal in Ma tribe. In order to earn a living, he went out to hunt, but because of his poor skills, he had no earnings. When he returned, he was tripped by a rock, he smashed this rock in anger, but discovered a white silver relic Gu under the rock. He contributed this rock to his tribe's young tribe leader.

The young tribe leader needed this white silver relic Gu and was overjoyed, not only did he reward Ma Hong Yun handsomely, he even gave him an opportunity to cultivate.

Ma Hong Yun awakened his aperture and had B grade aptitude, but did not have any useful Gu worms. He was often bullied by nearby Gu Masters, and was thrown into the river once.

Ma Hong Yun who could not swim drank a lot of water as he flowed downstream along the river.

At the lower stream, Sheng tribe leader's third daughter, Sheng Ling Er, was bathing. Ma Hong Yun saw everything and according to Sheng tribe's rules, the beautiful Sheng tribe genius female Gu Master had no choice but to become his wife.

Ma Hong Yun thus received a lot of help from Sheng Ling Er, he never lacked any Gu worms or primeval stones.

In fact, Sheng Ling Er even stole her tribe's precious Gu to raise his aptitude to A grade.

When the matter was exposed, Sheng tribe leader did not want his daughter to marry this poor lad, thus he secretly sent an expert to kill Ma Hong Yun.

But this expert had an argument with someone along the way and was killed by another expert.

Ma Hong Yun and Sheng Ling Er thus became husband and wife, and held an important position in the tribe, he was hated by Sheng tribesmen due to jealousy, and they plotted against him secretly.

He had no choice but to escape to poison grassland, and just as he was about to be killed by the poison beard wolves, he found Chang Shan Yin. After saving Chang Shan Yin, he became his loyal subject.

Just like this, due to his ridiculously good luck on many occasions, Ma Hong Yun rose up slowly, eventually becoming the lord of the imperial court.

After Hei Lou Lan died, he became the overlord of the imperial court for over a hundred years, over a dozen times.

Later, he obtained Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's partial inheritance, and became a Gu Immortal. He was even given a blessed land by a Gu Master.

When battle and conflicts raged in the world, Ma Hong Yun became one of the powerhouses of northern plains, resisting the grand army from central continent and gaining overwhelming reputation.

"At this time, Ma Hong Yun should be thirteen years old. It is a pity I do not know his true identity. Ma Hong Yun is only a name given to him after he saved Ma tribe's young tribe leader. Ma tribe is part of the Huang Jin bloodline left behind by Giant Sun, to vie for the imperial court, they had been expanding these few years, absorbing the members of many tribes. I wonder if Ma Hong Yun has already become Ma tribe's slave."

Fang Yuan collected his thoughts, and found himself outside a gambling den.

There were two couplets on the door.

Left was: Show some courage, gain the fortune of the four seasons.

Right was: Show some skill, obtain the wealth of the four cardinal directions.

Across, it wrote: Luck changes with time.

The gambling den had great business, Fang Yuan was moved.

"With my experience, I might be able to earn a small fortune." With this thought, Fang Yuan smiled, thinking of Ma Hong Yun.

This lad with overwhelming luck, he was deceived by someone who gave him the lowest grade rock to gamble with him.

Under such absurd circumstances, he obtained a rank five Gu!

Fang Yuan still had some business at the moment, he did not enter the gambling den yet.

He walked past the entrance of the gambling den, and entered the central area of this market.

This place was much quieter, there was less traffic flow and almost all passersby were Gu Masters. Even if there were mortals, they were attendants and followed beside the Gu Master, lowering their heads as they carried goods. Other than that, there were some young masters and young ladies who had not awakened their aperture.

Although there were no guards, there was a clear distinction between the two areas for mortals and Gu Masters.

The difference in strength was a formless barrier, it divided the two types of people with evidently different lives.

Fang Yuan walked briskly, wherever he went, Gu Masters gave him a look of admiration and respect, when they were in front of him, they would stop and give way to him.

Some people started talking among themselves: "Why is there a rank four expert?"

"This person has an unfamiliar face, he does not seem to be from the few large tribes around here."

"Be careful, whenever the market opens, there will be some demonic Gu Masters who come in to get rid of their loot."

Rank three and four were completely different.

Rank three were the middle pillar, most tribe elders of major tribes were at this level. Rank four were experts among Gu Masters, most tribe leaders were rank four, and they could roam the mortal realm freely without restraint.

Rank four initial stage aura made every action of his attract the attention of everyone.

Reverence, curiosity, or apprehension.

This place was solely for the business of Gu Masters.

There was a Gu refinement area, where Gu refinement were done in place of a Gu Master, at the same time they sold and bought recipes.

Fang Yuan lacked the recipe of the wolf enslavement Gu, after a few transactions, he bought the recipe for the rank one to three wolf enslavement Gu.

The recipe for rank four was held in the hands of the few large tribes, it was rarely seen in the market.

Thereafter, Fang Yuan went to the restaurant, but did not manage to find any top quality wine.

He went to the largest shop next.

"Esteemed expert, your presence is our shop's honor. Please come in." The shopkeeper was a rank three elderly Gu Master, he came out personally to attend to Fang Yuan.

"I need large numbers of wolf enslavement Gu." Fang Yuan stated his needs immediately.

"Yes, please come with me for further discussion." The elderly brought Fang Yuan to a beautiful room on the third floor.

After some bargaining, Fang Yuan bought five rank three wolf enslavement Gu and thirty-eight rank two wolf enslavement Gu.

The shopkeeper was rubbing his palms in joy, he knew he had met a huge client: "Esteemed customer, is there anything you still need, feel free to state them."

"Do you have defensive Gu?" Fang Yuan asked.

The elderly reported a long list of Gu names, and Fang Yuan shook his head as he listened. There was one rank four Gu but it did not fit his enslavement path. The rest were all ordinary Gu worms.

Next, Fang Yuan asked about flying Gu.

Flying Gu were rarely seen, because it had a steep learning curve. Normally, only outstanding members of large tribes would train in it from young. But because they had their tribe's resources, they did not need to buy flying Gu.

As for other Gu Masters, very few tried to learn flying.

The shopkeeper said proudly: "Customer, you came to the right place. In this entire market, only my shop has a rank four flying cloud Gu!"

But Fang Yuan shook his head.

Although flying cloud Gu could ascend to a high altitude, it had poor maneuverability and had average speed, it was suitable for Gu Masters who did not have proper flying skills.

For him, he might as well use the rank three eagle wings Gu, it could twist and turn easily in the sky, he could use it more efficiently.

After buying one eagle wings Gu, Fang Yuan asked about the bone bamboo Gu and ghost fire Gu.

He needed these two Gu to repair the rank five battle bone wheel.

The shop had many rank two ghost fire Gu, but there was none of the rank one bone bamboo Gu.

The shopkeeper laughed bitterly: "Customer, my apologies. All the bone bamboo Gu in the market had been bought by Man tribe's new external tribe elder. Not just my shop, but none of the other shops have any left."

"Oh? Who is this person?" Fang Yuan's gaze shone.

Chapter 442: Jun Strength Gu

Man tribe owned Hong Yan valley, they had won a few battles these years and had expanded greatly.

Northern plains was different from southern border.

Southern borders had a forest and mountain terrain, it was easy to defend but hard to attack, long distance travelling causes huge expenditure. Southern border clans worked on self development, accumulating slowly and growing stably, keeping a pure bloodline.

But northern plains was a huge grassland, there were lots of conquests going on. The tribes of northern plains rise up fast but also fall just as quickly. A few wins might allow a small size tribe to become a medium size tribe, and from a medium size tribe, expand into a large size tribe. But one loss could also cause this large size tribe to break down into numerous small size tribes.

Man tribe had absorbed Shi tribe recently, and the elder Shi Wu from Shi tribe became Man tribe's external elder.

He was a bone path Gu Master, he was the one who bought all the bone bamboo Gu in the market, as he claimed to be researching a new bone path recipe.

Fang Yuan memorised this person to heart, before asking the shopkeeper about soul path and strength path Gu worms.

"I have a rank one jin strength Gu, it can raise the strength of a Gu Master by one jin[1]. Each Gu is sold for two hundred and twenty primeval stones."

"I have the rank two strength of ten jin Gu, it raises the Gu Master's strength by ten jin, it is sold for six hundred and ninety primeval stones."

"I also have the rank three jun strength Gu, one jun is thirty jin, each Gu is sold for four thousand five hundred and fifty primeval stones."

"Although I do not have the rank four strength of ten jun Gu, if customer needs it, i can arrange for it to be transported over, each strength of ten jun Gu is sold for thirty-six thousand primeval stones."

The shopkeeper gave a chain of prices that he was extremely familiar with.

At the end, he added: "Of course, this is only the jin strength Gu and jun strength Gu. If customer wants to walk on the strength path, and require beast strength Gu, we also have wolf strength Gu. It can give you the strength of a wolf, gaining stamina and endurance as well. I also have horse strength Gu, it can give you the strength of a horse, it is most useful for running."

Before, Fang Yuan was using beast strength Gu to walk on the ancient strength path. Jin strength Gu and jun strength Gu were new popular alternatives that appeared in the last few hundred years.

Although strength path was weak and no longer had its former glory, there was still developments done for it.

The one who had this contribution was a famous rank seven Gu Immortal in northern plains called Chu Du, titled 'Domination Immortal'. He was the one who invented the jin strength Gu and jun strength Gu, and even refined the rank six Immortal Gu 'Strength of a Thousand Jun'.

A jun was thirty jin.

A thousand jun was thirty thousand jin.

In one of Earth's legends, the Victorious Fighting Buddha's Jingu Bang was only thirteen thousand five hundred jin. Er Lang Shen's 'Three-pointed, Double-edged Lance' was only twenty five thousand two hundred jin.

Chu Du became a Gu Immortal three hundred years ago, the recipe he refined was widely spread, quickly becoming the main branch of the strength path in northern plains.

Ancient strength path used beast strength Gu, like green bull strength Gu, Biao strength Gu, dragon strength Gu and so on. However, because the materials from the ancient times were already extremely rare by now, the cost of refining Gu was huge.

Domination Immortal Chu Du's recipe was superior in that the materials were easy to find and had low cost, and the success rate of the Gu refinement was higher than beast strength Gu.

Northern plains was probably the region where strength path was most flourishing at the moment. Northern plains had battles and conquests often, with strength path's low cost, they gave evident increase in strength to low rank Gu Masters.

Thus, many Gu Masters in northern plains cultivated strength path as their minor path.

They often fought in fierce battles, when they expend their primeval essence, they would need their physical bodies to fight. Physical strength was very important then.

There is a phrase on Earth: war is the catalyst for technological advancement. This sentence worked perfectly well in this world as well. Northern plains was a place where new Gu worms were constantly invented.

From that Shi Wu elder who joined Man tribe, one could see the attitude that northern plains Gu Masters had towards innovation.

Domination Immortal later died in battle, by the hands of Feng Jiu Ge who descended from the heavenly court. After he died, he was crowned as the 'Twilight of Strength Path' by future generations, after his death was announced, countless Gu Masters in northern plains cried painfully.

"Sigh... the number of talents and geniuses in this world is like the number of stars in the night sky, the number of talented people are like carps in the river. The five regions are too big, the size of one Earth cannot compare to even one region. Especially in the battle five hundred years later, dragons and snakes rise from the land, experts and powerhouses compete, and old monsters come out of seclusion one after another, as new talents rise up to power. Countless heroes, conquerors, the differing personalities from the righteous and demonic paths clash and engage in a life-and-death battle. It is truly a grand and exciting event that would go down in history."

"I have already used old removal Gu secretly to remove ancient bronze skin, essence iron bones, and golden steel tendons, and even my beast phantoms. Firstly, these strength path beast phantoms originate from southern border, they would be restricted in northern plains, and could not be used well. Secondly, if I summon a beast phantom, there is a danger of exposing my identity."

"My greatest advantage now is Dang Hun mountain, and my five hundred years of experience, with the blessed land's resources, I can walk on the enslavement path. But enslavement path has a weakness, that is the 'beheading the leader' tactic, thus I need strength path to go along with it. Since I have Chang Shan Yin's appearance now, I also need to merge into northern plains, I should use this jun strength Gu."

Fang Yuan's thought flickered as he made a decision, requesting for the rank four strength of ten jun Gu from the shopkeeper.

Next, he looked at the soul path Gu worms.

There were much more soul path Gu worms than strength path.

There were ghost fire Gu, ghost cry Gu, ghost face Gu, ghost axe Gu and so on for attacking. There were ghost cage Gu, ghost hand Gu, ghost hitting wall for confinement and confusion.

For defense, there were ghost sealing shirt Gu, soul shield Gu and others. For healing, there were ghost qi Gu, ghost tears Gu and others. For investigation, there was ghost eye Gu. For movement, there were soul fly Gu, and elusive ghost Gu.

There were also ghost soldier Gu, impermanence ghost, air travel ghost, and nine son mother ghost Gu, all of them had to do with enslavement path.

This was the true manner of a great path.

Strength path was extremely weak now, while soul path was still standing strong, this point could be easily seen here.

Strength path Gu worms only consisted of jin strength Gu, jun strength Gu, and beast strength Gu, most were for attacking. In terms of defense, investigation, and assistance, there were little. It was hard to create a Gu set from just strength path Gu.

As for soul path, there were many Gu worms that were in all the different aspects. Forming into a set, they could help each other and obtain greater effects.

Look at that Domination Immortal Chu Du, he was a strength path Gu Immortal, but he used other Gu worms for defense, investigation, and storage etc.

Fang Yuan came with an objective, he set aside all these soul path Gu worms, only looking at those which could be used to refine the soul.

There were no rank four Gu for that, but a bunch of rank three.

There were divine soul Gu, dragon soul Gu, ice soul Gu, dream soul Gu, moon soul Gu, general soul Gu, grudge soul Gu, poem soul Gu, horse soul Gu, heroic soul Gu, qi spirit Gu, body spirit Gu, cloud spirit Gu, wind spirit Gu, tiger spirit Gu, and others.

These Gu worms could refine the soul, they all had their unique use.

For example, refining the soul into ice soul, in the future when the Gu Master uses ice type Gu worms, they would gain a considerate boost. Cloud spirit, wind spirit, had the same effects.

If one used dragon soul Gu to refine a dragon soul, when he uses dragon strength Gu, dragon scales Gu, or dragon travel Gu, there would be a boost to the effect.

Fang Yuan looked for a while, and did not find any Gu that was more suitable for him, thus he chose the wolf soul Gu that he had planned to buy.

From ancient times, soul and enslavement were of the same origins.

Enslavement path was originally split from the soul path, when Gu Masters combined it with the immemorial wisdom path, the enslavement path finally became an independent path.

Beast enslavement Gu, slavery Gu, they were used to control the soul, allowing one to become a ruler of the mind.

If Fang Yuan refined the wolf soul, it would greatly help him in enslaving wolf packs.

The rank three wolf soul Gu was seven thousand and seven hundred primeval stones. Fang Yuan bought them in bulk, buying all of the stock in the shop, getting all eight wolf soul Gu.

Wolf soul Gu's effort could be stacked, a rank three wolf soul Gu was not enough to refine Fang Yuan's hundred man soul.

Wild Gu worms had their own will, they were hard to refine. But the Gu worms Fang Yuan bought had already been refined by others, thus when the transaction ended, all these Gu were in Fang Yuan's control.

He kept all these Gu inside his aperture, and left the shop, going to other shops.

His aim was rank two and three wolf enslavement Gu, as well as rank three wolf soul Gu.

A million primeval stones was insufficient, but what Fang Yuan wanted were common rank two and three Gu.

He did want to buy rank four Gu.

But this market was too small, there were few rank four Gu, and were all not the ones he wanted.

After three days, Fang Yuan became famous in the market. Every shop knew that there was a rank four expert buying Gu in bulk.

By the fifth day, Fang Yuan spent a lot already, over five to six hundred thousand primeval stones.

During this period, he would walk around the market's ranch often.

In the ranch, there were many livestock sold, of which big stomach horses were most popular. This horse, even mortals needed it badly. As for those who bought the hump wolves for battle, they were mostly Gu Masters.

There were also many Gu Masters who caught wild beasts to sell here. Like bulls, horses, falcons etc. On the grassland, the most commonly seen were wolves, they were also sold in large numbers.

Fang Yuan asked around, comparing goods and prices, until he saw a pack of thick back wolves that he wanted.

Fang Yuan had poison beard wolves and wind wolves. It was hard to replenish poison beard wolves, and since they were weak in the sunlight, they were destined to be eliminated. Wind wolves had fast speed, while thick back wolves had high defense. If they could be added into his wolf army, they would cooperate well together, and form a proper wolf pack.

But on the ninth day, Fang Yuan accidentally found out that among a group of water wolves, there was a young mutated beast.

He immediately bought these water wolves without causing suspicion, getting a great deal for himself.

The market lasted thirteen days.

Fang Yuan bought over a thousand water wolves, and many Gu refinement materials, as well as food to feed his Gu worms, as he left on the tenth day.

After his purchases, he had only three thousand primeval stones left on him.

Money was spent like flowing water, Ge Guang watched in amazement as he admired 'Chang Shan Yin' secretly, this hero truly had a grand disposition.

Fang Yuan followed Ge tribe and returned to his original place to stay.

He cultivated with all his heart, using wolf soul Gu to refine his soul while refining Gu on the other hand.

After two failures, he successfully refined the rank three golden back wolf skin Gu into the rank four azure wolf skin Gu.

Azure wolf skin Gu was used for defense, although it was common, it fixed Fang Yuan's problem of insufficient defense.

On this day, he finished his soul refinement and stopped cultivating, when a cry was heard outside his room.

"What happened?" He opened the door and asked the Gu Master who was guarding the place.

The Gu Master said grimly: "Our big missy Ge Yao died. The search team found her torn clothes in poison grassland, she was killed by poison beard wolves!"

[1] This is about 500 grams.

Chapter 443: Man Tribe’s Challenge

A month later, Ge Yao's death was finally discovered.

The news spread as many Ge tribesmen cried. Although Ge Yao had a troublesome personality, she was kind-hearted and the beauty of the tribe, people loved her. She had many pursuers in Ge tribe.

"Oh my daughter, it was father who harmed you..." Old Ge tribe leader was extremely upset, falling terribly ill.

Ge Guang was the stand-in tribe leader with the elders assisting him. Ge tribe was anguished and upset, they had a heavy mood.

Ge Yao's death had huge impacts. Man tribe leader's third son Man Duo fell in love with Ge Yao at first sight, he had been demanding for her, now that she was dead, where were they going to find a girl for him?

Man tribe was a large tribe, they had expanded greatly these years, and had absorbed many small tribes in the process. After a few victories, their morale was high, and they were even more arrogant against the despondent Ge tribe. During their conversations, they gave Ge Guang great pressure as they demanded fiercely.

Ge tribe was a newly arrived tribe, they were not as huge as Man tribe, and now that they had lost their home, they had to live in someone else's territory, relying on Hong Yan valley during the snowy climate. Thus, Ge Guang was very passive now, he was extremely anxious.

　　...

In his room, Fang Yuan sat on his bed as he opened his eyes.

On his right palm was a wolf soul Gu.

This Gu was about thumb-sized, it was like a grey wolf-shaped doll, giving off an eerie blue light.

"This is the ninth wolf soul Gu." Fang Yuan injected his primeval essence and the wolf soul Gu expanded, in a few breaths' time, it turned into a grey-white wolf soul.

The wolf soul opened its mouth, howling silently as it crashed into Fang Yuan's body.

This impact was silent, but Fang Yuan could feel his soul trembling, as his eyes went into a daze.

The wolf soul directly crashed into his soul, the originally human-shaped hundred man soul underwent some reaction, and lost its human form, fusing with the wolf soul into a surging soul mist.

The soul mist did not disperse, instead it moved and rolled around in Fang Yuan's body, showing a wolf's head, tail, or even Fang Yuan's appearance at times.

After five minutes, the soul mist gathered and formed a new human soul.

Except this human soul was different.

Fang Yuan's hundred man soul earlier was completely his own appearance, his eyes, ears and nose were all the same. But after going through nine wolf soul Gu's refinement, although the hundred man soul was still human-shaped, there was a pair of wolf ears on his head, and his hair extended to his waist, his eyes also became wolf eyes, his entire body was thinner and his nose was sharper.

Before, his hundred man soul was huge and was almost bursting his actual body. But now, after refinement, it was more condensed and the color had turned from pale-white to a slight hint of grey-white.

Fang Yuan calculated, when he finishes using his wolf soul Gu, the hundred man soul would be refined to its limits.

By then, his entire soul would become half-man half-wolf, the so-called wolfman soul.

Wolfman soul is many times stronger than an ordinary hundred man soul.

After having the wolfman soul, Fang Yuan would be able to continue strengthening his soul, raising the hundred man soul to thousand or even ten thousand man soul.

Of course, ten thousand man soul was not the limit, there was even hundred million man soul.

"In theory, the soul can strengthen limitlessly. Back then, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable who created the soul path definitely surpassed hundred million man soul! His Demon Venerable Soul had a thousand arms and palms, three heads, the front head had dragon horns, lion mane, snake eyes, and elephant tusks. The left head had a peach forehead, grass hair, and three flower-like eyes. The right head had a cloud fringe, lightning eyes, fire ears, and golden mouth. He was unbelievable strong, his might was immeasurable. Even now, this appearance was still deeply worshipped and adored by many people. Many mortals in southern border use clay to create his statue, to pray to and give offerings."

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was the number one soul cultivator in history. Fang Yuan's wolfman soul now was like a ant against a giant, he still needed to grow stronger.

After a little rest, Fang Yuan took out the strength of ten jun Gu.

This Gu was an iron weight, it was very heavy to carry.

Fang Yuan bought five strength of ten jun Gu, he was already using the third now, his body's physical strength had increased to twenty jun, that is, six hundred jin.

The rank four strength of ten jun Gu was weaker than rank four beast strength Gu, but its advantage was that the strength could be stacked.

Previously, Fang Yuan had used a kunlun bull strength Gu, and obtained the beast phantom of the kunlun bull. But if he used a second kunlun bull strength Gu, there would be no effects, and he would not get another beast phantom either.

But jun strength Gu did not have this restriction, it could be stacked until the body's limit was reached.

Of course, although Fang Yuan had the strength of six hundred jin, he could not unleash them all at once normally.

The common weaknesses of strength path, jun strength Gu still had them. Otherwise, Domination Immortal Chu Du would not be called the 'twilight of strength path', but the 'rise of strength path'.

Of course, similar beast strength Gu could be stacked, but an additional beast fetus Gu was needed to do so.

Many different recipes of beast fetus Gu were passed down. But even so, the materials needed for the Gu refinement were very rare, as the cost of the Gu refinement was too high, and the success rate was inferior to jun strength Gu, it eventually got eliminated in the competition.

Fang Yuan activated his primeval essence, injecting them into jun strength Gu. The jun strength Gu flew above his head, giving off a strange light. The light shone on Fang Yuan as his body was steadily modified.

But at this time, there were knocks on his door.

Soon after, a voice was heard: "Uncle Chang Shan Yin, junior Ge Guang would like to meet you."

Fang Yuan let him in, only to see that Ge Guang was in a pathetic state, there was even a white bone arrow on his shoulder, he was in a terrible condition.

Upon seeing Fang Yuan, Ge Guang kneeled on the ground, his eyes were red, begging: "Uncle, please save me."

Fang Yuan's gaze shone, he had an answer in his heart, as he spoke: "What happened? Is Man tribe attacking us at full force, have they charged into Ge tribe's camp already?"

Ge Guang answered: "Uncle is half right, the problem is Man tribe. The Man tribe leader's third son Man Duo heard that father was bedridden and unconscious, thus he immediately brought his Man tribe experts over to challenge us, wanting us to hand over my sister Ge Yao. But my sister is already dead, how can I hand her over to him? No matter how I explained, that Man Duo lad did not believe me. According to the rules of the grassland, we Ge tribe have to accept the challenge. Now, he had already killed our tribe's third elder, and even injured three people, even I lost to them."

Fang Yuan's guess was completely right, these few days, Man tribe had been oppressive and tyrannical, the more Ge tribe endured, the more it fuelled Man tribe's arrogance.

Although Fang Yuan had been cultivating hard these days, he was not in closed cultivation, he was clear of the outside situation.

"Speaking of which, Chang Shan Yin's return to northern plains requires a grand stage to create some commotion. I should use this chance to announce the return of the former hero."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan helped Ge Guang up and said: "During these days, I have been imposing on Ge tribe, I cannot watch from the sidelines, bring me there."

"Uncle, I thank you on behalf of our entire tribe!" Ge Guang was overjoyed.

The two walked out, but before they got to the entrance, they heard the shouts and screams outside.

"Ge tribe is full of cowardly rats, come out and accept your death!" This was the voice of a young man.

"Man Duo, you are going too far!" A Ge tribe elder screamed.

"Hehehe, so what if I am bullying you. Leopards and wolves capture their prey, eagles and falcons bully small birds, this is the rule of the world! Quickly hand over Ge Yao, otherwise I will continue challenging you and kill every single member of Ge tribe."

"Despicable! If old tribe leader was here, would you dare?" Ge tribe elder rebuked.

Man Duo was furious: "Hmph, you are the despicable ones, you agreed to the wedding but now you refuse to hand over the woman. You went back on your words! I know, you are hiding Ge Yao, trying to stall for time. First, you said she ran away, now you said she's dead. Do you think I am a fool? If a mere rabbit dares to toy with a wolf, you will have to pay with your life. Shi Wu, continue beating them, challenge them. Ge tribe, quickly send your next victim here to fight. Hahaha!"

Ge tribe elders' expressions were pale, they looked at each other but none dared to go up.

Shi Wu was huge and bald, with his bulging muscles, he walked onto the stage with a cruel smile.

He was rank three peak stage, having great strength. The elder that Ge tribe sacrificed was beaten to death on the spot.

He walked on the center of the stage, staring at Ge tribe's camp: "Why is no one here? Don't tell me you are afraid!"

Ge tribe was furious and ashamed, fire burnt in their eyes as they stared at Shi Wu.

"Cowardly chickens, let me give you some courage. I have a hundred thousand primeval stones here, if anyone dares to come here and defeat me, I will hand the primeval stones over to you."

No one answered him.

Shi Wu laughed in a frenzy: "Ge tribe, Ge tribe, you are but a bunch of rabbits and sheep!"

"Have you laughed enough?" With Ge Guang leading the way, Fang Yuan walked out of the crowd with a plain expression.

Shi Wu's laughter stopped, his pupils shrunk as he looked at Fang Yuan in shock.

"Rank four Gu Master! Who is this person?" Not just Shi Wu, but all of the Man tribesmen here had this huge question.

"Was Man tribe concealing another rank four Gu Master?" Man Duo felt something amiss.

He came here to find trouble because old Ge tribe leader was bedridden. But to think that Ge tribe had a second rank four battle strength expert!

"Before I came, I had already checked clearly, where is this expert from?"

Carrying such suspicions, Man Duo jumped down from his horse, changing his attitude as he placed his right hand at his chest, greeting Fang Yuan: "Hello friend, you are not from Ge tribe, why must you interfere in our matters?"

Fang Yuan gave this Man Duo a glance, feeling amused by this young man.

The first time he had heard of this Man Duo was from Ge Yao's descriptions.

Although this Man Duo was the third son of Man tribe leader, being weak and sickly since he was young, and had poor aptitude, only C grade. Although he was over twenty years old now, he only had rank two cultivation. He was dark and skinny like a monkey.

But he was definitely not as feeble as Ge Yao described, he had a scheming and devious pair of eyes, with the flames of ambition burning within them.

Chapter 444: Man Tribe’s Invitation

In northern plains where only experts were respected, where only strength mattered, Man Duo was able to gain his father's favor, and was able to mobilize tribe elders to challenge Ge tribe. It showed his ability and courage, he was definitely not a good-for-nothing young master.

Fang Yuan's eyes showed amusement: "I, Chang Shan Yin, was fated to be Ge tribe's guest, I know northern plains rules and it is true that I should not interfere in others' business. But I had just heard this little brother taking out a hundred thousand primeval stones. I am lacking primeval stones recently, why would I reject money offered to me?"

Shi Wu heard this and wished he could slap his own mouth.

"My mouth was really itchy, to think I attracted a rank four expert." His heart was sour and bitter.

Man Duo laughed dryly: "This is an easy matter, if senior lacks primeval stones, this junior is willing to offer five hundred thousand primeval stones to you!"

What he meant was, he wanted Fang Yuan to keep out of this.

At once, Ge tribesmen looked nervously at Fang Yuan.

Although Fang Yuan was the legendary hero, it was only his reputation, those who truly acted like a hero were rare.

Moreover, there was a phrase: a wise man submits to circumstances. Ge tribe was in a slump now, while Man tribe was huge and powerful. Chang Shan Yin was only an outsider, he had no reason to help and bring trouble to himself.

Thus, Fang Yuan became the center of attention, his attitude decided how this situation would progress.

As everyone watched nervously, Fang Yuan laughed proudly: "A gentleman only takes wealth that he deserves. I do not feel that I deserve a gift of five hundred thousand primeval stones. But a hundred thousand primeval stones that I earn from battle is extremely valuable. Come, according to northern plains rules, I accept this battle."

Fang Yuan walked onto the stage.

"Uncle Chang Shan Yin!" Ge Guang felt extremely touched, tears were overflowing as he was lost for words, shouting behind Fang Yuan as he cheered.

The elders of Ge tribe were all extremely moved.

"As expected of Chang Shan Yin, a true righteous hero!"

"Unmoved by benefits and money, he is truly a man of justice."

"There are many people who offer icing on the cake, but few people help out in times of need. Chang Shan Yin will be an esteemed guest in our tribe forever!"

Man Duo's expression was grim, extremely ugly. He knew that there was no need to say more, he shut his mouth and looked at Shi Wu.

Shi Wu felt Man Duo's gaze and felt bitter in his heart.

He had just submitted to Man tribe not long ago, and became an external elder of Man tribe, he wanted to make contributions to the tribe badly. Although Man Duo's cultivation was low, he was the tribe elder's third son, upon hearing that old Ge tribe leader was sick, he came over with Man Duo to challenge them. But he did not expect to meet Chang Shan Yin!

Although the other party was only rank four initial stage, he was already rank three peak stage, the two stages might look close, but Shi Wu knew clearly that this difference in a large realm was incredibly large.

But in this situation, he had no other way out, if he avoided battle, he would be greatly despised and criticized. In northern plains which advocated courage and fighting spirit, he would no longer have a future.

Shi Wu gritted his teeth secretly as he entered the stage forcefully.

"Please." He bowed to Fang Yuan, barely forcing a smile.

Fang Yuan nodded lightly, standing on the spot as light azure wolf fur grew on his body rapidly.

The wolf fur covered his entire body, his ears, face, and even limbs.

"This is azure wolf skin Gu." Shi Wu's heart sank, although azure wolf skin Gu was a very common and ordinary rank four Gu, its defense was not something that a rank three Gu could easily penetrate.

The Ge tribesmen behind Fang Yuan all concentrated and watched as their eyes shone, awaiting Fang Yuan's grand display of his prowess.

Some even shouted loudly: "Kill this fellow, he killed our tribe's third elder!"

Shi Wu heard this and his heart shrunk, he sighed bitterly, feeling the huge trouble ahead of him: "Oh no! After the earlier battles, I have less than thirty percent of my primeval essence left, I am not his match at my peak condition, not to mention now."

Looking at Shi Wu who had a distracted gaze and stiff movements, Fang Yuan snickered in his heart. This person had lost his fighting spirit, even if he had his complete strength, he could not display half of it. After several matches, his primeval essence was obviously lacking.

Such an opponent, in Fang Yuan's eyes, was fish on a chopping board.

But Fang Yuan did not want to kill him.

For what?

He was Man tribe's external elder, if he killed him, that would be a slap on Man tribe's face. Although Fang Yuan was not afraid of trouble, he did not want to create unnecessary trouble for himself.

Even though Shi Wu killed a Ge tribe elder, that was their own business!

"Come!" Fang Yuan stepped, and activated wolf sprint Gu, bursting forward like an arrow, as afterimages appeared behind him.

Shi Wu's heart was already in despair, seeing Fang Yuan's fierce charge, he retreated in fear.

At the same time, he summoned three flying bone shields.

Piak piak piak!

Fang Yuan moved like a shadow, getting close for a physical fight, he struck three times and smashed all three bone shields.

Shi Wu tumbled and rolled away, summoning another three bone shields.

Piak piak piak!

As Fang Yuan attacked at lightning speed, the three bone shields broke again.

He had the strength of twenty jun now, although he could not display all of it, it was no problem breaking these shields.

"What other moves do you have, use them all." Fang Yuan did not attack again, he gave Shi Wu a chance to catch his breath.

Shi Wu was sweating profusely, he gritted his teeth and rubbed his hands, summoning two iron bone broad axes.

"Waaaaaaaah!" He shouted loudly, raising both axes as he attacked fiercely.

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan laughed lightly, not attacking but placing both arms behind his back, using the wolf travel Gu to move.

His movements were unpredictable, like petals floating in the air, his broad shoulders and thin waist gave a brilliant unrestrained feeling.

Shi Wu growled loudly, no matter how he moved both his axes, he could not even touch Fang Yuan's clothes, he was completely at Fang Yuan's mercy.

"Lie down." Fang Yuan sighed, stretching out one finger, it looked slow, but it rapidly touched the axe.

Shi Wu was already dizzy from Fang Yuan's movements, after feeling this force, he lost his balance and fell face flat on the ground.

Ge tribesmen saw his pathetic state and cheered loudly, as the thunderous sound turned into one phrase: "Kill him, kill him!"

Shi Wu's expression was ashen, his fighting spirit was gone. Fang Yuan had control of the entire situation, he was like a lion toying with a sheep. He felt that he was not Fang Yuan's match, but the more he thought like this, the less battle strength he could muster, and the worse the battle situation became.

Man Duo's heart also sank to rock-bottom.

"Damn it, this Shi Wu did not display his true ability, he was scared witless by the other party! But even so, that rank four Gu Master is too strong. He defeated elder Shi Wu without breaking a sweat. Sigh, If Shi Wu dies, I would lose a tribe elder, I would have to face the accusations and fury of my brothers when I return!"

But unexpectedly, Fang Yuan did not attack anymore.

"You are but a rank three, if I use rank four cultivation to kill you, others might think that I, the great Chang Shan Yin, am bullying the weak. Leave." Fang Yuan waved his hand.

"Uncle Chang Shan Yin! You cannot spare this scoundrel." Behind him, Ge Guang shouted.

But Fang Yuan ignored him.

Shi Wu reacted quickly, getting up and showed an expression of joy as he escaped death: "Thank you lord for sparing my life, thank you lord for sparing my life."

Fang Yuan frowned: "Scram."

"Yes, yes, yes." Shi Wu turned and left.

"Senior, I'll take my leave." Man Duo paid respects and rode his battle horse. Ge tribesmen mocked and scolded them as they left with great humiliation.

　　...

"Father, I have failed you, I am here to ask for punishment." Man Duo kneeled on the ground, lowering his head in shame and fear.

Man tribe leader had a muscular body, having rank four peak stage cultivation. He sat on the tiger skin chair grandly as he looked at Man Duo below his feet: "This time, old Ge tribe leader was bedridden, and you brought multiple rank three experts, how did you fail? You did badly for sure, but I heard news that Ge tribe brought out another rank four expert?"

"That is indeed so. Shi Wu was defeated by him. This person only displayed a bit of his actual strength, and he managed to toy around with our strongest elder Shi Wu, his true ability was unfathomable. However, I was in charge of this matter, it was my fault for not getting enough information, resulting in this failure. This child is very ashamed, I implore father to punish me!" Man Duo's eyes were red as he said in a sobbing manner.

Man tribe leader heard this and his tone relaxed: "Stand up, although you failed, you are still my son. Tell me about the incident."

Man Duo quickly spoke, describing the scenario that happened that day.

But when he had just started, Man tribe leader jumped up from his chair, staring fiercely at Man Duo: "He said he is Chang Shan Yin? Which Chang Shan Yin? Are you sure his name is Chang Shan Yin?"

"I would not dare to lie to father even with ten thousand guts." Man Duo quickly explained.

Man tribe leader was in a daze.

"Father, father." Man Duo called him softly: "Is this Chang Shan Yin an expert with a great background?"

Man tribe leader recovered from his daze, his expression was solemn: "I can't tell yet, he could be an imposter. But if it is true, then northern plains has another formidable character emerging... You can leave now, I will handle this matter."

Man Duo jumped from shock, his father was an extremely busy man, but now that he was handling this himself, that showed how important this Chang Shan Yin was.

"Chang Shan Yin, Chang Shan Yin, who in the world are you?"

　　...

A few days later, in Ge tribe.

"A few days ago, it was all thanks to brother Shan Yin's help. This is five hundred thousand primeval stones, it is a token of our gratitude, please accept it." Old Ge tribe leader had a pale expression, he seemed to have aged ten years after losing his daughter.

Fang Yuan rejected it for a few times before accepting it: "These days, I have been staying in your tribe, it is only right that I helped out. But I really lack primeval stones now, I shall borrow these from you for now."

"Brother Shan Yin has great morals, you are truly a hero of northern plains." Old Ge tribe leader was speaking, when his subordinate brought in an invitation, as well as a present.

The old tribe leader's expression was grim, he handed this invitation and present to Fang Yuan: "Brother Shan Yin, Man tribe leader knows you are here, he is inviting you to his tribe as a guest."

Chapter 445: Fixing Battle Bone Wheel

Fang Yuan took a look at the invitation, the words written were very polite, of course they were written using northern plains characters, they looked wild but profound, and at the end, there was Man tribe leader's name — Man Tu.

This letter was written by Man Tu personally, it showed his sincerity.

The content of the letter was Man tribe leader's admiration towards Chang Shan Yin, and stated that the matter earlier was but a misunderstanding among children, since Chang Shan Yin did not kill the external elder Shi Wu, Man tribe was extremely grateful.

Thus, he was holding a banquet at night, and was sincerely inviting Fang Yuan to come. At the same time, this present was an item to apologise on behalf of Shi Wu, for offending a hero.

Fang Yuan opened it and laughed: "This Man tribe spent a lot of effort."

In the box, there was a hundred bone bamboo Gu.

Evidently, after Man Duo returned, he investigated Fang Yuan clearly, and learnt that he was making purchases in the market.

"Oh brother Shan Yin, I have a favor to ask of you." Old tribe leader spoke.

Fang Yuan waved his hand: "I understand brother, don't worry, I will urge them during the banquet, to reduce the conflicts between both your tribes."

"Ah, my greatest thanks to you, brother Shan Yin!" The old tribe leader was very touched, he got up in a hurry and bowed deeply towards Fang Yuan.

There was still some time until the banquet, Fang Yuan sent them off before closing his door.

Fang Yuan sat on the bed, he willed and a light flew out of his aperture.

The weak light dispersed revealing the battle bone wheel.

This rank five Gu is huge, its height was almost at the ceiling, once it appeared, the large room instantly felt cramped.

There were many cracks on the battle wheel, and even some severe scars that threatened to destroy it. The deepest scar was extremely damaging, nearly splitting the wheel into two, only connected by a little bit of white bone. It was a shocking sight.

This rank five Gu worm's luck was not good, after being beaten up by Chang Shan Yin, its original owner Ha Tu Gu died, causing it to become a wild Gu. It had to eat the skeletons on the battleground to barely survive, unable to fix its injuries.

After that, it was attacked by Fang Yuan and Ge Yao together, the Spring Autumn Cicada was a rank six Gu, it could not subdue rank five Gu easily. Fang Yuan could only beat it till its last breath to subdue it.

But precise so, the battle bone wheel was at the brink of destruction, when it appeared, several bone fragments fell off the wheel.

One could say, its situation could not be any worse.

Fang Yuan took out a bone bamboo Gu from the gift box, using Spring Autumn Cicada's aura, he refined it instantly.

This Gu worm was shaped like a finger-bone bamboo, it was pale white and looked like a white candle.

Fang Yuan held the bone bamboo Gu in his hand, as his primeval essence moved according to his will, going out of the aperture towards the underside of his tongue.

The ghost fire Gu was residing at the underside of his tongue, having formed into a blue lump of fire.

Fang Yuan breathed in and blew out.

With a 'huuu' sound, he breathed out a lump of eerie blue ghost fire.

The ghost fire landed on the bone bamboo Gu, slowly burning the top of the bamboo.

Fang Yuan held the bottom of the ghost bamboo Gu like he was holding a candle.

Ghost fire continued to burn, emitting a cold feeling that was chilling to the bone. As the top part of the bone bamboo Gu burnt with ghost fire, it slowly melted and turned into a trace of white bone smoke, floating up.

Fang Yuan placed the bone bamboo Gu closer to the battle bone wheel, and the white bone smoke moved towards the crack of the battle bone wheel like it was sucked over. The battle bone wheel shook slightly as it recovered slowly.

In a while, the eerie blue ghost fire got smaller, as Fang Yuan breathed out another lump of fire to sustain the candle.

After five minutes, this bone bamboo Gu was used up, as Fang Yuan took out the second bone bamboo Gu from the gift box and continued using the ghost fire to ignite it, causing white bone smoke to appear.

As he repeated the cycle, after more than thirty bone bamboo Gu, Fang Yuan finally repaired the deepest crack on that battle bone wheel completely.

The gift box which was filled with bone bamboo Gu had lost about a quarter of them, if Fang Yuan wanted to repair the entire battle bone wheel, just these bone bamboo Gu were not enough.

And the battle bone wheel was far from being usable in battle.

The deepest wound was fixed, but the other injuries were still plaguing the wheel.

It was like a patient, after Fang Yuan's resuscitation, it was pulled back from the abyss of death. But this patient was still in grave danger, it needed to continue receiving treatment.

"You cannot get fat from eating one mouthful, battle bone wheel's damage is too severe. But if that was not the case, I would not have been able to subdue it. Even if it is fully fixed now, my primeval essence cannot activate it. There is no rush here."

Fang Yuan got down from the bed, flexing his numb limbs as he opened the windows, it was already dark, the stars were shining in the sky.

"It is time." Thinking of the banquet at night, Fang Yuan stepped out of his room.

As he walked out of the courtyard, Man Duo and Ge tribe's father and son were already waiting for him.

"Man Duo greets Lord Chang Shan Yin!" Man Duo saw Fang Yuan and immediately greeted, showing absolute respect.

"Have you all waited for a long time?" Fang Yuan nodded, asking casually.

Man Duo replied: "It has only been six hours, it is not a problem. It is my great honor to stand before lord's doors. Senior Chang Shan Yin, father has already set up a grand banquet nearby, awaiting your arrival. Ge tribe's father and son will accompany you to this banquet as well."

Fang Yuan looked at this Man Duo, feeling pity in his heart.

This lad was intelligent and capable, but fate toyed with him, giving him poor aptitude, he was just like Fang Yuan in his previous life.

"Alright then, come along." Fang Yuan rode his hump wolf as he left Ge tribe campgrounds with the rest of them.

Man Duo guided the group of about a dozen people as they rode their hump wolves to a faraway place.

The cool night breeze blew past the ears, as the grassland was running in the opposite direction.

Moonlight poured down like water, one could clearly see at a short distance, but from afar, the moonlight looked like a foggy veil. The grass on the ground was oozing with jade-green essence. The mountains looked like they were gradually flowing towards the sky.

Under such a night sky, wolves sprinted on the never-ending land, as the beautiful moon gave an unrestrained sense of freedom!

As everyone sprinted, they saw a group of hump wolves on a mound. There were a group of Gu Masters sitting on the wolves' back. A Gu Master was waving a huge flag in his hands, that had the word 'Man' on it.

After seeing Fang Yuan, the group of Gu Masters rode the hump wolves as they came over.

Man Duo saw this and laughed: "Lord Chang Shan Yin, my father is the one ahead, he is here to welcome you."

This was the custom of northern plains — if an esteemed guest was invited, the host would often travel ten li, to greet them.

The two groups of hump wolves met in the middle.

Man tribe leader got off his wolf, laughing as he walked over: "Hahaha, today's moon is as bright as the sun, this is the radiance to welcome the return of a northern plains hero. Lord Chang, I have heard so much about you."

Man tribe leader was nine feet tall, he was extremely muscular and strong. He wore a loose sleeveless fur robe, showing his two shoulders, his ancient-bronze colored arms were thicker than a normal male's leg.

But just as he finished his sentence, it seemed like heaven played a prank on him.

The night sky was covered by some dark clouds, as the moonlight vanished, causing the grassland to sink into darkness.

Man tribe leader's loud laughter became softer, as he felt extremely awkward.

It was Man Duo who was quick-witted, immediately laughing as his eyes rolled: "Senior Chang Shan Yin is our northern plains' great hero. Father, you are the most respected hero in our Man tribe. Tonight is a meeting of heroes! Look, the great aura of heroes caused heaven to tremble, causing winds and clouds to stir!"

His words caused the awkwardness to fade away, as Man tribe leader's expression returned to normal as he walked to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan and the others also got off the wolves.

Man Tu first gave Fang Yuan a deep greeting, as Fang Yuan placed his right hand at his chest to return the greeting.

Next, Man Tu stared at Man Duo intentionally, using a scolding tone: "Nonsense! How can I compare to Lord Chang. Lord Chang was renowned in northern plains as the Wolf King, he dominated the world with his wolf enslavement skill. He even killed the rank five Gu Master Ha Tu Gu, eliminating a bunch of bandits and got rid of a great evil, causing his name to go down in history."

"Hehehe, tribe leader Man Tu, why are you so humble?" Fang Yuan laughed lightly: "You are Man tribe leader, ruler of near a thousand Gu Masters. You are a true conqueror, leading Man tribe to many victories, and you even control Hong Yan valley, you are the overlord of this area. My cultivated had fallen to rank four initial stage, while you are at peak stage, you surpass me greatly. Although I have wolf enslavement skill, I can only control beasts, unlike you who control people, our difference is night and day. Tribe leader Man Tu is the true heroic conqueror!"

Man Tu was stunned.

The Wolf King was well-known for his aloofness and arrogance, he was hard to talk to, to think he was so talkative now, and showed such a humble attitude.

But he understood quickly after thinking about it.

This Chang Shan Yin was famous when he was young, with the nature of a young man, he was arrogant. Now that he was a middle-aged man, and had gotten into such trouble, his nature had already been refined, it was normal for him to be more composed now.

Man Tu did not expect Fang Yuan to be so approachable, but to receive such praise from Wolf King Chang Shan Yin, he was secretly happy.

He thought even more highly of Fang Yuan in his heart now.

Although his cultivation was rank four initial stage, he had once killed the rank five Ha Tu Gu, Man Tu did not dare to underestimate him.

He laughed and said: "Lord Chang was already rank four peak stage twenty years ago. Even though your cultivation fell due to injuries, you can still recover quickly, or even surpass your former cultivation. By then, how would my cultivation be your match?"

At this time, the dark clouds dispersed and moonlight shone down again.

"Hehehe, the two of you are the current hero and conqueror of northern plains." Ge tribe leader spoke at an appropriate timing: "The most valuable thing is that the meeting of tiger and wolf did not lead to a fight, but instead you appreciate each other. We are lucky to witness this, this is truly seeing the moon after the clouds part."

Such words made everyone laugh.

"Hahaha, brother Ge, your words described the scenery perfectly. Quick, the banquet has already been prepared, it is just nearby!" Man Tu looked at Fang Yuan and made an inviting pose.

He did not set the banquet at his camp, but rushed here to set up the banquet close to Ge tribe camp, it showed his hospitality and sincerity.

"Good, after you!" Fang Yuan laughed and agreed, but his heart tightened.

The dark clouds came and left quickly, it was a peculiar sight. Most likely, Gu Masters were on the move, it has not been a month since he buried fixed immortal travel Gu. The Immortal Gu aura has not faded yet, hopefully a Gu Immortal does not find it.

Chapter 446: Soul Path Gu Immortal Gui Wang

In the night sky, the moon shone brightly.

A large group of dark clouds moved quickly despite looking slow, it moved above Fang Yuan and gang's head, five thousand li towards the south, towards the sky of an unnamed little hill.

Dark clouds covered the beautiful moonlight, casting a large shadow as darkness engulfed this hill.

The dark clouds stopped moving as a sword light flew out from it, it was the flying sword letter Gu.

The flying sword letter Gu shot into the mound, and entered a mysterious space, vanishing.

After a while, the little hill shook, as a bright red light flashed.

The red light was dazzling, like the setting of the sun, it gathered into a lump, like the creation of a red sun.

At once, the radius of a few hundred li was engulfed in bright red light.

From this mini sun, a jade bridge stretched out.

A rank six Gu Immortal, having a youthful appearance and a round and white face, stepped on the bridge and walked out.

He wore a snow fox fur robe, his face was glowing with red light as he looked up at the dark clouds, laughing: "Gui Wang, it has been a while."

Kek kek kek...

Accompanying the terrible sounding laughter, a person emerged from the dark clouds.

He gave off the strong aura of a rank six Gu Immortal, it was Gui Wang.

Gui Wang quickly descended, just as he was about to land on the ground, a large pair of greenish-black bat wings appeared behind his back.

The bat wings flapped as he remained in the air, looking at the rank six Gu Immortal on the bridge.

"Loner Hong Yu, these are the lava bats I promised you, a total of three million and five hundred thousand. Take a look." Gui Wang spoke, his voice was very coarse and unpleasant, it gave people goosebumps.

His appearance was also extremely ugly, messy hair, a high forehead, deep eye sockets, tightly shut eyes, and ears as large as half his brain.

Loner Hong Yu heard this and raised his head, looking at the dark clouds in the sky.

His brown eyes started heating up and turning red, turning into a color resembling heated metal.

His gaze literally became hot, as it pierced through the dark clouds and allowed him to see the countless bats flying inside.

These bats were all dark-red in color, giving off great heat. They screeched as they flew around each other.

Loner Hong Yu looked around as he nodded in satisfaction: "Three and a half million lava bats indeed, with them, my Hong Yu blessed land would not need to get rid of lava into the ground every month, I can benefit from this greatly. I will keep these lava bats."

"Kekekekek..." Gui Wang laughed heartily, the dark clouds tore open as the bats flew out after losing their restraints.

These bats did not fly around randomly, they quickly descended like a black-red waterfall, entering the sun.

Each blessed land's door was different.

This mini sun was Hong Yu blessed land's entrance.

After these chaotic bats were brought into Hong Yu blessed land, Gui Wang said: "Loner Hong Yu, since you accepted these bats, it means you agreed to barge into Lang Ya blessed land with me."

"Of course, when have I, Loner Hong Yu, ever broken my promise? A month later, we will get to Lang Ya blessed land. But that land spirit is still around, with just the two of us, it might not be enough." Loner Hong Yu said in worry.

"You do not have to worry about this, I have asked the Hua Hai three immortals to help." Gui Wang said.

"Oh? The righteous path's Hua Hai three immortals agreed?" Loner Hong Yu was shocked.

"Hmph, what is righteous, what is demonic? It is but personal interests. Lang Ya blessed land has countless recipes, the Hua Hai three immortals are obviously moved."

"Haha, you are right! I have to make arrangements for these bats, Gui Wang, I will not send you off." Loner Hong Yu said.

Gui Wang snorted as his bat wings flapped, bringing his body into the dark clouds as quickly as lightning.

Dark clouds moved, flying towards the north, covering the moon in its path.

As it entered poison grassland's sky, the cloud stopped, Gui Wang stopped and showed some confusion: "Eh? What's going on! There is the aura of an Immortal Gu?"

He showed a look of disbelief as he landed, the place he was standing at was the location where Fang Yuan and Ge Yao first met.

"Although the Immortal Gu's aura is already extremely weak, it is a real Immortal Gu! Strange, there is the aura of an Immortal Gu, but no Gu Immortal's aura. Is this a wild Immortal Gu? No, that's not right, this is man-made. That means, a mortal obtained an Immortal Gu?"

Gui Wang thought about this and felt great excitement.

Fifty years had already passed since he rose to Gu Immortal realm, yet he still had no Immortal Gu, forced to use rank five Gu worms only.

Immortal Gu were extremely rare, many Gu Immortals live their entire life without having a single one.

"Don't tell me, after working hard for half my life, my luck is finally here?" An Immortal Gu's allure was overwhelming, Gui Wang's heart was palpitating.

He flapped his wings, following the Immortal Gu's aura as he flew over.

He wanted to search for the Gu using the trail of aura.

After a moment, he stopped, the sea of ghost face sunflowers was before him.

"To think there are so many ghost face sunflowers here, kekekek, they are mine!" Gui Wang laughed coldly, although his eyes were closed, it did not obstruct his vision.

He willed and the dark cloud which accompanied him started rolling, as it descended like a huge beast, biting the large field of sunflowers.

Immediately, countless ghost face Gu flew up as numerous ghost cry Gu started to shriek.

"Nether ghost claw!" Gui Wang stretched out his hand and a huge green claw shadow appeared, scooping up these ghost cry Gu and ghost face Gu.

At once, many wild Gu were caught.

A moment later, the dark clouds flew into the sky again, the sea of sunflowers was gone, only a huge crater was left in the ground.

"Great harvest." Gui Wang's mood was good, compared to the Immortal Gu, this was a small appetiser.

After leaving the newly created hole, Gui Wang frowned: "What's going on? The Immortal Gu's aura weakened? Don't tell me, it's sealed?"

He continued flying forward, trailing after fixed immortal travel Gu's aura, he was extremely fast.

After fifteen minutes, his eyebrows raised: "The Immortal Gu's aura moved from the ground to the air, how can this be?"

He looked around, and after a few breaths' time, he understood.

"I see, this is the earth spike rats' territory, this mortal Gu Master flew across it. Heh, his Gu worms are not bad, actually having a flying Gu."

Gui Wang snickered as he spread his wings and flew into the air.

He followed Fang Yuan's previous path, meeting the shadow crows along the way.

"A bunch of small birds." Gui Wang snorted, his body shook slightly as a hundred pale wandering ghosts flew out.

Rank five, hundred ghost night travel Gu!

The wandering spirits flew around, knocking into the shadow crows and smashing their soul to bits. The shadow crows' bodies were unharmed, but they fell down and were dismembered by the earth spike rats.

Gui Wang went on a slaughtering spree, as this area's blood smell intensified, causing more shadow crows to come and scavenge for food. At the same time, the entire earth spike rat group was alerted, they pierced out of the ground attempting to attack Gui Wang.

Gui Wang chuckled, activating hundred ghost night travel Gu and several hundred ghost face Gu.

At once, numerous spirits and souls flew in the air, different ghost faces danced in the air, like a stone mill crushing everything in its path.

Hundreds to thousands of shadow crows fell onto the ground like dumpling entering a pot. The earth spike rats feasted upon their bodies, but the wandering spirits and ghost faces caused damage to them as well.

Earth spikes hit Gui Wang's body one after another, but were repelled by the black light on his body. Other than that, many shadow crows assaulted him with their steel claws.

Gui Wang neither dodged nor avoided, he flew straight ahead.

If it was a rank five Gu Master, under such circumstances, facing numerous attacks every second, he would run out of primeval essence after a moment.

But Gu Immortals had immortal essence, one bead of green grape immortal essence could be diluted into a large amount of primeval essence, it could fill the entire blessed land for tens of years, even a hundred years without vanishing.

This meant that every Gu Immortal had endless primeval essence that they could use, able to use rank five Gu without stopping!

After thousands of shadow crows were sacrificed, the shadow crows retreated in fear.

Gui Wang did not chase them, after flying past the earth spike rats' territory, he landed at the place Fang Yuan landed.

This was where Fang Yuan used dusty Gu on bright pearl Gu.

"The aura thinned again! How can a mortal seal an Immortal Gu? No, there is another possibility, that is this Immortal Gu is heavily injured and is on the verge of death! I have to hurry." Gui Wang felt a strong sense of pressure as he continued flying close to the ground.

Using another rank five Gu worm to accelerate, he raised his speed again.

Twenty minutes later, he arrived at the battlefield where Chang Shan Yin and Ha Tu Gu fought to their deaths.

Here, Fang Yuan took out Chang Shan Yin's corpse and used dark toss Gu to suppress fixed immortal travel Gu's aura again.

Sensing that the Immortal Gu's aura was near indiscernible, Gui Wang's patience reached its limits. He stopped for a moment, using his investigative Gu to scan the surrounding, continuing on his journey after having no discoveries.

"This Immortal Gu will be mine. Be it dead or alive, I must see it!" Gui Wang flew close to the ground, swearing in his heart.

　　...

The banquet had already been going on for a long time, there were young women dancing, delicious wine and food to consume, under this lively atmosphere, Fang Yuan had already formed a brotherly relationship with Man Tu.

"Brother Man Tu, I offer you a toast. I hope that you can do me a favor and mend your relationship with Ge tribe." Fang Yuan raised his wine cup and drank.

Man Tu showed a look of difficulty, after drinking the wine in his cup, he said: "I would not dare to refuse brother Chang's wine, but Hong Yan valley is a small place, we Man tribe expanded quickly and now our numbers are huge. If we have to provide for another Ge tribe, I'm afraid... Moreover, Ge tribe went back on their words, the promised wedding was delayed and even fell through. We are truly angry and disappointed!"

Man Tu sounded angry but he already had a scheme in his heart.

He wanted to absorb Ge tribe, but he could not find an excuse. At the same time old Ge tribe leader was a rank four Gu Master, with him still around, Man tribe could not take them down easily.

Thus, when Man Duo proposed the wedding, he agreed immediately.

Next, with news of Ge Yao's death from Ge tribe, Man Tu did not believe it. In his opinion, this was an excuse of Ge tribe after they realized Man Tu's intention of devouring them!

Chapter 447: Hints and Clues Gu

Speaking about Ge tribe, the lively banquet atmosphere turned cold.

Old Ge tribe leader quickly stood up and gave an explanation.

Ge Guang stood at one side, looking at his father, he felt bitter and pained.

His sister was dead, his father was grieving, he wished none of this was real. But now, his father had to explain to outsiders, proving to them that his daughter was truly dead.

This was such a painful torture.

While Man Tu listened to their explanations, he refused to accept it.

Chang Shan Yin was a righteous hero, and also the genius Gu Master that Chang tribe nurtured back in the day. After he killed Ha Tu Gu and the bandits, he was praised by the people, and with his great reputation, he was known by almost everyone in northern plains.

Thus, to give Chang Shan Yin face, Man Tu gave them his full attention.

But even if Chang Shan Yin's reputation was five or six times higher than now, it could not match the benefits of him absorbing Ge tribe. Now that he had a proper excuse to do so, Man Tu would not let go of it so easily

Thus, he 'patiently' listened to Ge tribe leader's explanation before looking at his third son.

Man Duo laughed coldly in his heart, standing up.

He bowed deeply to Fang Yuan, before taking out a Gu worm in public: "Please take a look Senior Chang."

This Gu looked like a butterfly, its long body was like an incense stick, with its tail still burning with thick smoke. The smoke changed into rainbow-like colors at times, while being colorless and odorless at other times.

"Is this, the chase smoke Gu from ancient times?" Fang Yuan's gaze shone.

Man Duo was stunned, using a tone of admiration: "Senior is absolutely right, this junior is in awe of senior's knowledge. I obtained this Gu by chance, as long as one is stained by this smoke, it would not dissipate for months, it is perfect for finding someone's traces."

After pausing for a while, he continued: "To speak the truth, when junior first saw Ge Yao, I used this Gu on her. Now, as long as we activate this smoke Gu, the traces will appear and we can see it clearly."

Man Duo had a smug expression as he continued: "Ge tribe leader, if we use this Gu, and find Ge Yao hiding in your tribe's campgrounds, what will we do?"

He wanted to devour Ge tribe, he obviously had plans. This chase smoke Gu was suggested by Man Duo, to think that it would actually be used like this.

Facing Man Duo's threat, Ge tribe father and son relaxed in their heart.

This chase smoke Gu was good, once it was used, the truth of their words would be attested to without doubt.

But Fang Yuan's heart jumped, this chase smoke Gu could stain people who got close to it. He had once been in close proximity with Ge Yao, and even hugged her. With this smoke, wouldn't he be exposed?

What now?!

Fang Yuan did not expect this, his heart was sinking.

The Gu worm set on him was Chang Shan Yin's enslavement path Gu worms, it was good at huge battles, but had little use for personal fights.

At this banquet, he was only rank four initial stage, but Man tribe and Ge tribe leader had higher cultivation. There were even several elders and guards with rank three cultivation.

Even if he brought the wolves over, two to three thousand ordinary wolves could not turn this situation around!

At once, Fang Yuan's mind worked at lightning speed, all sorts of possibilities appeared as they sparked like flint.

Soon after, he laughed heartily: "This is great. With the chase smoke Gu to certify, the truth will be out. Junior, quickly use it."

He wanted to stall for time or reject the use of it, but that was impossible. Firstly, he as an outsider rejecting the use of chase smoke Gu was very strange, it was almost admitting his guilt. Secondly, be it Man tribe or Ge tribe, they both wanted to use chase smoke Gu to confirm some details, there was no way to change their minds now. Thirdly, chase smoke Gu was in the hands of someone else, even if Fang Yuan objected to it, could he stop Man tribe from using it?

Thus, Fang Yuan took the initiative to urge him, giving them an impression of being open and fearless.

Hearing Fang Yuan's words, Man Tu was overjoyed: "Since brother Chang Shan Yin has said it, son, use it."

But Man Duo was not happy, he observed the people's expressions, and realized that Ge tribe father and son were looking forward to this.

"Is Ge Yao really dead?" Man Duo controlled his uneasiness and willed, activating this chase smoke Gu.

At once, the colorless and odorless smoke appeared in the air, turning black.

"Hmm?"

"Eh, what's going on?"

"This is..."

As expected, there was a thick cloud of smoke on Fang Yuan, in this illuminated banquet, it was very eye-catching.

At once, everyone's gaze was on him!

The lively atmosphere immediately turned solemn, no one said a word, there was a heavy mood in everyone.

Fang Yuan frowned, his expression was a combination of shock and surprise, it made people think he was innocent.

As if he thought that he was not eye-catching enough, Fang Yuan stood up from among the crowd, leaving his seat as he walked around. The black smoke trailed after him, forming a black smoke tail behind Fang Yuan.

Man Duo's gaze flickered as Man Tu said happily: "That means brother Chang Shan Yin has met Ge Yao, and even had close interaction with her!"

Ge tribe leader had a complicated expression as he looked at Fang Yuan with a uncertain gaze.

Ge Guang was still young, he was not composed enough as he stood up from his seat, staring at Fang Yuan in suspicion, asking: "Uncle Chang Shan Yin, what is going on? Did you meet my sister Ge Yao when you were in poison grassland?"

Fang Yuan's expression was solemn, he did not explain himself, but walked back to his seat, saying seriously: "To speak the truth, you are suspicious, but so am I, why is there so much smoke following me?"

Man Duo said sinisterly: "Senior Chang is a great hero of northern plains, I would not dare to come up with a conjecture for your suspicions.

"Senior Chang Shan Yin!" Ge Guang could not hold it any longer, he stared at Fang Yuan with a flickering gaze.

Fang Yuan heard him and looked at Ge Guang in the eye with no guilt, then turning to old Ge tribe leader: "Brother Ge, you know my character. I swear in the name of the Wolf King, I did not meet your daughter in poison grassland!"

Ge tribe leader placed his right hand at his chest, making a great gesture with a solemn expression: "Brother Chang Shan Yin, we hit it off so well when we first met, I believe your words!"

Ge Guang by the side wanted to speak but he controlled himself.

Fang Yuan obviously understood that these words were not enough to dispel their suspicions. Immediately after, he frowned, showing a thinking expression, saying: "I slept for twenty years, after I woke up, I left poison grassland. Along the way, I subdued many poison beard wolves, during the cold nights, I rest on the fur of my wolves to gain warmth. Most likely, one of the wolves ate brother's daughter, and thus, the smoke was passed to me when we made contact."

"Is that so?" Ge Guang gritted his teeth, his gaze flickering continuously.

Fang Yuan's explanation made perfect sense, he was the first person who saw Fang Yuan leave poison grassland, when he saved him from the wind wolf group, he was manipulating the poison beard wolves.

"We can get to the truth easily, my wolf pack is still resting in Ge tribe's ranch, everyone can follow me to the ranch, and we will be able to see the truth." Fang Yuan suggested.

This suggestion made everyone interested.

"Then we will go ahead with this?" Man Tu turned his gaze at Ge tribe father and son, he still did not believe Ge Yao was dead.

Old Ge tribe leader stood up: "Let's go, we can be the witnesses."

Everyone rode their hump wolves towards Ge tribe's ranch.

Fang Yuan's wolf pack was resting inside, they were strong and fit.

Under the night sky, the poison beard wolves were more energetic.

Using the chase smoke Gu's black smoke, the group successfully found out that a few of the poison beard wolves had much thicker smoke than Fang Yuan.

Oh longevity heaven, with the blessing of our ancestors, the murderer of my daughter was here all along!" Ge tribe leader saw this and cried in pain, he next bowed deeply at Fang Yuan, just as he was about to speak, Fang Yuan stopped him.

"Brother Ge, I know what you want to say. These poison beard wolves are yours to deal with." Fang Yuan said.

Old Ge tribe leader cried tears of gratitude: "Benefactor Chang Shan Yin, thank you! You not only saved my son, but you also brought the murderer of my daughter here. You are the closest friend of our Ge tribe for eternity!"

Ge Guang was silent.

It was true that Fang Yuan saved him, but this was not enough to certify that he was innocent. If Chang Shan Yin killed his sister and ordered the poison beard wolves to consume his sister's corpse, that would also cause this result.

Man Tu was panicking at the side.

From start to end, he did not believe Ge Yao is dead.

If Ge tribe discovered the chase smoke Gu and cooperated with Ge Yao to fake this, it was very easy.

Thus, he spoke: "Ge tribe leader, you have truly misunderstood brother Chang Shan Yin. Brother Chang is a great hero of northern plains, he is such an admirable person, how could he commit such a sinful act? The way I see it, we should follow this chase smoke Gu into poison grassland and continue to collect evidence to clear brother Chang's name!"

He wanted to use Fang Yuan as an excuse to find out the truth, whether Ge Yao was really dead or not.

If Ge Yao entered poison grassland, there would surely be a trail of smoke along the way.

But at this time, Ge Guang spoke: "No need for that, I have a way to prove uncle Chang Shan Yin's innocence. Father, back then when you prepared a set of precious water path Gu worms for sister, you used the rank five hints and clues Gu on them. Sister knows this, thus if she is killed, she will follow your instructions to keep these Gu worms intact, leaving them for her murderer. This way, we can find her killer and exact revenge for her. As long as you take out that hints and clues Gu, that will be the best proof."

Saying so, Ge Guang looked deeply at Fang Yuan.

Chapter 448: Obtaining another Rank Five Gu

Gui Wang moved quickly along the way, following the faint Immortal Gu aura to a stalk of snow spirea.

"The Immortal Gu's aura stopped here, the trail ends here!" Gui Wang's gaze was anxious as he searched all around the snow spirea.

"No? No Immortal Gu! The snow spirea's snow wash Gu was already taken, obviously someone came here. But why is there no Immortal Gu? If the Immortal Gu continued moving, its aura would move too. But this aura ended here, is the Immortal Gu dead?" Gui Wang had a guess.

But he refused to believe this, he used his investigative Gu and searched the entire place thoroughly.

"No, there's nothing here!" Gui Wang gritted his teeth, his heart was filled with indignance and regret.

"Wait!" Suddenly, his gaze turned ruthless as he thought of a possibility: "At the center of this poison grass land is Zi Du blessed land, the rank seven Gu Immortal Lady Poison Scorpion lives in it. Did she take the Immortal Gu? A mortal's aperture cannot hold an Immortal Gu, but a Gu Immortal's aperture can. After the Immortal Gu enters the aperture, the aura would stop leaking. In that case, this would be the most logical explanation!"

"That means Lady Poison Scorpion stayed home and had an Immortal Gu arrive at her doorsteps? Damn it, curses!" Gui Wang stomped his feet, he would rather believe that the Gu was taken by Lady Poison Scorpion than the fact that it could have died.

But he would never guess that the real Immortal Gu did not die, but instead Fang Yuan used iron cabinet Gu to seal its aura before backtracking and burying the Gu along the way.

Gui Wang followed the aura's trail, moving forward, as Fang Yuan controlled the sealing, the Gu worm's aura weakened as he followed it, this created a speculation.

Gui Wang wanted to chase after the Gu, he would never have guessed that along the way, the fixed immortal travel Gu was buried somewhere.

When he thought of Lady Poison Scorpion, jealousy and hatred forced his speculations to hit a dead end.

"Lady Poison Scorpion is a rank seven Gu Immortal, she is very strong. I can gather the Hua Hai three immortals and Loner Hong Yu to attack Lang Ya blessed land, that is because of the promised benefits. I do not have the bargaining chips to get them to attack Zi Du blessed land as well. This is so hateful! If I came ten days ago, the Immortal Gu might have been mine."

"Looking at the time, Zi Du blessed land is about to open its doors and expel the poisonous gas inside, I am not her match, I should leave now."

Gui Wang stomped his feet and flew into the air, entering the dark clouds.

The dark cloud moved around as Gui Wang looked around with indignance, only after a long while did he fly back to his home.

　　...

This was destined to be a busy night, at Ge tribe ranch, everyone's attention was on Fang Yuan.

If Fang Yuan killed Ge Yao and took her Gu, the hints and clues Gu would cause him to be exposed.

Fang Yuan's earlier lie would be exposed as well — if you did not meet Ge Yao, why do you have her Gu?

By then, no explanations would work!

"Son!" Ge tribe leader stared angrily at Ge Guang, extremely furious: "Benefactor Chang Shan Yin is so righteous and upright, how can you be suspicious of him?! Quickly kneel down and kowtow to our benefactor to ask for forgiveness!"

"Father." Ge Guang was shocked, he did not expect Ge tribe leader's reaction.

Wasn't he always trying to get revenge for sister? Father missed out one point so I pointed it out for him, what did I do wrong?

At one side, Man tribe father and son started watching this show as bystanders.

"Brother Ge, your son had said that, you do have a hints and clues Gu right?" Fang Yuan's expression was calm, his gaze clear as water: "Then please take it out and activate it."

"This..." Old Ge tribe leader hesitated.

"Brother Ge, if you have a method to prove my innocence, why are you still hiding it? Hahaha, I am overjoyed by it." Fang Yuan smiled warmly.

Ge tribe leader observed his expression for a while, then looked at Man tribe's father and son. The two were staying silent, quietly watching this, but their gazes had deep meaning in them.

"Nevermind, since benefactor Chang Shan Yin insists, I will go ahead with it." Ge tribe leader gritted his teeth and took out hints and clues Gu.

This Gu was shaped like a black spider, it was fist-sized and was plump. Eight hairy black legs with shiny tips, resembling water chestnuts.

Ge tribe leader injected primeval essence, and hints and clues Gu's body gave out a faint white light. Within five hundred li, if there were Gu worms that were marked by the Gu Master, it would emit a red light and point in their direction. If the Gu Master was hiding the Gu worms inside their aperture, this range would be only within a thousand steps, but it stayed in Ge tribe leader's hand without having any changes.

Seeing this, Ge Guang kneeled on the ground with a plop and kowtowed to Fang Yuan: "Uncle Chang Shan Yin, I was wrong! I wanted to get to the bottom of the matter and offended you. Please punish me!"

"Quickly get up, I have to thank you for proving my innocence, what wrong did you do?" Fang Yuan smiled faintly as he helped Ge Guang get up.

......

Rewinding back to the day when Fang Yuan killed Ge Yao.

Before death, the young girl cried: "Chang Shan Yin! I don't know how I am blocking your path to success. But now, even if you kill me, I do not hate you. Maybe you are seeking revenge? I will leave all my Gu worms to you, I hope they can be of some use for your path to success."

"Cough cough..." The girl coughed out blood and begged Fang Yuan with a grieved smile, "I am going to die, but before I die, I have a small favor to ask. I hope you can hug me, I really want to feel your warm embrace..."

However, Fang Yuan did not move, his gaze coldly looking at the girl.

He looked at the girl and saw her expression becoming stiffer as vitality left her bit by bit.

Finally, the flower-like girl became an ice-cold corpse.

Fang Yuan fell into a long silence as he looked at Ge Yao's face.

"She gave all her Gu to me? What is the meaning of this?"

"She loved Chang Shan Yin indeed, but how can she not hate me for killing her? Her love was only a young girl's affection, breeding for only a few days. Her hatred was due to the loss of her life, the hatred of being killed. It is evident which is a stronger emotion."

"Heh! This girl is still too young, her acting is terrible, how can she hide that hatred in her eyes when she spoke to me? Although I lack Gu worms, and her Gu worms are all of high quality, she intentionally left them for me... to play it safe, I should not take them."

Next, Fang Yuan willed, and the poison beard wolves moved, devouring her corpse until nothing was left.

From start to end, he did not touch the Gu worms in Ge Yao's aperture at all.

"Seeing this result, Ge tribe leader breathed out a sigh of relief, praising Fang Yuan continuously: "Brother Chang Shan Yin, I have learnt much today. You are indeed a great hero of the grassland, your conduct is like tonight's moon, pure like water, with no impurities. No matter how dirty the floor is, it will not pollute the moon. No matter how thick the clouds are, they will not hinder your radiance. We Ge tribe owe you a great deal, my son was rash and suspected you. We only have this rank five hints and clues Gu, I will give it to you today as an apology, please accept it, otherwise, I will not be able to sleep properly."

Rank five Gu was hard to come by, but under everyone's gaze, Ge tribe leader handed it over to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan rejected it for a few times, but Ge tribe leader was very insistent, he had "no choice" but to accept it.

Just like this, Fang Yuan obtained his second rank five Gu in northern plains.

Next, everyone continued the banquet until late into the night, as they parted happily under the moon.

Man Tu invited Fang Yuan earnestly to be a guest as his tribe. But Fang Yuan said that he was going to leave not long later, to join the heroes assembly. But before leaving, he would go visit Man tribe first.

Looking at Fang Yuan and Ge tribe's father and son leave on their hump wolves, Man Tu's smile vanished and his expression turned ugly.

"It seems this Ge Yao is dead without doubt." Man Tu's tone was gloomy.

"Father, no need to fret." Man Duo at the side snickered: "This Ge tribe wants to make use of Hong Yan valley, he has to beg us, they have nowhere to run."

Listening to his son's words, Man Tu's expression relaxed, he patted Man Duo's shoulders: "You are right, I was too obsessed with it. These years, Man tribe had been expanding, you have contributed greatly to it. But you are only C grade in aptitude, your talent is insufficient, when father retires, and your elder brother takes charge of Man tribe, you have to assist him well."

"Yes father, do not worry." Man Duo replied curtly and positively, but he was snorting in his heart.

He was also his father's son, why can't he compete for the leader's role, why must he give it to his brother? Because of aptitude, he cannot become the tribe leader?

No!

"If elder brother ascended to the position of tribe leader, he will kill me. Sigh, what a pity, I wanted to marry Ge Yao to make Ge tribe part of my force, with this relationship tying us together. But heaven played a joke on me, Ge Yao actually died!"

　　...

"Unfilial son, kneel down!" Once they got into the secret room, with only the two of them left, Ge tribe leader's expression sank as he screamed at Ge Guang.

"Father!" Ge Guang was shocked, he did not understand why his father was so furious, but he subconsciously kneeled down first.

"Father, I am your son, you can scold or beat me, as long as your anger fades. But I have a request, I hope that father can tell me why you are so furious after you calm down. I will change and no longer make you angry." Ge Guang said.

Ge tribe leader laughed coldly, standing before Ge Guang and pointing at his nose: "I know you feel very indignant, let father tell you the reason, to let you know the immense danger we were in tonight! Did you really think Man Duo proposed to your sister because of her good looks?"

Ge Guang was stunned: "Was that not the case? Ge Yao was the beauty of our tribe, so many youngsters were chasing after her."

"Bullshit!" Ge tribe leader howled: "Beauty is just the icing on top of authority. Man Duo has Man Tu behind him, his objective is to devour our Ge tribe, that is why Man Tu supported Man Duo greatly to marry your sister."

Chapter 449: Strength is the most important

"Huh, Man tribe wants to devour our Ge tribe?" Ge Guang screamed.

Old Ge tribe leader sighed: "Sigh, your sister is already dead, they were not willing to listen to my explanation, why do you think that is the case? Because this excuse is perfect for them to send their troops! But I found Chang Shan Yin to assist us, he was the hero of northern plains, he had great reputation, and had Chang tribe behind him. Man Tu did not dare to accuse us blindly, thus he did not attack us tonight."

Ge Guang exclaimed: "There is such a twist behind it? But father, I do not understand, since you understood Man tribe's intentions already, why did you agree to this wedding, and betrothed sister to that monkey Man Duo?"

Ge tribe leader raised his finger, knocking on Ge Guang's head: "Do you not have a brain? Why did I agree to the wedding? Did you think I want to torture my own daughter?! It is because the great blizzard is coming, if we can become relatives through marriage, we can stay inside Hong Yan valley, and protect all our tribesmen! Sacrificing your sister's happiness to protect Ge tribe. This wedding is a transaction, sigh, but your sister ran away from her wedding, and died in poison grassland!"

Ge Guang frowned, blinking: "Father, I understand now."

"No, you know nothing." Ge tribe leader understood his son well, he explained in a disappointed tone: "Tonight, Man tribe leader invited Chang Shan Yin, and we followed him. But the truth is, their target was us, and I dragged Chang Shan Yin along as our shield."

"That Man Duo used the chase smoke Gu, he is truly evil! When all of you suspected Chang Shan Yin, I said to him that I trusted him completely. Did you think I was not suspicious? I am not so muddleheaded yet!"

Ge tribe leader stomped his foot, his tone was grim: "But I did not dare to suspect him. The reason we could contend with Man tribe is because of Chang Shan Yin. If we suspected him, their instigation would have succeeded, and ruined our relationship with Chang Shan Yin. If Chang Shan Yin did not side with us, we might not return alive from tonight's banquet."

Shock was written all over Ge Guang's face: "Ah, are they so daring, would they try to kill the both of us?"

"Hmph, why did you think that you met so many wind wolves during the search? In northern plains, there are lots of instances where beast groups were used to commit murder. But tonight, Man tribe might not kill us, but they would imprison us. By then, they would use Ge Yao's matter as an excuse to devour our Ge tribe, without us, Ge tribe would be without a leader, the result would be disastrous."

Hearing his father's explanation, Ge Guang finally understood the danger they were in, showing after-fear on his face.

"For the sake of the tribe, for the big picture, even if Chang Shan Yin was the killer, we cannot suspect him! Did you really think I forgot the hints and clues Gu? How can that be! But you had to mention it, if the killer was really Chang Shan Yin, what would we do?" Old Ge tribe leader spoke meaningfully.

Ge Guang fell into deep silence, after a long while, he said: "So that is why father gave the precious hints and clues Gu to Chang Shan Yin. It is to mend our relationship with him, so that he would side with us?"

Old Ge tribe leader nodded: "You are finally learning. Son, although you have outstanding aptitude, and high cultivation, you are still far from being the new Ge tribe leader."

"Father, it is great to have you around. I will have to learn more from you, Ge tribe can lose anybody but you father." Ge Guang said in admiration.

Ge tribe leader shook his head: "Time waits for no man, I am already old, Ge tribe is counting on you. Sigh... after this matter, I have understood Man Tu. He is a greedy jackal, no matter how much his wealth is, he would never be satisfied."

"Now that your sister is gone, we have no excuses left to use Hong Yan valley. But we cannot disband and join Man tribe right? Ge tribe cannot go extinct like this, otherwise I will be the greatest sinner of our tribe! After this night, I have already learnt that we cannot stay here any longer, otherwise we will definitely be devoured by Man tribe. A few days later, we will depart for the heroes assembly."

"Father, if we leave like this, will they let us go so easily?" Ge Guang was worried as he asked.

"Of course they are not willing to let us go, but we are travelling with Chang Shan Yin. Man Tu is wary of Chang Shan Yin, he would not strike." Ge tribe leader snickered.

"But, we are making use of senior Chang Shan Yin like this, isn't that..." Ge Guang was apprehensive.

"You fool! Why would we not make use of him? What's wrong with that? A good hunter makes full use of his surroundings. When we have insufficient strength, we use knowledge to supplement it. This is all for the survival of the clan!"

After Ge tribe leader scolded, he stopped and showed a complex expression: "But this Chang Shan Yin is truly a legendary heroic character... he might've already understood the situation, yet he still chose to side with us. Such a righteous and upright person, choosing to assist the weak, he is truly the role model of the righteous path, the light of the people. Son, rejoice, we Ge tribe actually met such a person!"

　　...

Time passed quickly, a few days went by.

Inside the room, Fang Yuan held his bone bamboo Gu as the ghost fire burnt it completely, breathing out heavily: "This is the final bone bamboo Gu."

These days, he worked hard and used up all hundred of the bone bamboo Gu in the gift box.

After his treatment, eight of battle bone wheel's most severe wounds were healed. Now, although the wheel was still covered in injuries and cracks, it had left the emergency stage.

Sending the battle bone wheel back to the aperture, Fang Yuan started to inspect his aperture.

He had rank four peak stage cultivation.

Thus, his aperture walls were in the form of transparent crystals. His primeval sea was at ninety percent full, all of it was true gold primeval essence.

But Fang Yuan had just arrived in northern plains, before he adapted to the environment, his true gold primeval essence was only at the initial stage light gold primeval essence.

Thus, Fang Yuan's cultivation was not progressing. Using light gold primeval essence, he could not break through the aperture walls and become a rank five Gu Master.

"To accelerate my adaptation, there are ways to do so, most commonly, it is to use the third watch Gu, to accelerate my own time. But that way, the Gu Master's lifespan will also be shortened proportionally.

Such a measure that pursued quick success was not acceptable to Fang Yuan.

It was not because he treasured his lifespan, but because of Spring Autumn Cicada.

If Fang Yuan used third watch Gu on himself, the river of time on him will flow three times faster. That way, the Spring Autumn Cicada's recovery will also be three times as fast.

Other than his vital Gu and fixed immortal travel Gu in poison grassland, Fang Yuan still had multiple Gu worms.

Among them were two rank five Gu from northern plains.

One was battle bone wheel, it was recovering and could not be used in the meantime.

The other was hints and clues Gu, it could be used to scout or track people.

"Ge tribe still had some foundations, they actually had a rank five hints and clues Gu. This Gu can be used to track Gu worms, it is used to capture wild Gu worms to prevent them from escaping. Unfortunately, even though Ge tribe leader had this Gu worm, he did not dare to search for his own daughter."

Towards the conflict between Ge tribe and Man tribe, Fang Yuan was clear as day.

Man Tu's third son Man Duo had great ambition, he wanted the tribe leader position, but because of his low cultivation, he wanted to have Ge tribe. After marrying Ge Yao, and making Ge tribe related to him through his wife, they would be able to fight for the tribe leader position.

Man Tu was not necessarily ignorant of his son's intentions, but he was very interested in devouring Ge tribe.

Meanwhile, Ge tribe wanted to use the marriage to sacrifice Ge Yao in exchange for Hong Yan valley, to survive the once in ten years great blizzard, and get through this difficulty.

Ge tribe naturally did not want to dissolve, but Man tribe wanted to gain the benefits of absorbing them without facing any consequences.

After Ge Yao escaped, Man tribe used this excuse to turn on them, in fact, they might have even caused Ge Guang's incident.

As long as they killed Ge tribe's father and son, Ge tribe would be leaderless, and they would fall into chaos, easily taken over by Man tribe.

Ge Guang was ignorant and naive, but old Ge tribe leader was experienced and wise, he knew the circumstances they were in, and found out that he was unable to satisfy Man Tu's greed, but at this point, they had no way out, thus he controlled himself and stayed inside the tribe, not giving Man tribe a chance to strike.

Chang Shan Yin's arrival gave Ge tribe hopes of getting out of this problem.

When old Ge tribe leader found out Fang Yuan's identity as Chang Shan Yin, he thought of using him. Thus, he attended to Fang Yuan warmly and even gave a million primeval stones as a gift.

Next, he did well, using Chang Shan Yin's power to contest with Man tribe.

At that moonlight banquet, it might have looked like a cosy gathering, but the three sides were competing, danger was lurking at every corner, and everyone was hiding their lethal weapons.

The result was —

Man tribe suffered a setback, not only did they fail to deal with Ge tribe, they even lost the excuse that they had, Ge Yao. But they did not lose, they were still the strongest among the three.

Ge tribe used Chang Shan Yin, making use of his reputation to protect their tribe, surviving this crisis. Even though they succeeded, they were still at the weaker position.

As for Fang Yuan, he pretended to be ignorant, using the two sides and their conflict to achieve his goal of spreading his name, while benefiting from their competition and strengthening himself.

Man is the spirit of all beings, when humans competed, it was not simply through fights and killing. Even in this primitive and open northern plains, knowledge and schemes was still used to compete..

As for Ge Yao...

This innocent young girl was only a sacrifice for the two tribes' political struggle.

In fact, according to Fang Yuan's personal guess, Ge Yao's escape was unnatural, she was able to get out of the tightly secured Ge tribe camp, mostly likely the old Ge tribe leader had arranged for it in an attempt to probe Man tribe. But accidents always happened in reality, plans cannot keep up with changes, Man tribe's eldest son or second son might've struck, afraid of Man Duo gaining power, hoping that Ge Yao would die. Anyway, after Ge Yao escaped to poison grassland and met Fang Yuan, the series of events unfolded.

Shaking his head, Fang Yuan cleared these guesses out of his mind: "The basis of any scheme is power. Why did Man tribe not attack Ge tribe directly, that is because they were not a super tribe but a large tribe only, they had limited strength. Why was Ge tribe able to stay safe until now, not just because of me, but also because of their foundation as a former large tribe. If old Ge tribe leader had rank five cultivation, he might've used hints and clues Gu long ago."

"No matter which world, strength is the foundation for everything. But now, the astute Ge tribe leader might be planning to migrate his tribe again. To deal with the ten year blizzard, he might need to borrow the imperial court's power!"

Chapter 450: Measuring the stature of great men by the yardstick of small men

What happened next was all according to Fang Yuan's expectations.

Just a day later, Ge tribe leader visited Fang Yuan, saying he had thought it through, he did not want to stay in Hong Yan valley, but instead wanted to migrate the entire tribe, to participate in the heroes assembly and fighting for a place in the imperial court.

Fang Yuan knew old Ge tribe leader's intentions, it was to make use of Chang Shan Yin once more to get free of Man tribe's control.

Fang Yuan agreed immediately, if he was to travel on the grassland alone, it would be troublesome. With the accompaniment of Ge tribe, the risks would be much lower, and he would have a layer of protection.

"Brother Ge is wise, but we cannot wait anymore, we should leave as soon as possible. Once we make a move, I'm sure Man tribe would notice immediately." Fang Yuan reminded.

Old Ge tribe leader's heart shook, just hearing this sentence, he knew Chang Shan Yin was aware of what was happening.

Fang Yuan continued: "I had originally promised Man tribe to visit them. But since Ge tribe is relocating, to play safe, I will not go to them. Just say that I had felt my cultivation returning during these few days and have gone into closed cultivation. I will write a letter now, I will have to trouble brother to find someone to send it over for me."

If Ge tribe did not relocate, then Fang Yuan would have no issues visiting Man tribe.

But if Ge tribe wanted to leave, Man tribe would not let go of them. Man tribe is worried about Ge tribe and Chang Shan Yin cooperating, they might even hold him captive, to deal with Ge tribe separately.

Earlier, when Ge Guang was attacked by the wind wolves, it was most likely done by Man tribe. Man tribe was after all part of the righteous faction, to prevent rumors from spreading, they would not kill Chang Shan Yin, but Ge tribe was too alluring, they could use all sorts of reasons to place Chang Shan Yin under house arrest, that was something they could do.

After old Ge tribe leader heard Fang Yuan's words, he looked at him deeply and stood up, bowing: "Standing before brother, my wisdom is nothing. I was muddleheaded earlier, brother has a clear picture of the current situation."

"Hehehe, as someone involved in this contest, it is easy for you to be misled, that is normal, do not worry about it. As long as we leave this area, Ge tribe would be free!" Fang Yuan consoled old Ge tribe leader as he wrote a letter and handed it to Ge tribe leader.

"Brother Ge, I have to cultivate, I will not send you off."

"Today, I will start the preparations for moving off, the letter will definitely be sent, goodbye."

Old Ge tribe leader took the letter and left the room.

After he returned to his tent, he called the elders for a meeting and gave the instructions to prepare for migration.

After Ge Yao's supposed marriage, Ge tribe elders have a terrible impression of Man tribe, they praised this ingenious decision.

After Ge tribe father and son returned to their study room, old Ge tribe leader opened Fang Yuan's letter immediately.

"Father, isn't this a bit..." Ge Guang felt embarrassed.

"Heh, let father teach you another lesson today. This is the letter Chang Shan Yin wrote to Man Tu, but he did not use a letter Gu, why do you think that is so?" Old Ge tribe leader snickered.

"Because he doesn't have a letter Gu? No, if he wants to use it, he can borrow it from us." Ge Guang thought about it, as his eyes flashed: "That mean, this is intentional?"

"Hehehe, that's right. The reason why he is sending a normal letter is so that we can see it. Ge tribe is about to migrate, next we will travel together, this letter is to display his intention to cooperate with us along the journey. Come here, we will look at this together." Saying so, Old Ge tribe leader unsealed the letter.

The content in the letter was very simple, it explained that Fang Yuan needed time to recover his cultivation through closed cultivation. He expressed great regret for not being able to visit Man tribe, and he would definitely make up for it in the future.

Next, he wanted to purchase bone bamboo Gu from Man tribe, saying that he will pay 120% of the market price for them. At the same time, he wrote a large number of Gu refinement materials, as well as Gu worms like third watch Gu, hoping they could have a transaction.

"Oh, so uncle Chang Shan Yin needed these Gu worms. Father, I think we should try and give them to him, after all, he has helped us so much." Ge Guang said.

Old Ge tribe leader stared at this letter, his eyes shining brilliantly as a chill emerged in his heart.

This battle between Ge tribe and Man tribe was mostly through hidden schemes, they did not fall out with each other on the surface, this was the rule of the righteous path that had to be adhered to.

They sacrificed many people, one of Ge tribe's elders died after being challenged by Man Duo, and Ge Yao also died in poison grassland. Other than that, many Gu Masters became the wolves' food.

In this contest, be it Man tribe or Ge tribe, neither of them were winners. Man tribe did not achieve their aims, and Ge tribe also had many sacrifices.

However, there was one person who benefited completely.

This person was 'Chang Shan Yin'.

Look at it this way, when 'Chang Shan Yin' left poison grassland, he was empty handed, without a proper set of Gu worms, but now?

In this hidden battle, he earned till his pockets were full, having over a million primeval stones as gains, not to mention the rank five hints and clues Gu.

Ge tribe leader suddenly understood: Ge tribe was making use of Chang Shan Yin, but was Chang Shan Yin not making use of them as well? Chang Shan Yin might seem like he was trapped between two tribes, forced into their political strife, and attracted problems for himself unnecessarily. But the truth was, neither of them wanted to offend him, thus he gained benefits from both sides!

"We do not need to prepare these for Chang Shan Yin. Man tribe will send these things over, in fact, they might even give these to him for free." Ge tribe leader heaved a sigh as he tried to expel that cold feeling in his heart.

"Huh?" Ge Guang was shocked: "How is that possible? Uncle Chang Shan Yin is evidently helping us, is Man tribe so stupid?"

"Someone in a high position sees things differently. What is the value of these things? Merely a few hundreds of thousands of primeval stones, it is nothing to Man tribe. Using these goods to gain the friendship of an expert, isn't that a good deal? Have you thought about how much we gave Chang Shan Yin already?"

Ge Guang immediately thought of the million primeval stones and the rank five hints and clues Gu.

Ge tribe leader sighed deeply, there was another meaning to this, but it was still too early for Ge Guang to comprehend.

Why did Chang Shan Yin want to deal with Man tribe?

He was not making a deal, he was establishing a relationship with them! Using this, Chang Shan Yin expressed to Man tribe that although he went back on his word and did not visit Man tribe, he was not their enemy despite being at Ge tribe. He did not want to be enemies with Man tribe, in fact he wanted to be friends, thus, they could undergo transactions.

Man Tu was not a fool, he would understand what Chang Shan Yin was trying to express in his letter, his goodwill. If Man tribe rejected this deal, that would be rejecting Fang Yuan's kindness. If they sold the goods according to their price, this would show an indifferent attitude. If they gifted the goods to Fang Yuan, that would mean Man tribe was accepting this kindness, and was willing to be friends with Chang Shan Yin.

This deal was not important, the underlying meaning was.

Such a hidden and implicit communication method was something the righteous path higher-ups often did.

Ge tribe leader suddenly had a flash of inspiration, thinking: "This Chang Shan Yin, the reason why he is helping Ge tribe might not be due to his righteous nature. But because he can have the greatest benefits by siding with us."

Man tribe was huge and powerful, having Chang Shan Yin was only adding icing on the cake. But Ge tribe was weak, with Chang Shan Yin, it was simply a great asset as he had the ability to stabilize the power balance between the two.

With this thought, old Ge tribe leader shuddered, the coldness in his heart became thicker, almost freezing his bones.

The old tribe leader subconsciously rejected this thought: "If Chang Shan Yin is such a scheming person despite being a hero of this magnitude, would there still be righteousness and light in this world? I am simply measuring the stature of great men by the yardstick of small men."

Three days later.

Man tribe's father and son stood on the mound, watching Ge tribe leave towards the south.

"Lord father... there is something I don't understand, I would like to ask father." Man Duo asked.

"Speak."

"You gave the things mentioned in the letter to Chang Shan Yin for free, I understand the meaning of that. But why did you also give Ge tribe a thousand and five hundred tonnes of provisions? Not only is our prey escaping, we even have to supply them, this..." Man Duo felt indignant.

Man Tu's expression was solemn, looking at the leaving Ge tribe, he said: "Man Hao, explain."

Elder Man Hao who was standing at the side laughed as he explained: "No need to worry third young master, lord tribe leader had planned this long ago. Ge tribe is dreaming if they want to leave so easily, there are a large number of wolf lure Gu inside the provisions, at the same time, we have tribesmen ahead, with three myriad wolf groups waiting in ambush for them."

"So that's it!" Man Duo understood at once: "Father is wise, once Ge tribe is unable to resist the wolf pack, our tribe will move out and save them, assimilating them using this chance. In future, if anyone suspects us, father can use these thousand and a half tonnes of provisions to show his sincerity and magnanimity, it will shut those suspicious people up. But..."

Towards the end, Man Duo was hesitant.

Man Hao sighed, saying: "But this way, Ge tribe would suffer great losses, and the gains of our tribe from taking over Ge tribe would be far less. In fact, we might even have to invest an amount of resources to take care of the injured."

But Man Duo shook his head, Man Hao's concerns were not the same as his: "Ge tribe has that Chang Shan Yin, he is hailed as the Wolf King, can these wolves stop him?"

Man Tu started frowning.

Man Duo expressed his own worry, he had such thoughts as well.

But Ge tribe left too quickly, Man tribe was part of the righteous path, they could not act recklessly, in this short period, they could only gather three myriad wolf groups.

If Ge tribe survives this assault, Man tribe can only watch them leave. But if they suffer great losses during the process, Man tribe would have the excuse to send 'reinforcements'.

The greatest uncertainty in this plan was Chang Shan Yin.

"Don't worry third young master, although this Chang Shan Yin is known as the Wolf King, that is over twenty years ago. His current cultivation is only rank four initial stage, and during the banquet, we checked secretly, his soul is no longer thousand man soul but has dropped to hundred man soul." Man Hao spoke with disdain.

"Hehe, even if he is the Wolf King, he is only a weak and barely surviving Old Wolf King. Moreover, what trump cards does he have? Only a thousand wind wolves and a thousand poison beard wolves, and a thousand water wolves. Hahaha, against three ten thousand wolf groups, what can his wolves do? The way I see it, his reputation will be ruined soon enough. We can prepare to devour Ge tribe already."

Man Duo did not rebuke him, but said: "Hopefully so."

Chapter 451: Turtleback Wolf Group

"Urgent report! A large group of turtleback wolves has appeared three thousand li ahead. They have a huge number, estimated to be a group of ten thousand wolves!" Ge tribe's investigative Gu Master came running over and reported to Ge tribe leader.

Ge tribe leader's expression turned solemn and waved his hand to the Gu Master: "Investigate it again."

Not long earlier, he had already received a letter Gu from investigative Gu Masters. But often in the battlefield, to prevent the letter Gu from being cut off by the enemies, investigative Gu Masters would come over to personally deliver the message.

"Turtleback wolf is the wolf species with the strongest defense. Ten thousand of these wolves will be a difficult bone to chew."

"We have already ordered Gu Masters to lure them, but there have been no results. This wolf group is heading towards us."

"Hmph, how long has it been since we started migrating? It seems Man tribe doesn't want to let us go...."

"Fortunately, these wolves are not fast which leaves us time to arrange our formation."

Ge tribe's elders made comments one after another.

In the chaotic northern plains, none of the Gu Masters that could climb to a high position were fools. Right now, all the elders had already realized the truth.

Most of Ge tribe's troops had already halted their movements and formed into a circular formation. A large number of Gu Masters were nervously using Gu worms to erect high walls, archer towers and many layers of defense.

The higher-ups of the Ge tribe were overseeing the situation from the central tent.

"Son." Ge tribe leader softly called.

"Father, I am here." Ge Guang immediately answered.

"Invite Lord Chang Shan Yin to come over." At this battle which concerned the survival of the tribe, Ge tribe leader was not willing to let go of any battle strength.

"Yes." Ge Guang bowed and left; he had just walked out of the main tent when he saw Fang Yuan.

"Uncle." Ge Guang greeted cheerfully.

Fang Yuan nodded his head, directly walking towards him and said in a slightly urgent tone: "I know about the wolf group's invasion. How is the situation?"

"We have about eight minutes before the wolf group reaches. Since our relocation, to prevent Man tribe from playing tricks, father had assigned light cavalries to scout a distance of six hundred li!" Ge Guang followed Fang Yuan and reported to him from the side.

The two walked inside the main tent which was situated on a mound.

The mound had already been raised by using Gu worms; the higher-ups of Ge tribe had an excellent field of view from the mound.

This was because they encountered the wolf group. If they had ran into the eagle or owl group, they would have dug a tunnel. Different methods dealt with different situations.

Seeing Fang Yuan, the Ge tribe higher-ups hurriedly greeted him. The atmosphere here was tense like a storm was brewing.

"Our Ge tribe is really fortunate to have brother Wolf King to help us, I can be at ease." Ge tribe leader sighed and spoke with gratitude.

"Hehehe, the fate between me and the Ge tribe is not shallow. Friends should help each other when they walk the same path! How is the situation?" Fang Yuan asked.

"Please take a look." Ge tribe leader led Fang Yuan towards a table where there was a sheepskin which had a map drawn on it. He pointed towards it and introduced the surrounding terrain, Ge tribe's defensive lines and wolf group's movement.

"Sir has arranged it properly, there is nothing wrong." Fang Yuan first praised, then pointed towards a mark on the map.

Everyone's gaze followed his finger; it was a river beside their camp.

"Since there is such a danger area, why don't you use it for defense?" Fang Yuan proposed.

"Brother might not know yet, we have already thought of it, but most of the troops have slow movement and it will be too late by the time we reach the river, set up a camp again and arrange new defensive lines." Ge tribe leader gave a bitter smile.

For the tribe's migration, most of the tribesmen were using big stomach horses. However, due to many things being stored in the big stomach horses, their speed was slow.

Ge tribe's Gu Masters could quickly reach the riverside on the hump wolves. But most of the mortals would fall behind and once the wolf group arrived, all the mortals might be annihilated.

Without mortals, how could there be any future new Gu Masters in any tribes? Mortals were the cornerstone of all tribes.

However, Fang Yuan gave a bright smile: "Brother, I am also a northern plainsmen, I naturally know this. We are not able to go to the riverside, but we can let the river come to us."

The Ge tribe's higher-ups' eyes brightened at these words.

"Right, we can dig a canal and draw in the river to help us defend."

"Turtleback wolves have heavy bodies and are unable to swim; once they fall into the river, they will sink to the bottom and drown to death."

"Lord tribe leader, send the command quickly!"

Ge tribe leader also directly sent the command: "I command Ge Cui, Ge Xiang, and Ge Mi to lead the first, seventh and eighteenth troop respectively, immediately stop all current tasks and go to the riverside to dig a canal. As for the third, fifth and the sixteenth troop, you shall take over the unfinished tasks of first, seventh and eighteenth troop."

"Yes!" The investigative Gu Master outside the tent immediately received the order.

Several breaths later, three letter Gu flew out separately towards distant locations.

"Fortunately, brother was here to guide us out of this bewilderment." The old tribe leader greeted Fang Yuan again with a grateful expression that came from the depths of his heart.

Just relying on this suggestion from Fang Yuan, they could preserve around a hundred Gu Masters and even could reduce the casualties.

He is the Wolf King after all...

Instantly, all the Ge tribe's elders' gaze towards Fang Yuan faintly changed into that of praise and admiration.

During this tense and busy period, time passed quickly.

Investigative Gu Masters came to the camp one after another to report the position of the wolf group. At the same time, they had also clearly scouted the numbers of the turtleback wolves.

Over thirty-eight thousand!

When the wolf group was only eight hundred li away from the camp, Ge tribe leader began to call back the investigative Gu Masters steadily.

By the time the wolf group had reached five hundred li away from the camp, the canal was formed and the river water was drawn in.

When they reached three hundred li, three defensive lines finished forming and combat troops were deployed urgently. The support and logistics Gu Masters in charge of the construction retreated one after another, using primeval stones to quickly recover their primeval essence. They did not dare to relax for even a moment. When the battlefront was unable to endure, they would have to go as reinforcements.

At a hundred li away, everyone could see a large number of ghostly shadows of the wolves in the horizon.

In the main tent, eight investigative Gu were activated; smoke rose and could be seen from all directions.

Turtleback wolf group was mainly coming from the northern side. At the same time, there were also a lot of wolves coming from the northeast and southeast.

As the wolf group neared closer and closer, all the mortals could see them clearly.

Turtleback wolves possessed broad physique, their whole body was dark-green and had dark-blue eyes. On their back was a shell like that of a turtle.

This shell was very heavy and about one-third of a turtleback wolf's weight was due to it. Apart from defensive purpose, it could also store nutrition just like camels.

The charging of a few tens of thousands of wolves caused the ground to start shaking.

Fang Yuan walked out of the main tent and gazed at the grassland only to see large numbers of wolves moving on the ground. He then looked at the camp below; the Ge tribesmen were moving about busily without disorder, it was a normal thing to encounter beast attacks in northern plains. Thus, whether it were Gu Masters or mortals, they had cultivated a strong mind.

The first defensive line at the north was the first to meet the attack.

"Fight!" A Gu Master leader who was watching from a tower shouted loudly and threw a wind blade.

Soon after, the surrounding Gu Masters also began to make their moves.

A row of wind blades flew far, cutting over dozens of turtleback wolves instantly.

When the wolf group reached closer, the Gu Masters abandoned the wind blades and used the more powerful fire Gu, lightning Gu and so on.

For a moment, countless colorful lights burst out in the battlefield, like simultaneously fired fireworks. Human shouts, furious wolf howls and the piercing sounds from the wind blades formed into a medley of sounds.

The wolf group's offensive was like a rain that came unceasingly, and succeeded in charging over. They first came across the earth walls.

The earth walls were thick, and their foundation had been reinforced with copper and iron.

Countless turtleback wolves were badly bruised when they smashed against these earth walls and even died on the spot.

However, the wolf group advanced wave upon wave, some trampled upon the corpses and leapt high, while some clawed the earth walls to pierce through.

Next, the defensive lines at the south east and north east also entered the battlefield.

Shouts resounded all over the sky and casualties began to appear. Healing Gu Masters began to show their worth.

Because they had made sufficient preparations, the whole Ge tribe was moving in an orderly fashion.

"Look, it is a myriad wolf king!" Someone shouted while pointing at a certain direction.

Everyone immediately followed the voice and looked.

This turtleback myriad wolf king was enormous, even ten times the size of a normal turtleback wolf was slightly inferior to it. Its tyrannical aura manifested as it crouched on the ground and howled, commanding the wolf group to divide.

Turtleback wolf group divided into five to six groups and began to circle around the Ge tribe camp, searching for a hole in the defense.

Like this, Ge tribe was surrounded by wolves from every directions, and battle unfolded everywhere.

On a nameless hill outside of the battlefield, a group of Man tribesmen were using Gu worms to conceal themselves and were using investigative Gu to observe the situation.

"The battle has started!" Man Hao smiled, taking joy in Ge tribe's calamity.

"Ge tribe actually channeled the river through a canal, Ge tribe leader is truly an old fox! But, there are over thirty thousand turtleback wolves, even if Ge tribe is able to resist them, they would suffer serious losses." Man Hong smiled coldly.

His appearance was strikingly similar to the tribe leader Man Tu; he was Man Tu's eldest son and had a cultivation of rank three middle stage.

"Young tribe leader is right. Even if Ge tribe can block the first wave of the wolf group, there is still the second wave and also third wave." Man Hao flattered.

Although Man Hong was the eldest son, but he was still not truly the young tribe leader. However, Man Hao had already pledged his allegiance to Man Hong and was his zealous supporter; he called Man Hong young tribe leader, it was a flattery and also his expectation.

"Young tribe leader?" Man Hong did not refute and instead nodded his head, "Father has given this important task to me, I will be establishing great merits by finishing this and might indeed be a young tribe leader when we return to the tribe. Unfortunately, that sneaky brat Man Duo did not come over, otherwise I could borrow the strength of others and conveniently get rid of that sinister brat!"

"Man Duo might be somewhat intelligent, but his aptitude is lacking and he is simply not young tribe leader's match. Look, hundred wolf kings have made their move!" Man Hao said.

Hundred beast kings had rank two Gu worms residing in their bodies, and were very strong. Their appearance immediately caused the pressure on the Ge tribe's frontline forces to increase greatly. The number of casualties increased sharply, and 2 to 3 hundred wolf kings smashed the earth walls and pierced through the Ge tribe's defense.

"Hehehe." Looking at the Ge tribe's Gu Masters dying one after another, Man Hong showed a pleased, sinister smile.

This ignorant bunch of fools actually did not join Man tribe, now weren't they suffering their just desserts?

"Hmm?" Man Hong's smile stiffened; through the investigative Gu worm, he saw a wolf enslavement Gu entering a hundred wolf king.

It immediately changed its alignment and let out a howl, causing the wolves beside it to fall into chaos.

Soon after, these turtleback wolves followed the wolf king towards the Ge tribe's camp and gathered under a Gu Master.

Man Hong narrowed his eyes and looked at this Gu Master: "Could this person be the Wolf King, Chang Shan Yin?"

"Yes, young tribe leader." Man Hao confirmed.

Man Hong scoffed: "Father said he was the greatest uncertainty. Let me see what ability he has!"

Chapter 452: Intense Battle (1/3)

"Look there, it is the great hero of northern plains, Chang Shan Yin!"

"Chang Shan Yin struck, he truly is spectacular!"

The camp was cheering.

Not only Man tribe, but even Ge tribe Gu Masters were looking at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had just tested his skills, subduing a hundred wolf king and instantly made several hundred turtleback wolves part of his force, it turned this battlefield into a safe zone.

"Chang Shan Yin..." High up on the mound, old Ge tribe leader looked at Fang Yuan's back view as he muttered.

In everyone's mind, there was one question — The former Wolf King, the genius of northern plains, how much battle strength did he have left now?

Fang Yuan looked at the tens of thousands of turtleback wolves in front of him with an earnest gaze.

In other people's perspective, these wolves were a threat, but in Fang Yuan's eyes, these were presents sent to him.

He was worried about not having enough wolves in his group, but if he could subdue these wolf kings, his battle strength would surge!

At this time, it was a clear blue sky as sunlight shone down, vision was clear as the battle was ongoing.

Ge tribe had prepared sufficiently, having three earth walls to defend them, and also built water canals to divide the incoming wolves into segments, preventing them from encircling the Gu Masters, this was a terrain advantage.

Looking at themselves, Ge tribe's Gu Masters were defending with young tribe leader Ge Guang leading, they were extremely safe. Ge tribe were united in defending against the wolf groups, their hearts were as one, this was the most favourable condition.

"If I travelled alone, I would have to run away from a beast group of such a grand scale. But now, all the conditions were perfect for me! This is a godsent opportunity placed in front of me, how can I not make full use of it?"

Thinking so, Fang Yuan laughed cheerfully, his battle intent rose as he said to the people: "Everyone, come with me!"

Ge Guang and the others responded.

Under Fang Yuan's lead, the Gu Masters started to move their formation, going to another area of the battlefield.

Bam!

A tall arrow tower fell onto the ground, smashed into pieces.

The culprit behind this roared loudly as it battled a dozen rank two Gu Masters around it.

This was a hundred wolf king.

At this point, all the wolves around it had died, it was battling alone fiercely.

The surrounding Gu Masters used their Gu worms to attack from a distance, trapping it as they whittled away its life slowly.

On the battlefield, there were three Gu Master corpses.

At this point, Fang Yuan and the others rode their hump wolves and arrived.

"Wolf enslavement Gu, go!" Fang Yuan pointed with his finger and the rank two wolf enslavement Gu turned into a light smoke, landing on this hundred wolf king's body.

The wolf king howled angrily, unwilling to be enslaved, resisting with all its energy.

Fang Yuan's eyes shone as he suppressed it with his hundred man soul!

The wolf king whimpered as the smoke settled into its body, turning it into Fang Yuan's personal pet instantly.

The hundred wolf king sprawled on the ground, keeping its claws and teeth as its body was covered in injuries, oozing with blood.

"Healing Gu Master." Fang Yuan instructed, and a Gu Master walked out from behind him, activating his Gu worm and healing this hundred wolf king.

"This goddamn beast! He killed my brother!" A young Gu Master who had entered battle still wanted to attack.

"Ge Can!" Ge Guang shouted, staring at this person.

The young Gu Master's neck stiffened as he walked to the hundred wolf king, kicking it fiercely, but did not try to kill it.

Next, he covered his face and cried, sobbing uncontrollably.

The surrounding Gu Masters felt a strong resonance with him.

After the young Gu Master cried for a while, he raised his head, wiping his tears as he said: "Go, let's continue killing wolves!"

"Alright!"

"Let's follow brother Ge Can."

This ordinary small group entered the battlefield again.

"Let's go to the next stop." Fang Yuan continued to move ahead.

At the northwest area, 3 hundred wolf kings broke through the earth walls and were ravaging the line of defense.

Fang Yuan quickly arrived: "I am Wolf King Chang Shan Yin, all Gu Masters listen to my instructions."

With Ge Guang beside him, he successfully gained the commanding rights.

"These 3 hundred wolf kings, what are their respective Gu worms?" Fang Yuan asked.

Immediately someone reported.

Fang Yuan's eyes shone as he split the people into three groups.

"Group one will lure the left hundred wolf king, and bring it to the second line of defense." Fang Yuan instructed.

"Bring it there?" A Gu Master was shocked, expressing his concern.

Fang Yuan stared at him fiercely: "I said bring it over, so do as I say. This is an order!"

"Yes!"

"Group two, restrict the wolf king on the right, make sure you destroy its defensive Gu."

"Yes!"

"Group three, follow me." Fang Yuan waved his hand and entered the battlefield personally.

After a bit of battle, he used the wolf enslavement Gu.

The light smoke was about to land, when this wolf king shot out a flame that burnt the smoke away.

Fang Yuan's expression turned cold, he felt heartache losing this rank two wolf enslavement Gu.

Ge Guang scolded: "Why did it still have a firelight Gu?"

"Please forgive me young tribe leader, this is the first time this Gu has been used!' The subordinate quickly reported.

"Ge Guang, you are in charge of this firelight Gu, use all methods you have, I will come back shortly." Fang Yuan saw that this wolf king could not be handled in the meantime, thus he gave his instructions and passed the trouble to others. Meanwhile, he swapped his target to another wolf king, using a wolf enslavement Gu.

This wolf king's defensive Gu worms were already destroyed by Gu Masters, without any accidents, Fang Yuan easily captured it.

When he turned around, Ge Guang already created trees and sealed this hundred wolf king's mouth with vines, it could not shoot out any more flames.

"Good job." Fang Yuan praised as he used a wolf enslavement Gu.

The hundred wolf king watched the light smoke enter its body, after a mild resistance, it lost to the hundred man soul, becoming another one of Fang Yuan's pets.

After keeping these 2 hundred wolf kings, Fang Yuan turned around and captured the hundred wolf king at the second line of defense as well.

In just a short time, Fang Yuan divided the 3 hundred wolf kings up, and captured them one by one, resolving this crisis.

Everyone was amazed, they continued following behind Fang Yuan, listening to his commands. Eventually, they realised that as long as they followed his commands, they would result in the least injuries or deaths possible.

"This Chang Shan Yin has some skills." Outside the battlefield, eldest son Man Hong used his investigative Gu worm to watch Fang Yuan's performance, his expression sinking.

"His soul is a hundred man soul, it is not hard to subdue these hundred wolf kings. But just this cannot change the situation. It will depend on his wolf manipulation skill!" Man Hao consoled at the side.

"Mmm..."

Fang Yuan sat on the ground directly, holding two primeval stones as he recovered his primeval essence.

Activating wolf enslavement Gu did not expend much primeval essence, but most importantly, it was the burden on his soul.

Fang Yuan subdued hundred wolf kings one after another, he used his hundred man soul to suppress the wolf kings. After the competition between souls, Fang Yuan's soul became more impatient and impulsive, while the annoyed feeling in his heart intensified.

If he left this symptom alone, he might develop dizziness, or worse, his soul might get damaged, losing his memories or lowering his intelligence.

Fang Yuan closed his eyes and meditated, calming his mind and soothing his soul.

After resting for a while, the hundred man soul stabilized, all his negative emotions vanished into thin air!

"Everyone, continue following me on our conquest." Fang Yuan rode on his hump wolf as Ge Guang and the others followed.

Like this, after moving around the battlefield for a while, Fang Yuan subdued 3 hundred wolf kings, and eight hundred ordinary turtleback wolves.

Howl!

Fang Yuan's actions angered a thousand wolf king.

Seeing its subordinates surrender to an enemy, this thousand wolf king howled as it led the wolf group towards Fang Yuan, attacking fiercely.

A thousand beast king could control thousands of wild beasts, while also having several hundred beasts kings under it.

There were rank three Gu worms in its body, ignoring the wolf group, at least three cooperative Gu Master groups were needed to kill one thousand beast king. If there were three rank three Gu Masters, they could barely match evenly with it.

Seeing the thousand beast king charging over, Ge Guang and the others' expressions changed. They were mostly rank two elites, only Ge Guang was a rank three Gu Master.

"Don't worry young tribe leader, we are here to give you a hand!" Just at this moment, three Ge tribe elders came over.

Fang Yuan had made an agreement with Ge tribe higher-ups in the main tent, Ge tribe had to help out in this.

"Hahaha, with your help, this wolf is as good as ours." Fang Yuan laughed heartily.

An intense battle occured.

This thousand wolf king attacked in a frenzy, it used its claws and teeth, and was even able to summon a wolf strength phantom. On the battlefield, it rampaged and moved about without restraints, attacking mercilessly.

But on Fang Yuan's side, they had greater strength. Four rank three Gu Masters, one rank four Gu Master, as well as a number of rank two elites.

After two elders were mildly injured, Fang Yuan found a good opportunity and used a rank three wolf enslavement Gu.

The rank three wolf enslavement Gu turned into a light smoke, much thicker than the rank two version, as it landed on the thousand wolf king.

Fang Yuan used his hundred man soul to suppress it, and after a dozen breaths' time, the light smoke succeeded and completely fused into the thousand wolf king's soul.

This was the first thousand beast king Fang Yuan subdued in this battle.

After the thousand wolf king surrendered, the 2 hundred wolf kings and several thousand ordinary turtleback wolves under it also changed allegiance.

Such a great number of turtleback wolves revolted and switched to Ge tribe's faction, causing this part of the battlefield to cease battle.

The entire wolf group only had around 15 thousand wolf kings, but now one was taken by Fang Yuan.

At this moment, even the myriad wolf king felt something amiss, it howled as a huge four-leaf windblade rotated and shot towards Fang Yuan.

"Three claw water dragon Gu!" A clan elder shouted, pushing with his hands as a light blue water dragon crashed into the windblade, exploding and causing a small drizzle.

"Fist stone Gu!" The second elder punched with his right fist, as a large rock was created in mid air, flying forward like a fist, but was shaved by the windblade.

"Lightning web Gu!" The third elder shot out a large web made of lightning, covering the windblade.

The windblade was weakened, after it was covered by the lightning web, it rotated furiously and cut the web open, but it was at its final moments. As it flew in the air, it slowly dissipated.

Throughout the whole process, Fang Yuan did not do anything.

Ge tribe's Gu Masters were very protective of Fang Yuan, even if he was a rank four Gu Master that had higher cutlivation than them.

Enslavement path Gu Masters' lives were extremely important. Thus, when they battled, there were often Gu Masters in charge of protecting them.

Ge tribe's actions were not overly protective, it was just a norm of the Gu Master world.

Chapter 453: Intense Battle (2/3)

Myriad wolf king's attack caused all of Ge tribe to be nervous.

Far away, Man Hong's eyes brightened: "Is this myriad wolf king going to join the fight?"

But soon, his gaze dimmed.

After myriad wolf king failed in its attack, it did not make another attack and instead continued sitting at the rear while commanding the wolf group.

A branch of a thousand wolf group moved over to fill the gap created due to the previous thousand wolf king's surrender.

Crimson flames burned all over this thousand wolf king and its nose let out thick black smoke from time to time.

"A rank three self-ignition Gu." Fang Yuan recognized one of the Gu.

With this Gu worm protecting the thousand wolf king, wolf enslavement Gu's smoke would be burned off before it even landed.

Fang Yuan's eyelids twitched and he glanced at the far away myriad wolf king. Myriad wolf king also seemed to be staring back at him; when beasts evolves to myriad beast king stage, their intelligence would greatly surpass similar species, and this myriad wolf king was clearly indicating its decision to target Fang Yuan.

"Ge Guang stay behind and cooperate with three elders to kill this wolf! As for the others, follow me." Fang Yuan turned around and walked; subduing this thousand wolf king was not an impossible matter, but it would be very troublesome and time consuming.

This wolf was not suitable, so it was better to go to another. Anyway, the battlefield was so large, Fang Yuan did not believe all of them would have methods to suppress wolf enslavement Gu.

Sure enough, he moved around to several places and reaped great harvests. In just about two hours, he subdued 17 hundred wolf kings and 2 thousand wolf kings.

In total, Fang Yuan now had 4 thousand wolf kings, over 30 hundred wolf kings, and ordinary wolves were already over eight thousand in number, he was close to having a myriad wolf group.

Most of them were all turtleback wolves, but there was also a thousand beast level wind wolf king. Among the hundred wolf kings, there were also poison beard wolf king, water wolf king and wind wolf king.

With his actions, the military strength between the two sides in the battlefield was being equalized. Out of the thirty thousand wolves, a portion was incorporated by Fang Yuan into his troops and adding in countless deaths, the wolf group only had about twenty thousand remaining now.

The battle surged on like wildfire and Ge tribe leader eased his brows, seeing the hope of victory.

"With Chang Shan Yin making his move, the pressure on my tribe's troops has greatly decreased."

"He is after all the legendary hero, his skills are truly exceptional!"

"This is not strange, he is a rank four Gu Master, moreover he walks the enslavement path; such battlefields are his domain."

All the elders praised and the atmosphere in the main tent became relaxed.

"Don't be careless, myriad wolf king still has not made its move, the outcome of this battle is yet to be certain." Ge tribe leader promptly warned others.

"Lord tribe leader is right, we can't relax yet."

"In my opinion, this myriad wolf king might not join the fight. The wolf group has suffered huge losses, it is normal for the wolf king to retreat in this situation."

"Huh? Not good!"

Just as they were talking of it, myriad wolf king suddenly let out a long howl. All the wolves in the battlefield simultaneously went into crazed offense when they heard this howl.

Over twenty thousand turtleback wolves charged towards the camp without caring for their lives; for a moment, Ge tribe was caught off-guard and was utterly losing.

"Order the frontline to quickly retreat to the second defensive line." Ge tribe leader immediately commanded.

"The wolf group is making an all-out attack!" Ge Guang who was on the frontline paled.

"Go help the Gu Masters to retreat, I will go back to the ranch to rest and organize, wait for my support." Fang Yuan's expression was dark.

"Lord, we have been ordered by the tribe leader to protect you." Some Gu Masters hesitated.

Fang Yuan opened his eyes and let out a sharp gaze; the Gu Masters where his gaze landed all lowered their head.

"Ge Guang." Fang Yuan looked at the young tribe leader of Ge tribe.

Ge Guang gritted his teeth: "I shall listen to uncle."

He then waved his hand: "All of you follow me!"

Fang Yuan returned to the ranch alone, surrounded by wolves.

He gathered all the wolves together. With close to ten thousand wolves crowding together, this temporary ranch immediately felt narrow.

Fang Yuan willed and a strong vigorous water wolf moved out of the wolf group.

To ordinary people, this was a water wolf. But in Fang Yuan's eyes, it was a white-eyes wolf.

White-eyes wolf was a mutated beast, like Biao among tigers and lightning boar among boars. Every single ordinary adult mutated beast would attract wild Gu worms and possessed the strength that could match myriad beast kings.

However, this white-eyes wolf was still in infancy and had not matured yet. The fur on its whole body was like water and was dyed with a light blue color; the appearance of a common water wolf. But as long as people carefully observed it, they would discover its pupils was more white with little black, greatly differing from ordinary water wolves.

When it completely reached adulthood, its pupils would become white. At the same time, its vision would be greatly magnified, comparable to some rank four investigative Gu and even at night, its vision would not be affected.

Fang Yuan had accidentally discovered this white-eyes wolf in the market, and without making any suspicious movements, he bought all the water wolves.

At present, this white-eyes wolf had already been planted with rank three wolf enslavement Gu by Fang Yuan. And to speed up its growth, he had used third watch Gu.

This created a violent increase in the white-eyes wolf's appetite, about thirteen times more than the ordinary water wolves. Also, its lifespan had shortened.

"Go." Fang Yuan gave a command and this white-eyes wolf whose speed already surpassed that of the wind wolves, quickly moved out of the ranch towards the higher grounds.

Wolf care Gu!

Fang Yuan covered his right eye and only used his left eye to look at the white-eyes wolf. At the same time, he poured his primeval essence into Chang Shan Yin's investigative Gu.

Instantly, the scene in his left eye changed; as if he was overlooking the battlefield from a high ground.

This was the ability of the wolf care Gu; it could share the sight of the specific wolf to the Gu Master's eyes.

Fang Yuan then opened his right eye, and two different scenes transmitted to his brain at the same time.

His left eye showed the battlefield, letting him be clear on the situation; and his right eye showed the ranch where the wolves were crowded together.

Fang Yuan summoned all the wolf kings and searched through the Gu worms in their body.

If there were any rare Gu worms, Fang Yuan would take them so as to not let them be destroyed in the battlefield.

Naturally, his main focus was the wolf enslavement Gu.

Wolf enslavement Gu was a one time expendable Gu.

To capture so many wolf kings, Fang Yuan had used up a lot of wolf enslavement Gu.

Generally speaking, wolf kings would have corresponding wolf enslavement Gu on them.

Sure enough, Fang Yuan got a rank three wolf enslavement Gu and five rank two wolf enslavement Gu from these wolf kings.

As for other Gu worms, they were all ordinary with only one or two being better. But they could not catch Fang Yuan's eyes, so he left them on the wolf kings to preserve their battle strength.

Wolf smoke Gu!

Fang Yuan activated this rank four healing Gu which was especially used to heal the injuries on wolves. Surging smoke enveloped the whole ranch for a long time.

Fang Yuan's primeval sea rapidly lowered to the bottom.

The primeval essence consumption to heal so many wolves at once was very huge.

When the primeval sea hit the bottom, Fang Yuan took out primeval stones and quickly recovered his primeval essence.

After healing them twice more, Fang Yuan saw Ge tribe leader lead a group of elders and rush towards the frontlines. Soon, intense explosions sounded out from the frontlines.

Through his left eye, Fang Yuan saw that the motionless myriad wolf king had also joined the fight. Ge tribe leader and others went all-out against it.

With myriad wolf king joining the fight, there was a tremendous influence on the wolves and under its lead, the wolf group began to fight with even more madness.

The second defensive line of Ge tribe was also thus broken.

Fortunately, with the canal blocking the way, most of Ge tribe's Gu Masters could smoothly retreat towards the third defensive line and maintain the defense. For a moment, the atmosphere on the battlefield intensified to the extreme, causing great palpitation in the people.

The third defensive line was the final defense. Behind it was the weakest mortals, in case it was broken through, the consequences would be unimaginable.

"There is no time to heal again." After recovering the primeval essence in his aperture to ninety percent, Fang Yuan looked at the surroundings.

After three rounds of healing, the heavy injuries on these wolves had become light injuries while the light injuries were completely healed.

Wolf howl Gu!

Fang Yuan howled towards the sky, letting out a furious howl like that of a wolf king.

Under the effect of the Gu worm, the wolf group on the ranch faintly enlarged, their energy inflated and their battle strength multiplied!

Fang Yuan laughed loudly and rode on a hump wolf, with a shift of his mind, the wolf group immediately started howling together.

Howl---!

At this moment, when the sky was dyed red with the setting sun, when the wind was starting to blow strongly and when the battle was raging, the wolf howl spread without restraint, travelling a thousand li.

"Eh? Chang Shan Yin is making his move!" Outside the battlefield, Man Hong and Man Hao's expressions turned grave.

Ge tribe, however, was jubilant.

"Chang Shan Yin, it is lord Chang Shan Yin!"

"We still have lord Chang Shan Yin..."

"Lord Chang Shan Yin is coming to support us, everyone persevere!!"

"Step aside, open up a path for lord Chang Shan Yin."

Instantly, Ge tribe's troop morale rose rapidly.

Fang Yuan sat upright on the hump wolf and lightly waved his hand; close to ten thousand wolves surged forward, moving past the simplistic fence around the ranch, but they did not go to rescue the northern side, but instead moved towards the south.

Just like the collapse of a large dam, a powerful flood burst out! The whole wolf group rapidly charged out of the camp; 12 hundred wolf kings arranged as the arrowhead ruthlessly charged into the battlefield

The enemy wolf group had fought for a long time and was already exhausted, and now this new battle force attacked them, causing countless deaths in moments.

With only one assault, Fang Yuan collapsed the offense of the turtleback wolves on the southern side of the camp.

Wolf enslavement Gu! Wolf enslavement Gu! Wolf enslavement Gu!

Under the protection of the wolf group, Fang Yuan repeatedly activated three wolf enslavement Gu; the enslavement Gu changed into faint smoke and subdued 3 hundred wolf kings in moments.

"Charge to the left!" He willed it and the whole wolf army smoothly changed direction and charged towards the southeast battle.

Fang Yuan's gaze scanned the battle like an eagle and soon locked onto the thousand wolf king.

Thousand wolf king howled and did its utmost to command the wolf group. But most of the wolf group were deeply locked in the battle in the frontline and would be difficult for them to turn around for a while.

This thousand wolf king could only mobilize a few hundred wolves which were easily drowned by Fang Yuan's army.

Rank three wolf enslavement Gu!

Fang Yuan caught the chance and a faint smoke drilled down into the thousand wolf king; this thousand wolf king might have been scared stiff as it let out a whimper, its soul did not give any resistance and was quickly subdued.

This was the fifth thousand wolf king!

The wolf group that had been fighting with the Gu Masters, under its beckoning, stopped the fight and gathered under Fang Yuan's army.

The chaos at the southeast area immediately ceased!

Chapter 454: Intense Battle (3/3)

The battle that the Gu Masters had been fighting with their lives on the line was settled in the blink of an eye. Their mortal enemies had instead become their allies.

"Is this the ability of lord Chang Shan Yin?"

"Terrifying, terrifying..."

"Leading myriad wolf groups by himself, no wonder he is called Wolf King!"

Gu Masters looked at Fang Yuan with stupefied gazes. Their gazes looked at his receding figure, leaving this place towards another battlefield.

Moving unhindered, truly unhindered!

All those who dared to block his way were completely swept away.

Under his will, tens of thousands of wolves rushed forward. Under his indication, his troops moved everywhere, unrivalled!

With just his lone strength, he was overturning the crisis, changing the whole situation; he was the light of the enslavement path!

Outside the battlefield, Man Hong, Man Hao and the rest all lost color in their face.

Under their complicated gaze, Fang Yuan's wolf group rapidly expanded like a rolling snowball, getting bigger the more they killed. Everywhere they moved, they would leave behind ruins and a group of stupefied Gu Masters, before they swaggered off.

This wolf commanding tactic was simply unreasonable and also extremely domineering!

Under this huge strength, small hindrances were directly crushed.

Fang Yuan intentionally avoided the myriad wolf king's battlefield and circled around the Ge tribe camp, subduing three thousand wolf kings. In total, the number of thousand wolf kings he had reached eight.

As for the number of hundred wolf kings, they had almost doubled, reaching fifty-nine.

Fang Yuan's wolf formation was like a mythical beast, swallowing all turtleback wolves on its path and expanding itself.

After repeatedly subduing these wolf kings, Fang Yuan's soul also suffered from backlash; he felt jittery and nauseous.

Fang Yuan endured this feeling and gathered the wolf group before returning to the ranch.

The ranch could not hold these wolves anymore.

There were too many wolves, Fang Yuan also did not know the exact amount clearly, he could only guess the amount had surpassed twelve thousand.

Fang Yuan did not hurry to join the battle.

The situation was already determined now. He got off the hump wolf and closed his eyes to rest his spirit.

Every set interval, he would open his eyes to observe the battlefield through the white-eyes wolf's vision and keep an eye on the situation of Ge tribe leader and the others. These higher-ups of Ge tribe could not die. If they died, Man tribe might be roused into making a move.

After resting for a while, although Fang Yuan had not fully recovered, there was no problem in commanding the wolves. He joined the battlefield again.

This time, he only mobilized the eight thousand wolf kings to the battle. Ordinary wolves was too low of a threat against the myriad wolf king.

On his way, every Ge tribesmen would call out his name loudly.

"Chang Shan Yin has come to assist!" Hearing such voices, Ge tribe's higher-ups who were surrounding the myriad wolf king all felt their spirits invigorated.

"Everyone, please take a step back and rest for a moment, let me handle this!" Fang Yuan reached the battlefield and under his will, the eight thousand wolf kings encircled the myriad wolf king.

Myriad wolf king already had the intention to retreat, but whether it charged left or right, it could not break through the encirclement.

"Such wolf manipulation skills!" Seeing the myriad wolf king being played around by Fang Yuan, Man Hao, Man Hong and the rest revealed astonished expressions.

Previously, Fang Yuan had charged with grand troops, flattening everything on his way, so they were not able to see his wolf manipulating skill. Now, he was commanding the wolves meticulously, revealing the top-tier wolf manipulation skill of the northern plains.

There were merely 8 thousand wolf kings, and seven of them could not display their full strength due to the pressure from the myriad wolf king.

However, under Fang Yuan's control, the myriad wolf king felt like it was encircled by thousands of soldiers, as if it was a fly that was trapped in spider web.

Finally, the myriad wolf king was thoroughly exhausted to death by Fang Yuan, and in its final counterattack before death, it took away a thousand wolf king's life.

"Wolf King! Lord Chang Shan Yin is truly the Wolf King!" Looking at the myriad wolf king's enormous body falling down loudly, all the Gu Masters cheered loudly.

"Wolf King!"

"Wolf King! Wolf King!"

With this battle, everyone felt the nickname of Wolf King was truly fitting.

The shouting surged one after another and soon many joined in, shouting loudly with fervent gazes, and some even had tears falling from their eyes.

This was a type of emotional feeling, a type of worship towards the heroes, reverence towards the strength.

"With this person here, it is easier said than done for us to annex Ge tribe!" Man Hong's expression looked ashen to the extreme, this battle had thoroughly dispelled his ambitions.

"Wolf King..." Man Hao who had felt contempt towards Chang Shan Yin, absent-mindedly muttered this name. He had never felt how heavy the weight of this name was as much as this moment!

On the battlefield, Ge tribe leader brought the elders towards Fang Yuan.

"The might of the former hero still remains! Today's battle really makes me prostrate in admiration. I, on behalf of the whole Ge tribe, express my utmost gratitude to your favor of helping us!" Ge tribe leader deeply bowed towards Fang Yuan.

"Brother Ge, you speak too highly of me. Let's clean up the battlefield quickly." Fang Yuan smiled.

The myriad wolf king's corpse was lying on the ground, but Fang Yuan did not take the matters into his own hand to avoid suspicion.

"If I had a rank four wolf enslavement Gu, I could have taken in this turtleback myriad wolf king, such a pity." Fang Yuan felt regret in his heart.

Rank four beast enslavement Gu could control myriad beast kings. A myriad beast group was a huge force to a tribe.

Thus, normally, rank four beast enslavement Gu was not sold in the markets of northern plains.

For the price of many Gu worms, once they reached rank four, would rise sharply. Beast enslavement Gu was one of them, there was also relic Gu besides this.

Fang Yuan had only been able to purchase rank two and rank three wolf enslavement Gu in the market, and did not get a rank four wolf enslavement Gu.

"Right now, I have a large amount of rank two and three wolf enslavement Gu. But it seems I will have to refine the rank four wolf enslavement Gu myself."

Fang Yuan currently lacked rank four wolf enslavement Gu; with rank four wolf enslavement Gu, he could control myriad wolf king, and the burden on his soul to control the wolf group through the wolf king would decrease by a lot.

His mutated beast white-eyes wolf was currently an infant and could be enslaved by rank three Gu. But once it matured, it would require rank four enslavement Gu, otherwise it would not listen to commands and could even flee.

"Lord, we have found a rank four wolf enslavement Gu!" Right at this time, a Gu Master that was searching through the myriad wolf king's corpse shouted loudly.

"What?" Ge tribe leader's eyes flashed brightly and soon after, laughed, "Haha, precious Gu should fit a hero, this Gu should be given to brother Chang."

Although there was a great probability for a rank four beast enslavement Gu to reside in myriad beast king, Fang Yuan was still happy.

There might have been some flaws in today's battle, but the outcome still made Fang Yuan very satisfied.

It was regretful to have killed the myriad wolf king, but he was still able to obtain a rank four wolf enslavement Gu.

This Gu worm's arrival was really at great timing, it had been a long time since Fang Yuan had such a good thing happen to him.

He carefully accepted this Gu worm and said his goodbye to the Ge tribe's higher-ups, he did not even join in the celebratory banquet, using the excuse of refining this rank four Gu to evade it.

Nightfall.

The celebratory bonfire outside the tents was burning brightly. The victorious shouts and the cries for the casualties mixed together and spread towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was sitting cross-legged on the ground, his mind was calm as he looked in his aperture.　

The ninety percent primeval sea was tranquil, the water shining brightly like gold. Unfortunately, Fang Yuan had still not completely adapted to the northern plains, thus there was still the suppression, causing his cultivation to temporarily stagnate; the true gold primeval essence looked amazing but was useless right now.

However, cultivation was only one part of strength.

There were other ways for Fang Yuan to increase his strength.

For example, the strength of ten jun Gu he was currently holding.

This Gu was also a rank four Gu, but its price was much lower than a rank four beast enslavement Gu. And because it could be easily refined and the manufacturing costs were also low, it was rather common in the market.

Strength of ten jun Gu did not look anything special, looking just like a common iron weight.

Fang Yuan poured primeval essence to it, it then floated above Fang Yuan and let out dreamy light which shone upon Fang Yuan's whole body, engraving some Dao marks of the strength path on Fang Yuan's body.

After a while, the strength of ten jun Gu suddenly let out a slight explosion and broke into pieces, falling down on Fang Yuan's hair.

Strength of ten jun Gu was an expendable Gu, this was the third strength of ten jun Gu Fang Yuan had used.

Fang Yuan shook off the iron pieces and grasped his fists, feeling an increased strength: "The strength increase has reached a bottleneck. Next, I need to enhance my skeleton, skin, tendons and so on, to cause the water bucket - my body - to become deeper, larger and firmer, so it can hold even more strength.

Fang Yuan's gaze flashed as he took out a wolf soul Gu.

"This is the final wolf soul Gu."

Fang Yuan poured his primeval essence into the wolf soul Gu; the wolf soul Gu burst and changed into a grey wolf soul that smashed into his body.

Hundred man soul and wolf soul tangled with each other, the difficulty this time was many times more than before. Previously, when Fang Yuan used the wolf soul Gu, he only had over three thousand wolves under him. Now, after today's battle, he had taken in many wolf kings and thus the burden on his soul was much bigger.

Fang Yuan's brows furrowed into a knot, sweat perspired out of his forehead and he gritted his teeth to persevere; finally, the hundred man soul and the wolf soul merged together.

Boom!

A soft sound echoed in his ears, the long term quantitative accumulation had brought a qualitative change at this moment.

Hundred man soul had thoroughly changed into the wolfman soul.

The wolfman soul looked like a grey color that had been condensed to an extreme. The soul's appearance was mostly like Fang Yuan's, except the bridge of the nose was longer, eyes sharper and his body thinner. There were two sharp wolf ears, long hair that reached his waist and a hairy wolf tail that grew out of his butt.

With the formation of the wolfman soul, Fang Yuan felt relaxed as if he had gotten rid of a very heavy burden.

In his mind, the connection to the wolves became much more close, and he could even feel a faint familiar feeling from the wolf kings' souls.

This was not there when he had the hundred man soul.

After forming the wolfman soul, Fang Yuan gained the aura of a wolf, causing these wolf kings to think him as one of their species. Thus, it was no longer the pure suppression using the hundred man soul, but also a feeling of approval from the wolves.

"Hundred man soul was almost reaching its limits after enslaving so many wolves. Now, with wolfman soul, I can take in three times more wolf kings!"

"It is just that there will probably be few opportunities like today. But the grassland is so big and the wolf groups are plenty, I will at least be able to double this wolf group on our way to the heroes assembly."

Looking at the large amount of rank two wolf enslavement Gu in his aperture, many rank three wolf enslavement Gu and one rank four wolf enslavement Gu, Fang Yuan was full of expectations towards the future.

Chapter 455: Night Assault

There were few stars in the sky.

Bone-chilling wind blew through the grassland at night.

Two hump wolves were moving through this night; carrying Ge tribe's investigative Gu Masters, one old and one young.

"Huff huff huff, so cold." The young Gu Master curled up his body and blew out hot air.

"I told you to wear some more clothes, but you didn't want to. This is called suffering from not listening to your elders." The old Gu Master laughed, he was wearing a thick leather robe with long sleeves and long boots, along with a felt hat; he did not feel the slightest bit of cold.

"Uncle, this is my first time scouting, I lack experience." The young Gu Master mumbled in a soft voice before swearing, "F*ck, when I go out to scout tomorrow, I will definitely wear the thickest clothes."

"It should not be overly thick. Overly thick clothes will only affect your movement in battle. Moreover, you are likely to doze off if it is too warm. We are the eyes of Ge tribe, we need to be vigilant at all times. The best would be clothes that will keep you just warm, so you will feel cold if you stay still for long, this will urge you to keep on scouting." The old Gu Master shared his experience solemnly.

It was already the third day since the battle with the turtleback wolves.

The old Gu Master's partner had died in the battlefield, thus the young Gu Master was sent over to make up for the gap; the young Gu Master was still inexperienced and needed the old Gu Master's guidance.

"Uncle..." The young Gu Master was just about to open his mouth.

"Shush!" The old Gu Master suddenly stretched out his hand to signal a stop, his eyes squinted and looked at the light that suddenly emerged far away.

"What is that?" The old Gu Master was immediately on guard, he used his investigative Gu but could not make out anything.

"Kid, use your hand-ear Gu to listen!" The old Gu Master commanded.

"Yes!" The young Gu Master did not dare to be careless, he immediately turned over his body and got off the hump wolf and stretched out his right hand.

He transferred primeval essence towards his right palm; grass sprouted out from the palm, creating a flesh bud. The flesh bud then opened up to form an ear.

The young man closely stuck this ear on the ground and attentively listened.

"There is nothing other than the sound of the wind." The young Gu Master did his best to listen but got no result.

He laughed: "Uncle, are you trying to scare me? There is not even a fart."

"The battle just ended, so maybe I was too nervous." The old Gu Master heaved a sigh. He again looked into the distance, but there was nothing unusual; he felt his eyesight might have blurred just before.

"What is there to be nervous about, there is the old tribe leader here and we also have the Wolf King Chang Shan Yin with us. There is no need to be afraid even if another group of turtleback wolves come." The young man's gaze flashed when he talked of Fang Yuan, unable to conceal the worship in his eyes.

"Yes, it is indeed our tribe's fortune to have the help of the Wolf King." The old Gu Master sighed as he recalled the scene in the battlefield.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!

Suddenly, the sound of arrows quickly moving through the air spread towards them!

"Who?" The old Gu Master shouted, he subconsciously jumped off the hump wolf and smoothly rolled several times.

Thud thud thud...

Sharp bone spears pierced the ground one after another.

"Enemy attack!" The old Gu Master had this thought the first moment. He quickly stood up and hurriedly warned towards the young Gu Master.

The young man had already been pierced by a bone spear and had died on the spot.

The old Gu Master's heart twitched, but he did not have the time to grieve, immediately taking out a signal Gu from his aperture.

But before he was able to activate it, he was hit by a fatal attack.

He stiffly stood on the spot like a statue. A line of blood slowly appeared on his neck, becoming clearer and clearer.

Finally, his head inclined towards the side and fell on the ground, completely separated from the neck.

Fresh blood spurted out like a geyser from his neck.

Several figures walked out of the darkness, leading them was Man tribe's external elder Shi Wu. He looked at the two corpses and proudly said: "These ants, killing them is as easy as flipping my palm."

"Lord elder is formidable!"

"With lord elder here, Ge tribe's investigative Gu Masters are only empty shells!"

Several Gu Masters following behind flattered.

Shi Wu narrowed his eyes in joy and looked towards the direction of the Ge tribe's troops: "Hmph, this Ge tribe could win earlier because of their scouting, being able to make ample preparation in advance. This time, lord tribe leader has dispatched almost all the elders, Ge tribe will not be able to escape the calamity this time! Hehehe, I really want to see the shocked and frightened expressions on these people when ten thousand night wolves attack them at once."

Ge tribe might have already been on the move for several days, leaving Hong Yan valley and succeeding in defeating the turtleback wolf group, but Man tribe had no intention to let them go.

Three days after the attack of the turtleback wolf group, Man tribe Gu Masters secretly led night wolf group to make the second wave of attack on Ge tribe. At the same time, Man tribe's elders also moved out to kill large numbers of Ge tribe's investigative Gu Masters.

A large conspiracy against Ge tribe was already unfolding.

When this ten thousand wolf group was discovered, they were only hundred li away from the camp.

"Wolf attack! Wolf attack!" An investigative Gu Master observing from a watchtower shouted.

Whoosh Whoosh Whoosh...

Several signal Gu were shot out into the sky, bursting into bright fireworks.

"Everyone get up, there is an attack, it is a group of ten thousand night wolves!!" The Ge tribesmen who were in a deep sleep were startled awake.

"Quick, notify the tribe leader!" Investigative Gu Masters rushed about as quickly as they could.

Human figures gradually appeared from everywhere in the Ge tribe camp; doubts and panicked shouts mixed to form a commotion.

In the main tent, Ge tribe leader's expression paled when he got this news.

"Those damned investigative Gu Masters!" This was the first thought of the old tribe leader.

But he soon frowned.

Even if the night wolves were difficult to detect at night, but with so many night wolves, why hadn't the investigative Gu Masters reported sooner?

His sharp senses smelled a trace of conspiracy.

He quickly threw these thoughts to the back of his mind. It was not the time to think of these!

"The night wolves are already so close to the camp, there is no time to construct defensive lines! What do we do?""

In this boundless darkness, there was no clear intel on the enemy situation.

Ge tribe leader only knew this wolf group was large, at least a ten thousand wolf group. But he did not know if there were other wolf groups or if Man tribe's Gu Masters were hiding in the surroundings.

At this urgent moment, Ge tribe leader could not think of a countermeasure and could only send an order: "Send my command, all Ge tribe Gu Masters shall gather in the main tent!"

The night wolf group was fast and had reached the camp.

"The wolf group is here!"

"Block them, we must block them!"

"Quick, activate light sphere Gu."

A Gu Master who was at the frontline shot out a rank two light sphere Gu towards the sky.

Under the illumination of the light sphere, the densely packed night wolf group showed their appearances.

These night wolves were thin with strong posture, they had black glossy skin but had no fur. Their black pupils and claws gave off a cruel light.

A hundred wolf king growled and charged over.

"My god!" The Gu Master could only shout in shock before he was killed instantly by the wolf king.

The night wolf group was like a torrent, bursting through the simplistic stakes around the camp, and started their massacre.

Right now, Ge tribe's Gu Masters were still gathering towards the central main tent.

The vast outer camp had already turned into a sight of the netherworld. The wolves were howling excitedly, humans were wailing in grief and the cries of fear bursted forth together.

Night wolves were fast, and were tearing through the tents. Many mortals who were still in their sleep died cruelly under their claws.

They used death and blood as a warning.

The inner camp was in an uproar; the terrified humans surged out and tried to run away, trampling over each other.

A night raid!

Ge tribe leader stood outside the main tent; the corners of his eyes were almost torn open at this sight, his heart was bleeding.

The wolf group's massacre indeed caused many deaths, but even more deaths were caused by the people trampling on each other. Such a chaotic situation was already beyond control, causing the Ge tribe leader's plan to counterattack after organizing the troops to be in vain.

Most of the Gu Masters were trapped among the chaos.

Only many of the elders and a few elite Gu Masters were able to successfully gather in the main tent.

"Our advantage is no more!"

Ge tribe leader closed his eyes in pain, his body was cold as he fell into deep despair and grief.

"With this battle, even if we luckily gather in the remaining people, Ge tribe will fall down to a small scale tribe! Ge tribe had fallen in my hands! I am ashamed to face my ancestors! I am Ge tribe's sinner!"

In the main tent; some elders were shouting, some had lifeless expressions and some were panicking.

"Ge tribe is still not finished, everyone, there is only one way left to turn around this situation!" Following the sound, Fang Yuan walked into the main tent.

Ge tribe leader's eyes brightened like a drowning person finding a life-saving log.

"Brother, please speak quickly!" He looked at Fang Yuan and asked hurriedly.

Fang Yuan got right to the point and said resolutely: "Now, the camp is in chaos, we cannot simply defend, the situation has gone out of control. Only by using offense as defense, can we have a chance at survival."

"Wolf King, your meaning is?" Ge tribe leader mumbled.

Everyone looked at each other.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly: "Brother Ge, did you forget that I have a rank four wolf enslavement Gu with me?"

He looked at everyone's expressions and continued: "The ones here are all Ge tribe's elites, its strongest battle strength. We will form into a group and immediately move out, flowing against the wolf raid towards the myriad wolf king. In the battle, I will subdue the myriad wolf king, and the whole situation will turn around!"

Everyone's expressions changed.

This was a thoroughly messed up plan!

One should know, Gu Masters would rely on terrain advantage to resist the myriad beast group and fight a war of attrition, but even this would create huge casualties. Now, Fang Yuan wanted them to use their flesh and blood to charge against the offense of the myriad beast group and attack myriad wolf king among the countless wolves; this was simply courting doom.

This method was too risky, if someone else said it, they would have been furiously rebuked and even ruthlessly ridiculed.

However, it was Chang Shan Yin proposing it which caused everyone to fall into silence.

"Madness, this is complete madness." An elder mumbled.

Others showed hesitant expressions; going against the momentum of the wolf group would result in deaths nine out of ten times. Frankly speaking, it was asking them to give up their lives in exchange for the survival of the whole clan.

These rank three Gu Masters had been higher-ups for a long time and would normally be living luxuriously. All of them cherished their lives.

Chapter 456: A Hero’s Call

Ge tribe leader was hesitating, he was not a coward afraid of dying, because at this age, his cultivation was stagnant and he had already stopped caring about life and death.

His hesitation was, whether to use this method or not.

Ge tribe's era was over, but that did not mean it was destroyed completely.

If mortals died, they can just be replenished through snatching, in a Gu Master's eye, mortals were just numbers. As long as the Gu masters were intact, and the elders were intact, the tribe's structure would still be around.

If they retreated now, and gave up on the rest, only Ge tribe's higher-ups would be left, they would have to seek refuge with Man tribe.

But Man tribe had the intention to devour Ge tribe, this night wolf group's assault was most likely part of their schemes!

But if they used Fang Yuan's method, the risks were too great. If they fail, Ge tribe's higher-ups were finished, and the mortals would only be sheep waiting to get eaten.

"Father, and all the uncles here, I think that uncle Chang is right, this is the only way to save the tribe!" Ge Guang spoke, seeing the hesitant group, he felt a chill in his heart.

He was still young, he was hot blooded. At the crucial moment, he saw everyone's true colors, he had never seen this fragile side of Ge tribe.

Fang Yuan snickered in his heart.

When he first heard that the wolves were attacking, he was shocked, but soon he felt great joy.

If he was able to subdue this myriad beast king here, then his strength would rise once more, it could potentially double!

This was a one-off opportunity, he wanted to grab onto it. But under such circumstances, to enslave the myriad wolf king, he would need Ge tribe's help.

There was danger in charging at the frontlines, but to Fang Yuan, it was not too much of a problem.

He was a rank four Gu Master with a rank three eagle wings Gu, if the situation turned south, he could fly away to escape easily.

It was too much of a pity to let Ge tribe decline like this, since he wanted to make use of them, he should maximise their worth.

"Everyone!" Fang Yuan shouted, attracting everyone's gazes.

His words resounded like thunder, as he shouted: "What are you waiting for? Why are you hesitant? Are all Ge tribesmen cowardly and afraid of death?!"

"Listen, those are the cries of our Ge tribesmen, these vile night wolves are slaughtering our parents, our friends, our wives and children! If Ge tribe is wiped out tonight, you will all be homeless!"

"Can you bear to see our family die right under our very eyes? I cannot! Although I, Chang Shan Yin, am just an outsider, during these days of living here, I felt warmth, I felt the intense love that the Ge tribesmen had towards each other. For your friends, for the justice of this world, I will charge forward, and fight for a chance of survival for everyone."

"The males of Ge tribe, are your sabres still around? Your ancestors are watching you. Are cowardice and weakness flowing in your blood?"

Fang Yuan shouted in a righteous tone, his aura was overwhelming.

His voice was so loud, even the Gu Masters outside the king tent were attracted. The tribe elders looked at him deeply with a shocked gaze.

What was a hero?

The ability to turn the tides and overcome difficulty, that was only the hero's strength.

But at the crucial moment, at the moment of death, he would step forward and face the difficulty head on, he brought confidence and courage to others. That was the true demeanour of a hero!

Ge Guang heard Fang Yuan's words and his body trembled.

At this moment, Fang Yuan's image was so majestic, it was deeply engraved in his heart.

His eyes were shining, his pupils turned red, his heart was pounding, he felt a warm feeling surging inside him.

Swoosh, Ge Guang activated sabre Gu, holding it in his right hand as he raised it up highly.

Next, this young Ge tribe leader screamed: "No! The warriors of Ge tribe are still around. Ge tribe's sabres are still around! Our ancestors are all watching us descendants! Oh Wolf King, others might be afraid of death, but I, Ge Guang, am willing to follow you to the depths of hell!!"

Saying so, a few hot-tempered elders were so triggered they shouted in shame.

"So what, the worst result is death, there is nothing to fear!"

"Those f*cking night wolves, I will kill you all!"

"Wolf King, young tribe leader, consider me, Ge De, a member of the vanguard troop!"

These people not only responded, they even gave a disdainful and scornful gaze towards their surroundings.

Even more people were triggered by this, after all, northern plainsmen were usually very courageous.

"Kill! Use our blood to prove the bravery of us Ge tribesmen!"

"Battle to the death, battle to the death!"

"Count me in, I will battle too!!"

The overwhelming atmosphere burst out in the tent.

Even elders who did not want to join this fight shouted out their willingness to participate. They did not want to be called a coward for life. In northern plains, as long as one gains such a bad reputation, they would be despised by everyone.

The development of this situation was far beyond the hesitant Ge tribe leader's control.

He was old, he did not want to take risks.

He already had the intention to retreat long ago, as long as the higher-up Gu Masters were around, Ge tribe had their foundation and could start all over again.

If they charged forward, the risks were too great, there was an unknown number of night wolves in the darkness of the night, other than that, Man tribe might even be scheming something, and Chang Shan Yin might not succeed in subduing the myriad wolf king. Even if everyone charged out, if the myriad wolf king refused to fight them head on and chose to escape, what then?

Fang Yuan's plans had too many flaws, it was not reliable.

"Oh no." Old Ge tribe leader saw the surrounding elders' red eyes and realized that his hesitation was already useless, they had no choice but to fight now.

"Battle to the death! Battle to the death!"

"For Ge tribe, for tomorrow!"

"A battle of life and death, this will show our overwhelming bravery and courage!"

Outside the main tent, cheers and slogans were resounding as the morale of the troops surged, they were united now.

Fang Yuan's words easily turned the situation towards his intended direction.

Everyone's hearts were united, old Ge tribe leader no choice but to go along with them, he bowed deeply towards Fang Yuan: "Wolf King, you are a true hero! Ge tribe's future lies in your hands, we will accompany your wolf group in charging forward and taking down the myriad wolf king."

Everyone accepted the orders.

Fang Yuan's gaze shone, Ge tribe leader's intention was to sacrifice the wolf group to protect the Ge tribe Gu Masters.

But a little sacrifice was no big deal. As long as he obtains the myriad wolf king, it would be a huge gain!

"Everyone, charge with me!" Fang Yuan shouted, bringing all the Gu Masters and left the main tent.

A few hundred wolf kings and thousand wolf kings also gathered.

"Brother Chang, why are there only these wolves? Where are your other wolf kings? Where is your wolf army?" Old Ge tribe leader questioned, his heart sinking.

Fang Yuan snorted in his heart, why did he have to sacrifice his wolf kings to protect these Ge tribesmen?

All living beings in this world were equal, there were none who were more valuable or royal than another.

Wolves and men were both living beings, ignoring their standpoint, they were equal lifeforms.

Why did wolves have to sacrifice their lives for men? Were humans more noble than wolves?

No.

Whether one was noble or lowly, that was only a class system. And that system was based off strength.

Be it Earth or this world, the biggest law was the elimination of the weak, the big fish eats the small fish, the small fish eats the shrimps.

The so-called nobility was built on the foundation of greater strength. Without this, even the purest and most elegant lady is nothing more than a promiscuous b*tch!

Fang Yuan needed Ge tribe's accompaniment earlier because he had few wolves, it was dangerous for him to travel alone, and there were greater difficulties in doing so.

But now, he had the myriad wolf group, Ge tribe's value diminished greatly.

The wolves obeyed him, he could control their life and death at will. But could Ge tribesmen allow this?

"For an outsider, you want me to sacrifice my closest and most loyal subjects? Did you really think I was a dimwit like all your hot-blooded tribesmen?" Although Fang Yuan felt great disdain in his heart, he showed a confident and warm smile, saying to old Ge tribe leader: "Don't worry brother Ge, the situation is chaotic now, the ranch was destroyed and the wolves are scattered. I have ordered the wolf kings to assemble, soon, we will have a reinforcement wolf troop coming."

Old Ge tribe leader looked at Fang Yuan deeply, and was about to speak.

But Fang Yuan did not give him the chance, he shouted: "Everyone, Ge tribe's survival depends on this moment, charge with me!"

Saying so, he squeezed with his legs and ordered the hump wolf below him to charge forward.

"Kill!"

"Kill these goddamn wolves!"

"For Ge tribe, for tomorrow!"

Everyone shouted in a frenzy, as young Ge tribe leader followed behind Fang Yuan closely.

Old Ge tribe leader was so angry he pulled his son back, shouting at his ear: "Remember, you are the young tribe leader of Ge tribe!"

After that, the father and son started to charge towards the night wolves while protected deep inside the formation.

Two rank four, seventeen rank three, and a great number of rank two elites, it was a great strength, like a sabre that stabbed into the battlefield.

They had an overwhelming aura, no wolves could stop them, soon, they charged out of the camp and went straight for the myriad wolf king.

Once out of the camp, everyone's pressure intensified. Especially the Gu Masters at the outer edge, all they could see were night wolves.

Wind blades, water dragons, stone fists, golden cones... all sorts of attacks were unleashed like cheap fireworks. The wolves were hit unguarded, and many died in the process.

Everyone fought and killed, creating a path for themselves.

Howl!

Myriad wolf king howled, and twelve thousand wolf kings and tens of hundred wolf kings gathered, attacking Fang Yuan and gang from all directions.

Myriad wolf king understood Fang Yuan's intentions, to compete against him, it sent elites to fight the elites.

Fang Yuan had stealthily gone to the most inner circle of the group, he shouted in a frenzy: "Chaaaaaarge! Faster, if you do not charge faster, we are all dead meat! If we enslave the myriad wolf king, we would overturn the situation!"

In a moment, hundred wolf kings and thousand wolf kings entered the battle.

The troop's advancement became even slower, as many rank two elites were sacrificed.

"Oh no, my primeval essence is running low, I can only activate the self-detonate Gu... For the tribe!" A tribe elder shouted loudly, going out of the formation and charging into the wolves.

The wolf king opened its mouth as it bit him.

This tribe elder snickered as he exploded, killing this thousand wolf king on the spot!

This was the first tribe elder that died in this battle.

Old tribe leader saw this and he felt his heart bleeding.

These elders were the foundation of Ge tribe, they were the main pillars of support. Seeing their deaths, old tribe leader could almost see the collapse of the main tent.

Chapter 457: Wolf King, where are your reinforcements?!

The old tribe leader became increasingly dissatisfied with Fang Yuan, shouting: "Wolf King, where are your promised reinforcements?"

"Brother Ge need not worry, they will arrive soon! Everyone, follow me to take revenge for the elder's death!!" Fang Yuan roared and moved ahead of everyone towards the frontline.

"Protect Lord Chang Shan Yin!" Ge Guang immediately shouted.

"Lord Wolf King, you are our key to victory, please stay within our protection zone!"

"Kill, kill these beasts!!"

Everyone in the troop had bloodshot eyes, they forgot any worries of death and entered a berserk state. Even if they died, they would take the wolves with them.

The ferocious nature of northern plains natives could be seen clearly.

Ge Guang who was charging towards the front was dragged behind by the old tribe leader: "Stay behind me!"

Ge Guang shouted and after killing for a while, he moved towards the front again.

Ge tribe leader angrily grabbed him again and raised his hand: "Stay behind me, don't forget you are our Ge tribe's young tribe leader!"

"This old guy..." Fang Yuan sneered inwardly when he saw this scene. In the whole troop, the old tribe leader and him were the only two people with a clear mind.

"You guys go ahead, I will pin down these damned wolves!" Battle hall elder shouted.

His body suddenly inflated and became a giant rockman. He was a Gu Master at rank three peak stage, but now his cultivation suddenly surged to be comparable to rank four stage!

"Battle hall elder!" Ge tribe leader felt extreme heartache; battle hall elder was Ge tribe's second strongest expert, but he was sacrificing his life here.

"Once lord battle hall elder used this Gu, he had already sacrificed his own life..." Everyone felt an intense tragic feeling.

"Don't let battle hall elder's sacrifice be in vain, we will definitely turn the tide!" Fang Yuan shouted.

"Come, you beasts, let this old man keep you company. Hahaha!" Battle hall elder laughed heartily and with just his own strength, temporarily pinned down almost all the hundred wolf kings and thousand wolf kings.

With his help, the troop could finally reach the myriad wolf king.

"Kill!" Since things had already happened, Ge tribe leader charged forward without saying anything.

The rest also followed behind and sent out formidable killer moves.

Night wolf king spurted out acidic liquid and shot out poisonous needles, its whole body was covered with a layer of golden light and looked extremely ferocious.

"This is golden bell shield Gu, we must destroy it, only then can I use wolf enslavement Gu." Fang Yuan shouted.

Howl....

The wolf group howled and snarled as they surrounded the troop. Besides the Gu Masters, large numbers of night wolves were near the night wolf king.

The Gu Masters would have to deal with the night wolf king and also these ordinary night wolves.

More and more Gu Masters died; they used their life and blood to compose a moving battle song.

Night wolf king was extremely fast, much more faster than cheetahs. It did not have any fur but its black skin shone like armor and had great defensive power.

It moved here and there, and every time its strong and sharp claws attacked, an unlucky Gu Master would be torn to pieces. Every time its slender tail flung, the surrounding battlefield would be cleared.

Gu Masters continued to die and injuries also started accumulating on the night wolf king's body. But the golden bell shield Gu was still not broken.

The offense had only continued for a short while when a large group of wolf kings rushed over from behind.

Battle hall elder was dead and these wolf kings were no longer hindered.

"Wolf King, where are your reinforcements?!" Ge tribe leader shouted as his heart became filled with worry.

"Soon, just a little longer!" Fang Yuan hurriedly replied and ordered, "Ge Guang, lead a group and pin down these wolf kings."

"Understood! Uncle Chang can rest at ease, as long as I have a breath left, I will not let these wolf kings disturb you! Those willing to follow me, come over!" Ge Guang shouted and turned around, valiantly rushing towards those wolf kings.

Ge tribe leader's face turned purple with anger.

Fang Yuan shouted again from the side: "Brother Ge, don't be dazed, we need to quickly break the golden bell shield Gu. Once I enslave the wolf king, not only us, even the whole Ge tribe will be rescued!"

"Chang Shan Yin... If anything happens to my son, I will not let you off!" The old tribe leader swore in his heart.

He did not dare to call back Ge Guang under everyone's eyes, this would be showing favoritism openly. He could only attack the night wolf king in a frenzy.

"Tribe leader is mighty!" All the elders felt their morale raise when they saw the old tribe leader showing off his might.

"This old guy has extraordinary battle strength, he really concealed it deeply." Even Fang Yuan could not help looking at the old tribe leader in a new light.

Those who were at high positions definitely had some areas that surpassed others. The old tribe leader had led Ge tribe for so long, he was astute, capable and not a simple character.

The wolf king was ruthlessly beaten by the old tribe leader; it suddenly opened its mouth and shot out numerous eerie blue ghost fire.

Ghost fire Gu was a rank two soul path Gu. Once it advanced, it would be rank three ghost flame Gu. However, the ones being let out now were from the rank four ghost blaze Gu on the night wolf king.

The ghost fire surged rapidly, its bone-chilling coldness forced the Gu Masters to retreat; the tight encirclement also loosened.

Night wolf king thus gained precious time to take a breather and immediately prepared to retreat.

"Don't even think about it!" Ge tribe leader shouted and suddenly breathed in violently, sucking in all the ghost fire into his stomach.

Rank four — swallow fire Gu!

This Gu was not an attack Gu. Accurately speaking, it was a storage Gu, especially meant to store fire.

"This old guy has many good Gu worms." Fang Yuan was inwardly surprised.

Ge tribe leader's stomach inflated by three times after he swallowed all the ghost fire, appearing quite abnormal.

At the same time, his skin turned dark-blue, and blood started flowing out of his eyes, nose, mouth and ears.

Rank four — vine claw Gu!

Ge tribe leader shouted and extended out his left hand.

His left hand inflated by five times and turned into wooden root. His five fingers turned into strong purple vines and like a snake or a whip, it lashed towards the night wolf king.

The purple vines grew quickly and bound the night wolf king.

Night wolf king's attempt to flee was thwarted, it struggled with all its might and used its enormous brute force to violently tear apart the vines.

Ge tribe leader's face turned pale, although he had cultivated strength path as a minor path, how could his strength compare to the strength of the night wolf king.

The purple vines were roughly torn apart. Ge tribe leader screamed in pain, his left hand turned back to its original shape and his five fingers were all broken!

"Wolf King..." The old tribe leader snarled.

Fang Yuan knew he was going to ask 'where are your reinforcements', thus he walked towards him and said: "Brother Ge, careful!"

Right at this time, the night wolf king's tail flung over.

Fang Yuan activated azure wolf skin Gu and moved towards the tail, appearing like he was blocking the attack for Ge tribe leader.

Smash.

A clear sound echoed and he was thrown far away by the wolf tail.

"This... I could have avoided it!" The old tribe leader was stupefied.

"Quick, go save Lord Wolf King!" Academy elder furiously shouted and rushed towards Fang Yuan.

The night wolf king rushed over, it could sense that Ge tribe leader possessed the greatest threat towards it, so it directed most of its attacks towards the old tribe leader.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

The old tribe leader dodged and used his Gu worms to bombard the night wolf king; a man and a beast were fighting a life and death battle.

"Dragon Head Drill!" The old tribe leader attacked and retreated, before suddenly activating three Gu simultaneously, unleashing his killer move!

A four clawed wood dragon roared and soared. The dragon head turned into a pike and continuously spiralled, directly smashing against the night wolf king.

The golden bell shield Gu that had been protecting the night wolf king until now, flickered and finally broke.

Dragon head drill still had plenty of strength left as it pierced into the night wolf king's body. The night wolf king let out a painful howl; the sound was so loud that it seemed to tear everyone's eardrums, even suppressing all the mixed sounds in the battlefield.

With this heavy injury, the night wolf king's speed was greatly reduced and blood flowed out of it like a fountain.

But before the Gu Masters could rejoice, this night wolf king's eyes suddenly turned crimson, its battle intent surged and it counterattacked madly, forgetting all its pain.

Its battle strength had not fallen, but instead rose to almost double of its original strength.

"This is the rank four brave fight Gu, damn it! Chang Shan Yin, where is Chang Shan Yin!" The old tribe leader shouted.

"Lord Wolf King has fainted, we are currently healing him!" Academy elder and the others were protecting the 'fainted' Wolf King from the wolf group.

"Of all times, he chose this moment to faint!" The old tribe leader almost spurted out blood when he heard this. His eyelids twitched and he fiercely shouted: "Then, we won't wait for Chang Shan Yin! We will kill this myriad wolf king. The wolf group will collapse when we kill it!"

Although the night wolf king's strength rose, but without the protection of the golden bell shield Gu, it was easily injured.

The battle turned extremely bitter, almost every moment, there would be rank three Gu Masters being heavily injured or even dead.

With the intense battle lasting till now, the primeval essence in the Gu Masters were also almost used up. For the victory, they had to use this limited primeval essence to continue to battle.

Exchanging injuries for injuries, wasting each other's energy, the side that was able to remain standing at the end would be the victor.

The night wolf king felt the aura of death and became even more berserk.

The Gu Masters were all in disorder, only the old tribe leader was holding up a fight.

"Persevere, hold on!" The old tribe leader moved here and there, working as a rescue worker, and timely saved an elder. He repeatedly shouted, causing his voice to become very hoarse. His speed also became slower and his concentration started to slip.

He was old after all.

"Old tribe leader, careful!" An elder shouted from a short distance away.

The old tribe leader quickly turned his head and saw the night wolf king high in the air, pouncing towards him with murderous intent.

"Retreat!"

The old tribe leader had this thought, but his body could only stagger, the exhaustion had accumulated so much that had finally surpassed what his aged body could endure.

He was out of energy!

Boom!

The next moment, the night wolf king pounced and ruthlessly smashed him to the ground.

"Old tribe leader!!" Everyone shouted and rushed over as they forgot about the danger around them.

Ge tribe leader madly poured his primeval essence into his defensive Gu, creating a thick wooden shield.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

The night wolf king's claws repeatedly smashed the wooden shield; the wooden shield only lasted for few breaths' time before it collapsed. The enormous wolf claws then smashed upon Ge tribe leader.

The old tribe leader had also used Gu worms similar to ancient bronze skin and essence iron bones Gu, but he was not able to resist the tyrannical strike of the night wolf king.

"Old tribe leader!" Everyone cried out and crazily attacked, trying to draw away the night wolf king's attention.

But the night wolf king only had Ge tribe leader in its eyes, it was going to kill the old tribe leader to vent its anger even if it had to endure the attacks.

Chapter 458: Death of the Old Tribe Leader

"Father!" Ge Guang immediately let out a wild howl at this scene, his eyes almost splitting open.

Brave fight Gu's effect disappeared, the night wolf king's battle intent disappeared and it got away from Ge tribe leader's body, pushed back by everyone's attacks.

"This is the moment!" Fang Yuan's heart stirred and he 'woke up'.

Rank four — wolf enslavement Gu!

Wolf enslavement Gu turned into a large cloud of smoke and moved towards night wolf king's head, covering it.

The night wolf king's battle intent had disappeared and with its heavy injuries, its consciousness was almost already on the verge of collapsing; and now it had to contend against Fang Yuan's soul.

Fang Yuan's soul already surpassed the strength of hundred man soul.

Night wolf king had an intense feeling of conflict, but it sensed the aura of a similar species from Fang Yuan's wolfman soul.

This feeling of conflict thus rapidly decreased and under the pressure of Fang Yuan's soul, it did not last for long; the smoke merged with its body.

"Success!" Fang Yuan's eyes shone brightly.

Wolf smoke Gu!

He quickly hurried to the battlefield and breathed out large amounts of wolf smoke, covering the night wolf king.

Night wolf king's critical injuries were soon stabilized.

It let out a long howl; under this howl, the night wolf group turned chaotic and shortly retreated.

Ge tribe's crisis was resolved!

However, the surviving Gu Masters did not have any happiness of winning. They gathered around a deep pit.

Inside the deep pit was Ge tribe leader.

Several Gu Masters were beside him, doing all they could to heal him.

Ge tribe leader's body had already become a mushy paste, but under this intensive healing, most of his body was gradually restored.

However, it was in vain!

His injuries were fatal, and following the exhaustion of the healing Gu Masters' primeval essence, the slight hope of bringing the old tribe leader back to life also completely disappeared.

"Father, father!" Ge Guang kneeled on the ground, grabbed Ge tribe leader's hand and shouted loudly in heartache.

"Old tribe leader..." Remaining elders were also filled with tears.

The old tribe leader's face suddenly had a trace of red, and before his death, he exerted his last strength to grab Ge Guang's hand: "My son, be careful of..."

He was just about to say Chang Shan Yin's name, but right at this time, Fang Yuan pushed his way through the crowd.

"Brother Ge!" His face was full of sorrow, his shoulders slightly shook and warm tears trickled down his eyes.

The old tribe leader gazed deeply at Fang Yuan, his mouth opened and closed a few times but in the end, he had no choice but to change the subject: "Son, from today on, you are Ge tribe's leader!"

"Father, you can't die, I am still lacking by a lot, I still need your guidance. Ge tribe needs you!" Ge Guang replied with tears covering his face.

The old tribe leader gasped like a fish that was out of water, his vision dimmed and his consciousness rapidly faded like the ebbing wave.

The aura of death on him was already extremely dense.

"But I am not at ease! I have too many things I am unable to let go of..."

The obsession in him allowed the old tribe leader to muster the final drop and trace of strength; he grabbed Ge Guang's hand, as his blurred vision cleared up for an instant.

An unknown burst of strength gave him a final breath of life; he shook Ge Guang's hand: "Son, you need to remember you are Ge tribe's leader. For the tribe, never let yourself be impetuous and let your emotions affect you!"

With these words, the old tribe leader's body stiffened and his raised head also softly fell down.

Life left his body. This Ge tribe leader who did his utmost for the tribe, becoming the leader at thirty-eight, and dying in battle at eighty-seven. For Ge tribe, he did everything that he could, using every last drop of his blood.

To protect Ge tribe, he fought an intense battle against the wolf group and bravely sacrificed himself!

"Father? Father!!" Ge Guang howled, not willing to accept this cruel reality.

But truth was truth, since it had already happened, there is no way to salvage or change it.

"Father..."

"Old tribe leader..."

The battlefield was engulfed in great sadness and crying voices lingered in everyone's ears.

　　...

Dawn gradually approached, in the main tent, bright light had been kept on for the entire night.

At daybreak, Man Tu finally received a letter Gu from the battlefield.

"As long as we take over Ge tribe, our Man tribe's power will double!" With this expectation, he opened the letter Gu and hurriedly skimmed through it.

His gaze soon dimmed, disappointment appearing on his face.

"Lord father, could it be that even though we exerted almost all our forces, we still didn't succeed?" Man Duo was at the side, having waited similarly for a long time.

Man Tu let out a long sigh: "The night wolf group had already charged to Ge tribe camp, but Ge tribe leader and Chang Shan Yin joined hands to gather all their high level strength and staked everything on a counterattack. Chang Shan Yin subdued the night wolf king and put an end to the desperate battle. Ge tribe made a comeback..."

"Chang Shan Yin, him again..." Man Duo fell into deep silence.

Soon after, his eyes brightened as he suggested: "Lord father, we have not lost yet, there is still the final third wave of the wind wolf group. I have a plan."

"Ah? Speak."

"Our Man tribe was defeated twice, the real reason being the Wolf King Chang Shan Yin. This person is indeed amazing, as long as we get rid of him, Ge tribe will be ours."

"What plan do you have, speak up, don't keep me in suspense."

Man Duo laughed sinisterly and frankly said: "Chang Shan Yin has subdued the night wolf king, this is his strength but also his weakness. With the night wolf king, he has control over the wolf night wolf group. Such huge battle strength surpasses the whole of Ge tribe. Chang Shan Yin has become a ferocious beast that is lying beside Ge tribe, as long as he has a slightly bad intention, Ge tribe will be in danger. An astute person like Ge tribe leader will definitely be fearful and afraid. We will use this to spread rumors and make Ge tribe suspicious of Chang Shan Yin, driving a wedge between them."

Man Tu regretfully sighed: "This plan is good, but is no longer useful. I haven't told you that the Ge tribe leader has already died under the night wolf king. Ge Guang has already succeeded the tribe leader position."

"What?" Man Duo was stunned, "That old fox actually died? How could it happen so coincidentally?"

With the Ge tribe leader's death, the whole Ge tribe only had Chang Shan Yin as a rank four Gu Master, others simply could not compete with him.

Add in the losses the Ge tribe suffered after two battles, and Chang Shan Yin's wolf group enlarging to over twenty thousand, the strength between the two sides was already completely overturned. The situation was all up to Fang Yuan now and with his high prestige, no rumors could shake his authority.

"Ge tribe leader died, but the Wolf King still remains strong and has again subdued a large wolf group. Lord father, does this mean we have no more chance?" Man Duo asked indignantly.

Man Tu snorted, he put the letter Gu on the table and got up from his seat, pacing across the main tent with his hands behind his back.

"What more can we do? Are we going to mobilize the tribe and send troops? We have already lost the excuse called Ge Yao, we have no proper reasons left. This time, I listened to your plan and mobilized the elders, that was already overstepping the borders. Chang Shan Yin, our Man tribe lost simply because of this person." Man Tu heaved a long sigh.

"Then the third wave of wolf group..." Man Duo hesitated before asking.

A ferocious light flashed past Man Tu's eyes: "Since we have already reached this stage, then continue luring them. We will create even more losses to Ge tribe. If this wind wolf group is also taken by Chang Shan Yin, then I will wait to see the great Wolf King make a fool out of himself!"

　　...

Several days later, Fang Yuan let his large army and welcomed the wind wolf group.

With his exquisite control, he was able to gain a huge victory. Besides killing the myriad wind wolf king, he also subdued large numbers of thousand wolf kings and hundred wolf kings.

After calculating the results after the battle, Fang Yuan discovered his wolf group had already reached an enormous number of thirty-five thousand.

It was like doing business, the early stage was the most difficult, once capital was accumulated, it would be easy to expand.

After three battles, Fang Yuan's army of wolves had taken its form.

But to reach this stage, Ge tribe also paid a huge price. Countless mortals died along with large numbers of higher-up Gu Masters. Less than half of the elders remained and even Ge tribe leader had to sacrifice himself.

"Uncle Chang, it is really thanks to you that our Ge tribe could break away from Man tribe's control." Several days later, Ge Guang paid a visit to Fang Yuan, bringing a rank four impermanence bone Gu with him.

"Uncle Chang's favor to Ge tribe is as great as the mountains and rivers. But Ge tribe is beset with difficulties inside and out, so we are not able to repay your kindness. Junior saw this rank four Gu in the tribe's warehouse, I thought it might be of use to uncle so I brought it over." Ge Guang calmly said.

Setbacks force people to mature. With his father's death, Ge Guang received the position and became the tribe leader. His entire personality seemed to have changed and was much more steadfast.

"You have only recently assumed the tribe leader position and have been managing the tribe, if you need any help, you can tell me. Maybe there are some disagreements with the other elders, you can tell me." Fang Yuan accepted the impermanence bone Gu and asked in concern.

"There might be two-faced elders. It is only that the tribe has few primeval stones currently and we also suffered huge losses to our provisions, providing for the injured and so on are emptying the tribe warehouse. The situation has stabilized now, several days ago, some tribesmen even secretly escaped. Sigh, especially the matter regarding food, if this continues, the provisions will be emptied out in half a month and the whole tribe will have to go hungry." Ge Guang said this and looked at Fang Yuan, his gaze somewhat evasive.

Fang Yuan chuckled: "I know what you want to say, the tribe has to expend a lot to feed my wolf group."

Ge Guang promptly stood up: "Junior is ashamed, uncle Chang has shown kindness to our Ge tribe, but right now, Uncle you..."

"Hehehe, no matter. Actually, even if you had not mentioned it today, I would have done so. The wolf group's number has gone up a lot, I do not wish to trouble your tribe. So I will personally lead the wolf group to hunt for food. At the same time, while hunting, I will intentionally cut down on their numbers. The wolf meat produced can be used as rations for Ge tribesmen." Fang Yuan warmly smiled.

"Uncle Chang, I don't know what I can say to express my respect towards you!" Ge Guang was moved, his eyes reddened as he realized a friend in need is a friend indeed.

"Speaking of it, I am also to blame for your father's death. After all, I made that suggestion. I will reduce my wolf group to thirty-two thousand, I will move along with your Ge tribe, I'm sure you need this protective force as well, do you understand what I am saying?"

"I understand."

Fang Yuan patted his shoulder: "Work hard, don't let down your father's expectations. You can leave now."

"Yes, I will take my leave."

Looking at Ge Guang's receding figure, Fang Yuan sneered.

The young man was so naive and tender, if Ge tribe leader was here, he would already have tried all ways to weaken the wolf group right now.

After all, Fang Yuan already had the strength to exterminate the whole Ge tribe.

Chapter 459: Lang Ya Blessed Land

The sun slowly rose from the east, as rays shone down on the vast, limitless grassland.

Enormous iron-shelled flowers bloomed at a visible rate. A small pink rabbit jumped out of the flower.

This was a pink flower rabbit, a common animal in the grassland.

It did not dig holes, but instead lived in the stamen of the iron-shelled flowers. Iron-shelled flowers had steel-like firm petals and could defend against wolves and birds.

The pink flower rabbit hopped towards a flower. It sniffed first and after sensing there was no poison, it began to eat it.

Suddenly, the pink flower rabbit's ears twitched, an intense warning emerging in its heart.

Whoosh.

Immediately, an iron feather arrow shot through it and stabbed into the grassland.

Two investigative Gu Masters were coming over from a distance on their hump wolf.

"Brother, your iron feather arrow Gu never misses."

"Sigh, the provisions in the tribe have been decreasing. We have no choice but to hunt down wild animals and provide food for the tribesmen."

The two were talking about Ge tribe's recent situation with worried expressions.

Although Fang Yuan decreased the numbers of his wolves and the dead wolves were also made into dried meat, to Ge tribe that had so many tribesmen, it could only ease a portion of their problems regarding supplies.

As the provisions decreased further, Ge tribesmen were panicking.

The two investigative Gu Masters continued forward.

Not long later, Ge tribe's troops also moved here like an old beast.

Most of the mortals were pulling big stomach horses, while some slightly well-off households were letting curved-horn bulls pull handcarts which were packed with goods.

Gu Masters were mostly riding on hump wolves and because there was no need to battle, a lot of goods were tied around the hump wolves as well.

Besides these, there were also the lizard house Gu that were very prominent, moving forward like an elephant with their huge legs.

Fang Yuan was lying in a lizard house Gu, his eyes closed as he rested his mind while meditating.

After he had taken in large numbers of wolves, the burden on his soul had become very heavy. Every day, he needed to sleep for at least four hours, and also close his eyes to rest his spirits from time to time.

It was not easy to become an enslavement path Gu Master.

Every path had its own expertise and advantages. At the same time, there were also disadvantages and difficulties.

His body followed lizard house Gu's movement, bobbing up and down. His mind went into his aperture.

The true gold primeval sea was slightly billowing in waves, the crystal walls were bright and clear. With such degree of clearness, if he was in Hu Immortal blessed land, he could have already tried advancing to rank five.

But right now, Fang Yuan was in northern plains and his cultivation was slowed down temporarily.

He looked at his Gu worms.

His vital Gu rank six Spring Autumn Cicada was hiding its figure, hibernating at the center of the aperture.

Above the sea, a lump of dark cloud with the shape of a wolf was floating. This was the wolf smoke Gu, used specifically to heal wolves.

On the surface of the primeval sea was the rank five battle bone wheel; it still had many cracks and was drifting along with the waves.

The snow wash Gu was doing the same. It was like a snow willow leaf floating on the surface of the sea.

Hints and clues Gu that looked like a cuttlefish was swimming in the primeval sea.

At the bottom of the sea were large numbers of wolf enslavement Gu; there were many rank two, few rank three and no rank four wolf enslavement Gu.

There were also two Strength of ten Jun Gu at the bottom. Fang Yuan had bought five Strength of ten Jun Gu, he had used three and now only two remained.

A Gu with the head of a wolf and stomach of a fish was lying at the bottom of the sea, roaming around from time to time.

This was wolf swallow Gu, a rank four storage Gu.

Fang Yuan had another storage Gu as well. It looked like a cup, it was the rank five moving perspective cup Gu. Naturally, it only had rank four effectiveness in northern plains.

Besides the ones in the aperture, there was a vague second pupil in Fang Yuan's left eye; it was wolf care Gu.

In his throat was wolf howl Gu.

On the underside of his tongue was ghost fire Gu.

On his chest was an azure wolf tattoo; it was azure wolf skin Gu.

On his back was a tattoo of a pair of eagle wings; it was rank three eagle wings Gu.

He also had bone bamboo Gu and wolf soul Gu, but they were already used up.

There were two rank four wolf sprint Gu on both his feet, they were used for movement.

Of course, Immortal Gu fixed immortal travel was buried in poison grassland.

"I have inherited Chang Shan Yin's set of Gu worms. Now, I have tens of thousands of wolves, I can say that I already have achieved small success in enslavement path."

But with this level of strength, bullying the weak was possibly but there were still many glaring weaknesses when fighting against experts.

Enslavement path's Gu Master's greatest fear was 'beheading the leader' tactics. When Fang Yuan collaborated with Ge tribe earlier, they were dealing with a wolf group that did not have high intelligence. It would be much more difficult to fight against Gu Masters.

As long as the Gu Master was not stupid, they would target Fang Yuan first.

Back then, Chang Shan Yin was able to kill off Ha Tu Gu's group of bandits; besides having thousand man soul, he had several myriad wolf kings, hundreds of thousands of wolves, and even a trump card; a pack of elite wolves made up of mutated white-eye wolves.

Fang Yuan's current strength in enslavement path was not even twenty percent of the real Chang Shan Yin.

"My biggest problem now is that I have hit a bottleneck, my cultivation in all aspects have halted. Regarding my soul, I have already cultivated a wolfman soul, and to further strengthen it, the best method is to use guts Gu. Unfortunately, I am in northern plains and cannot go back to Hu Immortal blessed land. Dang Hun mountain is also dying, waiting for me to save it. Because of Immortal Gu Gruel Mud's effects, fewer guts Gu are being produced now."

Several days ago, Fang Yuan used impermanence bone Gu to completely transform his bones into impermanence bones.

Human bodies were like leather bags where soul was stowed. Impermanence bones allowed Fang Yuan to make this leather bag firmer, containing thousand man soul was no longer a problem.

"My cultivation has stagnated because of the suppression from the region. My soul has also reached a bottleneck. Regarding strength path, after using three Strength of ten Jun Gu and raising my strength by thirty jun, it had also reached my body's limit."

"Besides this, with the explosive expansion of the wolf group, the disadvantage of enslavement path has become prominent. To feed this wolf group, I have to release them every day to let them hunt by themselves or lead them to hunt, and if my luck is bad, they might have to starve. The burden is too heavy and the resource consumption is also a lot. If this task was not entrusted to Ge tribe, it would not be something I can do alone."

Fang Yuan had taken the initiative to reduce the numbers of the wolf wolf group to reduce the pressure on him.

Enslavement path Gu Masters consumed a lot of resources and were often only raised by large scale clans. Even super clans could only nurture two to three of them.

These days, Fang Yuan had been considering how to solve the problem of food.

Different from others, he had one great advantage; he controlled a blessed land.

If the wolf group could be sent to the blessed land for feeding and be taken out when he needed them, this problem would be perfectly resolved.

But Hu Immortal blessed land was in central continent and hole earth Gu's range was limited to a region. That is to say, hole earth Gu could connect to any place in central continent, but it would be useless beyond central continent.

Hole earth Gu was of no use, so Fang Yuan thought of stargate Gu.

This was a new Gu invented during the chaotic battle of the five regions in his past life.

It was a rank five expendable Gu and had stricter activation requirements than hole earth Gu. It could only be activated using the power of the stars in black heaven, and only during the night when there were many stars in the sky.

But it had a huge range that could traverse the five regions.

Fang Yuan had the recipe for stargate Gu, but the materials required were rare; it needed many ancient Gu worms and one or two supplementary materials were even from the immemorial era.

Moreover, the refinement success rate of stargate Gu was extremely low, there might not even be one success out of a hundred refinement attempts.

A reason as to why Fang Yuan did not try to exchange for the materials to make stargate Gu in his transaction with Immortal Crane Sect was this.

Another important reason was blue charm lightning shadow.

After Fang Yuan expelled the blue charm lightning shadow from the blessed land, it had been hovering around Tian Ti mountain, not having the slightest intent to give up entering Hu Immortal blessed land.

Immortal Crane Sect also did not take care of this problem, the Gu Immortals on Tian Ti mountain also only cared about their own problems and did not bother about other people's misfortune.

How was the use of stargate Gu and blue charm lightning shadow related?

As mentioned earlier, stargate Gu needed time to absorb the power of the stars in black heaven to form. But Hu Immortal blessed land was a world of its own and had neither a sun nor stars.

If Fang Yuan wanted to absorb the power of the stars, he would have to open the entrance and let the starlight from the outside world enter.

But if he did this, blue charm lightning shadow would use the chance to break in.

The trade-off was absolutely unacceptable.

Dang Hun mountain was dying, its might had greatly reduced; if blue charm lightning shadow entered the blessed land, it would make the current situation many times worse.

Thus, stargate Gu could not be used.

"It seems I can only look at Lang Ya blessed land to see if there is a way to resolve this. According to this speed, we will reach crescent lake in about seven days."

Fang Yuan sighed, placing his hopes on Lang Ya blessed land.

　　...

In the dark night with sparse stars, the moon shone brightly and cold wind blew.

On the grassland, there was a crescent moon shaped lake that was fifteen thousand li long and five thousand li wide. The two ends of the lakes were bent and pointed while the middle part was wide like a crescent moon. The lake was tranquil and gave off a crystal-like sparkle. The crescent moon in the sky and the crescent lake gave off their respective light.

It was crescent lake.

The aquatic plants were plentiful here, the surrounding was tranquil, and many kinds of living beings lived here.

There were three-horned rhinos, water wolves, dragon-fish, iron-shelled flowers, steep cliff grass and so on. Horseshoe trees surrounded this lake, forming a sparse woodland.

Lumps of pitch black dark clouds surged over from far away, bringing a chilling and evil aura.

The dark clouds blocked the moonlight and casted a dense shadow. The shadow was like an evil beast, crossing across the crescent lake's surface and stopping at its center.

"It is here." Several people stood on the cloud, and one of them was cackling.

He was ugly, his forehead was bulging out, his eye sockets were deep, his eyes were closed, and his ears were big and conspicuous. Having disheveled hair and wearing a black robe, he was giving off a thick evil aura.

It was none other than the rank six Gu Immortal — Gui Wang.

"Lang Ya blessed land is hidden here?" Loner Hong Yu casually asked from the side.

He was also a rank six Gu Immortal; with the appearance of a youth, round face and fair appearance.

"I personally investigated this, there can be no mistake. Calculating the time, it will soon be the time for Lang Ya blessed land to face its earthly calamity. Kekekek, we will observe the changes first and make our move together when the time comes." Gui Wang's tone was filled with confidence.

Chapter 460: Number One Refinement Path Immortal of All Times

Time passed bit by bit. The several figures on the dark clouds waited quietly.

Other than Gui Wang and Loner Hong Yu, there were also three female immortals.

Each of these three immortals were beautiful and charming; they were the Hua Hai three immortals.

The cold looking blue robed immortal was Fairy Qing Suo. The petite and fair girl wearing a yellow garment was Fairy Huang Sha. The coquettish girl wearing a pink skirt was Fairy Fen Meng.

The three stood together at some distance away from Gui Wang and Loner Hong Yu; like they were on different sides.

Fairy Qing Suo looked at crescent lake while Fairy Huang Sha and Fairy Fen Meng were conversing softly, glancing at Gui Wang and Loner Hong Yu from time to time with vigilant gazes.

Not mentioning Gui Wang's ugly appearance that caused the three beauties to feel revulsion, Loner Hong Yu killed his own parents to refine a Gu, and betrayed his brothers, it caused the three female immortals of the righteous path to feel contempt.

But Lang Ya blessed land was an extremely important matter, the Gu Immortal that had resided here before was the famous 'number one refinement path immortal'— Long Hair Ancestor.

This person had rank eight cultivation and was extremely proficient in refinement path, having great talent in refinement path that was rare even during immemorial times.

He had lived a long life, he lived during the era of two venerables; Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

What did this mean? This meant that these two rank nine Gu Immortals did not live as long as him.

His refinement path talent even made Thieving Heaven and Giant Sun, two venerables, sigh in admiration countless times, and concede to him. They had both requested Long Hair Ancestor to refine Gu for them.

In the statistics made by later generations, Long Hair Ancestor had refined at least thirty-eight Immortal Gu in his life; this was only the conclusive summary, it did not account for his many legends and rumors.

However, such a person also could not fight against the flow of the river of time and finally died of old age.

According to the rumors, he became a land spirit after death and was still refining Gu incessantly in Lang Ya blessed land.

Lang Ya blessed land was Long Hair Ancestor's residence, thus it contained large amounts of Gu worm recipes, including recipes for Immortal Gu!

Hua Hai three immortals might not like Gui Wang and Loner Hong Yu, but the allure of Immortal Gu recipes were enough to let them set aside their righteous path identity and collaborate with these two demonic path Gu Immortals.

Time slowly passed.

Crack.

Suddenly a soft sound echoed, the space on top of crescent lake cracked open and revealed a shining flash of lightning.

"The earthly calamity has begun!" Gui Wang shouted excitedly.

For a while, above the center of crescent lake, lightning rumbled unceasingly.

This was no doubt the descent of the earthly calamity, having created a hole in the blessed land.

Loner Hong Yu's gaze shone as he stared at this scene without blinking.

Hua Hai three immortals glanced at each other and saw the excitement in each other's eyes; their breathing also became faster.

Immortal Gu were difficult to find, none of these five Gu Immortals possessed a single Immortal Gu. Of course, they had rank five Gu, and in large amounts at that, with all of them being top quality Gu.

But no matter how many mortal Gu they had, it could not match a single Immortal Gu.

Gu Immortals' thirst for Immortal Gu were much greater than a lecherous person seeing an absolute beauty.

Rumble...

Thunder rumbled in the air above the lake with lightning smashing down continually, resembling a thunderstorm pouring from above.

The second hole, third hole... the earthly calamity created hole after holes.

"This is the earthly calamity — 'Endless Thunder and Lightning Rain', such terrifying might." Loner Hong Yu expressed shock at this sight.

"If this occurred in our Hua Hai blessed land, even if we three sisters join forces, we might not be able to resist it. Lang Ya blessed land is indeed worthy of being Long Hair Ancestor's residence, can we really snatch the Immortal Gu recipe this time?" Hua Hai three immortals looked at each other, their faces were pale.

Previously, Gui Wang had given them many benefits and thus Hua Hai three immortals came rushing over. Now, the three felt this task would not be easy and forcing their way into Lang Ya blessed land would not be a simple matter.

Gu Immortals were the elites of the human race with wisdom that far surpassed the norm.

Be it the Hua Hai three immortals or Loner Hong Yu, they were all cautious and vigilant.

Gui Wang observed everyone's expressions and coarsely laughed: "This dogshit world has always been trying to maintain balance! Blessed land has fortune, so the world sends down calamities and tribulations, doing all that it can to wear down this fortune. The better the blessed land is managed, the stronger the calamities and tribulations they will face. Look at the might of this 'endless thunder and lightning rain', isn't it comparable to those blessed lands that have forbidden grounds? Everyone, just think of it, how many recipes are stored in this Lang Ya blessed land? There are definitely many Immortal Gu recipes, otherwise why would this shitty heaven send down such a powerful earthly calamity?"

These words moved the immortals' heart.

Desire and vigor appeared in these people's gaze when they thought of the Immortal Gu.

"Gui Wang is right. I have also entered some blessed lands before, and those ownerless blessed lands that were on the verge of collapse had earthly calamities that were as weak as a drizzle. But the blessed land is extremely important, which Gu Immortal would not want it to develop well?" Loner Hong Yu laughed bitterly: "The more developed the blessed land, the stronger the calamities and tribulations, it is not easy to be a Gu Immortal..."

"Kekekekek... cultivation means going against heaven, this shitty heaven wants to weaken us and suppress us, so we have to go against it and progress." Gui Wang added.

"Both of you are rather extreme. Cultivation is actually following the mandate of heaven. We use Gu worms to study the great Dao and law of the world. We manage the blessed land in order to bring blessings and nurture fortune in place of heaven and earth, for all living things to prosper." Immortal Qing Suo retorted with a clear and pleasant voice.

Loner Hong Yu did not reply, he did not want to argue about this topic, considering the situation.

This was the difference in ideals between demonic path and righteous path. Since immemorial times, the difference in perspective had been debated with no conclusion to which is closer to the truth.

Gui Wang laughed and pointed to the hole below: "The earthly calamity has become even more dangerous. To prevent the land spirit from cutting off these holes, we should strike now."

"Alright." Loner Hong Yu expressed his support.

"Please make a move first, Gui Wang." The three immortal fairies reached a consensus.

Gui Wang snickered and took out a green grape immortal essence bead, he then activated a Gu worm that flew towards the hole while holding the immortal essence bead.

This Gu worm entered the blessed land, but it was either suppressed or destroyed by the earthly calamity, as Gui Wang instantly lost his connection with it.

However, Gui Wang's green grape immortal essence also entered Lang Ya blessed land and immediately exploded, causing the immortal essence in Lang Ya blessed land to be expended.

To Gu Immortals, every bead of immortal essence was very precious. Normally, the Gu Immortals would always try to accumulate them and would not use them lightly unless absolutely necessary.

Seeing Gui Wang act as the example, the other four successively sent out an immortal essence bead.

Gui Wang sent his second immortal essence bead, and the others also sent their second immortal essence bead.

After Gu Immortals die, they would form into the land spirit, but will no longer produce immortal essence. The immortal essence left for the land spirit, would decrease the more it was used, while Gui Wang and the group were four people and occupied the advantage in numbers.

But even after a hundred rounds, this Lang Ya blessed land still had immortal essence to use.

Besides Gui Wang, the other immortals showed signs of hesitation.

"That Long Hair Ancestor was a rank eight Gu Immortal, although he died, the immortal essence he left were white litchi immortal essence. One hundred green grape immortal essence beads cannot compare to one white litchi immortal essence." When it was Fairy Fen Meng's turn, she held a green grape immortal essence bead but did not immediately make a move.

Gui Wang's eyes flickered with a dark light and sneered: "What are you afraid of? Long Hair Ancestor is a person from Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's times, and did everything to prolong his life till he was struggling at death's door during Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's times, and finally died of old age. Although he left behind white litchi immortal essence, but the blessed land has already endured through the eras of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable and Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable. The former Lang Ya grotto-heaven had already fell and became a blessed land. Now, how much white litchi immortal essence would there be left? Probably only some diluted immortal essence paste."

Loner Hong Yu chuckled: "Gui Wang makes sense. You guys also saw the earthly calamity just before. Lang Ya blessed land holds so many recipes, even including many Immortal Gu recipes, this good fortune is too big and thus the earthly calamity is so strong. Even if it has more white litchi immortal essence left, they would also be quickly exhausted."

"In this world, the daring are rewarded and the cowards starve! Throw in more immortal essence, having invested so much already, do we give up at this point? We might not be that far from succeeding." Gui Wang enticed.

The three female immortals glanced at each other, Fairy Qing Suo spoke: "You are correct, but our immortal essence was saved by us bit by bit, and did not appear out of nowhere. Let's do this, we will throw in fifty more beads and see what happens."

Like this, after sending immortal essence beads for fifty more rounds, Lang Ya blessed land started to show its inability to keep up.

Gui Wang laughed heartily as he cackled.

The three female immortals used to feel that Gui Wang's laughter was coarse and ear-piercing, but now they felt happiness from hearing it. They could almost see the Immortal Gu recipes beckoning them.

Thirty more rounds later, the four immortals' immortal essence entered the blessed land and inflated, mutually affecting each other and creating a chain explosion, but the blessed land had no activity.

This meant the blessed land's immortal essence was used up!

"Everyone, I shall move first!" Gui Wang suddenly laughed, and flapped his blue-black bat wings towards the hole, and was the first one to enter Lang Ya blessed land.

"Not good!" Loner Hong Yu shouted, and fearing he would fall behind, he turned into a red light and shot ahead.

"These demonic path Gu Masters are indeed treacherous and crafty!"

Hua Hai three immortals twitched their nose with anger and quickly followed behind.

The three immortals entered the blessed land and felt their rank five Gu could be casually activated.

"Lang Ya blessed land's immortal essence has definitely been emptied!" Fairy Huang Sha said with excitement.

The three immortals charged past the endless thunder and lightning rain and arrived at the depths of the blessed land.

However, what they saw was a scene of white clouds covering the whole area.

In the sea of clouds, there were twelve buildings, each decorated grandly and was majestic, having the beauty of a thousand years of history. Around the buildings; immortal cranes flew, feathermen hovered in the air, colorful clouds moved around and the fragrance of sandalwood pervaded the air.

"This is cloud soil, one can step on it like real land and its soil is very fertile, far surpassing the mortal world's soil." Fairy Qing Suo stepped with her beautiful feet and spoke excitedly.

"A scene worthy of the Old Ancestor Immortal!" Fairy Fen Meng exclaimed in admiration.

"Legend has it that within the twelve cloud buildings, there are countless recipes stored! To think I can see them personally today." Fairy Huang Sha felt really fortunate.

"Hahaha, everything is mine!" Far away, Gui Wang's ear-piercing voice spread to them, he was flying into a building on the sea of clouds.

As for Loner Hong Yu, he had already approached a nearby cloud building.

Hua Hai three immortals frowned and after looking at each other, they flew separately towards three cloud buildings.

Chapter 461: Prophecy of Three Venerables

Several days later.

Carts rumbled and horses neighed.

Ge tribesmen arrived at crescent lake and set up camp around the sparse horseshoe trees.

Ge Guang and the Ge tribe's higher-ups could finally heave a sigh of relief.

Aquatic plants were plentiful here along with large numbers of beast groups. They could hold a hunting festival and store provisions for their later journey.

"We finally arrived." Fang Yuan was overwhelmed in his heart.

At night, he used the excuse of leading the wolf group to hunt to leave Ge tribe's sight.

It was a moonless night, but there were many stars.

The wolf group sprinted against the flow of the night wind as they discovered several small-mid sized beast groups, devouring them one by one.

The wolf group excitedly howled, they had been in a half-starving state these days and now they could eat to their fill.

Even if he had a group of thirty thousand wolves, Fang Yuan still carefully maneuvered the wolf group's movement. The wolf group might be of a large scale, but crescent lake had many dangers, there was an even larger group of water wolves, a three-horned rhino group and a group of a thousand mutated beasts, and finally, a worm group that had hundreds of thousands and even up to a million insects.

Of course these worm groups and beast groups had their own territory and would not move around everywhere like those on the grassland.

There was plenty of aquatic plants beside crescent lake; they did not need to move around to search for food.

As long as Fang Yuan and Ge tribe did not invade their territory, the beasts and worms would not find any issues with them.

According to his previous life's memories, Fang Yuan moved along the lakeside towards the east and arrived at a stone forest.

This stone forest was very common; there were stone pillars which were grey, purplish black, greenish-yellow and so on, quietly standing straight with a precise distance between them.

There were many stone forests beside crescent lake, but this particular forest was rather special. If someone looked from high above, they would only see grey-white stone pillars and would discover that the stone pillars vaguely formed into a 'thief'[1] character.

This stone forest had a really impressive origin; it was personally created by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable.

Back then, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable requested Long Hair Ancestor to refine a Gu for him. Thus, he made a bet with him, he won three rounds out of five; the Long Hair Ancestor had no choice but to accept his loss and agreed to refine the Gu.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable wanted to enter the legendary space door all his life, and requested Long Hair Ancestor to refine the Immortal Gu — Space Escape Gu, an Immortal Gu that could allow a Gu Master to enter the space door.

He placed all his effort in researching the recipe for it. Long Hair Ancestor was very excited and felt that the recipe was good and proper, but there were some places that could be improved.

After discussing with Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, the Demon Venerable became very happy and exclaimed that Long Hair Ancestor's refinement path attainment far surpassed his.

The two immortals cooperated and spent twenty-one years to successfully refine 'Space Escape Gu'.

However, although this Gu was refined and Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable could activate it, it was not able to enter the Space Door no matter what he did.

The Demon Venerable felt discouraged and the proud Long Hair Ancestor also suffered a huge setback.

Later, Long Hair Ancestor researched with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable but did not make any progress. The space escape Gu became the only failure in Long Hair Ancestor's life.

It was said that even at his deathbed, Long Hair Ancestor could not forget this. His good friend Immortal Yi Yan could not endure seeing his old friend pass away like this and expended fifty years of his life to deduce the future.

He predicted that many years later, after three great eras, three venerables would appear, two men and one woman. The first was Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, second was Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable and third was Great Dream Immortal Venerable. As for the problem regarding the space escape Gu, it would be solved by Great Dream Immortal Venerable.

Immortal Yi Yan was a rank eight wisdom path Gu Immortal and was proficient in making predictions, he often made accurate one sentence predictions, and was thus known as Immortal Yi Yan[2]. And this deduced prophecy would later be known as the famous 'Prophecy of Three Venerables'.

Sure enough, the world went through countless changes and continuously moved forward, after Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable appeared. After the Demon Venerable died, a rank nine male Gu Immortal appeared in righteous path and was, as predicted, known as Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable.

Now Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable was already dead, 'Prophecy of Three Venerables' was mostly complete, only Great Dream Immortal Venerable who has yet to be born remains.

Speaking of it, Long Hair Ancestor was both happy and sad at this prophecy.

Happy because the problem of space escape Gu could finally be resolved. Sad because he would not be able to see that day.

Long Hair Ancestor died and turned into a land spirit with only one obsession - to see Great Dream Immortal Venerable. As long as she solved the problem of space escape Gu, the whole Lang Ya blessed land would belong to her.

"Back then, when Long Hair Ancestor refined the space escape Gu for Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, the result was a failure but they could not find the problem with it. Being greatly embarrassed, he promised to refine nine more Gu worms for Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable and he would even provide all the materials required to refine the Gu. Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable later requested Long Hair Ancestor to refine six Immortal Gu. Before Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable mysteriously disappeared, he set up his inheritances in the five regions and made an agreement with Long Hair Ancestor that the remaining three chances for Gu refinement will be left for his inheritor. Long Hair Ancestor agreed and the two made a secret code."

"After more than a decade from now, one of the Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritances would suddenly activate and be known by everyone. The content of the inheritance is a riddle and the riddle points towards Lang Ya blessed land. From then on, a craze of solving riddles in northern plains with countless people trying to solve it started. The rumors spread endlessly, but no one succeeded."

"Later, Ma Hong Yun was forced to flee after being defeated on the battlefield and came running to crescent lake. At the lakeside, he encountered a premeditated ambush. Panicked and left with no choice, he ran over to this stone forest and accidentally discovered a passage in the stone forest. Going through this secret passage, he entered Lang Ya blessed land and met the land spirit. After getting the secret code right, Lang Ya land spirit refined three Gu worms for him as per the agreement."

"Ma Hong Yun obtained these three rank five Gu and after recovering from his injuries, he returned to the stone forest and turned the tide with great might; starting all over again and finally, he obtained the throne of the imperial court for the second time."

Fang Yuan recalled while slowly moving forward.

Then, his eyes brightened and he stopped before a purple stone pillar.

This stone pillar was also common, but a stone that was flat like a stool was near the bottom of the pillar.

During that time, after Ma Hong Yun was defeated, he was chased by the enemy troops and was already on the verge of death. He fled to this place and had nowhere to run with his injuries reaching a critical state.

He sat on this stone stool and gazed up at the sky while leaning on the stone pillar.

Suddenly, he felt that this stone pillar looked like his dear wife.

His consciousness was on the verge of collapsing, he used his blood-stained hand to gently caress the stone pillar and said with deep love: "Lian Yun, oh Lian Yun... I really regret not listening to your advice. I want to see you, I want to tell you personally: I love you, I was wrong..."

At this time, the enemies had already arrived and were raising their sabres high.

But at the next moment!

Ma Hong Yun suddenly disappeared; he had entered Lang Ya blessed land.

Fang Yuan sat at this stone stool, leaning on the pillar and gazing up.

But he could not see a woman's appearance anywhere on the stone pillar.

Fang Yuan laughed uncontrollably: "It seems this Ma Hong Yun was just thinking of his wife when he stared at the stone pillar. His longing was so deep that he could see Zhao Lian Yun on anything."

This Zhao Lian Yun was also a weird woman, in the future she became a wisdom path Gu Immortal and was a good wife to Ma Hong Yun, helping him strategise. But currently, she was only a little girl.

Fang Yuan took out a dagger and cut his flesh, letting the fresh blood smear this purple stone pillar.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had put a mysterious Gu worm on this purple stone pillar. Blood was only the first criteria for its activation, there was still the second criteria, that was to say 'I want'.

When Fang Yuan said these two words, his body instantly disappeared and his vision suddenly changed.

When he regained his senses, he was in a room.

In the room, the smell of an alchemy furnace wafted in the air. There were dragon pillars, golden curtains, crane lanterns and vermillion windows.

A sagely old man was sitting cross legged on a bed of cloud, his eyes closed as if he was meditating.

He was thin with white hair, having a beard that reached his chest and a ruddy face like that of a baby's. He was wearing a wide robe and the two sleeves were fluttering in the air.

"Demon Venerable's inheritor Chang Shan Yin has come to pay respects." Fang Yuan touched his chest with his right hand and slightly bowed.

"You are Chang Shan Yin?" The old man slightly opened his eyes, his eyes flashed with bright light as he looked at Fang Yuan with a gaze that seemed to materialized, "This outer skin of yours is quite interesting. Hm... you used human skin along with shame plum, autumn voice grass. Hmm, there is also pill fire Gu, medicine strength Gu, and some..."

The land spirit frowned deeply and caressed his beard, a hesitant expression on his face.

He could actually see through Fang Yuan's disguise and even roughly deduce human skin Gu's recipe by just observing.

"Lad, do you want to exchange this Gu worm's recipe? I will use a similar grade Gu worm to exchange for it. Or you can choose a similar grade Gu worm recipe. Ah, right! Secret code, the secret code!" After speaking for a while, the land spirit suddenly remembered the secret code and smacked his head.

Fang Yuan shrugged his shoulders: "The secret code that you created with the Demon Venerable back then? Ha, there is no secret code. As for the human skin Gu recipe, I cannot exchange it yet."

"You don't want to exchange? Why!" The land spirit was furious, a heavy pressure pressed down on Fang Yuan; he could not budge, his whole skeleton emitted creaking noises under the suppression.

But he sneered with no concern: "I have my reasons for not doing the exchange. You do not need to know about it!"

The land spirit laughed sinisterly: "Hehe, you don't want to exchange, then I shall imprison you here and peel off your skin. After studying it few times, I can reverse engineer the recipe of this human skin Gu."

"No, you can't make a move on me." Fang Yuan was confident, "I am Demon Venerable's inheritor, you can't do anything to me before the agreement of the three Gu is completed."

According to Earth's understanding, the land spirit was equivalent to an artificial intelligence.

Except that, this land spirit birthed from Long Hair Ancestor had quite a high intelligence and was good at scaring others. In his past life, Ma Hong Yun had been scared by the land spirit and lost the precious opportunity to refine Immortal Gu, refining only three rank five Gu. After that incident, Ma Hong Yun regretted it endlessly. After becoming a Gu Immortal, whenever he thought of this matter, he would wring his hands and sigh.

"You!" The land spirit blew its beard and opened its eyes which seemed to puff out fire; a posture that seemed ready to kill.

But Fang Yuan remained unmoved.

The land spirit kept on staring for a long while before suddenly turning exhausted like a ball that was leaking air.

He then scowled miserably and got off the bed of clouds, walking towards Fang Yuan and softly pleaded while pulling his sleeves: "Young lad, please do a good deed and exchange this recipe with me, please?!"

Fang Yuan was speechless!

This... what was this situation? His attitude change was way too fast!

[1] Chinese character of course. Back

[2] Literally means "Immortal One Sentence". Back

Chapter 462: Exchanging Gu

"Young lad, please have some tea. This is a high-grade cloud smoke tea, have a taste of it." Lang Ya land spirit sat at the edge of the bed as he brewed a cup of tea for Fang Yuan personally.

Fang Yuan sat at the spot the land spirit was sitting at previously, looking at this 'peculiar' land spirit wordlessly.

In the conversation earlier, Fang Yuan had talked to this land spirit, and understood — this land spirit liked collecting recipes, it will try its best to get its hands on any new recipes it discovers.

If it were any other person, the land spirit would've extorted and threatened him already. But Fang Yuan was a Demon Venerable's inheritor, he did not dare to do so, thus he could only beg nicely.

"Handsome young lad, is the tea not nice? Are you happy? For the sake of this tea, exchange that human skin recipe with me please." Lang Ya land spirit showed a smiling expression as he tried to please Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan drank his tea silently.

The mysterious, strong, and sagely image of Lang Ya land spirit collapsed rapidly.

"Young lad, do me a favor, pity this old man! I live alone here, I am so lonely, so bored, so thirsty. I can only look at these recipes daily to pass time. Are you so cruel, to reject the request of such a pitiful old man like me?" The land spirit had a grandpa appearance, having white beard, white hair, and white eyebrows, staring at Fang Yuan pitifully.

"Hey, have some self awareness, you are a land spirit, not a human." Fang Yuan's eyes were twitching.

"Young lad, whatever you say, as long as you will give the recipe to me, you can do anything to me!" The 'grandpa' winked at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan controlled his urge to kick this creep, as he shouted: "No means no."

"Lang Ya land spirit's body shuddered, as it started crying, rolling on the ground: "No, I want to exchange. I want the recipe, I want the recipe, young lad, you are too cruel, too ruthless, you lack compassion. Why are you not exchanging the recipe with me, will it kill you? Please just exchange it."

"Seriously, rumors cannot compare to meeting in real life..." Fang Yuan's head was full of black lines as the image of Lang Ya land spirit that he had broke into pieces, and was stepped into tiny shards on the ground.

However, this showed Lang Ya land spirit's innocence and sincerity.

The land spirit grandpa rolled on the ground and cried for a long time, but Fang Yuan did not relent.

He had no choice but to stand up, with tears all over his face, even his beard, hair, and eyebrows were wet.

"Young lad, what's wrong with your conscience? You are simply too cruel, as expected of the inheritor of a Demon Venerable..." The grandpa complained as he looked at Fang Yuan, like a wife who had just been cheated on.

Fang Yuan could not stand this gaze, he shuddered as he sighed: "Nevermind, nevermind, I can give you the human skin Gu's recipe. But you have to wait until the time is right."

"Young lad, you are awesome, you are the kindest person ever. So when will the time be right?" Land spirit was extremely overjoyed.

"Hehehe, five hundred years later."

Land spirit grandpa frowned, and immediately slumped: "That's so long away..."

"Hmph, this is the best I am willing to offer, why, you don't want to exchange anymore?"

"Of course I want to exchange. It's just five hundred years, I can wait. Young lad, I will be waiting for you, this is our agreement for a lifetime." The old grandpa said affectionately.

Fang Yuan held his face, sighing deeply: "I have a recipe here, I want to exchange it for connecting heaven Gu."

Once he heard Fang Yuan's request, Lang Ya land spirit's expression changed, he stood up right and raised his head slightly, showing an arrogant expression: "Oh, you want to get connecting heaven Gu..."

He spoke slowly and casually: "To tell you the truth young lad, I have an uncountable number of recipes here. If the recipe you produce is already owned by me, I will not take it."

Fang Yuan laughed confidently: "Old man, your era is long over. Bring me a brush and paper, I will write a portion of it for you."

Just after he wrote half of the content, Fang Yuan stopped.

"Write, write it, what else is there?" Land spirit stood at the side, scratching his ears as his eyes shone. He had already confirmed that this was a new recipe, he had never seen it before.

"This is a rank five recipe, where is your connecting heaven Gu?"

"Here, here." Land spirit waved his hand and a connecting heaven Gu appeared on the table.

Fang Yuan finished writing this recipe and refined the connecting heaven Gu, keeping it in his aperture.

At the side, land spirit looked at this recipe gleefully.

The Gu worm in the recipe was a new Gu discovered by Gu Masters five hundred years later. During the chaotic five region battle, it was an era of innovation, of all sorts of new Gu were developed and created.

Every time such a chaotic era appeared, a rank nine Gu Immortal would be born.

Fang Yuan had his previous life's memories, although he forgot a lot of things, he still had a great number of recipes inside his head.

These recipes, to exaggerate, were ahead of the current times by an era! Of course the land spirit had never heard of them.

"Do you have divine sense Gu?" Fang Yuan kept connecting heaven Gu and asked.

"Yes."

"Exchange?"

"You still have recipes?" Land spirit grandpa was shocked and overjoyed.

Fang Yuan smiled as he took the brush and paper, writing once again.

But this time, halfway through, the land spirit laughed: "Young man, I have the recipe of this Gu worm already."

"Oh?" Fang Yuan stopped writing, his expression was stunned.

He did not think that the land spirit was lying. Land spirits were pure, yes means yes, and no means no.

"If you don't believe me, you can look at this." Lang Ya land spirit grabbed the air, and a cowhide recipe appeared, landing on the table.

Fang Yuan took a look, it was the real deal.

"It seems that the Gu worms in my memories, although they only appeared five hundred years later, might not be new Gu after all."

Thinking so, Fang Yuan laughed, saying to the land spirit: "No worries, if this is no use, I have another recipe."

But this time, Fang Yuan only wrote a third of it before the land spirit clapped: "Although I do not have this recipe, I have something very similar, look at this."

Saying so, he handed Fang Yuan a recipe, it was 90% similar to his.

Fang Yuan immediately understood: "My recipe might have been improved on by a Gu Master using an ancient recipe."

"Young lad, this recipe does not have much value, I will not exchange for it." Land spirit said.

Fang Yuan revised his plans.

When Long Hair Ancestor was alive, he loved to collect and research on recipes. He was known as the number one immortal of the refinement path of all times. He lived for a long period of time, and collected a vast number of recipes, he could be said to have been an extremely successful collector.

As for Fang Yuan's generation of the new age, they had not reached the apex of the time period, at least Great Dream Immortal Venerable had not appeared yet. The Gu worm recipes in Fang Yuan's memories, compared to Lang Ya blessed land's accumulation from many eras, seemed to be extremely insignificant.

"Look at these then." Fang Yuan started scribbling again.

But for these recipes, either Lang Ya blessed land had it or it was a modified ancient recipe, the land spirit had no intentions to get them.

Fang Yuan was helpless.

In his memories, there were some Gu worms that were definitely new, but they had a great importance in the future, each represented a great benefit to him, and could easily change the situation of the regions. Once they get exposed by Lang Ya blessed land, his losses were small issues, but it might potentially alter history, the disadvantages were too great for Fang Yuan compared to the gains.

"Land spirit, look at this recipe." Fang Yuan thought, and wrote the stargate Gu's recipe.

Land spirit took a look and was interested. The more Fang Yuan wrote, the more its interest grew.

"I've never seen these recipes before, they are rather peculiar, very peculiar." The old grandpa muttered as he rubbed his chin.

This was a rank five Gu recipe, Fang Yuan successfully obtained the divine sense Gu from it.

"Young lad, this stargate Gu is interesting, it has the effect to cross the five regions. The five regions have their respective barriers at the boundaries, but this can actually make use of the power of black heaven. This type of Gu worm, usually only hole earth Gu and connecting heaven Gu are popular classics. But this stargate Gu can compete with the two of them, and is not inferior in any way! Did you create this Gu's recipe?" Land spirit asked.

"Of course!" Fang Yuan admitted it without hesitation.

He had zero guilt in impersonating and taking this glory for himself.

Next, he started to brag shamelessly: "The few recipes earlier were also devised by me, although I also used some current recipes as the base for my research."

This act undoubtedly deepened his relationship with Lang Ya land spirit.

"Little friend, you have talent for refinement path, I am truly amazed!" Land spirit grandpa stopped calling Fang Yuan young lad, but started calling him little friend.

"But this stargate Gu has its weaknesses. You need to gather starlight at night to activate it. Other than that, this Gu's refinement success rate is low, but if we add a few supplementary materials into it, we can raise the success rate by 30%."

Next, the land spirit listed a few materials.

Fang Yuan frowned as he listened, he had never heard of these materials.

It seems that they were either materials from the immemorial era, or just simply too rare and unique, with little use normally.

Land spirit continued: "It seems this stargate Gu is best paired with the starlight fireflies. With the starlight fireflies, you will have starlight, and the stargate Gu can be used regardless of time or location."

"What?" Fang Yuan heard this and his heart pounded, asking quickly: "Starlight fireflies, what are starlight fireflies?"

"You don't know about starlight fireflies? That's true, they were already extremely rare during the immemorial era, and were extinct during the olden era. When the immemorial nine heavens were still around, most of the starlight fireflies lived in orange heaven." Land spirit exposed another ancient secret.

Fang Yuan was disappointed: "Since it is extinct, there's no need to mention it."

"The so-called extinct is merely in the mortal realm, recently, I saw a swarm of starlight firelight when making a transaction in treasure yellow heaven, I think it belongs to Star Lord Wan Xiang." Land spirit recalled.

"Really?" Fang Yuan's eyes were shining.

The reason he exchanged for connecting heaven Gu and divine sense Gu were so that he could impersonate a Gu Immortal and make transactions in treasure yellow heaven, to obtain resources and stop his reliance on Immortal Crane Sect.

Land spirit's words greatly increased his interest in the starlight fireflies.

Fang Yuan's eyes rolled, laughing craftily: "Land spirit, I still have many recipes here, but I only want starlight fireflies!"

Land spirit shook its head: "I can't exchange that."

"Why?"

"I do not have starlight firefly Gu." Land spirit said as a matter of fact.

Fang Yuan said snappily: "If you do not have starlight firefly Gu, can't you use connecting heaven Gu to buy it in treasure yellow heaven?"

The land spirit looked at Fang Yuan with a weird expression: "Why do I have to buy starlight firefly Gu?"

"If you do not buy starlight firefly Gu, how are you going to exchange for my recipe?"

Land spirit shook its head, adamantly saying: "Your recipe can only exchange for Gu worms I currently have in the blessed land."

Fang Yuan was speechless, the land spirit was rigid, it could not make such compromises, after all, it was not human, as a land spirit, it could not make flexible decisions.

In the end, after Fang Yuan talked until his lips were about to tear, no progress was made.

The land spirit only followed the rules.

Fang Yuan could only stop his attempt, but suddenly he had a thought: "Wait, you said you will only exchange for Gu that are currently in your blessed land?"

"Yes."

Fang Yuan licked his dry lips: "Then I'll use my Immortal Gu recipe to exchange for your Heavenly Treasure Essence Imperial Lotus, is that okay?"

Chapter 463: Fang Yuan’s awkwardness

Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus was a rank six Immortal Gu, but it was not a natural Gu, instead was invented by Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable.

Rank three Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, rank four Heavenly Essence Treasure Monarch Lotus and rank five Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus could produce primeval essence, giving an enormous help in a Gu Master's primeval essence recovery.

Rank six and above Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, however, produced immortal essence and had extremely huge use.

Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable relied on this Gu to become the person with the most abundant immortal essence among rank nine Gu Immortals in all history.

After Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable died, his Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus was protected with layers of layers of security, becoming a famous treasure in the world. However, after more than a hundred thousand years, an extremely daring rank seven Gu Immortal stole it.

This rank seven Gu Immortal was the venerable after Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, the one who became the heavenly thief, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable.

After Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable died, this Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus was also destroyed.

Long Hair Ancestor had many interactions with Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable and after the Demon Venerable went missing for hundreds of years, Long Hair Ancestor tried to refine the Gu. Finally, he succeeded in refining a rank six Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus.

Later, he developed a preference for it and advanced it to rank eight stage.

Immortal Gu were one of a kind and their names also remained the same. After they advance to stages beyond rank six , their names would not change.

For example — Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus and Spring Autumn Cicada; when they advanced from rank six to rank seven, they would still be called Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus and Spring Autumn Cicada.

After Long Hair Ancestor died, his obsession merged with the heavenly power to form a land spirit. This rank eight Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus also remained in Lang Ya blessed land.

"Lang Ya blessed land would later be accidentally discovered by a soul path Gu Immortal called Gui Wang, leading the first wave of attacks. The result was that they were captured by the land spirit. However, the news regarding Lang Ya blessed land was leaked by Gui Wang and attracted more Gu Immortals. Later, a second wave of attacks came, and later, the third wave and so on. During the seventh wave, the heavenly court dispatched several rank seven Gu Immortals who brought Immortal Gu to the mortal realm."

"After a tragic battle, Lang Ya blessed land finally collapsed while the Gu Immortals also suffered disastrous losses. Feng Jiu Ge died in this battle. However, Lang Ya blessed land's great number of recipes were taken by the heavenly court. Central continent's strength thus rose sharply and with just their strength, they attacked the four great regions."

With his previous life's memories, Fang Yuan was clear of the future development.

At this moment, when Fang Yuan suddenly mentioned the use of Immortal Gu recipe to exchange for Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus, the land spirit refused without hesitation: "This is not possible! Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus can produce immortal essence, it is the reason why I can defend against the calamities and tribulations. At the same time, I need to use these immortal essence to refine Gu. Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus is non-exchangeable."

"Is that so." Fang Yuan nodded with some disappointment since he had some expectations.

However, the land spirit's next sentence ignited his hope again.

"However, I have other Immortal Gu here. What recipe do you have? Rank seven recipe can only be exchanged for rank six Immortal Gu. Rank eight recipe can be exchanged for rank seven or rank six Immortal Gu."

Fang Yuan's eyes let out a bright light.

He knew Lang Ya blessed land had a rank seven beast enslavement Gu.

This Immortal Gu could subdue any wild beast in the world; including mutated beasts, myriad beast emperor, even desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts!

Long Hair Ancestor used this Gu to subdue many desolate beasts, including several ancient desolate beasts whom he buried under the twelve cloud buildings.

With these desolate beasts' protection, the whole Lang Ya blessed land became a fortified castle and was able to resist till the sixth wave of Gu Immortals' crazed attack, and finally fell at the seventh wave.

"This beast enslavement Gu is extremely important to the blessed land, the land spirit definitely won't exchange it. But Long Hair Ancestor has refined many Immortal Gu, he definitely had more than just beast enslavement Gu and Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus."

Fang Yuan felt a rush and after thinking for a moment, he began to write a recipe.

The old land spirit looked from the side with his hands behind his back. After observing for a while, he started laughing: "This is the second aperture Gu's recipe, right?"

"Eh? You have this recipe too?" Fang Yuan stopped writing.

"Of course, I have countless recipes here, including thousands of Immortal Gu recipes." The land spirit said proudly.

'Such wealth, I see why even the heavenly court decided to attack.' Fang Yuan's eyes flashed as he sighed inwardly.

"In that case..." He contemplated and started writing on another paper.

He was writing the recipe for the rank six Blood Deity.

The land spirit's eyes immediately let out a bright light when he saw the start of the recipe. But the light gradually dimmed.

When Fang Yuan had written the third line, the land spirit said: "Although your blood path recipe might be amazing, it is only a remnant recipe. Even though some parts were patched up, there are many conflicts in the steps; there is a very small chance of successfully refining it. You cannot exchange this recipe for an Immortal Gu."

Fang Yuan let out a sigh.

Back then, this Blood Deity recipe that he obtained was a remnant piece. After his painstaking research and request for other Gu Immortals to repair it, this current recipe was formed.

He knew, however, this recipe was not accurate. The reason why he did not choose to refine Blood Deity in his previous life was also mainly because of this.

Later, through a coincidental opportunity, he obtained the accurate recipe for Spring Autumn Cicada. Thereupon, he abandoned the Blood Deity to refine Spring Autumn Cicada.

However, Spring Autumn Cicada involved his greatest secret of rebirth, even if Lang Ya blessed land did not have this recipe, Fang Yuan would not take it out to exchange.

He had taken the initiative to expose it in three kings blessed land because he was in dire straits and wanted to gamble for an overwhelming benefit.

However, right now, he was not in a tight spot and thus did not need to take the risk.

Since it was like this, Fang Yuan did not continue writing the recipe for the Blood Deity.

The Immortal Gu recipes he knew were only about a dozen. But most of them were remnant recipes. Blood Deity's recipe was already the best of these remnant recipes.

He only had two intact and correct Immortal Gu recipes; second aperture Gu and Spring Autumn Cicada. However, Lang Ya blessed land already had the recipe of the former while Fang Yuan did not dare to expose the latter.

Fang Yuan fell into silence and after thinking for a while, he asked: "Land spirit, can I use rank five recipe to exchanged for a stargate Gu?"

The land spirit shook his head: "No. You can only exchange for the Gu worms that I currently have."

Fang Yuan was unresigned and asked: "Land spirit, could it be that you don't want to refine stargate Gu? This is a completely new Gu we are talking about here."

"Of course I want to. Although it is not suitable for me to use, I can put it in treasure yellow heaven to sell. Hmm... but I can refine it whenever I want to, and I am not certain when I will do it." The land spirit suddenly reacted.

He showed his intelligence at this time.

"Little friend, you are Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritor. You have three opportunities to ask me to refine Gu. But if you want to refine Immortal Gu, whether it succeeds or fails, it will be counted as one chance. If you want to refine mortal Gu, I will definitely make you the Gu. If you want the stargate Gu, I can refine it successfully for you." The land spirit proposed.

Fang Yuan suddenly realized that there were these small details.

No wonder Ma Hong Yun choose to refine three rank five Gu; at that time, when he fell into this place, he was only a mortal and might not know the value of a Immortal Gu. Moreover, a mortal body cannot use Immortal Gu. Thus, he refined three rank five Gu that could immediately increase his battle strength. After returning to the outside world, he turned the tide around, gathering his troops again and turned defeat into victory.

When Ma Hong Yun later became a Gu Immortal, he realized how precious the opportunity in Lang Ya blessed land was. Unfortunately, he could only regret at that time.

Ma Hong Yun's awkwardness became Fang Yuan's awkwardness too.

Fang Yuan was only a mortal now, even if he got an Immortal Gu, he could not use it. Little Hu land spirit could use Immortal Gu, but whether it was hole earth Gu, connecting heaven Gu or stargate Gu, they could not support an Immortal Gu.

That is to say, even if Fang Yuan possessed an Immortal Gu, he could not send it to Hu Immortal blessed land.

Moreover, these three opportunities to refine Immortal Gu also had a precondition, that is Fang Yuan had to provide the recipes for them.

If there was an error in the recipe, the refinement would fail. Immortal Gu were the only one of its kind, if someone else already possessed that Immortal Gu, the refinement would fail then as well.

According to the land spirit's words, if the Immortal Gu refinement fails, one opportunity would be lost.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable could refine six Immortal Gu at that time; one reason was because Long Hair Ancestor was arrogant and refused to fail intentionally, and another reason was Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was brimming with talent and formidable ability, he had made sufficient preparation and made use of every opportunity, causing Long Hair Ancestor to lose great amounts of precious and rare Gu refinement materials six times.

Now, Long Hair Ancestor was dead and had turned into a land spirit, although he would not play tricks when refining Immortal Gu for Fang Yuan, he was after all a land spirit and not Long Hair Ancestor himself, thus his ability in Gu refinement was greatly reduced.

'In that case, do I waste one precious opportunity to refine a stargate Gu?'

Fang Yuan fell into deep contemplation.

According to common sense, these three opportunities should be sufficiently exploited to refine three Immortal Gu like Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable did back in the day.

However, Fang Yuan had huge problems in doing so.

Firstly, he did not have Immortal Gu recipes. Secondly, he did not have the ability of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, and could not guarantee the success of an Immortal Gu's refinement. If the refinement failed, it would mean one chance wasted. It was worse than refining a rank five Gu. The final crucial point was that he was only a mortal and could not use Immortal Gu. Although Immortal Gu had a very high value, it was of no help to him and would instead attract disaster, it would be worse than a rank five Gu.

Even rank five Gu were not suitable for Fang Yuan; with Fang Yuan's current situation in northern plains, using rank four was the best.

"Of course, I can leave these three opportunities for now. Anyway, I have already obtained the opportunities, even if Ma Hong Yun came personally or that Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritor appears, there would be no effect. However, I truly need stargate Gu at present!"

Fang Yuan was hesitating and felt that he was in an awkward position.

His current strength path cultivation only had thirty jun of strength, he urgently needed Gu worms to reform his skin and flesh. In terms of enslavement path cultivation, there was a great burden in feeding the wolf group and without a tribe to support them, he could only maintain around thirty thousand wolves by himself.

In terms of soul, the wolfman soul was already formed, he could go to Dang Hun mountain and use guts Gu to strengthen it. In terms of cultivation, he fulfilled the conditions to breakthrough, but because of the region's suppression, he could not breakthrough to rank five right now.

His current situation was like a chess player with all the chess pieces in places where they could not be moved. He was stuck in a deadlock, facing a huge bottleneck.

Chapter 464: Either Eternal Life or Shit

If there were no external influences and Fang Yuan could just rely on his own strength, he would be able to accumulate strength and breakthrough when the opportunity comes.

However, because of Spring Autumn Cicada, what he lacked was time. Not only that, if he wasted time and could not make it to some opportunities, the advantage of his rebirth would also be gone.

"These three chances are indeed very precious. Although blindly saving these chances for the future may give the impression that I will be able to make full use of these opportunities, it will in fact delay my growth. Specific situations need specific analysis; I cannot blindly follow Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's example, but Ma Hong Yun's choices also wasted these three chances."

After deep and careful contemplation, Fang Yuan made his decision.

"Land spirit, I have thought it through." Fang Yuan spoke slowly, "This time, my request is for you to refine stargate Gu. As for the remaining two chances, I will leave it for later."

"You really want me to refine stargate Gu? You need to know you are giving up a precious chance to refine Immortal Gu. Maybe, you can take a gamble and use that recipe for Blood Deity." land spirit instead tried to persuade Fang Yuan.

He liked recipes to an extreme degree, Blood Deity's recipe might be damaged but he still wanted to collect it.

Fang Yuan shook his head, when he decided on something, he would not hesitate: "No, refine stargate Gu."

"Alright. There is no strongest Gu worm in this world, only a Gu worm that is most suitable for oneself. You can't use Immortal Gu, but looks like this stargate Gu is extremely useful to you. I will refine this Gu for you."

The land spirit grandpa then willed as he teleported five Gu Immortals over.

Among these five Gu Immortals; one was very ugly, one had a ruddy face, one wore blue clothes, one wore yellow garments and one wore a pink skirt. They were Gui Wang's group.

They attacked Lang Ya blessed land, throwing in their green grape immortal essence to expend Lang Ya blessed land's white litchi immortal essence.

However, the result was that the land spirit had intentionally shown weakness in order to capture all of them.

Lang Ya blessed land had rank eight Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus and would never lack white litchi immortal essence. Gui Wang and the group did not have an Immortal Gu, thus the land spirit enticed them into the blessed land.

It waited till these five rushed into the cloud buildings before confining their rank five Gu.

Gui Wang and the rest realized the situation was bad, promptly using all their immortal essence but they could not compare to the Lang Ya land spirit.

The land spirit did not use even a single desolate beast to capture these five immortals.

Having cultivated to this stage, the five immortals knew to adapt to the circumstances and immediately chose to save their lives by submitting to the land spirit.

After finding themselves teleported over, they soon reacted and bowed to the land spirit, greeting together: "Subordinates greet Lord Lang Ya land spirit!"

"Hm..." The land spirit stroked his snow white beard, recovering his sagely demeanor just like when Fang Yuan first saw him.

"This is Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritor Chang Shan Yin, greet him." Land spirit introduced Fang Yuan.

"Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritor?!" The five immortals looked at each other, clearly seeing the shock in each other's eyes.

Their contempt towards Fang Yuan because of his mortal identity immediately disappeared. Who was Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable? He was a rank nine Gu Immortal!

Since Immemorial Era to Remote Antiquity Era, Olden Antiquity Era, Medieval Antiquity Era, Early Antiquity Era to present age, only around ten venerable level Gu Immortals had appeared in human history.

An inheritor of a rank nine Gu Immortal...

This identity shocked the five immortals before this shock turned into envy and jealousy.

"Why don't I have such luck to become an inheritor?"

"This kid's luck is too good, simply too heaven defying. He actually became Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritor!"

"Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had set up many inheritances, it is rumored that his greatest inheritance is in space cave. I wonder how many inheritances did he get?"

The five immortals' thoughts surged rapidly while they greeted Fang Yuan.

The act of Gu Immortals greeting mortals was like an elephant kowtowing to an ant. But the five immortals did not feel any humiliation.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan was extremely indifferent, even if a rank nine Gu Immortal kowtowed to him, he would not feel any honor. If the roles were reversed, even if he had to beg and kneel to a mortal, he would not feel any humiliation.

In his eyes, all that would eventually die were equal. The only difference was whether they died early or late.

Be it those with status and social class, whether they were nobles or peasants, they were nothing more than a group of fools waiting to die. All of them live in a fake world with self-imposed rules, by comparing the lives of each other, a portion of these fools would feel that they were living a great life.

In truth, those fools who think of themselves as nobles or aristocrats were only deceiving themselves. And those fools who think of themselves as lowly are even more pitiful. Are kings given their high status upon birth? All living beings are born equal, why should one bow to others?

"There is only immortality, only eternal life should be the goal one should pursue! If one cannot live forever, is there any difference between a rank nine Gu Immortal and a pile of shit in the gutter?! I am a huge fool, but I do not wish to be a fool that is made of shit..."

There was no way to express such mental behavior and aspirations to others, and even more importantly Fang Yuan did not want to express them.

Fang Yuan indifferently accepted the greetings of the five immortals then looked at Lang Ya land spirit: "Land spirit, are you not going to personally refine the Gu?"

"Of course I will personally refine it, but having these five as support can be considered making use of trash." Land spirit snickered.

Being called trash and also being disregarded by Fang Yuan caused these five immortals' expressions to turn unsightly.

Rage was burning in them, but they were captives right now and they could not flare out. They could only helplessly hold in this anger and listen to the land spirit's commands.

However, the first try at Gu refinement by former Long Hair Ancestor who turned into a land spirit, along with the help of five immortals, ended up in failure.

"Hmph, this stargate Gu is rather difficult. There was no mistakes from me, but rather the refinement itself has only a fixed success rate." The land spirit explained and said to Fang Yuan, "Don't worry, stargate Gu is only rank five, I will definitely complete the refinement for you."

"Hehe, I will be waiting." Fang Yuan lied down on the cloud bed with no hurry.

The time flow in Lang Ya blessed land was thirty-six times faster than the outside world. Over a month here would only be a day in the outside world.

The land spirit had inherited Long Hair Ancestor's arrogance and his temperament became bad when he failed.

He glanced at Fang Yuan and saw that he had already finished drinking the cloud mist tea, he casually pointed to an immortal: "You! Clumsy and having breasts for brains, I don't need you to refine the Gu, go make tea for my little friend!"

The female immortal who was scolded and ordered was Fairy Huang Sha.

She was furious, but did not dare to flare up as her life was in Lang Ya land spirit's hands. She could only bite her lips and forcibly restrain her anger to steep tea for Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan, however, said: "I don't like to drink tea, do you have wine here? I only like drinking top quality wine, there should be some in your grand Lang Ya blessed land, right?"

"Hmph! Why would there not be? Celestial horse wine and destitute wine, both are top quality wine, which one do you want to drink?"

"Bring out both of them for me to taste." Fang Yuan said without batting an eyelid.

Thereupon, Fairy Huang Sha became Fang Yuan's serving maid.

The celestial horse wine was milky white and gave off a thick fragrance of milk; it tasted silky, mellow and soft. Destitute wine did not have any special color, looking like clear soup, and did not have even a bit of wine fragrance; it also tasted flavorless. However, the after-effect was extremely strong, usually only one mouthful would be enough to make one completely drunk for seven-eight days.

Taking advantage of the land spirit refining Gu, Fang Yuan just took a light sip before openly storing these two vats of wine in wolf swallow Gu.

The second Gu refinement attempt also failed.

The land spirit's expression became even more unsightly as he howled: "Hmph, I don't believe it, I will continue!"

The land spirit naturally sensed Fang Yuan storing the wine, but right now because of his self-respect, he chose to ignore it.

"Young master, please be merciful and save this servant." Looking at the land spirit and the rest going for third attempt at Gu refinement, Fairy Huang Sha implored to Fang Yuan with a soft and weeping voice.

Her skin was white and tender, like a litchi whose skin had just been removed. Her eyebrows were bluish-black, her eyes were like a lake hiding an amorous gaze. Her breasts were very big and her waist was thin, her figure was endlessly seductive and one could even say it could shock heart and soul.

Right now, as she talked with eyes that had tears in them, let alone men, even women would be moved.

"If you can save this servant, I am willing to serve you for my whole life and follow your orders." Fairy Huang Sha implored again with soft voice.

This was a pleading from a female Gu Immortal!

If it were any other mortal men, they would already be extremely moved and their little brother would furiously rise up. Men all had a desire to conquer, especially if it was conquering a noble woman.

But Fang Yuan did not even glance at her. These five immortals were all cannon fodder in his past life, they all died in Lang Ya blessed land. They paid a proper price for their greed and impulse.

Although Fairy Huang Sha was beautiful, she was no different from a pile of dung in the gutter in Fang Yuan's mind.

"But if I cannot obtain immortality, I am also a pile of shit in the gutter... hehehe." Fang Yuan sneered in his mind.

Fairy Huang Sha was about to plead again. She had complete confidence in her beauty, and right now she had a feeling that this person might be her only chance to escape with her life.

However how could she know Fang Yuan was even more abnormal than Lang Ya land spirit.

"You are too noisy, get lost." Fang Yuan directly kicked the half leaning delicate body of Fairy Huang Sha.

Fairy Huang Sha fell down on the floor, she was baffled and could not react for a long while.

She was actually rejected? Is he not a man?!

A strong sense of humiliation struck her proud heart, causing her face to become twisted and her gaze towards Fang Yuan filled with extreme resentment.

"Hehe." Fang Yuan scoffed, got off the cloud bed and walked towards Fairy Huang Sha, then he lifted his foot in front of her face.

A dull sound was heard, Fairy Huang Sha was kicked over and her head struck the floor, producing another heavy dull sound.

Her rank five Gu worms were all taken away. Under the situation where her immortal essence was used up and was under Lang Ya blessed land's suppression as well, how could she be Fang Yuan's match?

"You!"

Fairy Huang Sha's lungs were about to burst with anger, her incisor tooth had broken from the kck, causing her mouth to fill with blood. She let out a deep growl and her expression turned malevolent; compared to her weeping and pitiful look just before, they looked like two completely different person.

"Hmph, how can mere beauty entice me? If you look at me one more time, do you believe I will not smash all your teeth?" Fang Yuan's dark and deep pupils shone with cruelty.

Fairy Huang Sha's delicate body shuddered, she tightly clenched her fists and seemed to exhaust all her strength to stand up.

But she lowered her head in the end and did not look at Fang Yuan again.

At the other side, stargate Gu's refinement failed again.

The land spirit stomped his foot in anger, his expression turning even worse. He was aware of the situation with Fairy Huang Sha.

He approached Fang Yuan and smiled: "Little friend, please don't get angry. I just captured this little thing, so haven't had the time to teach them properly. You can play with her if you want, make her dance or strip her clothes or do anything you want. Hehehe, materials have been used up, I will go buy them."

Hearing these words, Fairy Huang Sha seemed to have fallen into an ice hole. An intense feeling of humiliation surged in her heart like a tide.

"Make me strip my clothes and dance?!"

This proposal made her feel incomparably cold and afraid. Since young till now, she had never received such treatment. A grand Gu Immortal being played with, Fairy Huang Sha felt it would be better to die instead!

Gui Wang and Loner Hong Yu at the side seemed to have been stimulated as they licked their dry lips and looked at Fairy Huang Sha with burning gaze.

The two who were normally close to Fairy Huang Sha like sisters, Fairy Fen Meng and Fairy Qing Suo, remained silent as if they had not heard anything.

As the tragedy was about to unfold, Fang Yuan sneered: "Strip her clothes, make her dance? No need, what meaning is there in that? Lust? Desire to conquer? Hmph, nothing but pointless urges. What I am interested in now is only stargate Gu."

Chapter 465: The night sky is really beautiful

Gui Wang and Loner Hong Yu were very disappointed.

Fairy Qing Suo and Fairy Fen Meng let out a breath of turbid air, their expressions were complex.

The heavy stone in Fairy Huang Sha's heart fell and her body completely relaxed, almost falling down to the ground. The hatred in her heart towards Fang Yuan and the land spirit deepened by several times.

"As long as I can escape, as long as I can make a comeback, I will cut your bodies into a thousand pieces to relieve this hatred in my heart!"

"Hehe... little friend is indeed worthy of being a Demon Venerable's inheritor." The land spirit let out a forced laughter and took out connecting heaven Gu.

This connecting heaven Gu turned into a round mirror when it was activated and flew to the top of the land spirit and stayed there.

The scene of pitch darkness in the mirror suddenly changed, letting out a bright yellow light.

The land spirit activated divine sense Gu, divine sense was transmitted into the mirror in waves after waves, and exchanged with other waves of divine sense.

At the same time, the surface of the mirror continuously changed and showed pictures of all kinds of materials.

The land spirit seemed to have already made an agreement; he took out two immortal essence stones out of nowhere and threw into the connecting heaven Gu.

The surface of the mirror seemed to ripple; the immortal essence stones went into the mirror and materials were spurted out by the mirror one after another.

"This time, I have bought twenty sets of materials, I don't believe the refinement won't succeed!" The land spirit said fiercely.

The Gu refinement began again and at the final stage, bright starlight converged to become a pair of oval stones.

"Success!" The land spirit laughed heartily and handed these two oval blue gemstone like Gu worms to Fang Yuan, "This is stargate Gu, I have finished the agreement."

"How do I know if it works or not?" Fang Yuan held this pair of stargate Gu and asked.

The land spirit fumed in anger as if it had received a great insult: "Are you doubting my Gu refinement ability? You can exchange it if it won't do!"

"Alright, I shall take my leave then." Fang Yuan was extremely straightforward and expressed his intent to leave.

The land spirit fiercely stared at his eyes: "Leaving just like that? Then the remaining two chances, you won't use them now?"

"I am saving them for now. Where is the exit?"

The land spirit waved his hand, teleporting the five immortals away. His expression then greatly eased: "What recipes do you have now? Write them all out and let me look."

"None left. If I had any, I would have exchanged them with you." Fang Yuan shirked.

"I have a feeling little friend, you have something good still left!" The land spirit looked at Fang Yuan doubtfully and mumbled, "Alright then, I shall wait for your return."

The land spirit then waved his sleeve.

Fang Yuan's vision blurred and when it cleared, he saw he was back at the stone forest. Beside him was the stone stool he sat at before and behind was that purple stone pillar.

The stars shone brightly in the sky, the temperature was low and one could see their breath coming out.

Everything before seemed like a dream, causing Fang Yuan to feel like it was all a life-like illusion.

He looked at the sky, he had spent quite some time in Lang Ya blessed land, but only 1/36 of that time had passed in the outside world.

Stargate Gu, divine sense Gu, connecting heaven Gu and the two small vats of top quality wine in wolf swallow Gu were clear evidences that allowed Fang Yuan to recall this fortuitous encounter.

"I had intended to use all the three chances, but who knew I could use recipes to exchange for Gu, thus I still have two chances left. If this stargate Gu can be used, it would make spending a Gu refinement chance worth it!"

Fang Yuan thought of this as he left the place and returned to the wolf group.

This was a time where he had to make use of every second to prevent causing any complications. Fang Yuan sat cross-legged at the grassy land under the protection of the wolf kings and began writing a letter.

The letter was soon finished, he then activated moving perspective cup Gu. After a moment, the moving perspective cup exchanged with the other one through the space cave; and Fang Yuan took out a rank four Gu and a letter from it.

This Gu was like a dried fish, named dried pond Gu and was a water path Gu worm with a special effect. It is used to boost the effects of other Gu worms.

Once this Gu arrived in northern plains, it was immediately suppressed to rank three.

Fang Yuan browsed through the letter and nodded in satisfaction: "During these days when I was not at the blessed land, it seems little Hu Immortal had been extremely diligent and did not forget the task I gave before I left, refining twenty dried pond Gu. Great!"

Fang Yuan then sent another letter including several praises towards little Hu Immortal.

"Master praised me, I am so happy." Little Hu Immortal's face flushed with happiness after she read the letter.

"Master, I miss you..." Little Hu Immortal lay on the table and started writing, "When master is not here, I feel anxious. Master, are you okay? I am sending another dried pond Gu there."

Little Hu Immortal used her delicate small hand to fold the letter properly before putting it into moving perspective cup Gu.

At the same time, she also added a dried pond Gu.

After a good while, moving perspective cup Gu leisurely flew up and entered space cave, exchanging with the other moving perspective cup and appearing before Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan immediately took out the dried pond Gu and glanced at the letter. Then he absorbed primeval stones to recover his primeval essence before activating moving perspective cup Gu again.

After repeating this over and over, he received a total of eight dried pond Gu.

"If I use the eight dried pond Gu together, their effects should stack up and match a rank four level."

Fang Yuan crushed these dried pond Gu on the spot; the dried pond Gu turned into eight halos which twisted around moving perspective cup Gu. At the same time, on Hu Immortal blessed land, Little Hu Immortal also crushed eight dried pond Gu and overlaid them on moving perspective cup Gu.

Moving perspective cup Gu was a rank five Gu, but in northern plains, it was suppressed to rank four. Thus, it could only transport rank four Gu worms.

Now, after using eight dried pond Gu, moving perspective cup Gu's ability advanced to rank five and could transport rank five Gu.

Fang Yuan waited for a while before taking out connecting heaven Gu and gravely put it in moving perspective cup Gu, then transferred his primeval essence.

After successful activation, the two moving perspective cup completed their exchange in space cave and the cup with connecting heaven Gu appeared in Hu Immortal blessed land.

Little Hu Immortal cheered and took out the connecting heaven Gu.

Tiny cracks appeared on moving perspective cup Gu.

Although dried pond Gu could amplify a Gu worm's ability, it was like draining the pond to get the fish or burning the forest to hunt. Although it greatly raised the power, the Gu worm would perish because of the excessively forced power-up.

Next, Fang Yuan sent divine sense Gu to Hu Immortal blessed land, and the cracks on moving perspective cup Gu intensified.

Fang Yuan silently took out primeval stones and quickly replenished his primeval essence.

He then sent one blue gemstone of the stargate Gu to Hu Immortal blessed land.

Fortunately, stargate Gu was not an Immortal Gu, but a rank five Gu, allowing Fang Yuan to be barely able to use moving perspective cup Gu to send it to Hu Immortal blessed land.

After the stargate Gu was sent to the blessed land, moving perspective cup Gu had already become deformed with cracks all over it and was on the verge of collapse.

At this point, it could still be used for one last time.

Fang Yuan stored the moving perspective cup Gu in his aperture and did not use it again.

He was waiting now.

Moving perspective cup Gu had been refined by him and possessed his will. But he had already lent it to little Hu Immortal, thus she could also use it.

The several times before were all him using moving perspective cup Gu.

It was because Hu Immortal blessed land's timeflow was several times faster than at northern plains. If little Hu Immortal recklessly activated it from the blessed land, it was very possible Fang Yuan would not have been prepared.

"Puff... it is up to little Hu Immortal now. If she fails, she will have to send another moving perspective cup Gu for the final use. Hopefully, she can succeed."

Before Fang Yuan left, he had refined only one set of moving perspective cup Gu. But he had reminded Little Hu Immortal. For a period of time, Little Hu Immortal and Immortal Crane Sect had made several transactions and exchanged many Gu refinement materials, and had already refined the second set of moving perspective cup Gu.

Time was becoming somewhat difficult to endure.

Whether it was connecting heaven Gu or divine sense Gu, they were both rank five Gu and had an extremely huge demand for primeval essence. Even a rank five peak stage Gu Master might only be able to last for several breaths. Thus, usually only Gu Immortals or land spirits would consume immortal essence to use them.

As for why Fang Yuan did not activate moving perspective cup Gu at Lang Ya blessed land, it was because he did not want to expose them. If it was exposed, the Lang Ya land spirit would definitely demand for its recipe.

Minutes ticked by, and with several times the speed at Hu Immortal blessed land.

The chilly night wind made Fang Yuan slightly restless. He stood up and began to pace around.

The sky was filled with many stars, providing sufficient starlight. The stargate Gu in Fang Yuan's hand, however, had no movement.

"Did it fail? Was that group of starlight firefly Gu at treasure yellow heaven bought by someone else?" As time passed by, Fang Yuan's heart continued to sink.

He stopped pacing about and stood on the spot for a long while with his hands behind his back.

He gazed afar, crescent lake sparkled with light in tranquilness. The wolf group beside him; some were standing and some were lying down, all with different postures.

He could not help thinking back to that scene when he went to capture the liquor worm at Qing Mao mountain.

He broke out in laughter, his worries gone and his gaze once more became unclouded.

All the worries, all the pressure, all the impatience since the start till now dispersed with the wind.

He gazed at the night sky and breathed out all the turbid air in him, and suddenly felt that his current life was so beautiful; giving everything to pursue the greatest goal, having no regrets.

He came to an understanding, his heart was clear like a mirror that could not be stained by dust, tranquil like this crescent lake.

Since his rebirth at Qing Mao mountain, he had always been exhausting his mind, and now he suddenly understood something.

This comprehension was unclear as it lingered around his heart before finally turning into a sentence, he mumbled: "The night sky is really beautiful."

This was his heartfelt emotion.

The moment he said these words, Fang Yuan's body lightened and felt he had unloaded a thousand jin of weight, as if he was about to fly.

His entire disposition also seemed to have changed. The cold aura disappeared without a trace, turning into a clear and carefree aura. The dark pupils with abysmal depths let out a clear light now, just like a newborn baby or like a star.

The stargate Gu in his hand slightly shook at this moment and the shaking intensified.

Fang Yuan opened his hand.

The blue gemstone-like stargate Gu leisurely flew in the air, large amounts of starlight gathered and condensed towards it. The scene was beautiful and dreamy.

In an instant, the starlight formed into an enormous oval door.

Stargate Gu had succeeded!

Fang Yuan calmly watched it; the corner of his lips slightly curled up into a smile, but his eyes were still calm as water.

He unhurriedly stepped into the stargate, the starlight in front of him turned into a whirlpool and flew away with his body.

After a dozen or so breaths of time, he walked out of the stargate and appeared in Hu Immortal blessed land.

"Master, you are back!" Little Hu Immortal was extremely happy as she leapt into Fang Yuan's chest.

Fang Yuan chuckled and rubbed the land spirit's tiny head.

"Yes, I am back." He gently said.

Chapter 466: There is nothing that cannot be sold

After several months, Fang Yuan finally returned to Hu Immortal blessed land.

The little Hu Immortal land spirit became very excited upon his return; the flow of time inside of the immortal land was five times faster compared to the outside world. While Fang Yuan had only spent a few months in northern plains, to her, it had already been a year.

Fang Yuan looked at the stargate behind him.

This stargate, compared to the one in northern plains, was much smaller. It was about the height of a person, and barely allowed Fang Yuan to fit through.

The one at the crescent lake in northern plains was much taller, and was many times wider.

"Stargate Gu isn't split into main and sub Gu, it consumes too much primeval essence, even a rank five peak stage Gu Master cannot sustain it for three breaths' time, only immortal essence could allow it to be used continuously. If little Hu Immortal land spirit activates it first, while I hold the other half in my hands and activate it along with her, I will not have to consume primeval essence."

"However, the stargate Gu's activation not only requires large amount of primeval essence, it also needs a large amount of starlight, in order to form the gate. Northern plains is one of the five regions, stars fill the sky and starlight is abundant. But here in the Hu Immortal blessed land, the starlight is vastly inferior, as the only source comes from the starlight firefly Gu."

As Fang Yuan inwardly thought to himself, his gaze rested upon the small swarm of starlight firefly Gu that fluttered about in the air.

The starlight firefly Gu was a rank three Gu, small in size, almost like a normal firefly, but when they were activated, they emitted genuine azure starlight.

This swarm of fireflies, originally consisted of more than five hundred, but because of the activations of the stargate Gu, thirty-two of them already died. In order to maintain the activated stargate Gu, one firefly dies in every three breath's time.

Five hundred starlight firefly Gu, while it may seem like a large amount, it could not maintain the gate for a long period of time.

Because of this, Fang Yuan commanded little Hu Immortal to deactivate the stargate Gu.

The stargate dissipated, and reverted back into a oval sapphire. Little Hu Immortal stretched out her pale and delicate hands, and commanded the precious stargate Gu to return to her.

"Master, here you go!" Little Hu Immortal cupped the stargate Gu with both of her hands, and looked up with her big watery eyes, offering the stargate Gu to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan gently rubbed her little fox ears, and gave her a soft smile: "I'm leaving it with you, so take good care of it. If I need to use it in the future, I will contact you using the moving perspective cup Gu."

"Yes, Master! I'll definitely take good care of it!" Little Hu Immortal solemnly put the stargate Gu within the small pocket of her dress, and patted it with her tiny hand.

As for the stargate Gu in northern plains, it rested on the grassland, closely guarded by the myriad wolf pack.

"Master, there are two pieces of immortal essence stones left. I listened to your instructions, using the Immortal Gu recipe to trade for the starlight firefly Gu, this is the excess." Little Hu immortal presented them to him.

Normal primeval stones, were the size of duck eggs, and were grey in color. Immortal essence stones were also the size of duck eggs, but were not oval in shape, rather, they were round like pearls, and the entire body was glossy, having a translucent and sparkly appearance. They resembled crystals, but had the lustre of jade.

If normal primeval stones were equated to mortals, then the immortal essence stones could be equated to immortals.

Immortal essence stones were extremely precious, as it can be used to replenish immortal essence. In addition, it was also used in transactions between immortals, adopted as a precious currency. In the vast Gu world, only the heavenly court could produce immortal essence stones.

"I see immortal essence stones once again." Fang Yuan smiled with a sigh.

These two immortal essence stones were incredibly valuable, more valuable than two hundred million primeval essence stones.

In his previous five hundred years, the most number of immortal essence stones Fang Yuan had held at one point in time was merely over sixty pieces.

Fang Yuan put away the immortal essence stones, "Good, let's return to Dang Hun mountain".

Little Hu Immortal grew delighted upon hearing this, and quickly held Fang Yuan's hand, and in the next moment they teleported inside Dang Hun palace.

"Quickly activate the connecting heaven Gu." Fang Yuan commanded.

There was another stargate Gu was in northern plains, he could not relax.

Trouble brews as time passes, Fang Yuan should act quickly and efficiently settle the matters of Hu Immortal blessed land.

Little Hu immortal promptly activated the connecting heaven Gu.

Hole earth Gu, once planted in the blessed land, could no longer be changed. It was the same for connecting heaven Gu.

Fang Yuan's connecting heaven Gu, since it was linked to treasure yellow heaven, it could no longer be altered.

Little Hu Immortal consumed a slight amount of immortal essence, and the entire body of the Gu worm grew into a round mirror, and floated in the air.

Reflected in the mirror was a scene of treasure yellow heaven.

The grotto-heaven was deserted and absolutely empty, with a lemon-like yellow color dying the air slightly. The grotto-heaven was devoid of any mountains, vegetation, and animals which were usually found in ordinary grotto-heavens.

Above blessed lands were grotto-heavens.

The most famous grotto-heaven was recorded within \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, it was the famous immemorial nine heavens.

Verdant Great Sun refined the fixed immortal travel Gu, and flew up to the nine heavens. In azure heaven, he obtained a segment of the jade-green jade bamboo. In blue heaven, he collected the eight-sided diamonds inside the star fragments.

The immemorial nine heavens consisted of; white heaven, red heaven, orange heaven, yellow heaven, green heaven, azure heaven, blue heaven, purple heaven, and black heaven.

But later, when Ren Zu's son caused havoc in heaven and earth, red, orange, yellow, green, azure, blue, and purple, the seven heavens were destroyed consecutively, and all that remained were white and black heavens, with the two alternating between day and night.

The treasure yellow heaven, was closely related to the yellow heaven of the immemorial nine heavens.

In the Medieval Antiquity Era, a rank eight Gu Immortal, known as Daoist Countless Treasures, acquired a fragment of yellow heaven by chance. He fused the fragment into his grotto-heaven, and formed treasure yellow heaven.

Treasure yellow heaven was a very unique grotto-heaven, it was empty without any mountains, trees, or rivers, and there were also no birds, beasts, worms, or fish, there were only precious treasure within.

There was a rank eight immortal Gu in treasure yellow heaven — treasure light Gu.

Rank one to rank three treasure light Gu were everywhere, rank four to rank five treasure light Gu were often held in the hands of large forces. Above rank five, the treasure light Immortal Gu, of course, there was only one which was inside treasure yellow heaven.

Treasure light Gu specialized in assessing the value of an item. The greater the value of the item, the brighter the light of the treasure light Gu.

In Shang clan city, the battle stage would use the treasure light Gu to evaluate the value of their various Gu worms, and thus assess the strength of the Gu master.

The main application of treasure light Gu was not merely appraisal, but it could also be used to search for treasure.

The range of the treasure light Gu was small, and often had to be used in tandem with other Gu worms to boost its detection range.

In the past, Daoist Countless Treasures used the Immortal Gu treasure light to find countless treasures. As time passed, he gained his reputation and title of "Countless Treasures".

Little Hu Immortal continuously activated the connecting heaven Gu, the image in the mirror changed constantly, as pictures of various objects appeared.

Gu worms, beast groups, variant humans, vegetation, ore veins, soil, water, quality wine, and other various supplies, all that could be bought was sold.

Suddenly, the screen displayed a swarm of starlight firefly Gu.

"Master, this is sold by Starlord Wan Xiang." Little Hu Immortal land spirit used the divine sense Gu to communicate with the merchant.

"Starlight firefly Gu cannot reproduce, I need a large amount of ordinary starlight fireflies." Fang Yuan nodded as he said.

Little Hu Immortal communicated for a while, then turned to Fang Yuan: "Master, Starlord Wan Xiang said he's not selling."

Fang Yuan was not upset, but instead chuckled: "Hehe, there is nothing that cannot be sold in this world. Not selling merely means the price isn't high enough, the benefits are not enough to entice them."

As he spoke, he recalled the remnant recipes of a few Immortal Gu, he wrote them down on a piece of cowhide, and threw it into the connecting heaven Gu.

The cowhide was completely ordinary, but because it recorded the remnant recipes of Immortal Gu, it was invaluable.

Once it passed through the connecting heaven Gu and arrived at treasure yellow heaven, all of the cowhide pieces showed three to nine meters of treasure light. This treasure light was rainbow-colored, a beautiful mix of purple and red, it was exceptionally beautiful.

"Inform him that the price is negotiable." Fang Yuan gave a bright smile, and informed little Hu Immortal.

He wasn't afraid of Starlord Wan Xiang's refusal.

Immortal Gu were incomparably enticing to Gu Immortals. Although they were just remnant recipes, they were still often in high demand without ample supply.

Looking at those Gu Immortals who had lived for a long time and had great foundations, which one of them did not have tens of Immortal Gu remnant recipes in their hands?

But these remnant recipes were rarely sold.

Similar or closely related Immortal Gu remnant recipes, when combined with each other, would often allow the actual recipe to be discovered. After the Immortal Gu were refined using the recipe, no one else would be able to create them.

Because of this, the Immortal Gu remnant recipes were rarely traded. Even if they were sold, it would be to exchange remnant recipes for remnant recipes.

Earlier, Fang Yuan had only given the most lacking recipe that he could remember, the treasure light only glowed for one meter, and Starlord Wan Xiang gave him a swarm of starlight fireflies, and two immortal essence stones in exchange.

Now, with so many secret recipes, the treasure light was at least three meters, Starlord Wan Xiang had to be moved.

These remnant recipes, once sent in, attracted countless gazes within treasure yellow heaven.

A large number of divine senses were immediately sent over, little Hu Immortal had to use the divine sense Gu until her little cheeks turned pale.

"Master, so many Gu Immortals have sent their divine senses over, asking for the price for these remnant recipes!"

Fang Yuan gave a laugh, "Send a message over, tell them: Each of these recipes can be sold, but they have to queue up one by one. Tell them about the starlight firefly, demand at least a hundred thousand."

Little Hu Immortal sent her divine sense over, and immediately, someone called 'Fairy Yao Guang', a female Gu Immortal said that she nurtured a large number of starlight fireflies in her blessed land, and wished to exchange.

Fang Yuan smiled.

As expected, Starlord Wan Xiang also changed his attitude, repeatedly approaching him with offers.

A third Gu immortal, calling himself 'Di Yuan' , said he possessed a large number of starlight fireflies.

Fang Yuan paused for a short while, and when he did not see another Gu Immortal making an offer, he could not help but let out a sigh of sorrow: these starlight fireflies were immemorial creatures, by the present age, only a small amount were still around.

With competitors, everything became easier.

Fang Yuan stayed silent, and let the three Immortals bid against each other. This was an undisguised scheme, but how could there be any morons who cultivated to the level of Gu Immortal? The three immortals did not bid against each other aggressively, instead they negotiated properly, each offering thirty-three thousand starlight fireflies.

The three groups of starlight fireflies, entered the connecting heaven Gu respectively, each emitting a treasure light.

Among them, Fairy Yao Guang's group of fireflies emitted the most feeble light, only three meters in length, Di Yuan's fireflies emitted a treasure light of five and a half meters, while Starlord Wan Xiang's fireflies emitted the most powerful light, seven meters in length. This was because there were many starlight firefly Gu mixed in with his group of fireflies.

"It seem this Starlord Wan Xiang nurtured a lot of starlight fireflies. I remember now, originally after the stargate Gu appeared, Starlord Wan Xiang acted quickly and relied on selling starlight fireflies Gu to earn a large amount of immortal essence stones."

Fang Yuan suddenly recalled this bit of information.

Five hundred years of memories contained too much information, many details were not clear, but upon seeing this, his originally obscure memory became clearer.

After the appearance of the stargate Gu, the price of starlight firefly Gu also rose like a boat riding the tide. In the future, the treasure yellow heaven would not even sell starlight firefly swarms anymore, but only sold starlight firefly Gu.

Gu worms cannot reproduce, but only ordinary insects had that capability.

Immediately, Fang Yuan traded three recipes, and obtained over a hundred thousand starlight fireflies. As long as he bred them carefully afterwards, Fang Yuan would be able to produce his own starlight firefly Gu and not need to pay an exorbitant price to purchase them in the future.

Chapter 467: Wisdom Path

Despite having purchased over a hundred thousand starlight fireflies, the trade was far from over.

Fang Yuan also needed to take care of the issue of feeding these insects.

"Starlight fireflies consume star fragment grass, I happen to have a large amount of star fragment grass on me, I can sell them to you." Starlord Wan Xiang conveyed his thoughts using divine sense.

"I need the seeds as well as your farming knowledge. Let's look at the treasure light intensity first." Fang Yuan spoke through little Hu Immortal, who relayed the information to Starlord Wan Xiang, Fairy Yao Guang, and Di Yuan using divine sense.

Soon, three documents entered into treasure yellow heaven, each giving off a strong treasure light.

This time, instead of Starlord Wan Xiang, it was Fairy Yao Guang's document which had the greatest treasure light, at nearly two meters tall.

"I am most fond of growing grass, I deliberately migrated a small swarm of starlight fireflies for the production of star fragment grass. If you follow my instructions, you will definitely not suffer losses." Fairy Yao Guang conveyed with her divine sense.

Fang Yuan contemplated.

Originally he had already forgotten about it, after all in his previous life, he had had no use for and had never use the stargate Gu.

Now, through the successive reminders from Lang Ya land spirit, connecting heaven Gu, and Starlord Wan Xiang, his brain gradually began to recall more distinct memories.

In his memories,once stargate Gu came into the limelight, everything related to starlight firefly Gu became secret, not a single person wanted to sell information.

"Now that Lang Ya land spirit had obtained stargate Gu's recipe, perhaps it might refine the stargate Gu, then put it in treasure yellow heaven for sale. Once the stargate Gu is put up for sale in treasure yellow heaven, getting more of such secret information will not be easy."

Thinking of that, Fang Yuan made his decision, he let little Hu Immortal transmit his thoughts: "I will buy from all three of you, we'll deal using immortal essence stones."

The purchasing power of immortal essence stones was very high.

One piece of immortal essence stone, could purchase all three documents, with a quarter remaining.

Fang Yuan opened the three documents, and saw many things written on them—

"Star fragment grass can only be planted in the sky, it grows on clouds. Therefore, it is a good idea to use high quality cloud soil..."

"Star fragment grass is fond of yin energy, but loathes yang energy, therefore excessive sunlight can kill the star fragment grass. However, it cannot be completely derived of light, the amount it requires is about..."

"If starlight fireflies live in the star fragment grass, it will aid in spreading the seeds, and possibly increase the area that the grass can grow in as well as its quality..."

Among the three documents: Di Yuan was simple and brief, Starlord Wan Xiang had innovative ideas, and Fairy Yao Guang was verbose and detailed. Fang Yuan used their knowledge to make up for his shortcomings, and quickly memorized everything. In an instant, he became an expert in cultivating star fragment grass.

He laughed internally: "With this, I will become the largest seller of starlight fireflies in the future. When the stargate Gu is becomes popular, I will make a fortune!"

"It's time to buy liquor." Fang Yuan did not forget the need to purchase top quality wine.

He had already collected three kinds of top quality wines, this was the last one left.

Within treasure yellow heaven, naturally, top quality wine was sold. It was primarily used to refine Gu by Gu Immortals, but it was also an excellent beverage for enjoying life.

But when Fang Yuan wanted to purchase his wine, the whole of treasure yellow heaven erupted, as countless divine senses were stirred up.

"Immortal Gu, someone is selling Immortal Gu!" Little Hu Immortal land spirit cried out.

The mirror flashed, and the image of an Immortal Gu appeared.

"Divine travel Gu!" Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk.

The immortal Gu that was being sold was exactly the one he needed, divine travel Gu. Someone was one step ahead of him and had already grabbed possession of the divine travel Gu.

"Sigh, after all is said and done, I was late by one step." Fang Yuan was stunned for a moment, then laughed out loud.

He wanted to refine second aperture Gu, thus he needed divine travel Gu. But in three kings blessed land, due to the circumstances, he refined divine travel Gu into fixed immortal travel Gu.

According to the records in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, consuming four top quality wines was the criteria to obtain divine travel Gu. Fang Yuan had been collecting wine for this purpose, but now, someone was a step ahead of him.

"Without divine travel Gu, the second aperture Gu would be stuck at the last step, I won't be able to complete it. Thankfully, there is still a few decades of its lifespan."

"All in all, it was because I was too high profile on San Cha mountain when I refined the Gu, causing everyone to know about it. It is not strange that someone snatched it from me."

Fang Yuan shrugged, he had predicted this long ago.

When he used divine travel Gu to refine fixed immortal travel Gu, it was seen by a lot of Gu Masters. This definitely caused a great commotion, the Gu Immortals in southern border were not idiots, how could they not act?

But earlier, Fang Yuan was banking on the competition between Gu Immortals, that they would restrict each other and delay their progress, thus he was working hard to collect the wines.

In life, there were always a few things that one had to work hard for despite a low chance of success so that they would not have regrets. If they did not even work for it, then it would be absolutely hopeless.

"Regarding matters in this world, most do not go according to one's wishes, I am used to that. But since this divine travel Gu was put up for transaction here, I have to take a look, there might still be a chance."

Fang Yuan took it in his stride, he did not worry about losses or boast over gains, his mind was always peaceful and calm.

Since treasure yellow heaven was the greatest transaction market among Gu Immortals, there were very rare instances where Immortal Gu were sold.

These transactions were mostly using Immortal Gu to trade for Immortal Gu. But the Gu Immortal who sold the divine travel Gu, Old Man Yan Shi, had a rather peculiar transaction request.

"I want to use this divine travel Gu to exchange for the second aperture Gu's recipe."

The information in this request was too stunning, it created a lot of commotion. In treasure yellow heaven, the divine senses of all sorts of Gu Immortals were interacting with each other, turning the scene into chaos.

"Divine travel Gu! To think that we will get to see this legendary Gu worm today."

"Although it is an Immortal Gu, the divine travel Gu's ability is way too random. Back then, even Ren Zu's son got into trouble using it, it will be even more dangerous for us tiny Gu Immortals."

"But divine travel Gu is still an Immortal Gu, keeping it with you, when you are forced into a dead end, you can use it to gamble at the moment of despair."

"Compared to the divine travel Gu, I am more interested in the second aperture Gu's recipe!"

"That's right, I've heard of the second aperture Gu long ago, but to think the recipe really exists?"

"A second aperture! Hehe, mortals might not understand the full value of this, but to us Gu Immortals, who would not be moved?"

　　...

Fang Yuan had already stood up, gazing at the connecting heaven Gu in mid air.

He had the second aperture Gu's recipe, he just needed a thought to exchange for this Gu.

But!

"This Old Man Yan Shi who is selling the divine travel Gu is coming for me. He requested for the second aperture Gu's recipe... and his timing in selling this Gu was neither early nor late, he picked the exact moment when I was browsing through... impressive! This Gu Immortal is mostly likely on the immemorial wisdom path, he is adept at predictions and deductions. The fact that I had used connecting heaven Gu and was trading in treasure yellow heaven was already foreseen by him!"

Wisdom path was a very mysterious path among Gu Masters. It had been passed down since the immemorial era, but the numbers were always very small.

The creator of the wisdom path was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, the lord of the second generation heavenly court. She lived for nineteen thousand years, and had the second longest lifespan among the rank nine Gu Immortals.

Before she died, she deduced from the heavenly secret, and obtained the information of all that happened three million years after her death. She found out that after her death, the heavenly court would be without a lord for a long time, causing a long period of turmoil as three Demon Venerables appear.

She made three arrangements that dealt with each of the three Demon Venerables respectively. Next, she instructed her descendants to follow what she said to ensure that the heavenly court was peaceful for three hundred years.

After she died, there was a huge turmoil indeed as the era shifted, as during three great generations, three Demon Venerables appeared one after another.

The three Demon Venerables were invincible during their times, attacking the heavenly court but were obstructed by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's plans, failing and causing the heavenly court to stay intact.

"Wisdom path Gu Immortal... Old Man Yan Shi..." Fang Yuan squinted his eyes, muttering. It was not a good thing to be targeted by a wisdom path Gu Immortal.

Wisdom path Gu Immortals knew about the heavenly secret and were most skilled at making arrangements ahead of time and making predictions about the future. Often, they could scheme against people without them knowing, causing others to fall into traps unknowingly.

"I gathered too much attention in southern border, and ended up attracting a wisdom path Gu Immortal. Hehehe, in this life I was courageous and made great progress, charging through a dangerous cliff, I went too fast and with just my mortal body, I gained the attention of a Gu Immortal!"

Such a scenario was like an ant attracting the attention of an elephant.

At once, Fang Yuan could almost see a pair of wise and scheming eyes piercing through the connecting heaven Gu to observe himself.

The air was filled with formless pressure.

But Fang Yuan's state of mind was no longer like before, he laughed with his head up high, dispelling the pressure in his heart.

"Good, the schemes of a wisdom path Gu Immortal makes this much more interesting. Hmph, just a mere divine travel Gu, just a mere second aperture Gu, how can that entice me?"

His five hundred years of experience nurtured a keen instinct that was sensitive to danger.

Fang Yuan had a vague feeling, this divine travel Gu was likely bait that Old Man Yan Shi was using to attract him.

"Although an Immortal Gu is good, my goal is eternal life, this so-called Immortal Gu is merely a tool in my cultivation journey."

　　...

At the same time, in southern border, Sheng Si blessed land.

An old man, wearing a black robe, gave off the eerie aura of a rank seven Gu Immortal as he sat on the cushion silently.

His face was wrinkled, his eyes were dark without any white parts in them.

He stared at the connecting heaven Gu in the sky, feeling the divine senses moving about inside treasure yellow heaven. He was expressionless and motionless.

It was Old Man Yan Shi!

Before the old man was the kneeling killer ghost doctor Chou Jiu.

He looked at connecting heaven Gu for a long time, before showing disappointment: "Supreme Master, it seems that Fang Yuan did not take the bait."

Old Man Yan Shi smiled, not showing any annoyance: "This tiny fish is interesting, he is able to let go so easily, as a mere mortal, his disposition surpasses a large number of Gu Immortals. But he was too daring, he turned you into his slave and messed with us Shadow Sect. He is simply courting death."

Chou Jiu quickly bowed: "All thanks to Supreme Master's return, otherwise, I would've suffered the fate of being a slave for life!"

"Mm..." Old Man Yan Shi raised his head: "Little disciple, I have already altered the slavery Gu on you. I calculated that Fang Yuan would join the righteous demonic battle of Yi Tian mountain, at that time you can be a spy by his side, and wait for a chance to strike."

"Yes, Supreme Master!"

"Mm, go down and call your junior sister Bai Ning Bing."

"Yes, this disciple takes his leave."

Chapter 468: Scheme

An Immortal Gu was hovering in the air, emitting quiet and exquisite light.

A lemon colored halo completely covered Bai Ning Bing's body and sank into her aperture.

Yellow-green light colored vines had already creeped around her aperture walls, densely attached to the walls.

After a moment, Old Man Yan Shi took a deep breath and recalled the Immortal Gu back to his aperture: "Alright, I have used everlasting Gu's ability on your aperture; you will be fine for the next three months. According to your cultivation speed, you must come here after three months to reinforce your aperture again."

It has already been a long time since the San Cha mountain battle. Bai Ning Bing's aptitude had already recovered to a hundred percent, restoring one of the ten extreme aptitudes - Northern Dark Ice Soul physique.

A hundred percent primeval essence emitted an extremely great pressure on her aperture. If not for Old Man Yan Shi using everlasting Gu to reinforce her aperture, Bai Ning Bing would not have survived till now.

Although Old Man Yan Shi was her life saving benefactor, Bai Ning Bing did not feel any gratitude, instead she stood upright with an ice cold demeanour.

After Old Man Yan Shi took away the Immortal Gu, she opened her blue eyes, her gaze cold and her expression indifferent.

She was no more the novice, greenhorn kid from back then.

By travelling alongside Fang Yuan, she had learned many things.

Old Man Yan Shi had taken the initiative to look for her after knowing about her through Chou Jiu, clearly to make use of her. Her joining Shadow Sect was also no more than a transaction.

Old Man Yan Shi smiled warmly: "Bai Ning Bing, as long as you sincerely pledge allegiance to Shadow Sect, and make a new sea oath, I will turn you back to a male."

"Hmph, no need. You are helping me to suppress my aperture, so I am joining Shadow Sect temporarily to help you deal with Fang Yuan and obtain fixed immortal travel Gu from him; this is nothing more than a fair transaction. As for my male body, I will personally retrieve it, only then can it be spectacular. How could I, Bai Ning Bing, do something like relying on others?"

Bai Ning Bing then turned around and left.

Only when she exited the secret room, did Bai Ning Bing's ice cold expression loosen up, her brows furrowed and her gaze turned cold.

She did not like this rank seven wisdom path Gu Immortal Old Man Yan Shi; she always felt he had a hidden motive.

Although the other was a Gu Immortal, Bai Ning Bing had never feared death. As a person who was not afraid of death, why would she be afraid of Gu Immortals?

However, they had the same objective, both f them wanted to deal with Fang Yuan, so Bai Ning Bing agreed to this transaction and joined Shadow Sect temporarily.

"Fang Yuan..."

When she thought of him, Bai Ning Bing could not help thinking back to the scene at three kings blessed land.

Under countless people's eyes, Fang Yuan flew towards heaven and with a mortal body, refined an Immortal Gu!

Shortly after, three kings blessed land collapsed and everyone fell into chaos as they hurried to leave San Cha mountain. Winds of assimilation blew and wiped out the whole San Cha mountain until it was a barren land.

Little beast king's name was talked by countless people and soon spread to the whole southern border crazily. Fang Yuan disappeared, and Gu Immortals gave orders to all their forces to look for him.

Bai Ning Bing who had travelled together with him, naturally became a target all great forces chased after. Whether it was righteous path or demonic path, they all wanted to get her.

If not for Wei Yang's sense of brotherhood and thus intentionally let go of Bai Ning Bing, as well as her meeting Chou Jiu while gravely injured, Bai Ning Bing would have been a captive somewhere already.

After Chou Jiu healed her injuries, he made a proposal to her to join Shadow Sect and deal with Fang Yuan together.

After Bai Ning Bing's scheme against Fang Yuan failed, she was even confident of her guess that Fang Yuan had a prediction Gu. And when she heard behind Chou Jiu was a similar predictive wisdom path Gu Immortal, she could not help but be moved.

Although she did not fear death, she was truly not resigned to losing her life like that and letting Fang Yuan live; it would be her greatest defeat, and was too lackluster.

Thus, she agreed to Chou Jiu's request and temporarily joined Shadow Sect, making an oath in front of the Immortal Gu, Sea Oath Gu, with Old Man Yan Shi and Chou Jiu: She was free to leave and regain her freedom once they killed Fang Yuan. At the same time, Shadow Sect cannot directly or indirectly make a move against her.

When Bai Ning Bing's receding figure disappeared, Old Man Yan Shi's expression slowly turned dark.

Bai Ning Bing had a demonic nature, causing even this wisdom path Gu Immortal Old Man Yan Shi to find it hard to control her.

"This kid has no care for laws and morality, and is only joining hands with me because of the situation. She is absolutely not someone who will stay under others for long." Old Man Yan Shi's gaze was extremely profound.

"But it is not important. I have planned for so many years in my quest for immortality, why would I be afraid of the tiny ripples that this little fish can create? Hmph!"

Old Man Yan Shi coldly snorted and turned his gaze to connecting heaven Gu's screen.

Right at this time, a divine sense was transmitted to him —"I have second aperture Gu's recipe here, I want to exchange with your divine travel Gu."

The owner of the divine sense called himself Lang Ya old immortal.

"Hehehehe..." Old Man Yan Shi laughed heartily.

The fish has taken the bait!

Who said this bait could only lure Fang Yuan? Fang Yuan was only a small fish, Lang Ya land spirit was the true big fish.

"Lang Ya blessed land is rumored to have stored countless recipes. It has dropped from a grotto-heaven to a blessed land, and in the present age, it can be said to be the number one blessed land! Even more importantly, this blessed land has a lot of Immortal Gu as well. Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus is at the top, I must obtain it!"

Old Man Yan Shi's eyes flickered with a burning light filled with avarice.

He had been scheming since a long, long time ago.

In actual fact, the second aperture Gu recipe that Lang Ya blessed land had was intentionally due to his planning.

With Lang Ya land spirit's love for collecting recipes and refining Gu, he would definitely want to refine second aperture Gu!

"Now I have to wait for a good opportunity!" Old Man Yan Shi sneered at the side while sending out his divine sense to accept Lang Ya land spirit's offer and began their transaction at Treasure Yellow Heaven.

Divine travel Gu came out from the mirror, even if the connecting heaven Gu's ability had been amplified by many other Gu, it still caused the connecting heaven Gu to be filled with cracks, and after several breaths, completely collapsed.

Lang Ya land spirit did not care about this connecting heaven Gu, there were still many connecting heaven Gu left in the blessed land.

The land spirit looked at divine travel Gu with a burning gaze and laughed heartily: "I had already wanted to refine second aperture Gu, haha, this is really too good!"

He took out another connecting heaven Gu on the spot and connected to treasure yellow heaven, looking for Gu refinement materials without restraint.

"Hehehe, an easy pray!" Old Man Yan Shi laughed heartily as he looked at this scene through connecting heaven Gu.

A heavyweight transaction relating to Immortal Gu naturally would be noticed by many Gu Immortals.

Fang Yuan was also paying attention.

"Who bought the divine travel Gu?" Fang Yuan's gaze flashed and immediately asked Little Hu Immortal.

"It is Lang Ya old immortal." Little Hu Immortal replied with clear voice.

"Lang Ya land spirit... Just like what I expected." Fang Yuan slightly narrowed his eyes before concentrating on connecting heaven Gu again.

After a moment, he discovered Lang Ya land spirit wantonly buying Gu refinement materials; his eyes flashed with rays of cold light.

"Hmph, so many Gu Immortals are dumping precious Gu refinement materials to Lang Ya land spirit. This is clearly a trap. The land spirits have wisdom, but their obsessions are much deeper and can be easily exploited by Gu Immortals. Wait a second..."

Fang Yuan's thoughts suddenly shook.

The immortals selling the Gu refinement materials were metal path Gu Immortal Tie Jia Zi, soul path Gu Immortal Wang Gan Yang, wood path Gu Immortal Fairy Tan Xiang, enslavement path Gu Immortal Great Immortal Xue Xiong... These names were familiar.

'Weren't they the Gu Immortals who participated in the second wave of attacks against Lang Ya blessed land?'

For a moment, Fang Yuan's eyes flickered with sharp light, he became aware of an enormous scheme that had not been recorded in the history.

"So it was like this! In my past life, Lang Ya blessed land endured six waves of attack before finally collapsing in the seventh wave. So there were manipulators behind the scene, they were hatching a sinister plot."

Before, Fang Yuan was only an audience, but now that he was involved, he discovered this truth.

"This Old Man Yan Shi's purpose in selling divine travel Gu is not just to aim at me, his bigger target is Lang Ya blessed land. Out of the seven waves of attack, how many did he organize?"

"If he is southern border's Gu Immortal, then why would these northern plains Gu Immortals listen to his arrangements? Is he indirectly making use of them or did he give them a direct order?"

No doubt, the wisdom path Gu Immortal Old Man Yan Shi had organized a group of immortals; just this information created a formless pressure.

Fang Yuan did not know right now that this organization was the Shadow Sect he had heard before!

But this did not hinder him from guessing the strength and the mystery of this organization.

An organization that spanned across southern border and northern plains, how big would it be? But Fang Yuan had never heard of such an organization, even in the five hundred years of his past life. How mysterious was this organization?

"Of course, all these speculations are based on the foundation that Old Man Yan Shi is a Gu Immortal of Southern Border. Maybe it is all just a coincidence?"

"Let me think again, did Old Man Yan Shi plan the first wave of attack? As for the next waves of attack, did he have a hand in them? As for the seventh wave, it was Heavenly Court's move, that was absolutely not something Old Man Yan Shi could control."

Fang Yuan was certain of this.

Heavenly Court was high above others, it originated from central continent and had a formidable background, it was not something an immortal of Southern Border could interfere in.

Among the five great regions, since ancient times till now, the greatest Gu Immortal organization was only the Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court's might made people feel suffocation. Only rank eight and rank nine Gu Immortals could establish their presence there.

This point could be judged from the conclusion.

After the Heavenly Court made their move, they left after taking away all the recipes in Lang Ya blessed land.

"Where was Old Man Yan Shi at that time in my previous life?"

Old Man Yan Shi was a mysterious character who had hidden in the depths of the history! Behind him was a mysterious organization that had influence in both northern plains and southern border, two great regions.

"Wisdom path Gu Immortal, a mysterious organization, Heavenly Court... The path to immortality is truly fraught with danger at every step. When I burst through these obstacles, how great would I feel?"

The higher the difficulty and stronger the enemies, the more fighting spirit Fang Yuan would have.

The path he was walking on was destined to be a lonely one from the start, destined to make an enemy of the world. Heavenly Court and the mysterious organization were like two giant beasts blocking this path. At the same time, this dark path was filled with thorns, traps and schemes.

This was an incomparably difficult path.

And no one had been able to reach the end since ancient times.

Fang Yuan, however, was fighting by himself, marching by himself and waging war by himself.

The source of all his motivation was the simplest, most insatiable, most sneered at and most incomprehensible...

Dream.

A seemingly unrealistic dream about eternal life.

Whether he could succeed or not, Fang Yuan had never considered it.

He only knew that even if he failed and died, he would have no regrets.

Today, through a transaction, he discovered the whirlpool that had been hidden in the shadows. Then he looked at the prospects of his own path which was filled with incomparable darkness, incomparable danger and dead ends at almost every step.

"Since there is no path to walk on, I shall carve out my own path."

Fang Yuan smiled, his gaze containing a profound light and his disordered thoughts all tidied up as he once again concentrated on connecting heaven Gu.

It was time to buy relic Gu.

Chapter 469: Living Chess

Relic Gu can directly increase the foundation of the aperture, raising a Gu Master's cultivation realm.

From rank one two five, they were: green copper, red steel, white silver, yellow gold, and purple crystal relic Gu. Relic Gu were mortal Gu, there were no rank six and above Immortal Gu for it.

Among them, green copper, red steel, and white silver relic Gu were widely sold in the market. As for yellow gold and purple crystal relic Gu, because they affected the battle strength of rank four and five Gu Masters, and could influence the status of many forces, they were restricted and controlled by large organisations, and were hardly sold in the market.

But in treasure yellow heaven, yellow gold and purple crystal relic Gu were available.

Gu Immortals could not raise their cultivation through purple crystal relic Gu, but they were still very rare Gu.

Because not only could these two Gu be used to rank cultivation, they were used to refine Immortal Gu as well. In Immortal Gu recipes, they were often used as important catalysts.

Other than refinement, if a Gu Immortal had descendants, they would collect many relic Gu for their clans or juniors to use.

Thus in treasure yellow heaven, although rank one to three relic Gu were sold in batches, there were few rank four yellow gold relic Gu, and even fewer purple crystal relic Gu.

Yellow gold, purple crystal relic Gu, these were widely used in Immortal Gu recipes, when Fang Yuan refined the Spring Autumn Cicada, and the second aperture Gu, he used them in the process. In fact, even the Immortal Gu Blood Deity's remnant recipe also required large amounts of relic Gu.

But because Immortal Gu were involved, prices of relic Gu were always sky high. Even so, this situation was way better than the mortal realm's restrict control.

Fang Yuan immediately bought three purple crystal relic Gu, and spent a great sum to buy an immediate success Gu.

This Gu was much more expensive than purple crystal relic Gu, because it could raise the success rate of Gu refinement.

Thereafter, Fang Yuan bought a large number of low rank Gu and refinement materials, preparing to refine rank five breath concealment Gu and others.

Although treasure yellow heaven could inspect the treasure light, just the height of the light could not detect whether the Gu worm had been tampered with. Thus, it is not very safe, and Fang Yuan decided to refine the Gu himself to be safe.

Selling all the remnant recipes in his hand and buying large amounts of resources, after deducting treasure yellow heaven's processing fee, Fang Yuan had twenty-eight pieces of immortal essence stones left in his possession.

Of course, he could repeatedly sell these Immortal Gu remnant recipes, but their corresponding treasure light would decrease, only after an amount of time would the treasure light recover.

Transactions in treasure yellow heaven heavily depended on the treasure light. The stronger the light, the higher the price. When the treasure light weakened, the sale price would fall as well.

After all, the value of remnant recipes drop when more people know about them. If he continued to sell them, Fang Yuan's earning will decrease, and the Gu Immortals who bought them earlier would feel that they suffered a loss. Waiting for a period of time before selling it again benefited both parties.

The seller sells at the original price, while buyers gain a lot of precious time to research on the recipe, after all, Immortal Gu were unique once they were created.

"This way, the most precious recipes I have left are Spring Autumn Cicada, second aperture Gu, and the remnant recipe of Blood Deity. As for the other recipes, I can sell them again, but only in a few months."

This time obviously referred to the five regions' time.

As for the other recipes like using divine travel Gu to refine fixed immortal travel Gu were known by all. There would be no light if it was placed into treasure yellow heaven.

"Rockmen, I have to provide them to Immortal Crane Sect, this is to make sure Immortal Crane Sect does not find out the truth, so that I can relieve our tensions and stall for time."

Now that Dang Hun mountain was dying, the production of guts Gu were decreasing. The number of rockmen in each transaction had been dropping, as Immortal Crane Sect's patience was running thin. They would fight eventually, but Fang Yuan had to stall for as much time as he could.

"But thankfully, they would only think that I was defending Hu Immortal blessed land from the inside, and was a trapped fish. They would never expect me to have gone to northern plains, and was even able to return. Even that Old Man Yan Shi would not see this coming."

Wisdom path Gu Immortals were skilled at deductions and predictions, but they could not gain information out of nothing. They had to use all sorts of clues and traces, to track back to the source and make their deductions.

Fang Yuan's vital Gu was Spring Autumn Cicada, his greatest advantage was rebirth. With five hundred years of memories, he had stargate Gu, moving perspective cup Gu, all these were Gu worms that were more advanced than the current five regions by a generation.

"I can't sell remnant recipes for the time being, and the rockmen have to be supplied to Immortal Crane Sect, but I have other things to sell!"

Fang Yuan had a plan long ago, this item was none other than soil.

The soil in treasure yellow heaven were all rare goods, like cloud soil, rotten soil, salt soil etc. Many blessed land produced soil, and they would sell it inside treasure yellow heaven to exchange for what they needed with other Gu Masters.

The soil Fang Yuan wanted to sell was not ordinary either, it was the gruel mud.

Back then, when the earthly calamity struck and Dang Hun mountain was damaged, polluted by the ability of Immortal Gu Gruel Mud, the entire mountain started to turn into rotten mud.

But in this world, fortune and misfortune came together.

Although Dang Hun mountain rocks were turned into mud, they contained the gruel mud Immortal Gu's power, in Gu Immortals' eyes, this was a must-have ingredient when refining the gruel mud Immortal Gu!

As expected, after Fang Yuan placed it into treasure yellow heaven, a large amount of attention was garnered.

"What day is it today, so many good things are on sale?"

"Gruel mud, this is the real gruel mud, I can feel the intense Immortal Gu aura from it."

"It is a pity I do not have the gruel mud Immortal Gu's recipe, I have no use for this mud..."

The divine senses of the Gu Immortals were moving about as many sent their divine senses to compete for the item.

"I need the gruel mud Immortal Gu's recipe, I will not exchange it for anything else." Under Fang Yuan's orders, little Hu Immortal sent her divine sense over.

This strict request caused the Gu Immortals to scoff.

"Using a pile of mud to exchange for an Immortal Gu's recipe? You are way too greedy."

"The gruel mud Immortal Gu is a one-time consumable Gu, the recipe is evidently more important than Gu worm itself, you have the face to say you want to exchange it for the recipe?"

"This is too unrealistic, I advice you to change your condition, otherwise, this pile of mud will stay in treasure yellow heaven without a buyer forever."

But little Hu Immortal quickly said: "I am not requesting for the complete Immortal recipe, whoever has the remnant recipe with the highest treasure light will get this."

The Gu Immortals stopped talking, starting to observe this.

Soon, a Gu Immortal took out a remnant recipe and the treasure light was about four meters.

This was not up to Fang Yuan's standards, he stared at the mirror and laughed, instructing little Hu Immortal: "As long as the other Gu Immortals each took out a remnant recipe, we will add one jin of gruel mud."

"Yes master!" Little Hu Immortal replied quickly.

In Hu Immortal blessed land, there was a lot of gruel mud.

From start to end, all the gruel mud were cleared out of Dang Hun mountain by little Hu Immortal, but they did not throw it out of the blessed land, instead transferring it to the west area.

After these years, through the conversion of the gruel mud inside the blessed land, there was a swamp forming slowly.

The former disaster was now a resource.

In treasure yellow heaven, the Gu Immortals' divine senses were in a commotion.

With the addition of every remnant recipe, little Hu Immortal would add a jin of gruel mud. Such an act was telling others clearly — we have a ton of it here!

All the remnant recipes were added in one by one, as the treasure light intensified. From the four meters, it had already rose to about six meters and was still increasing.

Fang Yuan looked for a while and his smile became wider.

His soul was from Earth, his marketing skills far surpassed this world. On Earth, enterprises boomed while in treasure yellow heaven, immortal essence stones could barely be used as the currency of trade, most transactions were done using the primitive bartering method.

Fang Yuan's method was a form of increasing his exposure, it attracted many Gu Immortals to sell the remnant recipe of the gruel mud Immortal Gu.

Of course, this was only a tiny trick.

Next, Fang Yuan instructed little Hu Immortal to handle the other matters one by one.

"It is about time, I have to go now."

Fang Yuan was counting the time, dividing the time he spent in Hu Immortal blessed land by five, was the amount of time that had passed in northern plains.

"Master, goodbye, you have to come back often okay." Little Hu Immortal brought Fang Yuan to the west area of the blessed land, and under the radiance of the starlight firefly Gu, it activated the stargate Gu once again.

Fang Yuan was carrying many refinement materials, as well as low rank Gu worms as he stepped into the stargate.

Not long after, he stepped out of the other stargate, back to the crescent lake in northern plains.

As he had calculated, it was currently near dawn, as the sun was rising, the first ray of sunlight shining on the land.

The light breeze caused small ripples along the surface of the lake.

The air was refreshing, there was dew on the grass near him, and there were bird groups gathering on the surface of the lake, spreading their wings like they were dancing.

Fang Yuan breathed in deeply, his heart was overjoyed.

Snatching Ma Hong Yun's fortune by force, Fang Yuan obtained Lang Ya land spirit's help this time. In Lang Ya blessed land, he used one of the chances to obtain the stargate Gu and others.

After that, he returned to Hu Immortal blessed land and used connecting heaven Gu to settle the problem of the lack of resources.

"But after this, all my stagnating chess pieces have room for further development. The entire chessboard is alive once more."

As the sky turned bright, Fang Yuan returned to Ge tribe camp under the wolf group's accompaniment.

"I am going to refine Gu in closed cultivation, nobody is to disturb me." He gave his orders as he locked himself inside the lizard house, starting his Gu refinement.

Regardless of where the Gu refinement materials came from, the Gu worms created belonged to the region it is born in. That is to say, although the materials in Fang Yuan's hands came from central continent, as long as he refined them inside northern plains, all of them will be northern plains Gu, and would not be suppressed here.

The first Gu he was going to refine was the moving perspective cup Gu.

Moving perspective cup Gu was rank five, the set that was refined in Hu Immortal blessed land was about to break, it could only be used one more time. After visiting treasure yellow heaven, Fang Yuan had the resources now, he was obviously going to refine another set of moving perspective cup Gu.

At the same time, in crescent lake.

Yan tribe's nine Gu Masters were travelling quickly on their hump wolves.

"Stop, there are wolf footprints here!" Yan tribe leader stopped his wolf, looking at the large number of footprints in front of him, he expressed great shock.

"So many wolves, this is a myriad wolf group..." The other Gu Masters exclaimed.

"Ge tribe camp is not too far away, do you think this myriad wolf group is heading towards them?"

"Not good! Look at these footprints, there are poison beard wolves, wind wolves, as well as turtleback wolves and night wolves and so on."

"Wild wolf groups only live among themselves, a mix of so many wolves only means that they are being controlled by a Gu Master!"

Yan tribe leader pondered: "Ge tribe was once a large size tribe, but now that they were forced to migrate, they are no longer as great as before, they have no way of feeding such a huge wolf group. Most likely, this wolf group belongs to a demonic Gu Master, our objective this time is to seek reinforcements from Ge tribe, let's go see what happens first. If Ge tribe faces trouble, we will retreat quietly. If we can do them a cheap favor, we will help them encircle the wolves."

"Yes lord tribe leader!" Everyone shouted.

"Go, let's go to Ge tribe."

The hump wolves moved again, bringing these people towards Ge tribe camp.

Chapter 470: Water Demon

"Halt!" The patrolling Ge tribe Gu Master saw the Yan tribe Gu Masters and shouted.

Yan tribe Gu Masters stopped their hump wolves, as an elder spoke: "The person beside me is Yan tribe leader Lord Yan Tian Ji, we are here to visit Ge tribe leader."

"Yan tribe?" Ge tribe Gu Master's expression changed.

"That's right, our main tent is about a hundred li away."

"Please wait here lords."

According to northern plains time, Ge tribe had just reached crescent lake and had set up camp for just a day. Ge tribe camp was still busy constructing their homes.

"Lord, the wolf group footprints all entered Ge tribe camp." A tribe elder said softly at Yan tribe leader Yan Tian Ji.

Yan Tian Ji nodded, his gaze turning firm: "To think this enslavement path Gu master is from Ge tribe. It seems we came to the right place, this is a strong aid in dealing with Water Demon Hao Ji Liu."

"But Ge tribe might not necessary help us." A tribe elder was worried.

Yan Tian Ji sneered, acting as if he had Ge tribe dancing in the palm of his hands: "Hmph, Ge tribe wants to attend the heroes assembly. My daughter is Liu Wen Wu's fiancée, if I use Liu tribe's name to ask for reinforcements, can this tiny Ge tribe refuse?"

Saying so, the newly constructed camp gates opened, as Ge tribe's new leader Ge Guang came out with the band of elders.

"Yan tribe leader has come personally, it is our honor. Please follow me to the main tent." Ge Guang invited him enthusiastically.

"Why is he only a rank three Gu Master?" Sensing Ge Guang's cultivation, the Yan tribesmen showed contempt.

Bringing the Yan tribesmen into the camp for a banquet, after they had some wine, Yan tribe leader gazed at his elder.

The elder quickly said: "To speak the truth, Ge tribe leader, we are here today to ask for help from your tribe."

"Help?"

The elder continued: "That's right. Our tribe's big missy Yan Cui Er was kidnapped by Hao Ji Liu, this person is unscrupulous and shameless, hiding in crescent lake and extorting our tribe. He is a water path Gu Master, he has great battle strength when fighting underwater, our tribe's few attempts at saving her failed. This time, we would like to ask for Ge tribe's help."

"Hao Ji Liu? You mean, that Water Demon Hao Ji Liu?" Ge Guang thought of this person and his expression changed.

This person was a rank four upper stage Gu Master, he walked the water path and his vile name was famous in northern plains, he was a devious and scheming demon.

Ge Guang frowned deeply, after thinking about it, he rejected: "Members of the demonic faction deserves to be brought to justice. As a member of the righteous faction, Ge tribe should help out, but right now, we do not have the ability to do so. My father had died in battle, I was tasked to be the tribe leader immediately after. We have already suffered great losses, we have no strength left to exterminate the Water Demon."

"Why? Ge tribe leader is unwilling to help?" Hearing Ge Guang's words, Yan tribe elders' expressions sank.

An elder sneered: "Ge tribe leader, you are too young, you do not know certain things, let me tell you. Our tribe's big missy Yan Cui Er had been engaged to Liu Wen Wu, her status is Liu Wen Wu's fiancée. If you do not help us save her, when Liu tribe pursues the matter, you will not be able to explain yourselves."

Ge Guang's expression changed.

There were a few super tribes in northern plains, among them were Hei tribe and Liu tribe.

Liu tribe's third young master Liu Wen Wu, was an expert in both the brush and sword, he had outstanding talent and high aspirations. This time, he brought his supporters from his tribe and separated from Liu tribe, trying to create his own tribe from scratch, he was one of the few most famous competitors for the throne of the imperial court.

Liu Wen Wu had a huge force, Yan Cui Er was his fiancée, if Ge tribe did not save her, Liu Wen Wu would definitely find trouble with them during the heroes assembly.

But now Ge tribe was in dire straits themselves, they had just lost a lot of high rank Gu Masters. If they fought the Water Demon, they would have to shoulder a great loss.

Ge Guang thought about his tribe's benefits and did not wish to make enemies with the Water Demon for no reason, but if they did nothing, it might attract Liu Wen Wu's animosity.

Ge Guang was very troubled.

Yan tribe leader saw Ge Guang's hesitation and laughed: "The righteous path had always stuck together, I believe that Ge tribe would not leave us in the lurch. Ge tribe has outstanding strength, you do not need to conceal it. When we came, we found a large number of wolf footprints, as long as Ge tribe mobilizes your enslavement path Gu Master, we are willing to pay three thousand primeval stones in advance."

Ge Guang was secretly furious.

Just three thousand primeval stones, were they giving loose change to a beggar?

He controlled his anger and laughed bitterly: "You might not know, this enslavement path Gu Master is not a member of Ge tribe, I cannot command him. He is Lord Chang Shan Yin."

"Chang Shan Yin?" Yan tribe leader was stunned, thinking that this name was very familiar.

Ge Guang then told him what he knew about Fang Yuan's origins and identity.

Yan tribe's gang were overjoyed at hearing the news.

"Chang Shan Yin, he is alive!"

"I remember now, he is someone from my generation. He was once famous throughout northern plains, a highly acclaimed genius enslavement path Gu Master."

"This is great! Even heaven is helping us, Chang tribe had already submitted to young master Liu Wen Wu, if we tell Chang Shan Yin our request, he will definitely help."

Yan tribe leader was candid: "Tribe leader Ge Guang, lead the way."

Ge Guang laughed bitterly: "If I can bring you to him, I would have done it long ago. Lord Chang Shan Yin returned this morning and announced he was going into closed cultivation to refine Gu, if we interrupt him, I'm afraid..."

"What are you afraid of?" Yan tribe leader stood up: "Chang Shan Yin is from the same generation as me, I've heard of him long ago. Chang tribe and Yan tribe are already under young master Liu Wen Wu, we are on the same side. Young master Liu Wen Wu is Chang Shan Yin's master. Furthermore, this matter is so important, it is no big deal even if we interrupt his Gu refinement. Bring me there."

"This..." Ge Guang hesitated.

Yan tribe leader's expression turned stiff: "Ge tribe leader, do not stall for time. If we are too late and my daughter faces mortal danger, when young master Liu Wen Wu blames you..."

Ge Guang gritted his teeth, conceding: "Alright, I will bring you there."

　　...

"Water Demon Hao Ji Liu?" Fang Yuan raised his eyebrows, looking at these Yan tribe Gu Masters.

"Brother Chang, you have been asleep for twenty years, you might not know this. This Water Demon was a rising star from the younger generation, after receiving a mysterious opportunity, he is already rank four upper stage at thirty-five years old." Yan tribe leader explained.

Fang Yuan nodded, exclaiming: "Northern plains is huge, there are countless heroes and conquerors! Since Yan tribe is asking with their life on the line, I shall make this trip."

The expression of Yan tribe's gang changed.

What was Chang Shan Yin saying! What 'life on the life', it sounded like they were very feeble and defenseless.

"Lord Chang Shan Yin, why are you lauding the spirit of the enemy and belittling that of our own? That Water Demon is scheming, hiding inside crescent lake while holding our big missy hostage, that is why we cannot take him down." An elder was indignant.

"Lord Chang Shan Yin, your Chang tribe has already submitted to young master Liu Wen Wu. This is your opportunity." Another elder spoke as if he was thinking for Fang Yuan's benefit.

Yan tribe leader smiled lightly: "Hehehe, brother Chang, with your help this time, what can a mere Water Demon amount to?"

Fang Yuan snickered: "By logic or emotion, I should help out. I will battle alongside all of you."

Yan tribe was overjoyed: "Good, let us set off now."

　　...

"Yan tribe's old man, I want ten million primeval stones and that backwater battle Gu, did you bring them?" Water Demon stood at the edge of crescent lake as he looked at the people with caution.

"Of course I brought it. Where is my daughter?" Yan Tian Ji said, taking out two Gu, one was a rank five storage Gu, the other was backwater battle Gu.

Backwater battle Gu was a rank five Gu, it could greatly boost the power of water path Gu worms, it was very precious with no market supply.

Seeing these two Gu, Water Demon's gaze became heated.

He had a young appearance, his face was pale as he had broad shoulders and a thin waist, he was handsome and had a carefree disposition. His sideburns were already turning white, giving him a mature aura.

"Return my daughter and I will pass you what you want. Now I want to see my daughter first." Yan Tian Ji said solemnly.

Water Demon snorted, snapping his fingers.

Swoosh!

In the lake water behind him, waves started moving as a giant fanshell appeared from under the water.

This fanshell was as big as an elephant, the surface was shiny. As the two sides of the shell opened, a young girl could be seen inside.

The young girl was tied up tightly, her mouth was gagged. When she saw Yan tribe leader she was so agitated that tears were flowing on her face as she struggled.

Water Demon snorted: "You've seen your daughter, now hand over the Gu. Don't try anything funny, your daughter is in my hands, if anything happens to her, how will you account to Liu Wen Wu? Hehehe..."

Damn it!"

"Despicable scum, fight me fair and square if you have the guts!"

Yan tribe elders gritted their teeth.

Yan tribe leader's expression was calm as water as he tossed two Gu towards Water Demon.

Water Demon received it carefully, he did not use his hand to grab it, but instead let the two Gu fall onto the ground.

"You did not do anything fishy to these Gu worms right?" Water Demon squinted, looking at Yan Tian Ji sharply.

Yan Tian Ji's expression was livid: "Hmph, go ahead and refine it."

Water Demon snickered: "Step back by thirty steps."

Yan tribe's gang had no choice but to comply.

Water Demon stared at the Yan tribe Gu Masters, before squatting down and picking up the two Gu worms.

He first inspected them and found no problems with them. Next, he carefully started refining the backwater battle Gu.

Backwater battle Gu had Yan Tian Ji's will, as he cooperated with Water Demon, it allowed him to refine the backwater battle Gu easily.

Water Demon chuckled: "Very good, Yan Tian Ji, you are very tactful. Next, I will inspect the primeval stones, if the amount of correct, I will return your precious daughter to you. Don't worry, I do not wish to be enemies with Liu Wen Wu, your daughter is still a virgin, I did not even touch her hands."

"Hmph!" Yan Tian Ji snorted, not saying a word.

He willed and aided Water Demon in refining the storage Gu.

Water Demon's mind entered the Gu as he saw a large amount of primeval stones, unable to control his joy as it showed on his face.

But at this time, from among these primeval stones, a Gu flew out and crashed onto him at breakneck speed.

Rank four — immobilization Gu!

"Strike!" Yan Tian Ji shouted, and the elders surrounded Water Demon quickly.

"Oh no!!" Water Demon was grabbing the storage Gu, as he was unable to move, he watched himself get surrounded helplessly.

"Water Demon, today will be your death date." Fang Yuan rode the hump wolf as he and a large group of wolves emerged from a nearby woodland.

Chapter 471: Wolf King, are you crazy?!

"Kill!" Yan Tian Ji shouted.

In an instant, Yan tribe's Gu Masters starting attacking, using an assortment of moves.

Water flow, starfire, white bone, firebird, all sorts of attacks were unleashed and targeted Water Demon.

Bright rainbow color lights soon shone on Water Demon's face.

These attacks were eye-catching and dazzling, they were like fireworks in the night sky, beautiful and lethal.

Water Demon was in a dangerous situation, but he did not dodge or evade, instead he showed a cold smile.

In his eyes, a piercing eerie light burst out, the light was shining brightly as it stunned a Yan tribe elder in front of Water Demon.

This Yan tribe elder grimaced as he felt his vision blurring.

This was Water Demon, activating the rank three sight blow Gu, his gaze had a strong attack and could bypass defensive measures, directly attacking the Gu Master's soul.

Yan tribe elder who was attacked took three steps back, trying to regain his composure.

A mere rank three sight blow Gu could only be used as a surprise attack, it caused little damage to Yan tribe elder, it could not change this dangerous situation around for Water Demon.

But Water Demon's lips curled into a cold smile.

He activated his rank four yellow gold primeval essence, injecting it into one of the Gu in his aperture.

Rank four — Location Swap Gu!

Swoosh!

With a light sound, Water Demon Hao Ji Liu's body vanished, and reappeared at Yan tribe elder's location. As an exchange, the Yan tribe elder who was attacked appeared at his original location.

"Oh no!"

"Oh no, quickly stop!"

Yan tribe's Gu Masters shouted, such a change caught them off guard, they were greatly shocked.

They wanted to hold back on their attacks, but the attacks were already formed, they could not be stopped.

That Yan tribe elder was scared out of his wits, he frantically activated his defensive Gu, but this Gu only lasted for half a breath's time before dying.

"Academy elder!" Yan tribe leader Yan Tian Ji shouted, seeing his tribesmen dying in front of him, engulfed by the assortment of attacks, beaten to a pulp.

"Hahaha, great, great. It seems that Yan tribe Gu Masters are all dumb pigs, you actually killed yourselves. Hahaha..." Water Demon Hao Ji Liu laughed as he raised his head, saying in a mocking tone.

"Water Demon, Yan tribe will be enemies with you for all eternity!"

"Hao Ji Liu, I will tear your tendons apart to relieve this anger in me."

"Kill, tear this demon to shreds!"

Yan tribe Gu Masters shouted angrily, their necks turning red from agitation.

But even though they shouted loudly, none of them attacked.

Water Demon had a rank four location swap Gu, this was beyond their expectations.

Rank four location swap Gu was a unique movement Gu. One had to make contact with the other party in order to swap locations. But the use of the Gu worm not only depended on suitability, but also its compatibility with other Gu worms.

Water Demon Hao Ji Liu used the rank three sight blow Gu together with the location swap Gu. As long as his gaze attack works, it means he made contact with the other party, and he could use the location swap Gu using this exploit.

Hao Ji Liu had such a Gu worm, he was not afraid of fighting a crowd. This was why he dared to challenge the entire Yan tribe higher-ups, kidnapping Yan tribe's big missy Yan Cui Er, and extorting Yan tribe.

Although there were many Yan tribe Gu Masters, the academy elder just died in front of them, everyone was lost and did not have any confidence at the moment.

"Water Demon, so what if you have location swap Gu? This Gu causes intense primeval essence expenditure. How many times can you still use it? I'll tell you, we invited the righteous hero Wolf King Chang Shan Yin who had just returned, you are now surrounded by the wolf group, there is nowhere to run." At the crucial moment, Yan Tian Ji stood up, his words were like a tranquilizer that stabilized the people.

"Wolf King Chang Shan Yin?" Hao Ji Liu's gaze concentrated on Fang Yuan who was sitting on his wolf.

Fang Yuan had a broad shoulder and thin waist, his gaze was sharp and divine. He rode the hump wolf as he was surrounded by wolves, like he was standing at the top of a mountain, although he was silent, he gave Hao Ji Liu a strong sense of pressure.

"Wolf King Chang Shan Yin, I have heard of your name since I was young. You are not dead?" Water Demon Hao Ji Liu concentrated on guarding against the Yan tribe Gu Masters as he tried probing Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was a little more than three hundred steps away from Water Demon, he observed him from far away with a plain expression.

Water Demon's heart shook, although the sight blow Gu had a wide attack range and could attack anyone who could be seen with his eyes, the further the distance, the weaker the attack would be. A distance of three hundred steps was the limit of the sight blow Gu, and it had zero threat once the target was further than three hundred steps away.

Fang Yuan's location made Water Demon very uncomfortable.

This was a very peculiar distance, if Water Demon moved a step out, he could hit Fang Yuan, but it felt like Fang Yuan was trying to trick him into doing so.

Hao Ji Liu's heart felt greater pressure: "If this person really is Chang Shan Yin, I cannot use the sight blow Gu to attack him. Sight based attacks compete the souls of both Gu Masters, as an enslavement path Gu Master, his soul is definitely extremely strong."

"Are you really Chang Shan Yin? What evidence do you have? Hmph, your Yan tribe randomly brought one person to impersonate the Wolf King, do you think I am a fool?" Hao Ji Liu purposely snorted.

Yan Tian Ji laughed coldly: "Water Demon, you really failed to recognise Mount Tai. Is the Wolf King so easy to impersonate? When we battle later, you will feel the Wolf King's true power!"

"Lord Chang Shan Yin, it is up to you."

"Kill this Water Demon, get rid of a great threat to the people!"

The other Yan tribe elders shouted, trying to make Fang Yuan fight for them.

Fang Yuan sat on the wolf back, looking around. When he saw that his wolf group was at their planned location, and encircled this battlefield completely, he knew the time was ripe.

His lips curled, revealing a cold and callous smile.

He nodded slightly, the killing intent surging in his eyes: "Indeed, you reminded me, it is time to strike."

As he said that, the wolves howled as they opened their bloodthirsty mouths, flashing their sharp claws and teeth as they charged relentlessly.

In an instant, ten thousand wolves attacked and starting killing the Gu Masters.

The grand army caused everyone's expressions to change.

"Chang Shan Yin, what are you doing? How can you attack us?" Yan Tian Ji shouted furiously, while feeling shocked and suspicious.

"Quickly stop! We are on the same side."

"Wolf King, are you crazy? You dare to attack us? Our Yan tribe and your Chang tribe had already submitted to young master Liu Wen Wu!"

The other elders blocked the wolves as they shouted frantically.

"That is exactly why I am dealing with you all. Go in peace, I will send the Chang tribesmen to accompany you soon enough." Fang Yuan said hatefully, his face distorting into a maniacal expression.

Soon after, he shouted: "Hmph, I swore long ago, I will take revenge for what happened back then one by one!"

"Back then, when Chang Shan Yin fought Ha Tu Gu and the bandits alone, Chang tribe did not send a single person to help him, there were hidden reasons after all!" Water Demon Hao Ji Liu felt his heart jump as he thought of something.

He did not expect such a huge change, he dodged the wolves' attacks as he shouted anxiously: "Wolf King, I do not wish to be your enemy. The enemy of an enemy is a friend right?"

Fang Yuan gave him a cold glance, saying lightly: "Look at you jumping all over the place, you are simply like a flea, just die together with them."

Chapter 472: Power of the Enslavement Path!

"What?" Water Demon Hao Ji Liu was furious.

Ever since he started travelling the world, no one had dared to make such remarks about him or showed such contempt.

"Wolf King, you are too arrogant! Today, I shall make you pay the price for it!!" Water Demon Hao Ji Liu roared furiously and pushed forward with his palms.

Rank four — waterfall Gu!

His primeval essence poured crazily into the Gu, causing water vapor to fill the air, then with a rumbling sound, an enormous water stream appeared out of nowhere.

The water stream was incomparably fast, just like a waterfall crashing down from a high altitude.

The light silver rapid stream brought with it an intense chilly might as it fiercely struck the wolf group.

In an instant, over a thousand wolves died or were injured. The rapid stream spread far away, thoroughly clearing the area around Hao Ji Liu.

At the same time, Yan tribe's Gu Masters jointly activated a Gu worm.

This was a rank five wind barrier Gu; and when activated, it formed an enormous wind. The wind was silky, and brought with it some green threads as it surrounded everyone.

The wolf group's assault was all blocked by the formless wind. The wild Gu on many wolf kings attacked the wind barrier, but it was like a pebble falling into a sea as the attacks vanished without trace.

"How can this be?" On crescent lake, Yan Cui Er who was taken as a hostage looked at the intense battle on the lakeside with a dumbfounded look.

She had never expected the situation would develop in such a way. She, who had been the main reason of the fight previously, was now a spectator instead.

Hump wolves retreated, pulling distance from Fang Yuan and Water Demon Hao Ji Liu.

"Idiots." Fang Yuan sneered as he looked at Water Demon Hao Ji Liu charging over, approaching closer, and Yan tribesmen who were in a defensive formation.

Water Demon Hao Ji Liu and Yan tribe leader Yan Tian Ji were two rank four Gu Masters. Moreover, there were also Yan tribe's higher-ups; a dozen or so rank three Gu Masters, their strength could be said to be truly formidable.

However, an enslavement path Gu Master's strength was the ability to fight an army alone!

Back then, Chang Shan Yin led his wolf group and battled higher realm experts, not only killing rank five Gu Master Ha Tu Gu, but even exterminating Ha Tu Gu's group of valiant generals.

How?

Because he was an enslavement path Gu Master.

At present, the wolf group with Fang Yuan had already taken shape to form a decent size. The wolf group's scale had reached thirty thousand and above; not only did it contain hundred wolf kings and some thousand wolf kings, there was also a night wolf myriad beast king and a young mutated beast white-eyes wolf.

This scale might not even be half the size of the wolf group Chang Shan Yin had at his peak period, but it was already enough to annihilate two to three Ge tribes!

And right now, Fang Yuan only had to deal with just twenty or so Gu Masters, it was like using an ox cleaver to kill a chicken.

Sure enough, after some time, Water Demon Hao Ji Liu was gasping and his momentum gradually stopped.

He felt exhausted!

"Damn it! Such troublesome wolf manipulation skills, there are only some hundred wolf kings and thousand wolf kings..." Water Demon Hao Ji Liu's gaze towards Fang Yuan had already changed right now.

It was not that he had not fought enslavement path Gu Masters, but how could those enslavement path Gu Masters he had fought before compare to Fang Yuan?

"Is this the Wolf King's wolf manipulation skills... being in it is like falling into a deep swamp, you sink deeper and deeper!" Water Demon Hao Ji Liu's heart turned cold as he kept on warding off the wolf group's assault.

He divided a bit of concentration to look into his aperture and grumbled.

That intense charge and the activation of many powerful abilities to clear the path had caused his primeval essence to be expended intensely, now there was less than half his total primeval essence left.

Once the primeval essence was at the point of exhaustion, a Gu Master's battle strength would start plummeting to the abyss.

Hao Ji Liu had no choice but to exercise restraint once he considered this to be a long battle. Like this, his momentum thoroughly disappeared and he was firmly surrounded by the wolf group.

"Water Demon Hao Ji Liu, a rank four Gu Master who uses water path Gu worms, has great offense and is an expert at fighting one against many. He roamed all over northern plains since his early years and has committed many crimes, gaining a bad reputation... After capturing Yan Cui Er and successfully extorting Yan tribe, he then went on to participate in the heroes assembly, offering Yan Cui Er to Hei Lou Lan. Hei Lou Lan was joyous and gave him great status. After entering Wang Ting blessed land and making great merits, Hao Ji Liu became Hei Lou Lan's number three general."

Fang Yuan recalled the relevant memories, his gaze flickering faintly.

In his past life, this Hao Ji Liu was also able to make a name for himself and after living actively for eighty-nine years, he was killed by Chang Shan Yin.

"Great offense usually means a huge consumption of primeval essence. Hao Ji Liu is nothing to worry about anymore, and right now, he should be secretly making an escape path for himself. He is good at escaping in water, it will not be easy to make him stay today. After all, there are not many water wolves with me. But my main target is not him, but Yan tribe's Gu Masters."

Fang Yuan turned his gaze towards the Yan tribesmen.

Yan tribe's Gu Masters were experts in defense and were famous for it in northern plains. These Gu Masters sure enough defended extremely well, their rank five wind barrier Gu was simply like a tortoise shell, firmly protecting everyone within it.

"Hmph, these Yan tribesmen are really naive, they still have the intention to protect their energy and watch from the sidelines when they are trapped. No wonder, history said Yan Tian Ji was extremely conservative, lacking initiative. Even though they want to stall for time, this is also exactly what I want." Fang Yuan sneered inwardly and intentionally slowed down the wolf group's offense.

As time passed, Hao Ji Liu and the Yan tribesmen's primeval essence were also being depleted.

Suddenly, a large group of shadows emerged from the woods.

"Lord Chang Shan Yin, we have arrived!" Ge tribe's current tribe leader Ge Guang arrived with Ge tribe's Gu Masters behind him.

"You came quite fast." Fang Yuan indifferently glanced at him with a profound meaning.

Ge Guang seemed to be pierced by the profound light in Fang Yuan's eyes as he unconsciously lowered his head and thought with reverence: 'This is the true heroic nature of the Wolf King, I didn't think I would see it today!'

"Yes, after receiving lord's letter, we immediately hurried over. People need to repay favors; lord, you have helped our Ge tribe time and again, lord's hatred is our Ge tribe's hatred too." Ge Guang immediately answered.

It would not have been good for Fang Yuan to make a move at Ge tribe camp, thus, he agreed to Yan tribe on the surface. After gathering all the wolves, he used a Gu worm to send a letter when they were halfway to the lake.

When Ge Guang received the letter and read it, his face was immediately filled with shock and horror.

"Lord Chang Shan Yin wants to attack the whole Yan tribe?" He could not help but cry out on the spot.

Stabilizing his emotions, he continued reading and saw Fang Yuan's reason for it.

It turned out that back then, Chang Shan Yin's mother had been secretly poisoned and Chang Shan Yin entered deep into poison grassland to search for the Gu worm that could detoxify the poison. On his way, he was ambushed by Ha Tu Gu and his group of experts. The whole matter was a sinister plot, it was due to internal conflict in Chang tribe and a move to suppress Chang Shan Yin.

In Fang Yuan's past life, after Chang Shan Yin was saved by Ma Hong Yun, he did not return to his tribe but instead joined Ma Hong Yun; it was also because of this reason. Later, after Chang Shan Yin helped Ma Hong Yun ascend to the position of Lord of the Imperial Court, he targeted Chang tribe, getting rid of all the Chang tribe higher-ups. He then became Chang tribe leader and took revenge for what happened back then.

Now, Fang Yuan was using this reason to deal with Yan tribe and persuade Ge Guang.

Ge tribe originally had ties of friendship with Chang tribe. When old Ge tribe leader had first met Fang Yuan, he had said that his second daughter was married in Chang tribe.

But after Ge Guang read the letter, he immediately made a decision to stand with Fang Yuan.

"Ge Guang, you have matured, Ge tribe will prosper under your rule." Fang Yuan lightly commented while sitting on a wolf, then waved his hand, "You don't need to move in this battle. It will be enough for you guys to make a tight encirclement. Remember that every Yan tribe elder that we block means a higher chance of success when we attack Yan tribe camp."

"Yes, junior shall listen to Wolf King's instruction!" Ge Guang agreed and brought the group of Gu Masters to outside the battlefield, forming an encirclement formation.

Seeing Ge tribe Gu Masters coming over to reinforce Fang Yuan, Yan tribe Gu Masters were shocked and furious.

"Ge Guang, you despicable, shameless scoundrel!" A Yan tribe elder shouted furiously.

"Ge tribe, you have made a wrong decision. Making our Yan tribe your enemy means you are going against young master Liu Wen Wu. None of you will have a good end!" Another elder cursed.

Ge Guang sneered, his heart filled with disdain.

Bringing out Liu tribe's name when their death was imminent, was there any use?

"We cannot wait any longer, we need to charge and break through!" Yan tribe elders realized the severity of the situation as they shouted with ashen expressions.

"Go!"

Yan tribesmen charged together, attempting to carve out a blood path.

Pill fire Gu, gold silkworm Gu, frost breath Gu, snowball Gu, tornado Gu, thunderclap Gu, fire claw Gu and other Gu were activated one after another. Fire and snow continually shot out, golden silkworm turned into a light ray and charged, blue frost breath was breathed out, tornado caused havoc, thunder rumbled in all directions, flames formed into claws and attacked...

Under this fierce assault from Yan tribe's Gu Masters, Fang Yuan's wolf group suffered heavy injuries, but they moved forward unceasingly, coming waves after waves disregarding their death.

"These Gu Masters might be experts among mortals, formed from rank three and rank four, but so what?" Fang Yuan maneuvered the wolf group while sitting on a wolf.

He had wolfman soul which made it a lot easier for him to maneuver these wolf group than when he had hundred man soul. It was as smooth as a wolf king personally commandeering them.

Fang Yuan's expression did not change at the sight of the wolves dying like flies, he remained aloof and indifferent.

These wolves were only ordinary wild beasts, if they died, then so be it, there was no heartache over it.

Instead, using them as cannon fodder to wear down these Gu Masters' primeval essence would be a great beneficial deal.

The weakness of these Yan tribe Gu Masters was their low numbers. Although they were experts, they lacked subordinates to share the pressure of the battlefield.

The battle was already in Fang Yuan's control and was moving in his intended direction; they simply did not have time to calm down and recover their primeval essence.

"Terrifying, there is actually such a fearsome wolf manipulation skill in this world!" A Yan tribe's elder said with ashen face.

"Could it be that we are going to die like this?" The aura of death was already pouncing upon them.

"Chang Shan Yin, by killing us, are you not afraid young master Liu Wen Wu would take revenge?!" An elder was hoping to pressure Fang Yuan.

"Charge, don't stop!" Yan Tian Ji shouted, his voice had already become hoarse and his primeval essence was less than half of his total amount.

Chapter 473: Righteous Path Hero

"It is time." Fang Yuan willed, as the night wolf myriad beast king brought over a dozen night wolf thousand beast kings and entered the battle, blocking the Yan tribe Gu Masters.

Under the wolf group's attacks, Yan tribe suffered their first death.

Wolf howl Gu!

Fang Yuan howled at the sky, crying like a wolf as his voice spread far and wide, increasing the wolf group's battle strength.

Wolf smoke Gu!

Immediately after, he emitted dense smoke that engulfed the battlefield, healing the wolves' injuries.

Yan tribe were shocked.

Water Demon Hao Ji Liu's face became pale and white.

Earlier, Fang Yuan merely dispatched his wolves, now that he joined in, he turned to advantage into a victory.

Tens of hateful, frightened, furious, and icy gazes shot towards Fang Yuan. Under everyone's stare, Fang Yuan smiled lightly as he moved backwards with the hump wolf, pulling some distance from Yan tribe's gang.

To prevent the 'beheading the leader' tactic, Fang Yuan had many wolves around him, he even had a white-eyes wolf, although it had not matured yet, it still surpassed ordinary hundred wolf kings in terms of battle strength.

Seeing Fang Yuan's movement, the trapped Gu masters felt their hearts sinking as their spirits dampened, they had a feeling of being captured by a demon, and had no way to escape.

TIme continued to pass, Yan tribe Gu Masters seemed to have fallen into a swamp as they sank deeper as they struggled.

Fang Yuan had used cannon fodder wolves earlier to expend their primeval essence, the effect was starting to show.

Yan tribe elders died in battle one by one, as a sad and angry atmosphere took over the battlefield.

"Chang Shan Yin, I will not let you off even as a ghost!" An elder screamed, cursing before his death.

But this curse only made Fang Yuan scoff coldly in his heart: "You have no chance to be a ghost, your soul will become fertilizer for Dang Hun mountain."

"Wolf King, fight me alone if you dare!" Yan tribe's battle hall elder screamed.

"Come, you coward, you chicken!" He tried to provoke Fang Yuan, using the last drop of his primeval essence to charge at Fang Yuan for the final time.

Fang Yuan looked at him expressionlessly, as he willed, the wolves charged over like a wave and ripped the battle hall elder to shreds even before he got near.

As the wolves dispersed, his broken corpse remained on the ground. His bones were showing as blood poured out, his furious eyes were staring wide towards the air.

"Battle hall elder..." Yan Tian Ji growled, his body was trembling. With the sacrifice of each elder, an intense pain assaulted his heart every time, he was turning numb from the anguish.

"Chang Shan Yin, you will die a painful death! In spite of being a righteous hero, you actually assaulted your comrades! You will not have a good ending, young master Liu Wen Wu will take revenge for us!!" Yan Tian Ji's face was full of hatred, his expression twisting into an ugly sight. If it was possible, he would love to eat Fang Yuan's flesh and drink his blood.

"Hmph, the curses of a loser is just like the whimpering of a dog before death. Entrusting your hopes of revenge to others, that is a weakling's mentality." Fang Yuan evaluated coldly before waving his hand, as the night wolf myriad beast king burst out like a dark lightning, sending Yan Tian Ji flying.

Yan Tian Ji's primeval essence was expended, after this blow, almost all his bones were broken.

He was like a kite with its strings cut, flying far away and drawing an arc of red blood in the air. When he landed, his entire body was smashed as he no longer breathed.

"Lord!" Ge Guang led a band of elders as he hurried over.

"Wolf King is mighty! After this battle, Yan tribe's higher-ups were all exterminated, there was only one rank three elder left in Yan tribe camp. The letter Gu that Yan Tian Ji sent out was obstructed by us, Yan tribe has no idea what just happened now. It is a good time to assault them." Ge tribe's battle hall elder shouted.

"It is a pity that Water Demon Hao Ji Liu escaped, Lord Wolf King, do you think we should chase after Water Demon or take down Yan tribe camp?" Ge Guang asked.

Fang Yuan smiled indifferently: "Of course we attack Yan tribe camp."

A clam Gu spun its body as it dived in crescent lake rapidly.

Swoosh!

The clam drilled out of the water surface as its shells opened, shoot out two people who were inside.

They were a male and a female, the male was Water Demon Hao Ji Liu, and the female was Yan tribe's big missy Yan Cui Er.

"Huff huff huff..." Hao Ji Liu's breathed roughly as he looked behind with lingering fear. He only relaxed after seeing there was no one chasing him.

This was a floating island on crescent lake, when Hao Ji Liu was scouting the area, he chose this as his third route to escape.

"Wolf King Chang Shan Yin..." Hao Ji Liu muttered this name in his heart. Hatred, anguish, fear, and shock were flashing in his eyes as he showed a complex expression.

Until now, he had never faced such a huge loss.

With rank four upper stage cultivation, he could roam northern plains freely. But today, he met Fang Yuan and felt an unprecedented weakness, helplessness, and loneliness.

"This is the strength of an enslavement path Gu Master? This is not even his peak condition. Back then, Chang Shan Yin could kill Ha Tu Gu who was a realm higher than him, and exterminate the entire group of bandits, how great was his strength back then?"

Hao Ji Liu thought about this as he felt difficulty in breathing.

Fang Yuan's wolf manipulation skills made him think of Jiang Bao Ya, Yang Po Ying and Ma Zun.

"It seems that among the first-rate enslavement masters in northern plains, they would no longer be just three people, but it would be a contest among four. Luckily, he did not have many water wolves with him, otherwise I would be dead meat today."

Thinking of the dangerous scene when he escaped for his life, Hao Ji Liu felt a great fear.

"But why do I have the feeling that Chang Shan Yin purposely gave me a way out?" Hao Ji Liu was a vigilant person, when he recalled the scene, he felt a sense of suspicion.

"A pity that Yan tribe's higher-ups were all killed by Chang Shan Yin, I can no longer extort them. But forget about that, I have already obtained backwater battle Gu, this trip was a success. Now, I should follow my original plan and escort this Yan tribe missy to young master Hei Lou Lan, as a gift." Thinking so, Hao Ji Liu's eyes shone with brilliance.

The ten year blizzard of northern plains, it was a huge challenge even for lone travelling demonic Gu Masters.

But with the lack of resources, Hao Ji Liu wanted to use the heroes assembly to join a certain force. If he was lucky enough to enter the imperial court, not only will Hao Ji Liu keep his life, his cultivation would even go a step further.

There were a few favourite candidates in this contest to be the lord of the imperial court.

Hao Ji Liu thought about it and decided to bet on the most popular person — young master Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan's lecherous nature was known to all. If Hao Ji Liu gave Yan Cui Er to him, he would be handsomely rewarded. Yan Cui Er was not only beautiful like a flower, she also had a special identity, the fiancée of young master Liu Wen Wu.

And Liu Wen Wu was one of Hei Lou Lan's fiercest competitors in this contest for the imperial court.

Making your arch-enemy's fiancee part of your harem, this was an irresistible temptation to Hei Lou Lan.

"If Yan tribe was still around, this gift would be extremely importantly. Unfortunately, after Wolf King killed Yan tribe's higher-ups, he would definitely deal with Yan tribe." Thinking of this, Hao Ji Liu gave a mocking gaze at the dazed Yan Cui Er, whistling.

He made fun of her: "Little beauty, you have to thank me. If I did not save you, you would've died in the hands of Chang Shan Yin."

Yan Cui Er's thick brows moved as she seemed to have woken up from a nightmare: "What do you mean?"

"Hmph, what meaning is there? Chang Shan Yin killed your father and all the elders with him. He will definitely take over Yan tribe, the wolf group must be on their way to Yan tribe camp already. Hehehe, you were a young missy, but now, you're going to be alone soon."

"No, no way!" Yan Cui Er shook her head, her expression was pale. She tried her best to deny it, but her logic told her that Hao Ji Liu's conjecture was accurate.

"Chang Shan Yin is a great righteous hero, how could he do something like this?" She refused to face such a cruel reality, her tears fell like pearls as they flowed down her cheeks, onto the ground. The crying of a beauty, the weeping of a lady, it was a painful scene.

"Righteous hero?" Hao Ji Liu sneered: "Sometimes, righteous heroes are more terrifying than us demonic path cultivators. I only kidnapped you and extorted your tribe, but when Chang Shan Yin strikes, he would destroy and devour your tribe. The worst thing is, he has a proper reason to do so, claiming he is taking revenge, he is the ultimate victor. Once Yan tribe is gone, who can rebuke him? Hmph, this is the truth of this dogshit world!"

Yan Cui Er was in shock as she listened, suddenly she kneeled on the ground as she grabbed Hao Ji Liu's pants, begging: "Please, please save my Yan tribe. My father's letter Gu were all blocked, Yan tribe is without a leader now, and have no clue what is coming, they don't know the danger waiting for them."

The world was wondrous and cruel, Yan Cui Er had never thought that one day, she would kneel down on the ground and beg the enemy she had hated the most.

"My father is dead, I am Yan tribe's next leader. Hao Ji Liu, help me, send a letter for me and inform them. As long as Yan tribe remains, I am Yan tribe leader, I can decide on this and make you Yan tribe's external elder, all of our resources will be yours to use!" Yan Cui Er gave her side of the deal.

The words made Water Demon Hao Ji Liu's heart jump, external elder? Yan tribe's resources?

It was a good suggestion!

But when Fang Yuan's figure appeared in Hao Ji Liu's mind, he shuddered.

"Hmph, you dare to tempt me?" His expression changed as he gave Yan Cui Er a tight slap.

Yan Cui Er grabbed her face as her tears fell, completely stunned by this as she looked at Hao Ji Liu blankly.

"Don't worry, I have already found a good partner for you. Hehehe..." Hao Ji Liu laughed as he grabbed Yan Cui Er, tossing her into the clam Gu.

The large clam's shells closed, as Hao Ji Liu stepped on the water surface, giving the shore one last look.

At Yan tribe camp's position, there were huge fires as smoke rose into the air.

"Yan tribe is finished!" Hao Ji Liu was gloating but he also felt a chill in his heart.

This world worked on the survival of the fittest, there is one mountain higher than a mountain, and a person stronger than another person. Yan tribe was a huge force to him, but to Chang Shan Yin, it was just a plump juicy meat.

"In the following competition for the imperial court, northern plains will definitely be shook as heroes and conquerors arise, I wonder how many people will lose their lives?"

Hao Ji Liu sighed and exclaimed as he travelled west on the large clam.

Chapter 474: Surrender

In the fire of war that spread everywhere, the wolf group surged forward with craze.

The attack on Yan tribe camp had already lasted for four hours. Yan tribe's Gu Masters were experts at defense, but because of the successful ambush and there being no leader, the Yan tribe camp was already ruined beyond recognition by now. There were broken walls everywhere along with human and wolf corpses.

"Brothers, hold on, we need to hold on!" In the center of the camp, the remaining forces of Yan tribe stubbornly resisted.

However, the wolf group surged forward with no end, and the whole defense line was already on the verge of collapse.

"Kill, kill these invaders!"

"Despicable Ge tribe, I curse your entire clan to perish!!"

Besides these curses, there were also the weeping of the old and feeble, the women and the children.

Seeing their family and friends behind them, the already exhausted Yan tribesmen squeezed out every bit of strength they could muster.

In their hearts, a thought kept them going, telling them to hold up their defense, that they must defend! Behind them were their wives, children and their parents. If they could not resist, then all their relatives would end up in the wolves' mouths!

Suddenly, a thousand wolf king broke through the battle line and charged into the depths of the formation.

"Nooo!"

"Careful!"

"Get away!"

The Gu Masters at the frontline roared with fury in their eyes, but it was already too late for them to rescue anyone; they could only stare as the thousand wolf king opened its bloody mouth and started slaughtering the old, feeble, women and children.

"Bastard, you are looking for death!" At this time, a seriously injured Gu Master who was lying on the ground with just one hand and one leg remaining, jumped up with a strength that god knew where it came from and threw himself into the wolf's mouth.

The thousand wolf king bit his waist and almost severed him into two.

The Gu Master foamed from his mouth, and gave a desperate yet satisfied smile.

He fiercely clenched the wolf's head and roared: "Evil beast, die with me."

With that, he self-destructed; blood splashed everywhere and the thousand beast king also died with him.

The encircling Ge tribesmen all saw this scene; someone sighed: "Yan tribe's sons are so brave!"

Fang Yuan lightly nodded.

Although Yan tribe did not show initiative, they were experts at defense and were extremely united. In this invasion, the number of wolves that died were truly beyond his original estimation.

However, Fang Yuan did not feel any pain and snorted: "What is the use even if they were to be more brave? Those defeated usually have no hope of reprieve; this is the cruelty of the struggle for Imperial Court. Okay, this is enough, go ask them to surrender."

These words caused the Ge tribe's Gu Masters to feel a chill: If they were ever to be defeated, their tribe would be at the same state as the Yan tribe before them.

However, when their gaze landed on Fang Yuan, their heart relaxed: With the Wolf King beside us, our Ge tribe has a great tree to lean on. We still need to rely on the Wolf King to lead us.

The intense and fierce battlefield gradually quietened.

The wolf group stopped their offence and slowly retreated, opening up a path. A Ge tribe elder moved through the path and appeared before Yan tribesmen.

"Yan tribesmen, surrender." The Ge tribe elder shouted loudly, "Northern plains elites are those who can adapt to circumstances!"

"Bullshit! I shall never surrender to you shameless sneak attackers!"

"Come, just cut my head off."

"Yan tribe's descendants would rather die than surrender!"

Some Gu Masters roared furiously, but there were also some whose gaze loosened and showed hesitation.

The Ge tribe elder sneered: "If you don't surrender, we won't lose anything in killing you all. But shouldn't you consider your wives and children behind you? They will die a cruel death just because of your stubborn resistance. You will be the ones who harmed them."

These words caused the Yan tribe's remnant forces to quieten.

The chilly wind blew across everyone's faces. Those Yan tribe's Gu Masters who had been roaring furiously had a sluggish expression now. They looked back and their expressions turned soft.

Only the Yan tribe elder felt extreme hatred towards Ge tribe's psychological tactics when he sensed everyone's fighting spirit crumbling. However, this discontent, when it reached his mouth, turned into a sigh.

Under everyone's gazes, he walked forward and said forcibly: "Our Yan tribe... surrenders!"

"Lord!"

"Lord elder..."

Yan tribe's Gu Masters shouted one after another; some couldn't believe it, some weeped with grief and some felt relieved.

At the same time, Ge tribe's Gu Masters also rejoiced.

"Victory, victory!"

"The situation is set, we have annexed Yan tribe!"

They were both at the same place, but their situation was as different as cloud was from mud.

"Gather the troops and clean up the battlefield." Ge Guang also had a joy he could hardly contain on his face. Considering their strength, Ge tribe was below Yan tribe, but they were able to swallow this big force in one move!

"As long as we digest these war spoils, our Ge tribe's strength will increase by three times, even surpassing the strength we had back at Hong Yan valley. This is all thanks to lord Chang Shan Yin!" Ge Guang could not help looking at Fang Yuan when he thought of this.

Truthfully, Ge Guang had hesitated when he received Fang Yuan's letter.

But this hesitation was only for an instant before it turned into resolution. Facts had proved his choice was a correct one.

"If I had refused the Wolf King back then, I'm afraid our Ge tribe would have had the same ending as the Yan tribe." Ge Guang's reverence towards Fang Yuan deepened by another level.

Fang Yuan sized up the whole Yan tribe camp from above the hump wolf.

There were broken debris everywhere; fire still lingered, corpses littered the place and blood dyed the ground red.

All the Yan tribesmen who were hiding were searched and arrested. Yan tribe's Gu Masters were tied with manacles and leg-irons, their Gu worms seized and their primeval essence locked as they were taken as captives and were strictly watched.

Fang Yuan's expression was tranquil, he had seen such situations many times. In the great battle of five regions in his previous life, the situation had been much more bitter and terrifying than this.

"Yan tribe is annihilated, next is the heroes assembly. Before this, I need to return to Hu Immortal blessed land. I also need to go to Lang Ya blessed land once, if my luck is good...."

Three days later, it was a night where many stars filled the sky.

Fang Yuan led the wolf group and came upon a remote area. He first used moving perspective cup Gu to communicate with Little Hu Immortal, then used stargate Gu to return back to Hu Immortal blessed land.

This time, thousands of wolves entered with him.

These wolves were either injured or old with weak battle strength.

Ordinary enslavement path Gu Masters' only choice, in this case, would be to sacrifice them as cannon fodder in battle to stop them from consuming more rations. However, Fang Yuan possessed a blessed land and thus had a better option.

That was to breed them.

"These wild wolves can reproduce at the blessed land and several months later, they should be able to give birth to wolf cubs." Fang Yuan moved this wolf group to the western part of the blessed land.

In this world, the wild beasts' ability to reproduce were very strong; adding on to the Hu Immortal blessed land's six times faster time flow than northern plains, Fang Yuan's troops would from now on be self-replenished.

With this, Hu Immortal blessed land's western part became the wolf group's farming land; the northern part was almost completely cut off by Fang Yuan; eastern part was covered with dark clouds along with tens of lakes which filled the air with moisture; and the southern part was the stonemen's homeland.

In the center was Dang Hun mountain which was gradually dying after being struck by gruel mud Gu.

"Master, master, I have already settled down the starlight fireflies according to your instructions. Come take a look." Little Hu Immortal was extremely happy at seeing Fang Yuan again, and dragged Fang Yuan to the eastern part of the blessed land.

"Master, look up!" Little Hu Immortal said with a delicate voice.

Fang Yuan looked up at the sky, and saw a large expanse of light blue color clouds.

Threads of starlight shone down like a dreamy gauze and shook gently with the breeze. The scene was very beautiful as if it was carved out of a painting.

Fang Yuan looked carefully and discovered these clouds were not originally blue color, but rather a large number of star fragment grass were planted on them. Star fragment grass were deep blue in color, and starlight fireflies fluttered among the grass, shining with specks of light. Moreover among the starlight fireflies were starlight firefly Gu that blossomed with true starlight radiance.

"Not bad." Fang Yuan evaluated.

Little Hu Immortal immediately squinted her eyes in happiness, rubbing her small head against Fang Yuan's hand and said with her delicate voice: "Master, pat me."

Fang Yuan lightly smiled and rubbed Little Hu Immortal's head.

Little Hu Immortal's long snowy tail immediately curled, the two furry ears on her head also lowered gently and her face reddened in happiness.

Fang Yuan had bought many star fragment grass from treasure yellow heaven. However the grass was extremely peculiar and could not be planted on any mortal soil, only on clouds.

When they had transacted, Fairy Yao Guang had suggested Fang Yuan to buy cloud soil to raise star fragment grass. But Fang Yuan did not take her suggestion because there was an enormous scale of dark clouds in Hu Immortal blessed land.

These dark clouds were created from the water and fire collision, when Fang Yuan eradicated the earthly calamities' effects.

The dark clouds did not dissipate and covered the eastern part of Hu Immortal blessed land, and was a problem that was neither big nor small. It had been obstructing light for a long time and was affecting the whole eastern part's ecology.

However, now, Fang Yuan used it to plant star fragment grass and turned this calamity into fortune. Not only was it making use of trash, but it also saved Fang Yuan a lot of expenses in buying large amounts of cloud soil.

At present, large plots of star fragment grass were already growing on the dark clouds. The starlight firefly worms lived among them, filling the whole eastern land with beautiful starlight.

"As long as I properly cultivate these star fragment grass, there will be a guaranteed reproduction of the starlight firefly worms. In future, there will be much more starlight firefly Gu to use. If the cultivation raises to an optimum level and there is a surplus of starlight firefly Gu, I can put them at treasure yellow heaven to sell. In the battle of five great regions, starlight firefly worms will be one of the Gu worms with most demand."

Fang Yuan slightly looked forward to the beautiful future, before returning to Dang Hun mountain with Little Hu Immortal.

Standing at the peak of the mountain, he grabbed the soul burial toad Gu.

When he besieged Yan tribe's higher-ups and during the whole process of attacking Yan tribe camp, he had been using the soul burial toad to collect the souls on the battlefield.

He released all the souls from the soul burial toad.

These pitiful souls had just exited when they were shaken up by the mystical power of Dang Hun mountain, and were turned into the purest nutrient, nourishing the whole Dang Hun mountain.

"Tomorrow, Dang Hun mountain will again be filled with guts Gu." Fang Yuan nodded his head with satisfaction.

Gathering large numbers of souls was one of the reasons why he killed Yan tribe.

"Tonight, it is time for me to breakthrough to rank five." Fang Yuan's cultivation did not receive any suppression when he got back to Hu Immortal blessed land, he was at true rank four peak stage.

He had already stayed at rank four peak stage for a long time. And with his current A grade aptitude, it was time to challenge the boundaries of rank five realm!

Chapter 475: Soaring Cultivation

Rumble...

The ninety percent primeval sea in the aperture surged with high waves, and true gold primeval essence shone brightly on the aperture walls.

The aperture walls were also extraordinary; sparkling and clear like crystals, containing life force in them. This was the crystal membrane of rank four peak stage realm.

Waves continually surged, reaching towards the sky. Then, they crashed towards the crystal membrane wave after waves.

At first, the crystal membrane was like the reef of a sea, being unmovable. But it gradually became unable to endure the fierce waves and cracks started appearing.

As time passed, bigger cracks appeared.

The primeval sea slowly reduced, while the crystal membrane was full of cracks and appeared extremely fragile. However, there was still a little distance left from breakthrough.

Fang Yuan was sitting cross-legged on the bed with both his eyes closed, and almost all his attention was on the aperture.

He possessed ninety percent aptitude which was classified as A grade, and also had very deep accumulation; he could breakthrough to rank five realm just by relying on his own strength.

Right now, there was about twenty percent left of the primeval sea; the sea waves had also weakened and was getting to the point of being tranquil.

But suddenly, as if it was accumulating its strength, a huge wave erupted out of the true gold primeval sea.

This wave was fierce and majestic, surpassing any of the waves from before; it was like a tsunami, soaring up and then fiercely smashing towards the aperture walls.

Boom!

A soft sound echoed, and the aperture walls were finally unable to bear the pressure. They were smashed into pieces by this enormous wave.

The shattered fragments of the crystal aperture walls were like a broken ice mountain, and as they fell into the sea they turned into pure essence before slowly melting down.

After a while, the fragments on the crystal walls had all fallen down, leaving behind a light membrane that covered everything.

The light membrane was dazzling with very powerful aura, far surpassing the rank four peak stage crystal wall; this was the appearance of a true rank five initial stage!

Following it, a trace of light purple primeval essence appeared in the depths of the sea.

Rank one Gu Masters had green copper primeval essence; rank two had red iron primeval essence; rank three had white silver primeval essence; rank four had yellow gold primeval essence; and rank five was purple crystal primeval essence.

Although it was only a thread of light purple, it was a qualitative difference.

From now on, Fang Yuan's primeval essence would be light purple primeval essence!

"Since my rebirth, I have wandered around everywhere, drifting miserably. Yet now I am finally a rank five Gu Master." Inside Dang Hun palace, Fang Yuan slowly opened his eyes and sighed with joy.

Rank five Gu Masters were the lords in this mortal world, the true peak stage. Those who could cultivate to this stage were not even one in ten thousand.

If it were others, they might have already become wild with joy. However, Fang Yuan had already experienced this in his previous life. Right now, rather than ecstasy, what he felt was joy towards his future prospects.

"Compared to my previous life, being able to enter rank five at such a young age is truly a success."

Fang Yuan was only thirty or so at present; cultivating to rank five at this age was a performance that would only be seen in the absolute top geniuses of the five great regions.

"But rank five is not my end point; it is only a starting point. Next, I need to once again advance to Gu Immortal!"

Those genius Gu Masters would feel some hesitation when they talked about charging to Gu Immortal realm. However, Fang Yuan had his previous life's experiences, thus he had plenty of confidence in advancing to Gu Immortal realm.

"After becoming a Gu Immortal, the deadly crisis from Spring Autumn Cicada can be completely resolved."

Fang Yuan looked at Spring Autumn Cicada.

Since this rebirth, Spring Autumn Cicada had fallen into deep hibernation, continually absorbing the water from the river of time and recuperating.

Right now, it had already mostly recovered and a faint pressure was filling Fang Yuan's aperture.

For a long time now, Spring Autumn Cicada was like a guillotine hovering above Fang Yuan's neck. As time passed, this enormous guillotine would move closer towards his neck.

Spring Autumn Cicada gave Fang Yuan an enormous death threat, forcing him to risk dangers and do everything he could to advance his cultivation.

Only by reaching the rank six Gu Immortal realm, could Fang Yuan's aperture be able to store Spring Autumn Cicada.

At that time, Fang Yuan would have more freedom and leisure, and not be so repressed like now.

Light purple primeval essence continually appeared in the aperture, settling down below the remaining gold primeval essence.

Fang Yuan gathered his concentration and slowly stood up, walking out of this secret room and into another room.

There were several large vats in this room.

There was green liquid in the vats and a purple crystal relic Gu was floating on each liquid.

There were six purple crystal relic Gu. Most of them had been purchased by Fang Yuan or Little Hu Immortal from treasure yellow heaven.

Purple crystal relic Gu could raise a rank five Gu Master's cultivation! Fang Yuan had paid a considerable price for them.

Fang Yuan only required three purple crystal relic Gu to raise his cultivation to the peak stage. But right now, he looked at the vats with various liquids.

One vat had muddy green liquid; another had a mixture of green and yellow; and the purple crystal relic Gu on two of the vats had tiny purple black hair growing out of them.

The remaining two vats had clear green liquid with no change.

Fang Yuan snorted; most of these six purple crystal relic Gu had been tampered with.

With his five hundred years of experience, Fang Yuan was able to conjecture something wrong with these relic Gu.

Among the purple crystal relic Gu in these six vats of green liquid, only two could be used. Fang Yuan immediately took out the two purple crystal relic Gu from the clear green liquid and used them.

Using two relic Gu, Fang Yuan's cultivation immediately rose to rank five upper stage realm.

Fang Yuan again took out two purple crystal relic Gu whose bodies were filled with tiny hairs, and repeatedly used them.

The two relic Gu's strength combined and was able to raise his cultivation to rank five peak stage!

In a short period of time, Fang Yuan advanced from rank five initial stage to rank five peak stage, completing an enormous jump. Moreover, relic Gu had no side-effects and would not cause his foundation to weaken.

Gu Master's cultivation was extremely focused on resources. As long as there were enough resources, cultivation could make rapid progress.

Theoretically, as long as one had sufficient relic Gu, a Gu Master's cultivation could advance in a lightning speed. But in reality, extremely few Gu Masters did this.

One reason was that relic Gu could only raise a Gu Master's cultivation by a small realm; every great realm required the Gu Masters to breakthrough by themselves. It was extremely easy to raise cultivation with enough relic Gu, but this would instead cause normal Gu Masters to be reliant on them, and breaking through a great realm would become much harder.

Second, higher realm did not represent everything. To survive in this cruel world, one still needed planning, wisdom, opportunity, experience and training. A sudden increase in strength without the knowledge to control it was like an infant brandishing a broadsword, they could injure somebody and injure themselves.

Third, relic Gu were extremely expensive, few Gu Masters could enjoy advancing so lavishly. Even if a Gu Immortal's descendants could enjoy such treatment, their elders would not allow them to be so spoiled.

Finally, there was an even more important point, and that was aptitude. Without good aptitude, relic Gu would have no use even if there were more of it. Fang Yuan could smoothly advance to rank five because of his experience and also the great help from A grade aptitude.

Fang Yuan might be the only one who could could use relic Gu like this repeatedly to sharply raise his cultivation.

If it were other rank five Gu Masters, even if they were geniuses from the Shang clan, they would still have to follow the prescribed order. After all, a Gu Master's cultivation still required long training of Gu worms. High cultivation could not directly indicate the battle strength, it was no more than making oneself look like a fat target.

Previous life experiences were Fang Yuan's great wealth that allowed him to smoothly control this burst of strength.

Unknowingly, a night had already passed while dashing through the cultivation levels. Fang Yuan walked out of Dang Hun palace and onto Dang Han mountain.

Just like he expected, many guts Gu had grown on the mountain rocks.

He walked a few steps and crouched, casually kneading one, but it was only a pile of yellow mud.

Even since Dang Hun mountain was struck by Immortal Gu Gruel Mud, it gradually began to die and a part of the guts Gu created on it would become yellow paste.

Fang Yuan's expression did not change as he had already expected this; he again pinched seven to eight guts Gu.

But in this process, he only got two good guts Gu. Using their strength, his wolfman soul slightly strengthened once more.

"The Immortal Gu Gruel Mud's strength has already invaded deep. I remember that four to five guts Gu would be intact out of ten. Now, only three or four are good." Fang Yuan sighed.

Although these yellow mud were all gruel mud and could be sold at treasure yellow heaven, but compared to the guts Gu, the difference in worth was as different as night and day, and was an enormous loss.

Fortunately, all these guts Gu belonged to Fang Yuan alone.

Although six or seven out of ten guts Gu were useless, with their enormous numbers it was still enough for Fang Yuan's soul to progress greatly.

"Now, I am at rank five peak stage, and the next step would be to attack the Gu Immortal realm. But this matter is quite difficult and I need many preparations and attempt it slowly." Fang Yuan inwardly planned.

With rank five peak stage aperture, Spring Autumn Cicada's pressure had greatly resolved.

The urgent matter was to rescue Dang Hun mountain.

Though Dang Hun mountain was dying, saving it would be a great help to Fang Yuan's future cultivation, even after he advanced to Gu Immortal realm.

After completely cleaning off all the guts Gu on the mountain, Fang Yuan entered Dang Hun palace again and collaborated with Little Hu Immortal to activate connecting heaven Gu.

Wave after waves of divine sense were mutually tangling up in treasure yellow heaven.

Just after they opened connecting heaven Gu, a large divine sense was transmitted to Little Hu Immortal, asking about the price of gruel mud.

Fang Yuan had sold great amounts of gruel mud and this attracted many Gu Immortals' interest.

Using these gruel mud for the Immortal Gu recipe, one could refine the Immortal Gu Gruel Mud. Although this Gu could only be used once, it was a genuine Immortal Gu. In this environment where Immortal Gu were scarce, Gu Immortals scrabbled madly for Fang Yuan's gruel mud.

As for these gruel mud, Fang Yuan's price was Immortal Gu Gruel Mud's recipe.

Originally, these Gu Immortals brought incomparably damaged remnant recipes that did not have even ten feet of treasure light. But after a few days, the recipes these Gu Immortals brought out had already reached a treasure light of thirty to forty feet.

Fang Yuan still kept on disregarding them; he had large amounts of gruel mud to sell. In fact, none of the gruel mud recipes that appeared nowadays could satisfy him.

Chapter 476: Air Bubble Fish

Connecting heaven Gu inlaid itself in the air, figures of wolves flashed past one after another in the mirror.

Suddenly, the scene fixed itself on a turtleback myriad wolf king.

Turtleback wolves possessed broad physique, their whole body was dark-green and they had dark-blue eyes. Every turtleback wolf had shell like that of a turtle.

This shell was very heavy and about one-third of a turtleback wolf's weight was due to it. Apart from defensive purposes, it could also store nutrition just like camels.

This species had the strongest defense among the wolves.

And the myriad beast wolf king that showed on connecting heaven Gu was no doubt even more enormous, being ten times larger than ordinary turtleback wolves. Its turtle back was towering high, the strong shell shone with a bronze color, giving a feeling of abundant strength and power.

"The scale of the wolf group I have is close to thirty thousand. They can mainly be divided into three wolf groups; turtleback wolves, night wolves and wind wolves. There are around ten thousand wolves in each group. Besides them, there are also a few poison beard wolves which were obtained from the poisonous grassland. There are also over a hundred water wolves which I bought because of white-eyes wolf."

Originally, Fang Yuan had over thirty thousand wolves. But after several battles, the loss accumulated and now he only had around twenty-seven thousand. After he sent the old, weak and injured wolves sent to Hu Immortal blessed land, the number of wolves left was less than twenty-five thousand.

Thus, they needed to be replenished.

If ordinary enslavement path Gu Masters wanted to replenish their beast group, they would need to organize a group to hunt, requiring much effort and time, moreover they could not take in too big of a beast group.

Fang Yuan, however, after possessing connecting heaven Gu, was like standing on a Gu Immortal's shoulder, he had one more option than ordinary Gu Masters, that is to purchase the beast groups in treasure yellow heaven.

Most blessed lands would breed wild beasts. However, when the beast population increased a lot, they would influence the ecology of the blessed lands, and the Gu Immortals that controlled the blessed lands would put them for sale in treasure yellow heaven. Like this, not only could it reduce the pressure on the blessed land, it could also provide some revenue.

Similarly, many Gu Immortals who wanted to nurture the blessed land and replenish the ecology, would purchase some beasts to breed in their blessed lands. Thus, transactions of beast groups were extremely common in treasure yellow heaven.

There were many dazzling lineups of wolf groups put for sale in treasure yellow heaven.

Northern plains' night wolves, wind wolves, water wolves, poison beard wolves, turtleback wolves; southern border's lightning wolves, azure wolves, blood wolves, two-headed wolves; western desert's silk wolves, pearl wolves, sand wolves, tyrant wolves; eastern seas' ink wolves, greed wolves, red wolves, goldback wolves; central continent's white-eyes wolves, star wolves, color wolves, blood wolves...

The wolves put for sale were not only common wild beasts, but also mutated beasts like white-eyes wolves, tyrant wolves and greed wolves.

Of course, there were no desolate beast level wolves which had battle strength comparable to Gu Immortals. But Fang Yuan knew there was a desolate beast peach wolf in Lang Ya blessed land.

"Among the three greatest wolf groups I have, only night wolf group has a myriad beast king. If my wind wolves and turtleback wolves also had myriad beast kings to unite them, I would not need to control the hundred wolf kings and thousand wolf kings; it will greatly reduce the burden when I command them. By reducing the burden on my soul, I can then take in even more wolf groups."

Fang Yuan did not intend to replace the wolf groups, that would be a superfluous move.

He decided to strengthen the wolf group on him.

Little Hu Immortal sent the divine sense for him and inquired the price of this turtleback myriad wolf king.

The Gu Immortal who put it for sale called himself South Sea Turtle Immortal. He wanted ten thousand stalks of blowpipe grass.

Blowpipe grass was the specialty of northern plains, every grass looked like an erect long pipe. When wind blew, the wind would enter the small holes on the grass and produce pleasant pipe sounds.

Blowpipe grass was a common material used in Gu refinement; at the same time, a large expanse of blowpipe grass would slowly give birth to some sound path and wood path Gu worms.

Fang Yuan did not have any blowpipe grass, and although he knew their location, this season was not the time for them to grow and they were all just seeds buried under the earth.

Fang Yuan knew this situation, but did not give up and made Little Hu Immortal ask: "Ask and see if he accepts immortal essence stones."

Little Hu Immortal conveyed with her divine sense and after communicating for a moment, she reported: "Master, he says he can sell twenty thousand turtleback wolves, but he is asking for two immortal essence stones."

Fang Yuan scoffed, this was a very expensive price. Immortal essence stones were very precious, turtleback wolves were no more than ordinary wild beasts but transactions required the process of bargaining.

After some haggling, Fang Yuan used an immortal essence stone to buy thirty thousand turtleback wolves and one turtleback myriad wolf king from South Sea Turtle Immortal.

After the transaction was finished, Fang Yuan bought another eighteen thousand wind wolves and one wind wolf myriad beast king. He replenished twenty thousand night wolves, five thousand poison beard wolves and six thousand water wolves. Altogether, he spent two and a half immortal essence stones.

It was not over yet.

The wolf groups entered Hu Immortal blessed land, bringing a grim ordeal to the original ecology and causing many effects. To say the least, Fang Yuan needed to provide enough food to these wolf groups, otherwise these wolves would starve to death because of insufficient food.

Hu Immortal blessed land also had many wild beasts like rabbits, pheasants and so on. But these animals were the food sources of fox groups.

Hu Immortal had cultivated large numbers of foxes in the blessed land; there were red foxes, gold foxes, cloud foxes, wind foxes, autumn water foxes, flowing light foxes and so on.

These fox groups had suffered disastrous damage in the sixth earthly calamity, but a number were still preserved. After many years of recuperation, they would also gradually grow into a large scale and recover some of their strength.

If there was insufficient food, the wolf groups and fox groups were bound to hunt each other and create an extremely severe internal friction; the losses would be more than profits.

Fang Yuan bought food for these fox groups and wolf groups.

"Golden koi, blue jade carp, fat mudfish, which would be good... Eh? There are actually fish roes of air bubble fish!"

Just as Fang Yuan was about to choose one, he accidentally discovered a Gu Immortal was selling fish roes of air bubble fish.

He immediately decided to buy it.

However, air bubble fish's fish roes had attracted some Gu Immortals' attention, causing there to be a price competition.

Fang Yuan made prompt decision and raised the price to one immortal essence stone.

"There are just over twenty thousand fish roes, someone is actually paying one immortal essence stone!"

"This person is mad, even if they are bred, there would only be around three thousand air bubble fish. Although they are precious but they are only worth less than one immortal essence stone."

Gu Immortals transmitted divine sense containing their ridicule and contempt.

Air bubble fish were difficult to incubate, with only around thirty percent chance of survival rate. To them, the price Fang Yuan was paying was too high.

"If my memory is not wrong, two Gu Immortals would fight over the air bubble sea at the end of this year, the intense poison would invade into the whole air bubble sea and turn it into a death zone. At that time, air bubble fish's price would sharply rise to over ten folds." Fang Yuan sneered after obtaining these fish roes.

Those able to become Gu Immortals were no doubt giants among men and great geniuses. Excluding some ignorant and incompetent second generation immortals, most of the Gu Immortals were those with great experiences and wisdom; if Fang Yuan had not started out with such a high price, it would be extremely difficult for him to get these fish roes.

"In future, when the battle of five regions breaks out, this air bubble fish's price would increase to hundred folds of now!"

Air bubble fish were the specialty of air bubble sea, they were quite peculiar with a translucent and round belly, like a round and glossy air bubble. Two dark sesame seeds seemed to be sewed in front of the air bubble, they were its eyes. The fins and tail were very small, giving it very weak movement power.

Air bubble fish were different from other fishes, its movement style was to move by rising and falling. When they were in danger, they would often float out of the surface of the water to the air, to hide from their enemies.

Some mature air bubble fish could even keep staying at the air throughout the year without needing to enter the water, eating the tiny insects in the air as their food.

The greatest use of the air bubble fish was to increase the production of Gu worms.

The worms air bubble fish devoured would be protected and nourished in its belly, gradually evolving into a Gu, then they would pierce out of the belly and fly away.

Because it could increase the rate of Gu worms' creation, air bubble fish became a product sought out by all Gu Immortals during the battle of the five regions.

"These air bubble fish needs to be slowly raised, although they only have thirty percent survival rate, they just need to be carefully tended to. Dozens of years later, they would reach a scale where they can be self-sufficient. Hundred years later, they would reach at least fifty thousand in numbers. And same as starlight firefly Gu, it will be a highly demanded good in the battle of five regions."

The fish roes of air bubble fish were an unexpected harvest, and could be considered a small pleasant surprise.

"With air bubble fish, I can't choose fat mudfish. Although fat mudfish are the easiest to raise, but they will eat the fish roes of air bubble fish, they can even eat mud to fill their stomach when they are hungry."

"Comparatively speaking, between gold koi and blue jade carps; one eats gold as food and another eats gemstones. Both have no interest towards the fish roes of air bubble fish."

Fang Yuan did not lack gold and gemstones because there was a large group of rockmen in Hu Immortal blessed land.

These rockmen lived underground and ate soil as their food. After a long time, all kinds of gold, gemstones and so on would form on their body.

"However gold has a harmful influence on the reproduction of air bubble fish and can decrease the reproduction rate. The mild gemstones, however, have no such disadvantages, so I shall choose blue jade carps."

Fang Yuan pondered and finally decided upon the fish species.

In his previous life of five hundred years, he had also managed a blessed land. And because of many setbacks he had experienced then, he could now make the most sensible choices.

After obtaining blue jade carps, the water wolves' food problem was solved. Fang Yuan then bought a large number of pink rabbits and iron-shell flowers as food for night wolves, wind wolves and turtleback wolves.

And because of poison beard wolves, Fang Yuan also chose some earth skin pigs. These pigs had a high reproduction rate and could eat both meat and grass; they were also put in the eastern part of the blessed land.

Finally, Fang Yuan bought many Gu worms and large numbers of Gu refinement materials. He spent altogether eight immortal essence stones and hundreds of thousands of primeval stones.

"At once, eight immortal essence stones have been spent." Fang Yuan would not feel any heartache at common primeval stones, but he still cared about immortal essence stones.

Previously, he had sold many remnant recipes and obtained twenty-eight immortal essence stones, now only twenty remained.

"I can still sell the remnant recipes with me, but the more they are sold, the cheaper they will get. I lack means for getting profits, as for the investment in air bubble fish and starlight firefly Gu, they would only show results after a hundred years. I need to use these remaining immortal essence stones carefully."

Fang Yuan heaved a sigh. He handed connecting heaven Gu to little Hu Immortal and let her be in charge of dealing with the residence and various other works regarding wolf groups, fish groups, iron-shell flowers and air bubble fish roes.

Fang Yuan entered Dang Hun palace and used the materials he bought to refine Gu.

Chapter 477: Rank Five Breath Concealment Gu

After one day and one night, Fang Yuan walked out of Dang Hun palace with an exhausted expression.

He came to Dang Hun mountain, many guts Gu had been created again during this period of time. But the quantity was half of the first time.

Fang Yuan pinched some of them, most were of no use because of Immortal Gu Gruel Mud's powers.

But Fang Yuan had slaughtered Yan tribe, after collecting many souls, there were lot of guts Gu. Relying on this enormous number, Fang Yuan's soul managed to advance by a lot.

"My current soul strength is over five times stronger than before. Unfortunately, there is still a large gap to thousand man soul." Fang Yuan closed his eyes for a while before opening them again with a slightly happy expression.

This progress was quite big. If it were normal Gu Masters, they would require ten years or more to accumulate such results.

But because of guts Gu's help, Fang Yuan could easily accomplish this feat in less than half a day.

"No wonder Dang Hun mountain was called one of the sacred lands of soul path by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. Among the things in my possession, Dang Hun mountain's value is only lower to Spring Autumn Cicada. No matter what, I can't let it die!"

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had once commented that soul path Gu Masters had two great sacred lands in this world. One was Dang Hun mountain to strengthen the soul; another was Luo Po valley to refine soul.

Soul needed to be strengthened and also required to be refined.

Fang Yuan used guts Gu to rapidly strengthen his soul. But he did not have Luo Po valley to refine his soul, thus he could only use wolf soul Gu instead.

Wolf soul Gu could transform a Gu Master's soul into wolfman soul, having the effect of refining soul.

Guts Gu's production continued to drop; by the third time, Fang Yuan only used one hour to pluck them all. Most of the guts Gu had become mud paste, and relying on the small portion of intact guts Gu, Fang Yuan strengthened his soul to six times.

Little Hu Immortal was busy with her work.

The stargate Gu was once again activated and Fang Yuan returned to northern plains.

The moment he stepped out of the stargate, Fang Yuan's first sight was the loyal guarding wolf group that surrounded the area.

The stargate was connected to Hu Immortal blessed land; Fang Yuan sent poison beard wolves and water wolves to the blessed land while bringing wind wolf myriad wolf king and turtleback myriad wolf king to northern plains. At the same time, he replenished the three wolf groups, raising the scale of the wolf group to sixty thousand!

Fang Yuan did not immediately return to Ge tribe, instead he picked up a half-finished product and began to refine Gu.

After spending a long while, when the first rays of sunlight shone on crescent lake, he obtained rank five breath concealment Gu.

The heaven and earth of the five regions were different, whether it were Gu worms or Gu Masters, once they went into other regions, they would be suppressed.

But different from Gu worms, human is the spirit of all living beings and had great intelligence and adaptability. As long as a few years went by, Gu Masters could completely adapt to the environment and obtain the recognition of the region, no longer facing suppression.

And for the Gu worms to not be suppressed, Fang Yuan refined the Gu at northern plains. No matter where the materials were from or whatever Gu worms were used, the moment the Gu refinement was completed, the new rank five breath concealment Gu was born in northern plains and obtained northern plains' recognition, not suffering from the suppression.

Back then, Fang Yuan had obtained rank two breath concealment Gu in Zi You mountain. By refining and ranking up this Gu worm, the rank five breath concealment Gu was finally formed.

At rank five, breath concealment Gu did not have any huge changes, was still like a purple exquisite tree leaf, it was just that the purple was deeper in color and even had a slight metallic luster.

After using the breath concealment Gu to hide his cultivation back to rank four middle stage, Fang Yuan let out a breath of turbid air.

He was now at rank five peak stage, and even after suffering the suppression in northern plains, he still had rank five initial stage aura.

If he returned to Ge tribe like this, it was sure to attract suspicion. At the same time, if one day, a portion of the suppression lifts and his cultivation suddenly rose, it would result in conjectures and doubts. Breath concealment Gu could prevent such an accident.

Fang Yuan returned to Ge tribe with the wolf group. As expected, the Ge tribesmen were shocked and pleasantly surprised.

But there were many wolf groups in northern plains, crescent lake was also a place filled with spirituality and many beast groups gathered around it; It was not difficult to explain how Fang Yuan gained such a bountiful harvest.

Fang Yuan placed a part of the wolf group inside the camp and another group outside, letting them move about.

When he returned to the giant lizard house Gu, Ge tribe leader Ge Guang immediately came over to pay respects, bringing two letters with him.

"Congratulations to lord for gaining a huge increase in strength after this hunt!" Ge Guang had two dark circles under his eyes, his face however had a joyous expression.

Throughout this day and night, he had been cleaning up the battlefield with Ge tribe elders, gathering the goods and dealing with those who surrendered, he was so busy that he had no time to sleep. Looking at Ge tribe's strength expand in his hands, Ge Guang was very excited, causing his respect towards Chang Shan Yin to deepen by another layer.

He understood clearly that without Chang Shan Yin, this day would not have come for Ge tribe.

"My luck was quite good and I had some gains." Fang Yuan sat on the seat and lightly nodded at Ge Guang.

His strength increase did not end with the wolf groups. His cultivation and soul also had huge advancement, Ge Guang and the rest would be terrified if they knew.

At Lang Ya blessed land, Fang Yuan had used up one chance to refine Immortal Gu, and obtained stargate Gu, thus causing his inactive chessboard to become alive again. Fang Yuan's strength progressed at an unimaginable speed every time he entered Hu Immortal blessed land.

Everyone would find it hard to believe such rapid progress. However, it was also very reasonable when one carefully looked.

Fang Yuan possessed a blessed land, he was growing using the foundation of a Gu Immortal. The difference between immortals and mortals were as different as night and day; adding in his five hundred years of experience that allowed him to absorb the rapid increase in strength, he could grow smoothly without facing any issues.

Fang Yuan had been risking his life, like walking on a tightrope in between cliffs to obtain these enormous wealth that changed into deep accumulation. Finally, the accumulation was changing into explosive growth in strength.

"Lord, by devouring Yan tribe we have obtained a total of over six hundred and thirty four thousand primeval stones, one rank five Gu, twenty-seven rank four Gu and many rank three, rank two and rank one Gu. Besides them, there are over two thousand Gu refinement recipes, three hundred hump wolves and many big stomach horses. Lizard house Gu numbers to thousands, hundreds of mush room Gu, and the number of captives are over seven thousand..." Ge Guang excitedly reported.

Fang Yuan quietly listened; because he had taken down Yan tribe's higher-ups in one move and also due to the surprise attack, Ge tribe was able to receive huge benefits.

Especially the amount of captives, it was unexpectedly over seven thousand. Among them were large numbers of rank two and rank one Gu Masters who wanted to surrender; after Ge tribe incorporated them, the tribe's strength had increased by over two-fold.

"Lord, this is the inventory list after calculating, please take a look. You can take anything you want." Ge Guang respectfully handed Fang Yuan a list.

To Fang Yuan, these resources were instead not essential.

He had Hu Immortal blessed land now, the appeal of primeval stones to him had fallen down to the abyss. The days where he had to scheme for one or two primeval stones on Qing Mao mountain had already left him.

He lacked immortal essence stones, the more he had the better. Unfortunately, Yan tribe did not have a Gu Immortal, so how could they have immortal essence stones?

The reason why Fang Yuan assisted Ge tribe was to have a chess piece, to act as a shield for him so that he could meddle in the heroes assembly.

If possible, he did not want to give up the identity of Chang Shan Yin prematurely. The longer he managed the tribe, the more use it would have for him in the battle of five regions.

"According to the rules of the grassland, the half of these spoils are all mine. But these things are not suited for me, so I shall leave them with Ge tribe." Fang Yuan gave back the list to Ge Guang.

"Yes, lord." Ge Guang promptly replied.

"My wolf groups will be fed by your tribe. Account for the expenses using my share of the spoils." Fang Yuan added.

Ge Guang, however, shook his head and said with sincerity: "Lord, the reason our Ge tribe can have this day is all because of you. How could I, Ge Guang, be a person who doesn't know favors? Feeding the wolf groups is our Ge tribe's responsibility, there is no need for lord to spend your wealth. I understand deeply that my abilities are not enough to manage the whole Ge tribe. I hope senior can guide and give me pointers in the coming days."

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan laughed and took a deep glance at Ge Guang. This young man before him could be considered to have some experience now.

Although he had only held the tribe leader position for a short time, he had experienced trials and wandered in between life and death, he took risks, and thus progressed rapidly.

As the saying goes: Heroes emerge in troubled times.

This Gu Master world had a cruel environment and it was not easy to live. And precisely so, heroes emerged in large numbers and endlessly.

"Ge Guang, you are pretty good. In that case, I shall become Ge tribe's external elder."

Ge Guang's whole body shook before wild joy emerged in his face.

He promptly kneeled on the ground: "Junior is presumptuous and sincerely request senior to become the supreme elder of Ge tribe!"

"Supreme elder?" Fang Yuan muttered.

Ge Guang raised his head and looked at Fang Yuan sincerely. He knew Ge tribe's current great situation was closely related to Chang Shan Yin, that is the only way they can move stably and far, while obtaining the most benefits.

If Chang Shan Yin was not around, just relying on his rank three cultivation would not be enough to suppress the expanding Ge tribe.

"Alright, I shall accept it." Fang Yuan agreed.

By this point, Ge tribe's circumstances was also part of his plan. Ge Guang was only a rank three Gu Master and had just taken the tribe leader position, Fang Yuan made Ge tribe take over Yan tribe, it allowed him to have greater control of this person.

By controlling this person , he controlled Ge tribe!

"What? Yan tribe was exterminated by Ge tribe!?" At another place beside crescent lake, Wang tribe leader listened to the news and looked at Bei tribe's envoy with shock.

Bei tribe's envoy was an old rank three Gu Master, his face filled with wrinkles, grey hair, sunken and dark eyes. He was an enslavement path expert with some reputation in northern plains, named Bei Cao Sheng.

"That is precisely so. Many tribes already know of this, not long later, the news will spread to the whole northern plains. Your tribe is in a remote location and has many large beast groups in the surroundings, thus you were not able to get this news immediately."

Bei Cao Sheng continued: "I have come here to represent the alliance of Bei, Zheng and Pei tribe to request Wang tribe to join the alliance and punish Ge tribe together!"

Chapter 478: Main Pillar

"Eh?" Hearing Bei tribe, Zheng tribe and Pei tribe had already allied, Wang tribe leader slightly furrowed his brows.

In northern plains, it was not strange for tribes to form an alliance. The struggle for the Imperial Court was arriving soon, the appearance of alliances also increased.

"I have a doubt. Ge tribe was originally weaker than Yan tribe, how could such a small existence swallow a bigger force?" Wang tribe leader questioned.

Bei Cao Sheng laughed: "Ge tribe could absorb Yan tribe all because of one person. I wonder if Lord Wang tribe leader has ever heard of Chang Shan Yin?"

"Chang Shan Yin?" Wang tribe leader slightly frowned, this name brought a familiar feeling in the depths of his heart as if he had heard it somewhere.

Soon after, his furrowed brows relaxed and an astonished look appeared on his face: "Chang Shan Yin... could it be the Wolf King who had killed Ha Tu Gu?"

"Hehe. I am in admiration of tribe leader's knowledge." Bei Cao Sheng cupped his fists, "Yes, it is because of this person's meddling that led to Ge tribe's victory. Who would have expected that the hero of northern plains would still alive after all this time? No one knows what happened in all these years. He appeared with low profile and with his lone strength, made Ge tribe, a small existence, swallow the big Yan tribe. Of course, this is also because Yan tribe's higher-ups were schemed against by Chang Shan Yin and were taken down collectively. This allowed Ge tribe to have dominance when they attacked Yan tribe camp."

Bei Cao Sheng spoke with assurance, he was actually very clear of this inside story.

In truth, after Yan tribe was exterminated, there were naturally some who were able to escape alive and went to Bei tribe to request protection. With such informants, Bei tribe was naturally very clear of the situation.

Wang tribe leader's brows furrowed deeper: "back in those days, Wolf King with his lone strength could bypass realms and kill rank five Gu Master Ha Tu Gu along with his bandit group. Such strength truly intimidates people. How can we deal with such expert with our strength?"

Rank four Gu Masters were already the leaders of small-mid scale tribes. Rank five Gu Masters were at the peak of the mortal world.

Long ago, the news of Chang Shan Yin killing Ha Tu Gu had created an uproar in the whole northern plains.

Reputation, whether good or bad, follows closely like a shadow; Chang Shan Yin's deeds had spread throughout northern plains for so many years, it was natural for Wang tribe leader to have some apprehension.

Bei Cao Sheng laughed loudly: "Hahaha, it is natural for lord tribe leader to have worries. Wolf King was indeed an amazing character. But times have changed, today's Wolf King is no longer as valiant as before."

"Eh? I would like to hear the details."

"Everyone knows the strength of enslavement path Gu Masters is determined by their troops. Wolf King has just come back, his wolf group is no longer of the same scale as before, with not even a single mutated beast. There are only ordinary wind wolves, night wolves and turtleback wolves with him. And in the battle with Yan tribe, they already suffered huge losses. His battle strength is not so mighty."

Bei Cao Sheng continued: "Moreover, Wolf King attacked Yan tribe without rhyme or reason, this is the conduct of the demonic path, slaughtering ordinary mortals goes against northern plains' rules. He is no longer the hero of our northern plains, but a demon everyone needs to hunt. The one we are punishing this time is a sinner who creates conflicts, an evildoer who invades at will! We have righteousness with us while Ge tribe is at the side of injustice and evil. The heroes assembly has not begun yet, the struggle for Imperial Court has not started yet, but they dared to openly wage a war with another tribe, this is unforgivable. Looking at the history of northern plains, which of the people that violated the bottom line like this has ever had a good ending?"

Bei Cao Sheng's words were full of passion, indeed as the political advisor of Bei tribe, his words had the power to incite people's hearts.

But Wang tribe leader also was a seasoned character and not someone who could be easily influenced. His gaze flashed and said with hesitation: "Although it is so, Wolf King is after all the Wolf King. In the battle between giants, there will definitely be injuries. After the battle ends, there is bound to be enormous losses."

Bei Cao Sheng shook his head and smiled without concern: "Hehehe. Wolf King might be strong, but two fists cannot defeat four hands. Ge tribe has just absorbed Yan tribe, they have eaten too much this time and inflated very quickly, they will not be stable for a long time. As long as Wang tribe joins us, why would our four tribes' alliance be afraid of a puny Ge tribe?"

Wang tribe leader muttered irresolutely for a while and said: "I am not afraid of Ge tribe, but Wolf King is the Wolf King. He mysteriously disappeared for so many years, who knows what happened, he might have even had fortuitous encounter. He definitely has some plan in making his appearance now. Such a character is sure to have trump cards that he has not shown yet."

Bei Cao Sheng scoffed: "Reputation usually comes from exaggeration. Wang tribe leader, why should we puff up the enemy and lower our morale? Why are you so afraid of the Wolf King? He is already past his prime, even if he has trump cards, he is no more than an enslavement path Gu Master in the end. Since he is an enslavement path Gu Master, we have ways to deal with him."

"Truthfully speaking, our Bei tribe also has enslavement path Gu Masters, our tribe's forest soldier corps which has made its name in northern plains; it can completely face Chang Shan Yin. Besides them, Zheng tribe has the renowned lightning spear battle formation while Pei tribe leader Lord Pei Yan Fei is a famous expert in northern plains and has already advanced to rank four peak stage. Even if Wolf King has much more troops, Lord Pei Yan Fei can move past the troops and directly attack and kill the Wolf King!"

It was common knowledge that enslavement path Gu Masters feared beheading the leader tactics.

As long as this tactic succeeded, even a huge army of millions would immediately fall into chaos and flee in disorder.

Wang tribe leader, however, was still hesitating, and evaded it saying he needed a few days to consider as it was a serious matter.

Disappointment flashed past Bei Cao Sheng's eyes: "This is a serious matter, it makes sense for Wang tribe leader to consider it carefully. However, this matter cannot be delayed, if we allow the Ge tribe to recover their senses and digest the spoils of the war, our losses when we fight will be much more larger. Please take note of this, lord tribe leader."

Wang tribe leader nodded: "At most three days, during this period, you can stay in our tribe and receive our warmest welcome."

Bei Cao Sheng could only take the initiative to say his farewell after hearing these words.

When he had just left the hall, a person entered.

This person was thin with a yellowish face, there were three strands of beard on his chin and a pair of sharp and bright eyes. He was Wang tribe leader's competent assistant; Wang tribe elder Wang De Dao, an experienced strategist.

"Lord tribe leader, are we really going to agree to Bei tribe and join this alliance?" Wang De Dao asked with some worries.

"Hehehe, of course not, you don't need to worry." Wang tribe leader laughed.

Wang De Dao let out a breath of relief: "Tribe leader is wise to not be bewitched by others. The power struggle for Imperial Court is arriving, and years of battle will follow it. Preserving strength is our main priority. The thoughts of Bei, Pei and Zheng tribe, these three mid scale tribes, are very clear. Yan tribe is in-laws of Liu tribe, Yan Cui Er is Liu tribe young master's fiancee. They are thinking of becoming dogs of Liu tribe, to curry favor with Lord Liu Wen Wu, but they want to involve my tribe to share the risks."

"Yes." Wang tribe leader nodded, "Our Wang tribe is a large scale tribe, we need to make our moves very carefully. The struggle for the Imperial Court is like a battle of dragons and snakes; in the end, who can become the final winner? We need to observe carefully and choose the side we are siding with."

Every ten years in northern plains, there would be a terrifying and shocking blizzard.

Only by entering the Imperial Court, could one have protection to not be affected by the blizzard.

But the quota in Imperial Court was limited; there were too many that wanted to enter, thus they would go through bitter battle, and after eliminating the weak, the master of the Imperial Court would be decided.

Wang tribe might be a large scale tribe but was classified as those tribes with superficial foundation, having no intents to vie for the throne. They only wanted to side with the correct force and become the one with the greatest contribution, thus entering the Imperial Court and avoiding the disaster.

"If we can't enter the Imperial Court, our tribe will definitely suffer disastrous damage during the blizzard. We will fall from our current large scale force to mid scale, small scale or even complete extermination with a high probability. But if we can enter Imperial Court, through the support of the resources of Imperial Court, we can recuperate and if our luck is good, we can have the qualifications to vie for the next rulership of Imperial Court!" Wang De Dao said with a grave expression.

This matter concerned the survival and prosperity of the whole Wang tribe; every Wang tribesman was cautious and careful.

"Then, how should we deal with Bei Cao Sheng?" Wang tribe leader asked.

Wang De Dao stroked his beard and said after a while: "We should properly entertain this person, and three days later, we can tactfully decline their alliance invitation. At the same time, we will send a letter to Ge tribe behind their back, to express our goodwill to the Wolf King and tell them of this matter. Let them fight each other while we will watch safely from the sideline. If there is an opportunity, we can have no worries in benefiting from their conflict."

"Hahaha, your words deeply resonates with my heart." Wang tribe leader could not help laughing heartily.

Gazing at the letter in his hand, Ge tribe leader Ge Guang had a worried expression.

All the Ge tribe elders beside him were also silent.

The atmosphere had become so heavy in the main tent that it was almost suffocating.

"Bei, Pei and Zheng tribe have allied to combine their strength and pass judgement to our tribe. They are wantonly attracting more allies now. Wang tribe leader has sent this information secretly, I am afraid not long later, the allied army would make their move. Elders, do you have any good plans?" Ge Guang asked.

"This matter is not looking good. Our tribe has just absorbed Yan tribe, although our morale is high, we have yet to digest the spoils of the war."

"If the enemy invades us, it is hard to say if the Yan tribe captives we have won't rise up in rebellion."

"At that time, with both external and internal threats, our Ge tribe won't be far from extermination!"

"Then should we retreat?"

"Retreat? Where? We have a camp now and can defend our positions. But if we retreat, there will be nothing to protect us, do we just wait for those tribes to surround us then?"

The elders started discussing.

Ge Guang looked at them with a disappointed gaze, the elders were just making random comments with no one giving reasonable suggestion.

This instead caused the atmosphere in the tent to become more repressing and was vaguely shaking up their battle will.

"Alright, no need to say anymore." He raised his hand and put an end to the discussion.

"I won't hide this from you, few days ago, Lord Wolf King Chang Shan Yin has agreed to become our tribe's supreme elder. We need to invite him to discuss this matter." Ge Guang revealed the news.

He had kept this news hidden, now that he said it out, it was like a cardiac stimulant that caused the elders to feel a rush of morale.

"Lord Wolf King has become our tribe's supreme elder?"

"Great, great, this is a cause for celebration!"

"With Lord Wolf King with us, we have a chance of survival."

The suppressing atmosphere in the tent was immediately swept clean and the fallen morale rapidly soared. This was the effect of an expert; in times of crisis, they were the main pillar that could hold up the sky and earth.

Seeing this, Ge Guang realized why only Gu Masters with high cultivation could become the ones in power in tribes.

Chapter 479: Good weather to kill

Fang Yuan was invited into Ge tribe's main tent.

"Oh, three tribes are allying to deal with us?" Fang Yuan heard this and his eyes shone, asking: "Which three?"

An elder immediately replied: "Reporting to lord supreme elder, it is Pei tribe, Bei tribe, and Zheng tribe."

Pausing for a second, this elder continued: "Pei tribe's Pei Yan Fei has rank four peak stage cultivation, he is a fierce general famous in northern plains. Although Bei tribe is only a middle-sized tribe, it has two enslavement path Gu Masters. As for Zheng tribe, although they were created not too long ago, their lightning spear battle formation is nothing to be trifled with."

Fang Yuan nodded, he had heard a familiar name, that was Pei Yan Fei.

This person was truly a fierce general in northern plains, after joining Liu Wen Wu, he became Liu tribe's third general.

In the future battles, he often fought his way into enemy formations alone, assaulting and disrupting their battle formations, as he charged through unstoppably, he aimed for the leader's head.

As for Bei tribe and Zheng tribe, although Fang Yuan had no memories of them, it did not obstruct him from estimating their strength.

Either of these two tribes were equal to Ge tribe back in Hong Yan valley.

Bei tribe had two enslavement path Gu Masters, this meant that they could resist Fang Yuan's wolf group head on. As for Zheng tribe, it seemed that they grew to power using the lightning spear battle formation, this was Zheng tribe's trump card, it could not be underestimated.

"However, I need large numbers of souls to feed Dang Hun mountain and strengthen my own soul. The alliance of the three tribes will allow me to kill many people right? Hehehe."

Thinking so, Fang Yuan's lips curled into a cold smile.

"Right now, the three tribes have allied, the situation is precarious, uncle Chang Shan Yin, what should Ge tribe do?" Ge Guang was yearning for an answer.

Fang Yuan raised his brows, his words oozing with killing intent: "What can we do? Since they want to kill us anyway, we will strike first and attack them immediately! You have to know, the best defense is offense!"

"What? Attack?!"

Hearing this, Ge tribe higher-ups were shocked.

In their earlier discussions, some people suggested retreating, some suggested defending, but no one had suggested attacking.

This idea was too aggressive and risky. After all, the power of the three allied tribes greatly surpassed Ge tribe. Now that Ge tribe had just assimilated Yan tribe's captives, they had internal woes as well.

"Is it too crazy to just attack them now?" The elders looked at each other, sensing each others worry from their expressions. But because of Fang Yuan's attitude, they did not dare to speak out.

At once, everyone went silent.

Ge Guang hesitated for a while, before meekly saying: "Uncle Chang Shan Yin, the enemy is strong while we are weak, but we are going to strike first and give up on defending the camp?"

Fang Yuan snorted: "If you are thinking like this, so are our enemies. Precisely so, we have to initiate the attack and catch them off guard."

"Tonight, we shall gather our forces and assault them in the dark! Which tribe is the closest to us?"

"The closest is Bei Tribe, following by Zheng tribe and then Pei tribe who are the furthest." Ge Guang replied.

Fang Yuan smiled coldly: "Very good, then we shall wipe out Bei tribe first, before slaughtering Zheng tribe and then find a chance to finish off Pei tribe. This battle will be tragic, be mentally prepared. But we cannot make progress without sacrifices, after we devour the three tribes, our Ge tribe will strengthen even further."

The tribe elders looked at each other, tongue-tied, shocked by Fang Yuan's ambition.

With Ge tribe's current situation, he still wanted to devour the allied enemies who were two to three times stronger than them. This was unimaginable.

Seeing the hesitant gang, Fang Yuan waved his hand: "Then that will be the plan, go and prepare for it."

"Yes." The higher-ups replied.

That night, the night winds blew and the moon was high in the sky.

Ge tribe camp opened its gates as the wolves ran out like a flowing river. Countless Gu Masters were mixed in with them, as they charged forward with strong killing intent.

"What a good weather, this is a perfect weather to kill people." Fang Yuan sat on a mutated beast as he laughed.

This mutated beast was that white-eyes wolf, it was an infant earlier, but after Fang Yuan used the time path Gu worm to accelerate its growth, it rapidly aged. Now, this white-eyes wolf was several times its original size.

Having a body of white snow-like fur, its body shape was slim and smooth like water, only slightly smaller than a hump wolf.

But its current battle strength was only comparable to an ordinary hundred wolf king. There were no wild Gu inside its body.

Time was needed for wild Gu to live in a beast king. During a beast king's long period of growth, multiple wild Gu worms would come to seek refuge with them.

But this white-eyes wolf grew too fast, it lacked the foundation built with time, and because it was always by Fang Yuan's side, there were no Gu on it.

Because of that, Fang Yuan used it as his steed and let it accompany him. Sometimes, using its vision, he could scout areas quickly.

The army moved quickly towards Bei tribe.

Bei tribe camp was situation on a mound, there were originally many trees on the mound, but now they were all removed and a tall wall was erected all around Bei tribe camp.

On the wall, there were observational towers that were giving off a bright light, lighting up the dark camp. On the surface of the wall, there were wooden spikes and several Bei tribe Gu Masters were standing at set intervals, giving off a strong impregnable aura.

"Lord, are we really attacking?" The army stealthily got closer as Ge Guang observed the wall, his heart jumped as he had the urge to retreat.

Fang Yuan laughed: "We will definitely win."

"What does lord supreme elder mean?" An elder did not understand and asked.

Fang Yuan pointed at the wall: "Precise because of the sturdy wall, these Bei tribe Gu Masters are complacent, sending only a few Gu Masters to guard it. The fact that we could get to near to them is proof of this. Furthermore, this light is too bright, it shows Bei tribe's intention to scare off the weak. Such a false bravado, while attempting to show that they were a stronghold, revealed all their little secrets."

Hearing this, Ge tribesmen were assured.

Fang Yuan instructed again: "Later, I will send the wolves to crush the wall, you will send the Yan tribe captives to charge and lead the way, while Ge tribe Gu Masters watch them. If anyone tries to rebel or run away, kill them on the spot!"

His icy cold voice made everyone shudder.

The moment he said that, before waiting for the elders to react, Fang Yuan waved his hand as two myriad wolf kings led their wolf groups and rushed out. In a few breaths' time, they got into the lighted area.

"Wolves, why are there so many wolves?!" Bei tribe Gu Masters rubbed their eyes, finding it unbelievable.

"Enemy assault, enemy assault!!" Some people reacted and shouted loudly, using their Gu worms to send signals.

"Block them, reinforcements are coming!" The Gu Masters shouted with all their strength.

But Fang Yuan's attack was ferocious and overwhelming, it was like two iron fists that had been storing energy for a day.

The battle strength of a myriad wolf king was not to be underestimated, often, a rank four Gu Master and multiple rank three experts were needed to deal with one.

Two myriad wolf kings, under Fang Yuan's manipulation, unleashed their strongest attacks without hesitation.

Bam! Bam! Bam!

Every impact was soul shaking. The study wall swayed in the wind like a flimsy paper.

Especially the turtleback myriad wolf king, it had a thick skin and a strong body, it caused the most damage to the wall.

Bei tribe Gu Masters were busy retaliating, but their scattered attacks were blocked by the myriad wolf king's defensive Gu.

When Bei tribe's reinforcements arrived in a hurry, they saw the collapse of an entire segment of the wall. Two myriad wolf kings led their endless wolf armies as they charged into the camp.

"Night wolf myriad beast king! Turtleback myriad wolf king!" Bei tribe leader saw this sight and he was shocked out of his wits.

These were two types of wolves, as wild wolf groups, they will never work together. This situation only meant one thing, there was someone controlling them.

Who was the culprit?

Bei tribe leader did not need to think twice before a name appeared in his heart — Wolf King Chang Shan Yin!

"Chang Shan Yin..." Bei tribe leader gritted his teeth and fire almost spewed out of his eyes.

But his fury could not stop the attack of the wolf group.

So be it if they were ordinary wolves, but under Fang Yuan's control, strength and knowledge became the best companions.

Bei tribe tried resisting, and formed many defensive formations, but the wolf group charged without worry for casualties, it was an all-out attack.

The Ge tribe Gu Masters behind the wolf group were like spectators.

Rank four — grass puppet Gu!

Bei tribe leader injected his primeval essence into the grass below his feet.

The grass grew to the size of a person, turning into a grass puppet, holding a green leaf long sword.

This was the grass sword elite soldier!

Large numbers of grass sword elite soldiers charged towards the wolf group.

The grass sword elite soldiers successfully resisted the wolf group's attack, they formed a formation near the main tent and blocked the wolves like a green monolith.

But this situation was only temporary, when Bei tribe leader's primeval essence was used up, the grass sword elite soldiers were out of steam and the monolith became smaller, submerged by the wolves.

"Retreat, we will retreat to Zheng tribe! As long we are alive, Bei tribe will have the hopes of returning one day." Bei tribe leader saw that the defeat was set in stone and resolutely decided to retreat.

"Hahaha." Fang Yuan rode the white-eyes wolf as he looked at the escaping Bei tribesmen, laughing loudly.

"Lord, we won!" Ge Guang said excitedly.

"We've only won the first out of three battles. Leave some people behind to clean up the battlefield, we will chase them!" Fang Yuan waved and the tens of thousands of wolves howled and changed directions towards Zheng tribe.

"They are chasing us!" The Bei tribe Gu Masters who were escaping saw such a grand army and were scared till their souls trembled.

"No wait, Chang Shan Yin's next target is Zheng tribe." Someone understood.

"Not only did he take down our tribe, he also wants to take down Zheng tribe?!" Someone furiously screamed.

"Tribe leader, what do we do? My primeval essence is almost used up, soon, they will catch up." Someone shouted frantically.

Bei tribe leader hesitated for a moment, he did not have much primeval essence left, he could only change directions and enter the forest near him.

Fang Yuan led the army and ignored these people, charging straight for Zheng tribe.

"He did not chase us, he went to Zheng tribe after all." Bei tribe's higher-ups breathed roughly, standing in the forest, they watched the stampede of over ten thousand wolves.

Bei tribe leader's expression was solemn, the veins on his fists were about to burst, the hatred in his heart and the flames of fury almost incinerated him, but there was nothing he could do!

Chapter 480: Go die, go die

"Prepare the lightning spears!" Zheng tribe leader shouted furiously as he went to the frontline.

After crushing Bei tribe, Fang Yuan led his army without stopping towards Zheng tribe camp.

A bitter battle erupted instantly.

Fang Yuan commanded two myriad beast kings to attack together, breaking through Zheng tribe's two defensive lines in moments. However, at the third line, they were finally stopped.

The ones who stopped the wolf tide was Zheng tribe's renowned trump card — the lightning spear corps.

These rank two Gu Masters stood in a row on the walls, emitting strong elite aura; forging a wall made of flesh and blood.

Hearing the tribe leader's shout, these Gu Masters immediately pushed forward their right hand and poured their primeval essence into the lightning imprint on their right palm.

This was the imprint of the lightning spear Gu.

Next, Ge tribesmen saw lightning emitting out of these Gu Masters' palms before forming into silverish blue colored spears.

These spears were four feet long and were completely condensed from lightning; lightning flickered and emitted a soft sizzling sound.

"Shoot!" Zheng tribe leader shouted.

Whoosh!

In an instant, five hundred and eighty lightning spears flew together and drew a dense arc in the sky.

The shining lightning illuminated the battlefield for a moment. The blue light shone on everyone's faces.

The difference was Ge Guang and his group had ashen expressions, while Zheng tribe leader had a proud smile.

Lightning spears rained down upon the charging wolf group.

Even though turtleback wolves had strong shells, they were still pierced by the lightning spears. Let alone the wind wolves and night wolves who were weak in defense.

The volley of lightning spears showed an extraordinary might, instantly clearing up a large area of the battlefield.

The densely packed wolf group also became thinner.

Over five hundred wolves fell, dead. The offense of the wolf group had slowed down.

"Hahaha, look, this is our tribe's lightning spear corps!"

"With such strong troops, who dares to look down on our tribe?"

"This is the strongest blood and flesh wall of our tribe, what could happen to us even if there were more wolves?"

Zheng tribe's Gu Masters shouted in excitement at this sight, their morale increasing rapidly. In contrast, Ge tribesmen had grave expressions.

"Chang Shan Yin." Zheng tribe leader used sound amplification Gu to amplify his voice, suppressing all the chaotic noises of the battlefield.

"You invaded my tribe without rhyme or reason, the heroes assembly has not started yet but you are recklessly starting a war with no care for law and order. Your brutal massacre will be punished by all the tribes of northern plains. You have not made a great mistake yet, you still have a chance at redemption, retreat quickly! Otherwise, I shall let the world know of your evil nature, you and the Ge tribe behind you shall be called rats by all northern plainsmen!" Zheng tribe leader berated and warned.

"Lord supreme elder..." Ge tribe's elders looked towards Fang Yuan with hesitation on their faces.

Fang Yuan's mad war campaign was indeed violating the rules. Although the three tribes allied to deal with Ge tribe, they had yet to act. Just relying on the evidence gathered by Ge tribe, they could not prove anything.

Northern plains Gu Masters liked to battle but they did not battle recklessly and everything was based on proper reasons.

The more sensible and grand the reasons were, the better it was.

Moreover, the struggle for the Imperial Court had not begun yet, so the tribes were mutually restraining each other. Back when Ge tribe was at Hong Yan valley, Man tribe clearly had more strength than Ge tribe, but they still did not make a direct move. Instead, they used schemes to create a wolf tide. This was because Man tribe did not have a proper reason to swallow Ge tribe.

This was the rule of the righteous path, the game rule between the tribes of northern plains.

Fang Yuan leading Ge tribe to invade the three tribes alliance was clearly breaking this rule. They were attacking without appropriate reasons which meant their actions lacked righteousness.

Ge tribe's invasive conduct which reeked of demonic nature would cause them to be isolated; other tribes might be vigilant towards them or even attack them.

Thus, Ge tribe's higher-ups were worried. But because of Chang Shan Yin's strength and prestige, they did not openly oppose him.

Right now, the wolf group's offense was obstructed and the Ge tribesmen were starting to show the first signs of worries.

Fang Yuan sat indifferently on the mutated beast white-eyes wolf, gazing at those Gu Masters on the wall.

"The lightning spear corps are indeed extraordinary."

His gaze continued to flash as he saw the ingenuity behind this

In the entire lightning spear corps, there were over five hundred offensive Gu Masters, but the truly important characters were the hundred or so support Gu Masters who were hiding in the corner and were strictly defended.

These Gu Masters used their Gu worms to strengthen the power of the lightning spears or condense the force of the lightning spears into an even stronger attack.

Fang Yuan then looked at the night wolf myriad beast king as well as turtleback myriad wolf king.

These two wolf kings were obstructed by Zheng tribe leader personally along with the lightning spear corps' combined strength, so they had no choice but to retreat.

Their bodies were riddled with wounds. Turtleback myriad wolf king was slightly better, but the night wolf myriad beast king's defense Gu was killed, its entire body was covered with blood and some wounds were so deep, one could even see the bone.

Even though Fang Yuan used wolf smoke Gu to heal most of these wounds, the night wolf myriad beast king's strength had dropped by a level.

Retreat?

Does retreating mean that the others won't pursue?

Fang Yuan sneered, retreating was the fastest way to die.

Only by advancing without stopping, charging forward, defeating the three tribe alliance, annihilating the survivors, could the bad influence of breaking northern plains rules be reduced to the minimum.

Right now, Ge tribe was like a drawn bow, there was no other option but to press on.

Ge tribe's higher-ups were short-sighted, so they could not see the situation clearly. But Fang Yuan, with his five hundred years of experience, naturally was a seasoned veteran and could clearly see the situation.

"Everyone, we are at the most crucial moment now. Ge tribesmen, charge forward, fight to the death, whoever dares to retreat a step shall be killed without question!" Fang Yuan shouted coldly while actively mobilizing all the remaining forces with him.

Howl!

Wind wolf myriad beast king lead the wind wolf group and rushed to the battlefield. Fang Yuan had been intentionally hiding this myriad wolf king outside. He had not brought it to Ge tribe camp and did not use it even when attacking Bei tribe.

"The third myriad wolf king!" Ge tribe and Zheng tribe's Gu Masters changed expression at the sight of this wind wolf king.

Ge tribe's higher-ups revealed joy, while Zheng tribe's Gu Masters felt like a heavy stone had landed on their hearts.

Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with cruel killing intent; he waved his hand and the three wolf kings rushed forward together.

Seeing three myriad wolf kings charge together, Zheng tribe leader's expression paled and furiously attacked.

Killer move — Thunder Bird!

The primeval sea level in his aperture violently dropped as three Gu worms were activated together, forming an enormous lightning bird in the air.

The giant bird flew towards the turtleback myriad wolf king and obstructed it.

"Lightning spear corps, shoot together!" Zheng tribe leader hastily shouted.

Hundreds of lightning spears were shot to the sky. Support Gu Masters acted together, converging the flying lightning spears together. In the blink of an eye, the lightning spears combined to form into a lightning snake.

Eagle claw Gu!

A rank three elder suddenly activated his Gu at the lightning snake. The lightning snake immediately grew out two sharp and steel-like claws.

Rhino horn Gu!

Another Zheng tribe elder activated his Gu; a sharp golden horn grew out of the lightning snake's head.

Silver scales Gu!

Another elder added bright silver colored, firm scale armor on the lightning snake's body.

This completely armed lightning spear made a circle in the air, looking like a divine dragon descending into the world. Next, it charged down valiantly towards the wind wolf myriad beast king.

"This move again." Fang Yuan's eyes twitched; previously, the night wolf myriad beast king had been obstructed by this killer move and suffered serious injuries.

This was the killer move — Gold and Silver Lightning Dragon!

Gu Masters nurtured, used and refined Gu; each aspect was a deep field of study. There was the killer move in the aspect of using Gu.

Some Gu Master experts would exquisitely activate many Gu worms' abilities consecutively in a very short period and fuse them into an even stronger attack. This was a killer move.

Normal killer moves were activated by one Gu Master. Like Zheng tribe leader's killer move thunder bird.

The gold and silver lightning dragon, however, was a killer move formed from the cooperation of hundreds of Gu Masters. It condensed the strength of hundreds of Gu Masters as well as rank three experts into an extremely terrifying attack.

As it was obstructed by gold and silver lightning dragon, the wind wolf myriad beast king had no hopes of advancing further temporarily.

However, Fang Yuan was not discouraged.

He still had a myriad wolf king!

Night wolf myriad beast king began a crazed assault under his control.

"Block it, block it!"

"Hold it back even if you die."

"Tribesmen, our parents, wives, children, brothers and sisters are behind us, we absolutely cannot lose!"

"This myriad beast king no longer has its defense Gu, we still have hope!!"

Zheng tribe's Gu Masters raised their morale and attacked fiercely.

Countless attacks shone brilliantly like fireworks as they landed on the night wolf myriad beast king's body.

This night wolf myriad beast king's defense Gu had already died. The attacks easily caused its flesh to lacerate, causing it to howl bitterly in pain.

The intense pain agitated the night wolf myriad beast king; its eyes reddened, its killing intent burst out and its offense became fiercer.

"Damn it!" Seeing the night wolf myriad beast king kill the lightning spear corps, destroying Zheng tribe's most precious trump card, Zheng tribe leader almost spurted out blood in anger.

However, he could not go to stop it, as right now, he was using all his strength to pin down turtleback myriad wolf king.

To protect their home and family, Zheng tribe's Gu Masters burst out with much greater strength.

"Die beast!" A rank three elder dashed out without a thought for his safety and flew towards the night wolf myriad beast king's eyes, fiercely piercing forwarding with his hands.

The night wolf king had no time to dodge and its eyes were pierced.

Amidst the incomparable pain, it opened its mouth and bit this rank three elder apart.

The rank three elder's body was split into two; but he had a smile on his face before dying.

He used his final trace of primeval essence to inflict heavy injuries on the night wolf king.

Such a situation was not rare. To block the night wolf king, many Zheng tribe's Gu Masters chose to sacrifice themselves and protect their home.

"Truly brave warriors!" Fang Yuan praised while laughing coldly.

In his mind, Fang Yuan sensed the night wolf king's intense desire to retreat. But he did not allow that and forcibly made it continue attacking.

Lightning spear corps suffered serious losses in the intense fight with the night wolf king, not even ten percent survived. With there being no decent resistance, Ge tribe's Gu Masters charged out and created an opening rapidly.

The scales of victory tilted towards Fang Yuan.

Time passed, gold and silver lightning dragon dissipated in the air and the wind wolf king became free; under Fang Yuan's control, it started killing Zheng tribe elders.

Next, the wolf group charged inside Zheng tribe camp like a tide, mercilessly killing the old, the weak, women and children.

Wretched screams, despairing shouts and shrieks resounded throughout the battlefield.

"Die, go and die, the more deaths there are, the more souls I can obtain." Fang Yuan looked expressionlessly at this living hell, as he secretly used his storage Gu.

Chapter 481: Bei Cao Chuan

In a distant dark corner, close to ten people were gazing at the battlefield; they were the higher-ups of Bei tribe who had escaped.

"Zheng tribe is done for." Bei tribe leader Bei Cao Chuan sighed.

"Who would have thought Chang Shan Yin had a third myriad wolf king!" An elder exclaimed in shock, expressing everyone's inner thoughts.

They had never expected Fang Yuan to be hiding his strength. In the attack against Bei clan, this myriad wolf king had been hidden all along and never made its appearance.

"With three myriad wolf kings, it is normal for Zheng tribe, a mid scale tribe, to be defeated even if they have the lightning spear corps."

"However, Chang Shan Yin is really sinister, he could actually wait so patiently to this degree. Such temperament is terrifying!"

"Hehe, so what? Zheng tribe leader killed night wolf myriad beast king before his death. Now, Chang Shan Yin only has two myriad wolf kings left."

Some of the remnant Bei tribe elders sighed with sorrow while some sneered.

Capturing a myriad beast king was not an easy matter. Fang Yuan's loss appeared to be very disastrous to them.

But in fact, replenishing the myriad wolf king was only a thought away for Fang Yuan who could connect to treasure yellow heaven.

"This Chang Shan Yin is crazy and cruel, he could have made the night wolf myriad beast king retreat temporarily, but he kept on pushing it firmly, leading to its death." An elder said with a chill in his heart.

Bei tribe leader narrowed his eyes, recalling the battlefield that was vivid in his mind: "If he had not pushed this strongly, they might not have been able to settle the battle so quickly. Ge tribe is unable to sustain a battle of attrition when attacking a large group with their small group. Chang Shan Yin's move was very wise."

"It is a pity Zheng tribe leader also died. He was a rank four upper stage expert, if he could have lived..." Bei tribe elders sighed.

The reason for this was also because Zheng tribe leader was overly fond of battles, using all his strength to fight with the enemy. After a long battle, his primeval essence was greatly consumed, but when he wanted to escape, his path was cut off by night wolf myriad beast king and in the end, did not manage to escape.

And Zheng tribe's lightning spear corps were almost completely exterminated with only two to three small-fry remaining.

These two matters were fatal strikes to Zheng tribe's morale.

Their tribe leader sacrificed himself and the corps was exterminated; Zheng tribe lost resistance and was utterly destroyed.

Ge tribesmen charged into the camp and unfolded an unrestrained massacre. Zheng tribe showed no intent to battle and did their best to escape; cries of agony and pleading could be heard endlessly.

There even appeared scenes where a rank one Gu Master chased after two to three rank two Gu Masters.

It was not that these rank two Gu Masters did not want to fight, but their primeval essence had been severely consumed in the battle with the wolf group.

Without primeval essence, a Gu Master's battle strength would fall to the abyss.

The remnant Bei tribesmen fell into silence as they saw Zheng tribe's miserable state.

They could not help thinking back to the scene where their own camp was attacked; everyone of them gnashed their teeth and clenched their fists, their heart filled with fury and also a bleak feeling.

Chaos was descending!

Every ten years in Northern Plains, a disastrous blizzard would appear, causing great unrest where heroes rose and vied for supremacy.

At that time, the unrest would spread to the entire Northern Plains; this situation was no more than a prelude of it.

Human lives would be cheap as grass as tribes wandered around without a home. Small or mid scale tribes would be like duckweed, being involuntarily swept up by the whirlpool of the battle; they could be crushed if they were in the slightest bit careless.

Even large scale tribes had to be extremely cautious and careful. Only those super tribes who had Gu Immortals and possessed blessed lands had the foundation to remain standing for ages.

"Lord tribe leader, our primeval essence is already recovered. Originally, we wanted to rescue Zheng tribe, but they are already defeated now. Why don't we go back and take down the Ge tribesmen at our camp and save our tribesmen!" At this moment, an elder suggested.

"Right, Chang Shan Yin's appetite is too big. He broke through our camp, then went on to destroy Zheng tribe. According to his crazy momentum, he might even be going to Pei tribe. We need to take the opportunity to go back and kill them."

"The people Ge tribe left behind there might be more in number, but they are all rank one and rank two Gu Masters, with only one rank three elder."

The elders could not help being agitated as they looked at their tribe leader.

Although they had fewer numbers, all of them had rank three cultivation while their tribe leader was at rank four realm. With such strength they had a huge chance to go back and save their tribe.

However, the young Bei tribe leader shook his head and resolutely refused: "We cannot! Although Ge tribe left behind very few people and we can go to seize back our camp, but what happens after that? We are too few in numbers, information about our return will definitely leak. After Chang Shan Yin obtains the news and if he returns, would we be able to defend? Can we escape safely with our tribesmen?"

The group of elders went mute.

Bei Cao Chuan was correct.

When they had been defending before, they were at full strength, yet they were still broken by the wolf tide, let alone now.

"Let them become captives. Relax, you saw that after the battle ended, Ge tribe bound the tribesmen and did not kill them. They want to expand their strength, hmph, their appetite is too big!"

Bei Cao Chuan snorted and continued: "We will leave our tribesmen with them for the moment. In a short period of time, this will cause their rations to be consumed and they will have to use more manpower and divide more energy."

An elder's eyes suddenly brightened: "Then why don't we directly attack their nest? Ge tribe is only a mid-sized tribe now and they have brought out almost all their forces; their camp definitely has poor defenses right now. We will kill and loot, empty their rations and increase the burden on them, and let them have a taste of being attacked!"

"Good idea!"

"Right, this is a good way!"

"I will definitely let Ge tribe taste the pain of being homeless!!"

The elders discussed in excitement.

"Fools!" Bei tribe leader slammed the suggestion and looked at everyone with a chilly and sharp gaze, "Do you all have pig brains? If we destroy their rations, the ones who would suffer would be our tribesmen. You think they won't kill the captives to reduce the consumption? If someone recognized us, what will we do if they kill the captives to vent their anger?"

Bei Cao Chuan let out a breath of turbid air, his eyes shining with wisdom as he said in a heavy voice: "True revenge is not indulging in quick pleasure. Attacking Ge tribe camp is a small thing, we can't hurt their foundation with it. Only by killing Chang Shan Yin, removing Ge tribe's main source of power, can we overturn the situation! We need to fight."

These words enlightened all the elders.

"Lord tribe leader is wise!"

"With lord tribe leader with us, our tribe has hope."

"We will listen to tribe leader's arrangements!"

The elders looked at Bei tribe leader with respect and admiration.

Bei tribe leader Bei Cao Chuan was also an outstanding person!

He had been pushed aside by his siblings when he was young; the most unlikely candidate to the young master position.

He took less actions, disguised his strength and showed a low cultivation, thus he would be taunted and ridiculed by his siblings in banquets and gatherings.

Bei Cao Chuan was an expert at enduring silently, he restrained himself from making a move. His brothers had internal conflicts while he silently accumulated his strength.

When the old Bei tribe leader was critically ill, he finally got the opportunity.

The old Bei tribe leader was injured because of a backlash from a Gu worm and required a specific Gu to heal. However, the tribe found that this Gu was residing in a spirit rhino myriad beast king.

The spirit rhino beast group had about eighty thousand in numbers, the tribe could do nothing and gave up all hope; but Bei Cao Chuan infiltrated the beast group's dwelling by himself.

After several days of observation, he discovered this spirit rhino myriad beast king would occasionally leave his group to roll and play in a mud swamp. After it played to its fill, it would sleep soundly.

The mud was as smelly as dung and many maggots lived in it; Bei Cao Chuan buried himself in the mud for seven days and seven nights without moving.

Hard work paid off; the spirit rhino myriad beast king finally came again to play. However, spirit rhino myriad beast king was huge and when it rolled about, it stepped on Bei Cao Chuan's leg, crushing it immediately.

Bei Cao Chuan silently endured the pain and did not even let out a groan!

When the myriad beast king played to its fill and was sleeping soundly, he quietly stole that wild Gu worm from the myriad beast king's body.

Bei Cao Chuan obtained the wild Gu worm; and he narrowly escaped this dangerous place, moving without stopping, hopping back to the tribe with his one leg and saved the old tribe leader.

The whole tribe was in an uproar!

Bei Cao Chuan's actions contained shocking filial piety, outstanding courage and meticulous planning; causing the whole tribe to look at him in a new light.

His siblings were also extremely surprised when he revealed his rank three peak stage cultivation.

After the old tribe leader survived, he emotionally shed tears: "The number of times I have cried in my life can be counted by my fingers. Today, I am crying not because I managed to escape from death's door, but because I have a son like this; as a father, I am moved by his filial piety, and as the tribe leader, I am happy for the future of my tribe!"

On the spot, Bei Cao Chuan was appointed as young tribe leader.

Bei Cao Chuan did not conceal himself anymore, he started to deal with all the tribe affairs and fought for everyone's approval. On another hand, he suppressed his siblings and fortified his position, not giving any opportunity to his competitors.

In the end, he became the tribe leader and made vigorous efforts to gradually expand Bei tribe. After repeatedly overcoming several difficulties, he had finally walked to this day.

Although Bei Cao Chuan was only about thirty or so, he had established deep prestige within the tribe and was trusted by all the elders!

.......

"Lord supreme elder, lord tribe leader and elders, we have already finished controlling Zheng tribe camp and have gained a lot of resources!" The elder who was in charge of cleaning the battlefield reported excitedly.

"From our initial estimations, we have obtained at least eight million primeval stones. We have obtained thousands of Gu worms with a hundred rank three Gu among them. There is also a Gu house secret room which we are opening right now."

Listening to such spoils of war, Ge tribesmen had extreme joy in their face.

The gains from Zheng tribe was much more than from Bei tribe.

Zheng tribe was a mid-sized tribe, but was a tribe with deep foundation. Even though there were much losses in the battle, the resources that were preserved were still enormous.

"Lord supreme elder, lord tribe leader, what should be our next course of action?" This elder asked after he finished reporting.

All the Ge tribesmen looked at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan said expressionlessly: "Continue attacking, our next target: Pei tribe!"

Chapter 482: Pei Yan Fei

The night wind whistled and the wolf group howled.

Pei tribe and Ge tribe were fighting an intense battle around the walls.

Flames, golden light, lightning, vines, all kinds of attacks converged to become a scene of brilliant fireworks, lifting the veil of the night.

"Kill, break the walls, then we can destroy the Pei tribe!"

"Fight them, kill these Ge tribe thieves!!"

The two sides roared with all their might to boost up their morale.

Thick blood smell was lingering around the battlefield.

Large numbers of cut limbs and bodies were everywhere. The normally respected Gu Masters had lives as cheap as grass here. Of course, there were even more corpses of wolves.

Seeing the turtleback myriad wolf king being repelled back again, Fang Yuan sighed to himself.

Because they had charged through Bei and Zheng tribe one after another, information was inevitably leaked; when Fang Yuan led Ge tribesmen to attack Pei tribe, the other side had already made tight defensive preparations.

After losing the night wolf myriad beast king, Fang Yuan only had two myriad wolf kings left - turtleback myriad wolf king and wind wolf myriad wolf king.

Originally, the attacks from both kings would pose threat to Pei tribe's defensive formations. But because of one person, Fang Yuan could only send one myriad beast king to attack.

This person was Pei tribe leader Pei Yan Fei!

He was the focus point of this battlefield, being in even more limelight than Fang Yuan's two myriad beast kings.

Pei Yan Fei was eight feet tall with a stately appearance. His eyes were sharp and full of power, his back wide and his waist thin; right now, he was charging through the wolf group, sweeping everything in his path and revealing the demeanor of an unparalleled general.

The characteristic that was the most focused on was his black eyebrows that shone with a dark luster. The eyebrows were thick in the middle and sharp in their two ends with the tip raised slightly, like a swallow's wings.

This was not a natural characteristic but the imprint of two rank four swallow wings Gu.

It was precisely because of this person rampaging around the battlefield with no one able to hold him down that Fang Yuan had to make one myriad wolf king stay for protection to defend against Pei Yan Fei's sudden attack.

With this, only turtle back myriad wolf king went to battle in the frontline, causing the charge towards Pei tribe to decrease by a lot.

"Ahh!" One Ge tribe elder let out a bitter scream before death.

Following his scream, his head flew to the air; cut by Pei Yan Fei.

"Another elder died under Pei Yan Fei's hands!" Ge tribesmen's eyes twitched at this scene.

Pei Yan Fei did not directly attack Fang Yuan, but instead rampaged in the wolf group and had already killed three Ge tribe's elders.

With this way, he was not entangled by the myriad wolf king and had his hands free. He was also indirectly restricting wind wolf myriad wolf king from fighting. One could see his wisdom along with his bravery.

"Is there anyone else?!" Pei Yan Fei used swallow wings Gu to fly in the air and shouted majestically.

His voice suppressed the wolf howls, and spread clearly to all parts of the battlefield.

Ge tribe was silent while Pei tribe's Gu Masters' morale was greatly increased.

"Truly a fierce general!" Fang Yuan lightly praised.

Pei Yan Fei possessed extremely strong flying techniques, being an expert in low altitude flying. Although he was not at master level, he was not too far from it.

He was a metal path Gu Master; his attacks were very sharp and ordinary Gu Masters would find it hard to block them, and he also possessed outstanding movement ability. He was moving all over the battlefield with a very fast speed, like a celestial horse going wherever it wanted. Usually, those that were stronger than him did not have a movement ability like his; while those that could catch up to him, did not have a battle strength that could match his.

Several times Fang Yuan tried to mobilize wind wolf myriad beast king towards the frontline but Pei Yan Fei would detour and charge towards him.

Ge tribesmen were unable to block him, so Fang Yuan could only make wind wolf king return.

This wind wolf myriad beast king was slightly stronger than Pei Yan Fei, but it was a wild beast after all and did not have enough intelligence. Even if it was controlled by Fang Yuan, its flexibility could not match with Pei Yan Fei.

"I have very few myriad beast kings, it is getting so difficult just to deal with one Pei Yan Fei. The wolf group's scale is also not big. A truly mature beast group would have at least hundred thousand beasts. The current three enslavement masters of Northern Plains - Ma Zun, Yang Po Ying and Jiang Bao Ya - have beast groups of hundreds of thousands of beasts. They even have a small group of mutated beasts as their trump card."

Fang Yuan's mind was on expanding the beast group as he observed the battlefield.

His beast group might have had taken shape, but its strength had clearly weakened after repeatedly fighting three battles. Most of all, the main battle strength was not powerful enough.

The ones that truly decided the war in the Gu Master world were still the high rank Gu Masters.

Fang Yuan pondered while mobilizing thousand wolf kings and hundred wolf kings to lead the wolf group to form a wave of concentrated attack towards the Pei tribe camp.

The wolves howled and charged forward aggressively like a tsunami, causing the Gu Masters on the walls to tense up and hurriedly mobilize everything.

"The attack this time is really fierce, bring the reserve troops here quickly to defend!"

"Earth path Gu Masters, restore the walls fast!"

"Hold on, we must hold on, don't stint on your primeval essence!"

BOOM BOOM BOOM.....

Large amount of flames shot down and exploded towards the wolf group. Golden spears and arrows flew like dense school of fish, striking down on the wolf group, causing massive casualties.

Several elders joined hands and created two-three small scale tornado that that sent the wolves flying fifty-sixty feet high; the wolves fell to their death.

"Let's attack!" Ge tribesmen also started their offence.

Ghost flame Gu!

Two-three balls of eerie blue ghost fire smashed towards the wall, hitting a group of Gu Masters; the Gu Masters' whole bodies were covered with the chilly ghost fire.

They let out the most tragic shouts. The ghost fire did not injure their body, but directly burned their souls; such pain was extremely intense.

Fist stone Gu!

An enormous stone that looked like a clenched fist whizzed through the sky, producing a rumbling sound like that of a lion or tiger, then it heavily smashed on the wall.

A deep crater immediately formed on the wall and the cracks quickly spread towards all directions; the Gu Masters on the wall could not maintain their balance and fell down.

Lightning net Gu!

A large net formed from lightning current flew towards the sky and fell down towards a part of the wall.

The Gu Masters on that part of the wall were paralyzed by the lightning; some stubbornly resisted with their defensive Gu, while some were scorched like coal - dead.

　　...

The fierce explosions caused huge numbers of casualties within a short period of time, and also quickly consumed the Gu Masters' primeval essence. Thus, after a while, they had to stop.

Pei tribe's and Ge tribe's Gu Masters stopped attacking and retreated. Some directly sat down on their spot and grasped every second to recover their primeval essence.

"Now is the time." Fang Yuan's eyes brightened as he saw this while sitting on the white eye wolf.When the two sides were gasping for breath, he made his move.

Wolf smoke Gu!

Wolf smoke surged, covering the battlefield and quickly healing the wolf group's wounds and recovering their battle strength.

Wolf howl Gu!

Fang Yuan let out a long howl towards the sky, and after the mournful howl, the wolf group also roared, their battle strength raising rapidly.

Another portion of wolf group rushed to the battlefield, joining with the remaining wolf group in the battlefield, forming a new wave of attack.

This offensive was directed towards a specific part of the wall.

This part was already on the verge of collapse after being smashed by the giant fist stone.

Howl!

The turtleback myriad wolf king also rushed forward!

The Gu Masters on the wall struggled to stand up and used all kinds of attacks, but turtleback myriad wolf king forcibly resisted the attack and smashed the wall into pieces.

The wall collapsed; a hole appeared in the defensive line. Countless wolves rushed through the hole and started killing Pei tribe's Gu Masters. Pei Yan Fei immediately activated swallow wings Gu to quickly go back.

Rank four golden coat Gu!

His whole body shone with a golden light which then dimmed down and formed an armor.

Rank four swallow wings Gu!

Another pair of swallow wings grew out from his back, and with two pair of wings, his speed was doubled.

Rank four rainbow transformation Gu!

CLAP, he put his two palms together and raised them above his head, his whole body like a straight pencil, then like a golden arrow, he made an arc through the air.

With the activation of the rainbow transformation Gu, his two pairs of wings and his whole body gradually turned into a golden halo.

Three rank four Gu activated together to form into a killer move.

Pei Yan Fei's killer move - Golden Rainbow Strike!

Like a rainbow, his whole body turned into a golden meteor, letting out dazzling light like a fragment of the sun, forcing people to narrow their eyes.

Golden rainbow carved out a stunning arc through the air before instantly striking turtleback myriad wolf king.

Under Fang Yuan's control, in the moment of imminent crisis, turtleback myriad wolf king turned its body and faced Pei Yan Fei with its shell.

BOOM!

The golden rainbow struck the turtleback, producing a huge sound and also giving off infinite golden light.

For a moment, the Gu Masters on the battlefield had no choice but to close their eyes, but even so, the dazzling light caused their eyes to tear up.

The golden rays of light dimmed down, and the Gu Masters slowly opened their blurred eyes.

The turtleback myriad wolf king's shell was unexpectedly pierced through by Pei Yan Fei, creating a hole from where one could see the right side of the wolf king from its left.

The turtleback myriad wolf king let out a mournful howl; with such injuries, its battle strength had fallen to the bottom.

Meanwhile, Pei Yan Fei's expression paled as he hovered in the air.

Many shocked sounds echoed at this moment.

Ge tribe's Gu Masters looked stifled, while Pei tribe's morale soared, shouting the might of their tribe leader.

"Lord, Pei Yan Fei has battled intensely for so long and now has used his killer move to injure myriad wolf king; his primeval essence should be exhausted. Now is the time to go in for the kill!" Ge Guang excitedly shouted.

Fang Yuan narrowed his eyes. Ge Guang was right, Pei Yan Fei had battled for so long, he should not have much primeval essence left.

Fang Yuan naturally knew this clearly.

But with his five hundred years of memories, Fang Yuan knew Pei Yan Fei had a mysterious Gu called do or die Gu. This Gu was a rank five Gu that could provide the Gu Master with large amounts of primeval essence instantly, but its after-effect was a decrease in their cultivation stage.

Of course, just this point was not enough for Fang Yuan to give up. But...

"Is there any bad news from our camp, Zheng tribe camp and Bei tribe camp?" Fang Yuan asked.

Ge Guang promptly replied: "Not yet."

Fang Yuan immediately knew something was up and sneered, before sending the command: "Our tribe's battle strength has fallen and Pei tribe has suffered even more casualties. We shall retreat."

Chapter 483: Safely Retreat

Bei Cao Chuan had been observing the development of the battle situation.

Beside him, there were eleven Gu Masters. Other than the Bei tribe elders, there were also several Zheng tribe elders, they are all summoned by Bei Cao Chuan.

Their only motive was to kill Chang Shan Yin, to reverse the outcome of this battle.

"Ge tribe is nothing but scattered sand, we do not have to worry about them. The only problem is Wolf King Chang Shan Yin. As long as we kill him, victory is ours! We can still win!!" Bei Cao Chuan's eyes shone brilliantly as he observed the battle while raising the morale of the people around him.

Zheng tribe elders were all convinced by him: "Bei tribe leader is right, but when do we attack?"

Bei Cao Chuan squinted his eyes: "We have to wait! Wolf King is very vigilant, he only sent the turtleback myriad wolf king to lead the attack, while the wind wolf myriad beast king was always near him. He has ample defensive forces around him, although we are strong, there is only one chance for us to attack him. Once we fail, we can only force our way through. By then, we would be in a hopeless situation, being surrounded by the wolf group, there will be little chance of killing Chang Shan Yin."

At this moment, the most intense clash happened on the battlefield.

All sorts of attacks, in all shapes and colors, filled the battlefield. The loud sound of explosions occurred continually.

Seeing this, everyone's hearts shuddered. In such a battlefield, even a rank three Gu Master was cannon fodder. Only rank four or five Gu Masters were the main force.

"Lord, now is the best time to attack." An elder suggested.

"No hurry." Bei Cao Chuan waved his hand.

After the attack persisted and eventually ended, an elder could not stand it anymore: "Lord tribe leader, now is the time. While Ge tribe Gu Masters are recovering their primeval essence, we can charge in and catch them unguarded."

"No! Our target is only Chang Shan Yin. Although they had an intense battle, the number of wolves near Chang Shan Yin had increased in numbers instead." Bei Cao Chuan rejected solemnly.

Next, Fang Yuan struck and made good use of his timing to destroy a portion of the defensive wall.

This was a crucial development.

Pei tribe's defenses were finally broken, large number of wolves charged in as the turtleback myriad wolf king also arrived.

"This is bad! Once the defensive line is broken, the wolf group would carry out a full frontal assault, Pei tribe would not be able to handle it, this is an emergency!"

"Lord, we have to attack. If not, Pei tribe is finished."

"If we strike now, we can still salvage this situation."

"No!" Bei Cao Chuan stood up, his eyes were flashing as he was filled with joy, the long-awaited chance had arrived.

As long as Pei tribe's defenses were broken, Chang Shan Yin would need to mobilize the wolf group and attack Pei tribe camp. This way, his defenses would be greatly weakened, it would give Bei Cao Chuan a good chance to kill him.

"If we strike now, it would only alert Chang Shan Yin and he would recall his wolves, causing the battle to turn into a stalemate again. After we expose ourselves, we would lose the precious chance to kill him. Our three tribes are allied, why was Pei tribe's losses so much less than ours? The Wolf King is so vigilant, he is not easy to deal with. Only with Pei tribe as the bait, allowing him to taste the sweetness of victory, can we kill him at the moment when he lets his guard down!"

In an instant, Bei Cao Chuan's brain worked intensely as he had several thoughts.

But he could not say that out loud, instead he said: "Wait a bit longer, we cannot be anxious. Believe in Pei Yan Fei! He is a famous general in northern plains, do you think he is so weak?"

The rank three Gu Masters heard this and stopped their charging momentum.

Bei Cao Chuan had just said that when Pei Yan Fei unleashed his killer move, Golden Rainbow Strike, the intense explosion forced everyone to raise their arms to shield their eyes from the bright light.

After the light dispersed, turtleback myriad wolf king suffered heavy injures while Pei Yan Fei floated above the rubbles of the defensive wall, his expression was pale.

"So strong!"

"With just one strike, he heavily injured the myriad beast king."

"This is Pei Yan Fei's famous killer move, it is truly formidable!"

"Bei tribe leader is amazing, he understood the battlefield so well, I have learnt much."

The elders expressed their amazement at Pei Yan Fei's battle strength, while praising Bei Cao Chuan's judgement.

Bei Cao Chuan's lips twitched, he would rather see Pei Yan Fei fail in guarding his camp.

"There is still hope, we have to wait a bit longer. Pei Yan Fei definitely used up a lot of his primeval essence for such a strong move. Looking at his expression, he must be at his wit's end. As long as wind wolf king is near Chang Shan Yin, he is near invincible. Pei tribe still had the lower hand, if the wolf group attacks Pei tribe camp again, I will continue my plan from earlier. If Pei Yan Fei has the advantage, I will make use of the opportunity and cooperate with him, dealing the fatal blow to Chang Shan Yin!"

Sparks were flying in Bei Cao Chuan's head, he blinked as he modified his plan.

"I have a chance, there is still hope! I cannot fluster at this moment, I have to calm down and endure... As long as we kill Chang Shan Yin, not only will we turn this around, I will also gain fame. After I become Liu Wen Wu's subordinate, I can gain important roles and fight for more opportunities for my tribe!"

Bei Cao Chuan cheered for himself in his heart.

But at this moment, his pupils shrunk as he swore: "Oh my god, what the f*ck!"

The elders sent him a peculiar gaze.

All along, even though the battle was tense, Bei Cao Chuan was extremely confident and had the situation in his grasp, why was he losing his nerves now?

Bei Cao Chuan could not care less about the gazes, he stared at the battlefield as he spoke out uncontrollably: "Why is this Chang Shan Yin retreating now of all times?"

The Wolf King was in an advantageous situation, although the turtleback myriad wolf king was heavily injured, it was not dead. He still had another wind wolf myriad beast king!

In contrast, Pei Yan Fei was at his wit's end. Most importantly, Pei tribe camp's defenses were broken. As long as he attacked following this weakness, Pei tribe's pressure in defending would be many times of before! Most likely, they would not able to hold on.

Once the wolf group invades Pei tribe camp, Bei Cao Chuan would have the chance to attack, dealing Wolf King the fatal blow from behind!

But now, he was retreating?!

Why was Chang Shan Yin retreating, Bei Cao Chuan had no time to think about this already.

He was extremely nervous now, his confident face started to show some anxiety.

Wolf King still had much strength now, once he retreated, the assault that he had painstaking waited for would be ruined.

The worst thing was, Bei tribe camp and Zheng tribe camp were in Ge tribe's control. Once the wolves retreated, they would bring all these captives and resources away, Bei Cao Chuan would lose his tribe completely.

Without even a tribe, only left with several elders, Bei Cao Chuan's tribe leader status would become the biggest laughingstock.

Just look at the current situation, once he goes to Liu Wen Wu, he would definitely not receive an important position.

"No, I cannot let Chang Shan Yin retreat so easily. Once he leaves, we have no hopes of succeeding!"

Bei Cao Chuan screamed in his heart.

He stood up abruptly, shouting: "Everyone, we cannot wait any longer. Chang Shan Yin is out of steam, they are trying to retreat, now is the time we attack and kill the Wolf King. Everyone, it is time to take back our tribe!"

The elders near him could see the battle situation too.

Bei Cao Chuan's words made them energized as their battle intent surged.

"Kill!"

"Chang Shan Yin, don't think of leaving!"

"Wolf King, fight me one on one if you have the guts!!"

A group of rank three Gu Masters left their hiding spot and started attacking Ge tribe's army from the back under Bei Cao Chuan's lead.

"Hmph, they appeared as expected." Fang Yuan foresaw this, he did not fluster upon seeing these people.

He understood clearly, Bei Cao Chuan and gang did not go back to reinforce their tribes, thus there were only two possibilities.

One was that they were attacking Ge tribe's main camp to exact revenge. The other was that they were reinforcing Pei tribe.

Since the three tribes and their camps were intact, these people were definitely hiding nearby.

If Fang Yuan continued attacking Pei tribe camp and fought with Pei Yan Fei with all his strength, during the crucial moment, he would definitely face an assassination. Thus, retreating was the wisest choice.

"But these people were really good at waiting, they appeared now after I forced them, it seems they have deep motives." Fang Yuan rode on the white-eyes wolf as he thought calmly.

Ge tribesmen were anxious.

Bei Cao Chuan and the other eleven people were experts, they were unstoppable in their attack, it brought a huge mental pressure to the Ge tribesmen.

"Lord supreme elder, what do we do?" Ge Guang asked.

"Why are you panicking, listen to my command and retreat." Fang Yuan laughed coldly.

Retreating in the battlefield was extremely risky. Often, when retreating, enemies would chase after them and cause them to fail in getting away. In his previous life, Fang Yuan had participated in many battles, he knew that these wolves were good for covering them when retreating. He had the ability to face pressure from two sides and escape.

He moved the turtleback myriad wolf king near him and recalled his wolf group, making the hundred wolf kings, thousand wolf kings gather towards the center of the army.

As for those ordinary wild wolves, they were left behind to expend the enemy's primeval essence.

As expected, after a moment, Bei Cao Chuan and gang lost their momentum, starting to use the primeval essence in their apertures sparingly.

"Damn it, do we just watch Chang Shan Yin retreat like this?" Bei Cao Chuan bit his lips, his eyes had turned red from killing, he was extremely indignant in his heart.

"Pei Yan Fei, why are you not attacking? If we cannot take the Wolf King's life today, how will we have the face to participate in the heroes assembly?" Bei Cao Chuan screamed.

Pei Yan Fei snorted, he was not a brute, he knew that Bei Cao Chuan's sudden assault was after he threw Pei tribe under the bus, he wanted to use them as bait.

But Wolf King Chang Shan Yin could not be let off.

During this battle, Ge tribe fought three tribes at one go, if they retreated successfully, they would shoot to fame, and these three tribes would become their stepping stones.

Moreover, Pei tribe suffered huge losses, how could he not take revenge for such deep hatred?

Thinking of this, Pei Yan Fei resolved himself.

Rank five — Do or Die Gu!

Swish swish swish!

Pei Yan Fei's heart felt hollow as large amounts of primeval essence appeared from thin air, filling up his dry aperture.

"Chang Shan Yin, hand over your life!" He howled, rushing over.

Ge tribesmen were flustered.

Fang Yuan laughed, asking around: "Who is this?"

Ge Guang admired Fang Yuan's calmness and the anxiety in his heart vanished, answering solemnly: "Bei tribe leader Bei Cao Chuan!"

"Bei Cao Chuan... Pei Yan Fei... hehehe, heroes emerge in chaotic times, very good, very good." Fang Yuan praised them loudly as his voice resounded in the air.

Next, he jumped down from the white-eyes wolf, changing his steed to a hump wolf.

White-eyes wolf took a few quick steps, standing together with wind wolf myriad beast king and turtleback myriad wolf king.

"That is..." Bei Cao Chuan's momentum froze, his pupils shrunk.

Pei Yan Fei's expression was grim, he was extremely bitter.

White-eyes wolf was a mutated beast with strength equalling a myriad beast king! Earlier, they were too focused on Fang Yuan, thus ignoring his white-eyes wolf. Now that the white-eyes wolf stood out, its identity was immediately exposed.

"Damn it!" Pei Yan Fei gritted his teeth, stopping his attack helplessly.

If Fang Yuan only had the wind wolf myriad beast king left, that would be fine, but with a white-eyes wolf, he had enough strength to resist their attacks and even fight back.

Pei Yan Fei did not dare to take the risk and place Pei tribe in danger again.

He chose to give up.

On the other end, Bei Cao Chuan had no choice but to stop his steps.

He looked at the army retreating, he not only felt dejection in his heart but also a strong chill: "Wolf King Chang Shan Yin, just how many trump cards do you have?"

Chapter 484: Influence

The noisy night winds gradually stopped, thick mist started to form near the wild grass on the ground.

Ge tribe army retreated along crescent lake, moving slowly.

Having successfully retreated, these people still had battle intent left in them.

Even though they did not take down Pei tribe in the end, they had made a name for themselves in this battle, Ge tribesmen were excitedly talking about it.

"This battle was amazing. That dogshit three tribe alliance, they dared to find trouble with us Ge tribe, they were simply courting death!"

'Hmph, what Zheng tribe, Bei tribe, or Pei tribe, they were merely so."

"Now, Bei tribe and Zheng tribe camps have been taken down by us, and Pei tribe suffered huge losses. After this battle tonight, Ge tribe is going to become famous throughout northern plains!"

Using the strength of one tribe to challenge three, such an accomplishment and bravery made the Ge tribe Gu Masters feel proud and confident of themselves.

"It was all thanks to Lord Wolf King Chang Shan Yin." A Gu Master exclaimed.

The words immediately caused a huge commotion.

"Mm, that is right. If not for the wolves charging ahead and paving the way for us, we would definitely suffer great losses and face many casualties."

"This is the power of an enslavement path Gu Master. No wonder so many tribes want to nurture one or two enslavement path Gu Masters even if they had to curb their spending.

"Lord Wolf King is our tribe's supreme elder. We are one family."

"Mm, it is really our honor to have Lord Wolf King by our side!"

After this battle, Fang Yuan's prestige in Ge tribe rose to an absurd level.

Fang Yuan rode the white-eyes wolf again, as Ge tribe leader and the band of elders accompanied him.

As the supreme elder, Fang Yuan had the authority to forcefully remove the tribe leader Ge Guang. Of course, Ge Guang was an obedient chess piece, Fang Yuan had no intention to remove him.

The grand army first returned to Zheng tribe camp, the Gu Masters left behind had already gathered the resources and placed them on the thirty blue farm slug transportation troops.

These slugs were known as mucus Gu worms, they were like snails without shells.

They were rank three with a body larger than elephants, they were blue and had blue water crystals growing on their bodies.

These blue farm slug Gu were easy to use.

They expended little primeval essence and Gu Masters only needed to 'stuff' the items into their bodies.

Blue farm slug Gu did not have any attacking capabilities, after 'swallowing' the items, their bodies would expand.

These thirty blue farm slug Gu were now five times their original size. Even a myriad beast king was not half of their size.

But even so, there was still a small portion of the resources in Zheng tribe that could not be carried, and could only be left behind in the camp.

The elder that stayed behind handed over the list of gains after calculation.

Fang Yuan browsed through it, the profits were huge.

"We are rich!" Ge Guang saw this and was elated.

"This is a huge fortune!"

"And we obtained so many captives as well, our Ge tribe can quickly become a large-sized tribe!"

"We have to be alert these few days, we have to strengthen our defenses, and prevent the surrounding tribes from eyeing our goods."

"But what do we do with the Gu Masters who surrendered? According to the norm, they will become slave Gu Masters. But we do not have so many slavery Gu."

Ge tribesmen started to feel a headache.

Ge tribe was only a middle-sized tribe, they had a weak foundation. If they were a large tribe, they would be able to better digest these gains.

They left behind a group of people to defend the place, and instructed them to retreat of Pei tribe's army came over, to preserve their strength.

Ge tribe's army brought the thirty blue farm slug Gu and large numbers of captives and continued on their journey.

When they reached Bei tribe camp, the troops stopped. When they set off again, the size of the group had expanded by several times again.

When they finally reached their Ge tribe camp, the returning warriors received a warm welcome from all the Ge tribesmen.

The cheers were extremely loud as the first rays of dawn shone on their faces. In contrast, those captives were all either numb or in despair, it was like the two sides lived in different worlds.

Fang Yuan lightly let out a breath of turbid air.

On the way back, he was afraid of Pei tribe's assault.

"It seems that Pei Yan Fei was concerned with his tribe's safety and wanted to preserve his forces, thus he did not attack. Otherwise, we will face much greater obstacles on the way. Of course, the main reason for this was because I showed them the white-eyes wolf, displaying a facade that it had the strength of a myriad beast king."

But the truth was, Fang Yuan's white-eyes wolf had grown because of third watch Gu. There was not a single wild Gu worm on it.

This was the world of Gu, without a single wild Gu, white-eyes wolf could not even defeat a thousand beast king.

If they really fought, white-eyes wolf was only a giant wild wolf.

But if Pei Yan Fei and Bei Cao Chuan were not deterred and continued attacking, Fang Yuan would be in trouble.

He had already exerted 120% of his wolf group's strength, in terms of strength path, he had just started, having only thirty jun of strength. In terms of soul, he had not reached thousand man soul yet.

"My current strength is still too weak, after three battles in one night, I can vividly feel all my weaknesses."

Now that they were safe, Fang Yuan looked at the wolf group.

The sixty thousand wolf group had suffered great losses, only less than half survived. But his greatest loss was his myriad beast kings.

Fang Yuan had three myriad beast kings, but after this battle, night wolf myriad beast king died in battle, and turtleback myriad wolf king suffered heavy injuries, although it has started receiving treatment, it was still unconscious. Wind wolf myriad beast king was full of injuries, it had lost a lot of the Gu worms on it and its battle strength fell greatly.

But Fang Yuan felt no regrets.

Compared to his gains, these losses were nothing.

Not to say his immense loot from the two camps, Fang Yuan had achieved all his goals from this battle.

Taking the initiative to attack and fighting three tribes alone, the name of Wolf King Chang Shan Yin would spread in northern plains again, becoming a widely known topic.

This was a testament to Fang Yuan's strength, it would be a great help to his future plans of participating in the heroes assembly and dealing with Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Furthermore, these dead wolves served a greater purpose.

Their souls were kept by Fang Yuan and were used to fertilize Dang Hun mountain.

"After this battle, I have created a name for myself, as well as displaying my ferocity. I'm sure this will deter the nearby forces, with this, Ge tribe can recuperate and regroup, while I can also take some time to expand my wolf group and cultivate my wolfman soul, at the same time, preparing my rank five enslavement path Gu worms."

Lying on his bed, Fang Yuan's thoughts spanned out and slowly faded.

Outside the Gu house, the cheers were getting louder as the Ge tribesmen celebrated like no tomorrow.

Fang Yuan gradually closed his eyes.

He felt tired.

Three battles in one night, controlling so many wolves to participate in intense battle, it expended his mental energy, a form of fatigue originating from his soul spread throughout his body.

Just when he was sleeping soundly, a great commotion had expanded all over crescent lake. In the morning, almost every tribe leader nearby or their strategist received the information regarding this battle.

There were suspicious people, threatened people, fearful people, or furious people.

But regardless of their feelings, at once, Ge tribe and Wolf King Chang Shan Yin became the hottest topic of every tribe.

"I thought he was just a cat, but he turned out to be a leopard!" Wang tribe leader was staring intently at the paper describing this battle, after a long while, he sighed as he was filled with lamentation.

He wanted to watch from the sidelines, if the situation permitted it, he would reap some rewards from this conflict.

But to think that Ge tribe challenged three tribes in one night under Fang Yuan's lead, dealing a huge blow to Pei tribe. Bei tribe leader Bei Cao Chuan became a vagabond, and Pei Yan Fei, a fierce general in northern plains, lost a small realm of his cultivation!

"He is simply too daring and ferocious, he is overly ruthless!" Even Wang tribe leader's stragetist Wang De Dao looked at this information and exclaimed as his expression changed.

"Ge tribe attacked without warning, striking first and catching the three tribes unguarded, two were destroyed while one was half ruined. This is overstepping the line, they broke our unspoken rule, aren't they afraid of being blamed by all of us?" Wang De Dao said furiously, Ge tribe's rampant invasion made him feel uneasy.

At this time, the Gu Master outside brought in another letter.

This was a letter from Ge tribe, it was sent to all the forces near crescent lake.

The letter was written by Ge Guang personally, it detailed how the three tribes had ill intentions, in order for Ge tribe to defend itself, they had to retaliate. The letter talked about Yan tribe and all the reasons and justifications they had, including Chang Shan Yin's grudges from many years ago.

"The truth is, back then, Chang Shan Yin was a victim, this was why he had to face Ha Tu Gu and the bandits alone. Now that he is back, he wants to exact revenge on his tribe. Meanwhile, Chang tribe was already part of young master Liu Wen Wu's forces, Yan tribe was Liu Wen Wu's family-in-law, but they did not know about his grudges and asked Chang Shan Yin for help, this is how everything started." Wang De Dao looked at this letter and his expression was uncertain, he became more furious: "Chang Shan Yin is involving the innocent with his personal grudges, what kind of northern plains hero is this?!"

Wang tribe leader was calm, he got to the point immediately: "But this way, Ge tribe has a reason to attack. Although this reason is so forced, they can at least cover themselves with a proper explanation. Ge tribe has Chang Shan Yin's protection, after defeating three tribes, their strength would definitely increase and they would expand. There is little hope of the other tribes gathering to deal with Chang Shan Yin after seeing the sorry states of these three tribes."

Wang De Dao nodded: "Then what do we do next?"

"Wolf King's actions were too quick, now that it had already happened, we cannot interfere anymore. Sigh, I underestimated the Wolf King..." Wang tribe leader sighed.

At this time, someone outside informed him that Bei tribe leader Bei Cao Chuan has brought his band of elders to meet Wang tribe leader.

"Bei Cao Chuan? Why is he here?" Wang tribe leader frowned.

Wang De Dao reminded him: "Lord tribe leader, did you forget, Bei tribe had sent an elder to invite us to join his alliance earlier, that elder is still staying with us."

Wang tribe leader patted his forehead: "Oh, I nearly forgot. I said I would host him for three days, today is the third day. No way, I should not meet this Bei Cao Chuan, go and meet him, tell him I have an important Gu to refine today, I cannot leave my closed cultivation."

Bei Cao Sheng had been well treated by Wang tribe these few days, but he did not forget his mission. During this time, he had requested to meet with Wang tribe leader several times but was rejected.

Seeing Bei Cao Chuan, he was very surprised: "Lord tribe leader, and all the other elders, why are you here personally?"

Before he got a reply, Bei Cao Sheng said with an expression of guilt: "Everyone, I have disappointed you. That Wang tribe leader keeps rejecting my offer, not agreeing to join the alliance. But no worry, with the strength of our three tribes, we can easily deal with Ge tribe!"

Bei tribe elders heard this and some of their eyebrows trembled, while the others' expressions turned grim.

Bei Cao Chuan felt bitter in his heart, at once, he did not know what to say, or how to explain the situation to this elder.

Chapter 485: Plotting against the Land Spirit

Eight days later, at night.

The stars shone in the sky as the night winds blew.

Fang Yuan rode on the white-eyes wolf's back, ready to move out.

Ge Guang stood by his side, reporting the situation of the last few days: "During these last eight days, large numbers of small to mid-sized tribes have started on their journey to attend the heroes assembly. Right now, only several large-sized tribes are left in crescent lake. Bei Cao Chuan, Pei Yan Fei and the others were the first to leave.

Fang Yuan adjusted his posture: "Mm, earlier when we took the initiative to challenge the three tribes, it made many tribes apprehensive. Since the heroes assembly was nearing, it is normal that they decided to leave. But for those large tribes, they have a lot of stuff to settle due to their many enterprises. Thus, they usually attend the second half of the heroes assembly."

"Supreme elder is wise, that is indeed so." Ge Guang started bootlicking.

Fang Yuan chuckled: "Crescent lake's aquatic plants are beautiful, we will stay here for the time being, we should be internalizing our gains from the battles now instead of travelling."

"Yes lord." Ge Guang heaved a sigh of relief, they had such intentions in their earlier discussions.

Ge tribe was now like a fat man who had eaten too much, they could not walk. These eight days, they had been expanding the campgrounds day and night, recruiting those captives. After calculating their resources, the strength of the tribe was growing day by day.

"Those water wolves, are they still there?" Fang Yuan asked.

"Yes, I sent investigative Gu Masters there many times to check them out. These water wolves amount to about five thousand, at night, they will enter that water den to rest. Lord, do you really not need guards?"

Fang Yuan snorted, replying arrogantly: "Any place with wolves will have me Chang Shan Yin. Why would I need guards?"

Ge Guang could hear his unhappiness, thus he quickly bowed and gave way: "I wish Lord Supreme Elder all the best in your recruitment of the water wolves."

"Mm, you will have to be careful of the matters in the tribe. Without me around, you have to take note of those Gu Masters who surrendered."

"Yes lord."

Fang Yuan left behind the wind wolf king, bringing the weakened turtleback myriad wolf king and eighteen thousand wolves, leaving the campsite and starting on their hunt.

He first followed the map that Ge tribe investigators had drawn, getting close to the water den.

Water wolves lived in the water, they ate fish as food. Often, when they were hungry, they would also come ashore to eat some rabbits or rats.

With the arrival of the wolf group, these water wolves were immediately alerted.

To defend their homes, the water wolves formed into a tight formation as they left the water den, staring at Fang Yuan vigilantly.

Fang Yuan expressionlessly sat on his white-eyes wolf's back, he waved with his hand and countless wild wolves howled as they attacked the water wolves.

The water wolves resisted as the two sides engaged in fierce combat.

Wolf howl Gu! Wolf smoke Gu!

Fang Yuan made his move from the back several times, firming grasping control of the battle in his hands.

His wolf group was larger to begin with, soon, they started killing water wolves.

More than a thousand water wolf corpses were left on the ground, as Fang Yuan used wolf enslavement Gu to subdue more than two thousand of them, the remaining thousand escaped to the deep parts of crescent lake.

Fang Yuan did not chase them, instead he destroyed this water den and obtained several hundred water wolf cubs.

Next, he went to the next location.

After destroying several wolf dens, by night time, Fang Yuan subdued over six thousand water wolves, two thousand turtleback wolves, and a thousand night wolves.

Crescent lake had the most water wolves, but there were also some turtleback wolves, night wolves, and wind wolves.

But the wind wolves were too fast, they were hard to catch. They often retreated at the slightest danger, Fang Yuan targeted a pack of wind wolves but they escaped quickly amidst battle.

Wolf groups were very crafty, in order to capture them, Fang Yuan had to pay a price as well. If the cost was too high, and was greater than the benefits, he would give up on them.

Some large water wolf groups had myriad wolf kings, Fang Yuan did not dare to attack them abruptly.

But this time, his expedition of hunting wolves was only a cover. Now that he had acted enough, he searched for a secluded spot and surrounded himself with wolves. Next, he activated moving perspective cup Gu and contacted little Hu Immortal.

Little Hu Immortal got the news and immediately summoned a group of starlight firefly Gu, using the starlight and green grape immortal essence to activate stargate Gu.

Stargate Gu came in pairs, using the power of black heaven, they could traverse regions.

Fang Yuan waited for a while, seeing the starlight in the night sky descending and gathering on his stargate Gu.

The stargate Gu was like a blue gemstone as it flew towards the sky, when it reached mid air, the starlight exploded as a door was formed.

This time, Fang Yuan did not enter the stargate anxiously, instead, he sent the weak and heavily injured turtleback myriad wolf king in first, as well as large numbers of injured wolves.

The large number of wolves entered the stargate like flowing river water, disappearing.

This way, Fang Yuan only had strong and elite wolves left with him, this greatly reduced his pressure of feeding them.

As for those injured wolves, they would reproduce and grow in the blessed land, giving birth to healthy cubs. As time in Hu Immortal blessed land was faster, they would grow quickly and become Fang Yuan's new source of wolves.

After sending these wolves into Hu Immortal blessed land, Fang Yuan also entered the door.

"Master, you asked me to check on connecting heaven Gu daily, I was very obedient and did as you said. That Lang Ya Old Immortal really appeared again and bought lots of materials in treasure yellow heaven." Little Hu Immortal was very happy upon seeing Fang Yuan, hugging his leg as she used her face to rub it, talking about the things that happened while Fang Yuan was gone.

"Oh? Is that so, what did he buy?" Fang Yuan heard this and was energized, quickly asking.

Little Hu Immortal took out a piece of paper from her pocket and handed it to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan looked and browsed through it, these Gu worms and materials were very familiar, they were used to refine second aperture Gu.

What did this mean?

Lang Ya Old Immortal was Lang Ya land spirit. He was going to refine second aperture Gu, thus, he definitely survived the second wave of attacks and had the urge to refine second aperture Gu.

At the same time, that divine travel Gu was definitely in his hands.

Otherwise, why would he purchase ingredients so urgently right after the second wave of attacks?

"Lang Ya land spirit was plotted against by Old Man Yan Shi, he should be defending Lang Ya blessed land now. Although this land spirit is intelligent, he is rigid, and does not possess the ability to scheme. What am I waiting for?"

Fang Yuan thought of this and his heart was palpitating!

He immediately left Hu Immortal blessed land, returning to northern plains' crescent lake.

Next, he led the wolf group as he charged to that stone forest without rest. Using Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's entry point again, he entered Lang Ya blessed land.

There were many new changes to Lang Ya blessed land, the twelve cloud buildings were attacked, there were much rubble and broken structures, scars from burning flames, lighting strikes, or results of frost.

These were traces of a huge battle.

Especially outside the buildings, on the pure white cloud soil, they were tainted with blood traces, a deer-like desolate beast with the size of a mountain was lying on the cloud soil, dead.

Even though it lost its life, the skin was still shiny and smooth, glowing with a rainbow-like luster, it gave off a holy feeling.

"Why are you here?" Lang Ya land spirit welcomed Fang Yuan grumpily.

"What happened?" Fang Yuan did not answer him, instead he asked and expressed his shock.

"Hmph, a bunch of daring scoundrels, they set their claws on this blessed land, they have all been killed!" Lang Ya land spirit's expression was grim as his killing intent surged.

Fang Yuan curiously looked at the land spirit: "Isn't Lang Ya blessed land very secretive, how did they get in? Unless you opened the doors yourself..."

"Get lost! Am I so stupid?" The land spirit howled: "These goddamn scoundrels plotted against me, they did something to the stuff I bought. I originally bought divine travel Gu to refine second aperture Gu, but during the refinement process, a passage formed and these little rats came in."

The land spirit called them rats, but as Fang Yuan looked at the state of the twelve cloud buildings, he could guess the intensity of the battle.

But Lang Ya blessed land was after all, Long Hair Ancestor's old home. As the 'Number One Refinement Immortal of all time', someone who was on equal status with two venerables, he definitely had deep foundations and many trump cards.

The second wave of attacks could not take down this deep foundation so easily. At least, Fang Yuan knew there were twelve desolate beasts in Lang Ya blessed land, now only one had died.

However, Old Man Yan Shi was still alive. The second wave of attacks was not the last, but the beginning. The show has just begun.

Fang Yuan laughed: "I guessed right, you are that Lang Ya Old Immortal, you bought divine travel Gu in treasure yellow heaven. It seems you managed to protect divine travel Gu."

Lang Ya land spirit laughed smugly: "Of course! Otherwise, that nine color spirit deer would not have died."

Suddenly, his expression changed, as he thought of something, staring vigilantly at Fang Yuan: "Why are you here lad?"

Fang Yuan bowed to the land spirit, replying as a matter of fact: "What else? I am obviously here to ask you to refine the second aperture Gu for me."

"What?!" Land spirit shouted, staring at Fang Yuan furiously, his eyes about to spew fire.

Long Hair Ancestor had failed to refine an important Immortal Gu for Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable back then, thus he made a promise to refine nine Gu worms for him without any costs, regardless of mortal or Immortal Gu.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable used six chances to receive six Immortal Gu. With three chances left, he sealed it into his inheritances to leave it to a fated person.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, this chance was taken by Ma Hong Yun. But now, Fang Yuan came here earlier and snatched this immortal opportunity.

Earlier, he had used one of the chances to ask Lang Ya land spirit to refine stargate Gu. Now that he was here again, he was going to use the second chance to refine second aperture Gu.

Lang Ya land spirit was formed from Long Hair Ancestor's obsessions, he could not reject such a request.

But in order to protect divine travel Gu, he had paid a huge choice. Seeing that the second aperture Gu was about to be successfully refined, the result was that Fang Yuan came to take it from him.

Lang Ya land spirit was furious as he stared angrily, using a grim tone to ask Fang Yuan: "Don't tell me you are the mastermind who planned the attack on my blessed land?"

Fang Yuan rubbed his nose, saying innocently: "Do you think that I, a mortal, could mobilize those Gu Immortals? I only knew you had the second aperture Gu's recipe after you bought divine travel Gu, and now that you bought a second set of materials, I came over."

Lang Ya blessed land gritted his teeth angrily, pointing at Fang Yuan: "You humans are all devious and scheming. I killed those Gu Immortal, but to think that it was all for naught, I still ended up being scammed by you, this little lad!"

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "This is not a scam, but a promise that you gave Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable back then. So, are you going to refine the second aperture Gu for me now?"

Land spirit was angry and wanted to chop Fang Yuan into a million pieces, but he had no choice but to refine the Gu for him.

Chapter 486: Two Immortal Gu obtained!

"I want to see you refine the Gu personally." Fang Yuan had a thought as he asked the question to probe the land spirit.

The refinement process of Gu Masters were secretive. If someone saw them, the recipe might leak out or even expose the Gu Master's unique methods.

"Of course, this was one of the agreements." Lang Ya land spirit agreed immediately, out of Fang Yuan's expectations.

Fang Yuan raised his brows, having a slight understanding.

Back then, when Long Hair Ancestor failed in refining space escape Gu, he wasted all of the materials that Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had collected for his entire life. Among them, many Gu materials were extremely rare and Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable only managed to get them out of pure luck.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was a rank nine Demon Venerable, to repay his losses, as well as saving his reputation, Long Hair Ancestor agreed to refine Gu for him.

Allowing Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable to view the entire refinement process, was not only to expose the recipe to pay back the Demon Venerable, it also proved his innocence — you saw the whole process. If the refinement fails, it has nothing to do with me!

But now right, there were no such concerns left.

Land spirits were formed from the blessed land's heavenly power, the obsessions of the Gu Immortals before death. They did not have vile thoughts, they were candid and straightforward.

However, Lang Ya land spirit was formed from the number one refinement immortal, Long Hair Ancestor, even though he lost most of his memories, he retained most of Long Hair Ancestor's refinement talent and attainments.

Observing the land spirit refining Gu was a huge benefit to Fang Yuan.

"I had refined second aperture Gu before. This time, I will observe the land spirit's techniques and gain some experience to improve myself. Maybe, I would get to see a trace of Long Hair Ancestor's glamor back in ancient times." Fang Yuan was looking forward to this Gu refinement.

Lang Ya land spirit waved his hand and teleported him to a huge hall.

This hall was really big, the diameter of it was at least ten li. There were all sorts of equipment, there were green copper cauldrons, red steel furnaces, rainbow water tanks, and even cave houses.

When Gu Masters refine Gu, they need the help of their equipment as well.

The equipment in this hall was like a comprehensive exhibition, it was a huge eye-opener to Fang Yuan.

Although he had five hundred years of experience due to rebirth, he spent about three hundred years wandering and fighting his way up to the top, he only managed to hold his own and freely roam the world to achieve his grand aspirations in his last two hundred years.

During that period, although he explored many other Gu paths, he had to resist the earthly calamities as well as manage his forces, all while gathering his Immortal Gu refinement materials, he was very busy and overwhelmed. Although his foundation in refinement path could surpass the mortal realm, among Gu Immortals, he was only second or third-rate. There was no comparison to a legend like Long Hair Ancestor.

"This is my Earth-grade Room C Gu refinement hall." Lang Ya land spirit introduced, as Fang Yuan's expression changed upon hearing it.

The land spirit would not lie, such a grand hall was only one of the many Gu refinement halls in Lang Ya blessed land.

Earth-grade Room C... how many of such halls did this blessed land have?

At this moment, the land spirit waved.

At an instant, a few thousand hairy men appeared in the hall.

These hairy men were teleported over with a stunned expression, but they soon kneeled on the ground, shouting: "The hairy men greets Lang Ya Old Immortal!"

They spoke at the same time, as their voices echoed in the hall.

Lang Ya land spirit's face showed some affection as he said: "Children, you may get up."

He then waved his hand, and sent the Gu refinement materials over to them: "Today, we are refining an Immortal Gu, use the Gu recipe that I gave you to do it."

The hairy men were obviously experienced in such matters.

Upon hearing that they were refining an Immortal Gu, the hairy men were stirred as they showed an excited expression.

But immediately after, they calmed down and started researching the recipe in their hands before starting the Gu refinement.

Several thousand hairy men refining Gu at once, this was not the first time Fang Yuan had seen this.

Among the variant men, hairy men were most skilled at refining Gu, they were born with the talent for it. According to the records in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, back in the immemorial era, the hairy men started to refine Gu, even tying up Ren Zu's first son Verdant Great Sun, attempting to use him to refine eternal Gu.

Hairy men refine Gu using their talent and inspiration, they worked casually and did not have the trace of toolwork left by human Gu Masters.

At Gu Immortal stage, having already surpassed mortals, to aid them in refining Gu, they would raise a number of hairy men. In Fang Yuan's previous life, he had kept some of them in his blessed land as well.

But that was blood sea blessed land, the environment was harsh and many batches of hairy men died, causing his interest in raising them to disappear.

After Fang Yuan became a Gu Immortal, he had gathered a large number of hairy men to refine Gu in bulk for his demonic sect.

Precisely because of his own experiences, he could tell that the hairy men here were not ordinary.

These hairy men were simply too well raised.

Look at their hair and skin, they were clear and shiny, their eyes has spirit and their faces were energetic, it showed that they lived in a good environment and had never been tortured by Lang Ya land spirit.

Most importantly, these hairy men were very agile and moved quickly, each of them were great experts in Gu refinement.

During the Gu refinement process, a few old hairy men even gave their suggestions to tweak the recipe!

Looking at their casual movements, Fang Yuan's heart was pounding.

Such a group of hairy men, if they were sold in treasure yellow heaven, they would be the elite of elite slaves. There would be at least 21 meters of treasure light, those Gu Immortals would fight for them.

These hairy men had shocking attainments, most of them were refinement masters. Several of the old hairy men who could suggest the tweaking of the recipe were already refinement grandmasters!

Right now, Fang Yuan was still barely a refinement master.

With such skilled subordinates, the refinement process was faster than Fang Yuan's refinement on San Cha mountain by more than ten times.

These hairy men made the half-done product and handed it over to the old hairy men for inspection before giving it to Lang Ya land spirit.

Lang Ya land spirit quickly collected the half-done products, and after checking them, destroyed a few pieces and made the hairy men refine them again.

After several tries, Lang Ya land spirit was finally satisfied and started doing it himself, easily getting the half-done product of second aperture Gu.

This was the same as the half-done version that Fang Yuan had right now.

But Fang Yuan knew that the one in Lang Ya land spirit's hands was way higher in quality.

Eventually, Lang Ya land spirit took out divine travel Gu.

This divine travel Gu's surface was damaged, it was filled with injuries and Fang Yuan's heart jumped upon seeing that.

"Lad, it is still not too late to change your mind." Lang Ya land spirit stopped his actions, urging Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan frowned, after thinking through it, he laughed: "No, please continue."

"Scheming fellow, I couldn't hide it from you!" Lang Ya land spirit cursed, pinching his nose as he teleported several Gu worms over along with some precious materials.

Fang Yuan stared with wide opened eyes, he only recognised two of them, they were precious items that increased the chances of success in Gu refinement. If they were placed in treasure yellow heaven, the treasure light would hit 18 meters!

Lang Ya land spirit's every movement attracted countless gazes.

The hairy men were watching in awe as their bodies shivered, their eyes were full of extreme reverence.

Fang Yuan watched with great anticipation, when Lang Ya land spirit refined the Gu, it moved as smooth as water, there were no unnecessary movements or any atmosphere of panic.

Lang Ya land spirit displayed exemplary control, Fang Yuan gained a lot of insights.

Although he wanted to continue watching like this, Fang Yuan bit his lips and forced himself to snap out of it, starting to execute his plan.

He sat down cross-legged, and took out two Gu that he had prepared prior to this.

One was clear mind Gu, the other was awaken cloud Gu.

These two Gu were rank four, after Fang Yuan injected primeval essence into them, they started working.

Clear mind Gu turned into a breeze, entering his brain. The cotton-like awaken cloud Gu turned into a small white cloud and floated about Fang Yuan's head.

Fang Yuan stared at the light lump that Lang Ya land spirit was manipulating while bringing out four top quality wines.

With connecting heaven Gu to enter treasure yellow heaven, it was easy for him to gather top quality wines. For this moment, he prepared at least fourteen different wines.

Sensing Fang Yuan's movement, Lang Ya land spirit snorted in displeasure, but did not do anything to him.

Fang Yuan sighed inwardly in relief, ignoring the piercing light that made his tears flow, he stared at the light lump intently.

Finally, he saw divine travel Gu turn into flowing water as it mixed with the other materials.

Fang Yuan quickly took out the wine vats and gulped the liquor.

At the same time, an intense feeling of tipsiness assaulted him.

Fang Yuan quickly activated clear mind Gu, forcing himself awake as clarity was restored in his mind. At the same time, awaken cloud Gu rumbled and ensured that his mind was at its peak condition.

After drinking four wines, Fang Yuan was still clear-headed, but he realized that nothing had happened yet.

The light was still transforming, it had expanded by many times already since the start, it was larger than an elephant.

"It seems that divine travel Gu has not disappeared yet, Immortal Gu are unique, I have to continue drinking." Fang Yuan took out another vat and unsealed it, gulping the content.

The light lump shrunk, as Lang Ya land spirit's expression became more serious as it held the light lump.

A moment later, after Fang Yuan drank the eighth wine, his vision was already turning blurry.

At this moment, in Lang Ya land spirit's hand, the light lump expanded and shrunk in intervals, after three to five times, it settled, becoming second aperture Gu!

The moment second aperture Gu was formed, Fang Yuan's body shuddered as all the drunkenness in his body gathered like the merging of rivers into the sea, condensing into one point.

Out of nowhere, a divine opportunity descended as the Dao mark formed, causing this point to explode into one Gu — divine travel Gu!

Second aperture Gu.

Divine travel Gu.

Two Immortal Gu obtained at the same time!

Fang Yuan became completely sober as he stood up excitedly, laughing heartily.

"A truly profound scheme!" Lang Ya land spirit looked at Fang Yuan with an expression of fatigue, its body was also turning hollow and weak.

Fang Yuan was the person who obtained Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritance, although Lang Ya land spirit wanted divine travel Gu, it could not attack Fang Yuan.

The hairy men stared at Fang Yuan with furious, disdainful eyes.

This vile human dared to plot against our beloved and supreme lord Lang Ya Old Immortal!

Fang Yuan paid these hairy men no heed, he stopped his laughter as he bowed to Lang Ya land spirit: "It was just a petty scheme, it is nowhere near graceful. Today, I had a true eye-opener, and had benefited a lot, I am shameful of my actions, but I am respectful towards you, I am willing to become your disciple."

Chapter 487: Immortal Gu Transaction

"Screw off! If accept you as my disciple, I reckon one day I will die from anger. My children are the best, giving me no worries. Now get lost, I don't want to see you." Lang Ya land spirit kept on waving his hand, refusing Fang Yuan's request to be his disciple without hesitation.

He could have obtained the second aperture Gu, but Fang Yuan plotted against him and made him offer the successfully refined second aperture Gu readily along with losing the divine travel Gu.

Fang Yuan chuckled, not minding the land spirit's refusal.

Land spirits were formed from the obsessions of the Gu Immortals; they were simple and biased, their refusal now meant they would still refuse in the future.

"Such a pity, I originally intended to give divine travel Gu to you as our apprenticeship gift."

"Hmph, the people I don't like the most are crafty people like you. The hairy men are still the best! I will tell you the truth, I have already taken eighteen hairy men as my disciples. In the future as well, I will only take hairymen as my disciples!"

"Alright, give me the second aperture Gu." Fang Yuan stretched out his hand.

Lang Ya land spirit's expression turned sluggish and glanced at the Immortal Gu on his hand with reluctance. This was the Gu he wanted to refine and now he had succeeded, but he had to give it up without even getting cozy with it.

But the agreement back then had formed a type of will that became a part of the land spirit. He was unable to violate it, and also did not intend to violate it.

"Kid, I will remember you!" Lang Ya land spirit growled and stuffed the second aperture Gu in Fang Yuan's hand.

This second aperture Gu looked like a beetle with two sharp ends and a fat middle body.

The beetle was the size of a young man's fist. It was like blue jade, and felt soft and cool to the touch.

There was a golden eye on its plump back. The golden eye flashed with lightning and had ample spirituality.

"This is the Gu I took the risks for at San Cha mountain and wanted to refine by all means. I hadn't expected I would obtain this in this way." Fang Yuan sighed, but did not use it hurriedly and stored it in his pouch first.

Under the cooperation of Lang Ya land spirit, this second aperture Gu was already Fang Yuan's object, but he was still not a Gu Immortal and did not have green grape immortal essence, so he could not activate it now.

"You already have the Immortal Gu, you can leave now if you don't want to use your final chance." Lang Ya land spirit wanted to make him leave.

Fang Yuan, however, took out divine travel Gu and waved it in front of Lang Ya land spirit with a smile: "You don't want this Immortal Gu?"

Lang Ya land spirit's brows raised: "What, you want to sell it?"

He had connecting heaven Gu and could connect to treasure yellow heaven to buy all kinds of Gu refinement materials. Even the human apertures required to refine second aperture Gu could be obtained by buying enslaved Gu Masters and killing them.

Second aperture gu was an expendable Gu; it would disappear after Fang Yuan used it.

Lang Ya land spirit could completely refine another. Of course, the precondition was that he needed to have divine travel Gu. Without divine travel Gu, he would never be able to refine second aperture Gu.

Fang Yuan, however, did not directly answer and instead asked: "Tell me, if I use another second aperture Gu, can I have a third aperture?"

"Hmph, keep on dreaming." Lang Ya land spirit immediately scoffed, "This is the second aperture Gu, not the third aperture Gu. You want to form a third aperture? Then go refine the recipe for third aperture gu!"

Fang Yuan nodded and said sincerely: "I also thought so."

The land spirit would not deceive him just because it wanted the divine travel Gu. At the same time, he also knew second aperture Gu's recipe, so he had already deduced this.

He asked this just to confirm it.

With this, the divine travel Gu and the semi-finished second aperture Gu with Fang Yuan had lost their use.

Fang Yuan already possessed a second aperture Gu; he was a lone force and did not have any trusted aide to support, so he did not need another second aperture Gu.

Moreover, when he observed the land spirit's Gu refinement process just before, he knew the final step was extremely dangerous! The light ball's inflation and contractions required extremely strong control which required at least thousand man soul to maintain.

How could Immortal Gu be so easy to refine? Fortunately, back at San Cha mountain, Fang Yuan did not set his heart in refining the second aperture Gu after rebirth. Otherwise, with his strength back then, he would absolutely have had a terrible ending. Just the backlash could put him on the brink of death.

Of course, he could also sell them at treasure yellow heaven.

But if he did so, he would attract Old Man Yan Shi's attention and expose many of his trump cards. At the same time, the things he got might be tampered with by other Gu Immortals.

Transacting with Lang Ya land spirit was different.

At least, the land spirit would not give him shoddy goods, and also had robust financial resources, so he could buy divine travel Gu to refine Gu.

Last but not least, Fang Yuan could also avoid revealing himself, thus it was very secure.

"Land spirit, take a look at what this is." Fang Yuan thought for a while before directly taking out the semi-finished second aperture Gu that he had personally refined.

This semi-finished product had a vague appearance like a semi-finished pottery, with no hints of life.

It was like a piece of grey stone that was carved into a beetle. Its big belly looked elegant with sharp head and tail, but no antennas or legs.

Although its appearance was similar to the real second aperture Gu, they clearly could not be compared because of qualitative difference.

Lang Ya land spirit's eyes could not help but brighten when he saw this semi-finished product: "To think you had actually reached such a stage. But the most difficult step in refining second aperture Gu is the final step. The steps before it, can be refined by the refinement path Gu Masters at master level."

The land spirit's tone carried a trace of joy.

Fang Yuan had divine travel Gu and also the semi-finished product. If he could get them both, then only the final step would be remaining to refine second aperture Gu.

To Lang Ya land spirit, this temptation was hard to resist."Speak, what do you want?" Lang Ya land spirit removed his burning gaze and looked at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan looked at the divine travel Gu on his right hand and immediately said: "Immortal Gu are priceless, so of course I want to exchange it with another Immortal Gu. This is the old rule in transacting Immortal Gu."

Lang Ya land spirit's expression immediately fell: "Although it is the old rule, it is not suitable for our situation. First of all, divine travel Gu is not practical and can only be used as an escape means as a last resort. In case it teleported the Gu Master to the depths of a volcano or to the depths of the earth, it would simply be finding one's doom. Secondly, I will be using divine travel Gu to refine Gu. But what use can second aperture Gu be for a land spirit like me?"

Fang Yuan was happy; the land spirit's gaze was fixed on the divine travel Gu when he was haggling over the price. Although he sounded unyielding, his expression betrayed his thoughts.

"Land spirit, you are too stingy. I know Lang Ya blessed land has many Immortal Gu. Divine travel Gu is a rank six Immortal Gu, I won't be greedy and only want to exchange it for a rank six Immortal Gu."

The land spirit shook his head repeatedly and said many things, but Fang Yuan did not loosen up. The land spirit gradually felt anxious and fury filled his expression. He looked like he wanted to eat Fang Yuan alive.

When Fang Yuan saw that the time was right he said: "Let's do this then, I shall take a step back and exchange for one of your expendable type rank six Immortal Gu. When I have used this Immortal Gu, you can then refine it again, right?"

The land spirit's expressions relaxed; Fang Yuan taking the step back first gave him a satisfying feeling of victory.

He snorted few times and raised his head, looking arrogantly at Fang Yuan: "Alright, we shall do it like that."

He then spread out his hands and brought five Immortal Gu out of nowhere.

"Lang Ya blessed land's foundation is really strong." Fang Yuan sighed inwardly - he was suddenly stupefied when he looked at them.

"I want this Immortal Gu." Fang Yuan's expression was slightly strange as he pointed to one Immortal Gu among them.

This Immortal Gu was none other than Immortal Gu Gruel Mud, the perpetrator in causing Dang Hun mountain to slowly die. He had not thought Lang Ya land spirit would refine it.

The two sides quickly completed the transaction. Fang Yuan obtained the Immortal Gu Gruel Mud; he did not put it in his aperture, but stored it in his pouch for the moment.

"I used all my mental and physical efforts for this semi-finished product, you will be saving great expenses by getting it. We are both familiar with each other now, I will sell it to you cheap; I only need one thousand hairy men. I won't be greedy, you can give me those old hairy men that refined the Gu just before as well."

"Bullshit!" The land spirit was fuming with anger, "You think I am a three year old kid? Those hairy men are at least of master level in Gu refinement, the treasure light if they are put in treasure yellow heaven will be at least seventy feet high!"

Fang Yuan snickered, he really coveted these hairy men. These hairy men would be of enormous help to him.

"Alright, I don't want a thousand, eight hundred will do."

"Bullshit eight hundred, all these hairy men are my children, I won't sell a single one!" Lang Ya land spirit roared in anger.

"All things have a price. We can still discuss!"

"Not for sale means not for sale! If you mention this again, you can take your semi-finished product with you, I am not buying it."

Fang Yuan was inwardly shocked at Lang Ya land spirit's firm attitude. He had dropped down the price to the bottom and Lang Ya land spirit would clearly have profited, but he still did not agree to sell the hairy men. It seems he really had emotional attachments to the hairymen.

This situation was not strange.

Many Gu Immortals raised variant humans in their blessed land like raising pets. They would see their growth and even expend many efforts in raising them. And when they died, the Gu Immortals would also shed tears because of heartache.

Of course, this situation would never happen to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan felt a pity at not being able to buy these hairy men, so he changed his request: "Since it is so, then I want to exchange for wolf enslavement Gu's recipes."

There were large numbers of recipes in Lang Ya blessed land. After gathering them from ancient times until now, one could even say they were as vast as the sea.

It was impossible for it to not have common recipes like that of wolf enslavement Gu.

Fang Yuan had been wanting to purchase these recipes all along, but ever since he discovered the existence of Old Man Yan Shi, he had been restraining his actions in yellow treasure heaven.

Wisdom path Gu Masters were experts at deductions, but deductions need a foundation and require large amounts of information. With these information as the base, they could then deduce and predict the outcome.

If Fang Yuan wantonly bought wolf enslavement Gu recipes from yellow treasure heaven, it was hard to guarantee that Old Man Yan Shi would not be be able to deduce something.

"Take them. These are the recipes for rank one to rank five wolf enslavement Gu." Lang Ya land spirit handed a large stack of recipes to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan skimmed over them and saw that there were eight types of recipes just for the rank five wolf enslavement Gu recipe. They used different materials and different procedures to obtain the similar Gu worm. And there were even more types of rank one to rank four wolf enslavement Gu recipes.

"This transaction is worth it!" Fang Yuan was inwardly happy.

"Transaction is finished, you can leave now." Lang Ya land spirit impatiently waved his hand.

Fang Yuan, however, smiled: "No hurry, no hurry, I still have a transaction you will definitely be interested in."

"Hmph, young man, don't talk big. There are not many things that can interest this old man in this world." Lang Ya land spirit stroked his beard and said with pride.

"What I am transacting this time is information. This information is about the time I will use the second aperture Gu."

Lang Ya land spirit's expression turned sluggish and looked dazedly at Fang Yuan, his brows deeply furrowed and looked at Fang Yuan with intense disdain and hatred: "You, how can you be so despicable and shameless!? Aren't there any limits to the degradation of your morals?!"

"Hahaha." Fang Yuan laughed loudly, "Could it be you are not interested in this information?"

Lang Ya land spirit immediately felt like he had been raped and he still had to bear the humiliation to apologize to the criminal.

Could he not be interested?

The second aperture Gu was an Immortal Gu and Immortal Gu were unique. If Fang Yuan never used it, then he would forever be unable to refine another second aperture Gu.

"How do you want to sell it?" The land spirit endured the impulse to beat up Fang Yuan and asked, swallowing his anger.

Fang Yuan narrowed his eyes, sharp rays of light flickering in them: "I won't take advantage of you, so I want to exchange information for information. I want to know all the information about the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building in Imperial Court blessed land."

"Eighty-Eight True Yang Building? You actually know that this Immortal Gu house has something to do with me!?" The land spirit was shocked.

Chapter 488: Ma Ying Jie

Thud Thud Thud.....

A series of hurried sounds came from afar.

Soon, a group of Gu Masters riding terror claw horses came to the swamp.

Terror claw horses had bloodshot eyes with fangs and were carnivorous.

They did not have any hair on its body. The skin was tight and their muscles were clearly visible, giving a feeling of strength that could not be underestimated. The most peculiar point was that they did not have horse hooves, but instead had four long sharp claws.

There were also webbings connecting the claws, so terror claw horse were not only suitable for climbing but could also move freely at swamps.

"Lord elders, they have passed through here towards that direction." An investigative Gu Master's eyes flickered with red light as he scanned all around and reported.

A young Gu Master at the side immediately frowned and anxiously said: "Not good, uncle! If we continue along this way, we will reach rocks pool over there. Once they cross rocks pool, they will be out of warm pond valley. It will be difficult to kill them then."

"Relax, Fei Qing has been struck by your dad's poison Gu and is in imminent crisis, moreover he is bringing his child with him. The further he moves with his ghost cloud, the more the poison will worsen. Hehe, he won't be able to run far. Let's continue our chase!"

The elders laughed and waved their hand, continuing the chase.

After they chased into the sparse woods, the swamp they had been standing at suddenly surged and a yellowish silkworm drilled out.

The silkworm was broken from the inside and two people walked out; a middle-aged Gu Master and a child.

The two looked in a very miserable state and gasped for breath as they dropped to the ground.

"We finally deceived them." The middle aged Gu Master, Fei Qing, had a purple hue all over his face; the poison had spread deep.

His movement Gu — the swift ghost cloud Gu, had been tampered with. Fei Qing had been feeling something wrong when they were chased all the way, thus he immediately gave up the swift ghost cloud Gu and let it fly away. After that, he took his son and hid within the swamp.

But with this, he lost his movement ability and his body was also poisoned; there was no longer any hope to escape.

"Fei Chang you despicable person! For the clan leader position, you actually secretly poisoned me, your own cousin! Damn it you abomination...."

Fei Qing got more angry the more he thought about it; under this desperation and with fury filling his heart, he suddenly spurted out a mouthful of green blood.

"Father, father! Are you okay? You need to hang on." The child started weeping when he saw the blood and threw himself into Fei Qing's chest.

"Son..." Fei Qing's despairing eyes showed a trace of hope and resolution.

He lovingly looked at his only heir and rubbed the small head: "Little Cai, father can't go on. Fei Chang has plotted deeply, I can only deceive him this one time. Not long later, he will definitely find something wrong and return back. Leave quickly, father will hold off these people for you. Go along that small path I told you of, and perhaps you can survive on."

"No, father, I want to leave with you. Let's run together... father, I beg you..." The son, Fei Cai, weeped in grief.

Fei Qing was feeling very anxious, so he roused his spirits and grabbed Fei Cai's shoulders: "Little Cai, don't cry. Northern Plains men can shed blood but not tears. You need to have confidence, in your body flows Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's bloodline, you are a member of the Huang Jin family. The bloodline in you is thick and rarely seen. You have the qualifications to enter Eighty-Eighth True Yang Building."

"Cough, cough...." Green blood continued to seep out from Fei Qing's mouth and nose, "Little Cai, take care of yourself. If you have a chance in the future to enter Imperial Court blessed land, go to Eighty-Eighth True Yang Building and obtain the grace Ancestor Giant Sun left behind for the later generations. Only then can you avenge me!"

"Father...."

"Leave, it will be too late if you delay any longer!"

Fei Qing pushed his son; Fei Cai took back several steps, helplessly looking at his father with tears filled face.

"Leave quickly!" Fei Qing growled.

Fei Cai wiped away his tears before tears immediately fell down. He fiercely gnashed his teeth, turned around and ran.

"Son, father has done his best, as long as you can escape the evil clutches..." Fei Qing sat on the ground and looked at Fei Cai's receding figure; but soon his eyes gradually widened.

"Fool, stop!" Fei Qing could not help straightening up his upper body and shouting at his son.

"Fa... father..." Fei Cai had only run a few steps before he heard Fei Qing's shout; he gazed back with doubt.

Veins popped out of Fei Qing's forehead as he shouted: "You idiot, I told you to run towards north-west direction. Why are you running towards south-east? Are you thinking of going back to the tribe camp to look for your own death?!"

"Ah, ah!" Fei Cai quickly changed direction.

But Fei Qing soon shouted again: "You dunce, that is south-west direction!"

Fei Cai quickly changed direction again, moving towards the correct path, and only then did Fei Qing let out a breath of turbid air.

"Sigh...." The middle aged Gu Master helplessly sighed. His son had thick bloodline, but was somewhat of an idiot and moreover had a really poor sense of direction. Could he truly escape to see the day?

Thinking of Fei Chang's deep conspiracy, Fei Qing did not have big hope, but he had done what he could do, now it all depended on the heavens.

After a while, like Fei Qing expected, Fei Chang returned with a gloomy face, leading three Gu Masters on their terror claw horse.

"Fei Qing, hmph, you were sure enough hiding here!" Fei Chang's voice was gloomy and hoarse; his gaze as sharp as a knife, not concealing the dense killing intent within.

"To think I would die by a vile character like you." Fei Qing scoffed with disdain; right now, his body was already paralyzed and could not budge.

Fei Chang snickered coldly, and said with an expression like that of a cat playing with a mouse: "I won't kill you so quickly. Fei Qing, Aren't you noble and aloof? Wait till I capture your son, I will let you witness your son being tortured and killed. Hehehe..."

Fei Qing couldn't keep his calm anymore and stared furiously: "Fei Chang, you are his senior, to think you actually can be so vicious!"

"Hmph, when you cut grass, if you don't root it out, then it can grow again when the spring wind arrives. Men, bring Fei Qing to me." Fei Chang ordered; the Gu Masters beside him immediately moved and bound Fei Qing tightly, then using a hemp rope, they dragged him on the ground.

"Hehehe, Fei Qing, get a good taste of the mud. Chase, we must find that kid and kill him!" Fei Chang laughed loudly, full of satisfaction.

Fei Chang was thinking: Since Fei Qing was caught, catching that stupid kid would be an easy matter.

But reality was different.

Fei Chang came to the rocks pool, but he did not find anyone besides his men.

"F*ck, this kid didn't run towards here? Speak, where did he go?" Fei Chang asked in a chilly voice.

Fei Qing had been dragged all the way, his body was badly battered and had already lost his consciousness.

Fei Chang kicked him awake, but he only got Fei Qing's ridiculing gaze.

Fei Chang laughed sinisterly: "You think I won't know if you don't speak?"

Saying so, his eyes let out a weird light that shone on Fei Qing's body. Fei Qing's body shuddered, his soul immediately receiving heavy injuries.

Soul search Gu!

Fei Chang stretched out his bony right hand and grabbed Fei Qing's head before closing his eyes and agitating his primeval essence.

Fei Qing's body shuddered and started foaming. The two Gu Masters at the sight kept quiet in fear.

In an instant, Fei Chang opened his eyes; his face had paled and his gaze was blurred.

This rank three soul search Gu could search a portion of the memories stored in the soul. But it had a lot of restrictions; first the memories it obtained would be very disordered and secondly it could not be frequently used, otherwise it could confuse the soul and make one have blurred consciousness; thus could be extremely harmful to oneself.

Fei Chang had grievances with Fei Qing for a long time and also knew Fei Cai had a thick bloodline; he could only be at ease when he personally killed the kid. Thus, he did not stint on using soul search Gu.

"So there was a hidden path nearby. Hmph!" Fei Chang smiled proudly; he was fortunately able to search the memories he wanted.

He turned around his horse and immediately moved towards that hidden path.

But when they arrived at this place, he could not find any traces of a person.

"How can this be? That kid is still not of age and has not opened his aperture yet, is only a mortal. It is impossible for him to hide from my investigative Gu. Could it be the memories I plundered is only a part of the crucial point?" Fei Chang scouted once more and saw the narrow road in the bushes; his face became very cloudy.

Wooo Woooo....

Right at this time, a deep and powerful bugle horn sounded from outside the warm pond valley.

Fei Chang and the rest immediately paled.

"Lord elders, lord elders, please go back to reinforce the troops! Ma tribe has brought a huge army, starting a war without any notice. The tribe is already is a state of emergency!" A Gu Master hurried over on a flying bird with the information.

"What?!" Fei Chang was extremely surprised, just as the Fei tribe's internal disorder had started, Ma tribe came to invade, this timing was too coincidental!

'If there is no Fei tribe, then what meaning would there be in taking the Fei tribe's tribe leader position? Defend, defend to death, we must defend! Warm pond valley is easy to defend and hard to attack, Ma tribe's army retreat isn't impossible. Right, I still have hope!' Thinking of this, Fei Chang immediately threw Fei Cai off his mind, then hurriedly rushed to the tribe camp.

However, Ma tribe's invasion had been planned in advance. They took advantage of Fei tribe's internal disorder and ambushed.

Fei tribe might have the advantage of occupying warm pond valley, but they finally could not resist Ma tribe's strong and huge wave of soldiers.

Right as Fang Yuan entered Lang Ya blessed land, a great event occured in Northern Plains -

A large scale force of the Huang Jin family — Fei tribe that were occupying warm pond valley was exterminated!

No doubt this news would create a huge influence in the whole Northern Plains.

On a slope, Ma tribe's higher-ups were observing the ruined Fei tribe camp from their war horses.

These people were circling around a young man, like the stars surrounding the moon.

Seeing batch after batch of goods being stored in the carts and groups of captives being escorted away, Ma tribe's higher ups had a joyous expression.

One rank three Gu Master elder cupped his fists towards the young man in the center: "Congratulations to young master! It was all because of young master's plan to drive a discord and create internal disorder in Fei tribe that we could so easily capture warm pond valley, swallow Fei tribe and establish great merits for the tribe!"

This young man was Ma tribe's young tribe leader Ma Ying Jie.

He had a wide back with thin waist, sharp brows and bright eyes, a heroic spirit and a cultivation of rank four middle stage. He was an enslavement path Gu Master with some fame, also called Little Ma Zun!